<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mt. Auburn St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.371338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-699-1221 </phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>363595</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116469</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NOTE: You cannot RSVP for this workshop through Meet Up. You need to reserve a spot at the below link.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, February 28th, 10-3pm &lt;br /&gt;Sliding Scale: $40-$80 (Full and partial scholarships available.) &lt;br /&gt;Workshop with Toby Hemenway: Permaculture Solutions for City and Suburb &lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the Urban Homesteaders' League&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve a space here: &lt;a href="https://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/98307" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.brownpape...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: The Democracy Center &lt;br /&gt;45 Mt. Auburn, Cambridge, MA 02138&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How does permaculture work in urban and suburban places? Though land may be limited, cities are rich in other resources, especially social capital. This workshop will show how to find, harvest, and integrate the many resources in our cities in sustainable ways, including getting access to land for gardening, creating business guilds and networks, learning the pattern language of the city, creating public space in neighborhoods, and building urban ecovillages. We'll learn how permaculture's principles and design methods apply to the dense, rich environments of our cities, and how to leverage the special opportunities that cities provide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: &lt;br /&gt;Toby Hemenway is a writer, university professor, and freelance educator based in Portland, Oregon. He is the author of &amp;quot;Gaia's Garden: A Guide to Home-Scale Permaculture&amp;quot;, which for the past seven years has been the world&amp;#8217;s best-selling book on permaculture. Toby is an adjunct professor in the School of Graduate Education at Portland State University, and Scholar-in-Residence at Pacific University. His writing has appeared in publications such as Natural Home, Whole Earth Review, and WorldWatch, and he has taught workshops all over the continent and in many countries.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Dion</member_name><member_id>6134374</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267542838000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265214329000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Workshop with Toby Hemenway: Permaculture Solutions for City and Suburb</name><id>12507516</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267369200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/12507516/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/7/global_7064327.jpeg</photo_url></item>