<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>THIS EVENT IS SOLD OUT!  CHECK OUT OUR NEXT WEEKEND AT THE CLUB ON 7/25!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The annual Wedeln Ski and Outdoor Club Canoe Trip will take place Saturday July 11th. We put in at Canal Bridge in Fryeburg Main and take out at Walkers Bridge. The total trip is just under seven miles but our mellow pace means we enjoy a full day (about 5 hours) on the river. Please feel free to RSVP on this site BUT to reserve your spot you MUST mail in the Registration form.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost includes canoe rental(including paddle, pfd), dinner(including beer), lunch, breakfast, and a bus to and from the river. We also host a bonfire party at night with beer/wine cost included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost for the weekend ($75) does not include guest fees so please add $20 dollar a night for guests staying at the Wedeln House. I recommend guests stay both Friday and Saturday. Friday night is the best time to meet people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have your own canoe or kayak then cost for the weekend is only $45(no bus), there are no other substitutions or savings even if you plan to skip meals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mail checks and form by JUNE 12th to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer Vecchi &lt;br /&gt;{email tom_lane@harvard.edu to get full address}&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3 important things: &lt;br /&gt;1. Check should be made out to &amp;quot;Wedeln&amp;quot; - not me, not Jen, not Wedlens :). &lt;br /&gt;2. Please use the enclosed Registration form, follow directions &lt;br /&gt;3. No LATE people&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guest fees should be pay ahead of time (include $40 added to check):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT - This is a huge weekend for the canoe outfitters on the Saco. If your check/letter is not postmarked by 6/12 it is highly likely that we will not have a spot for you. If you are late please do not show up with your own canoe and hope to &amp;quot;tag along&amp;quot;, This trip is difficult to organize and supervise and having people who are &amp;quot;kind of with us but not really&amp;quot; can lead to problems. Thank You.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SCHEDULE&lt;br /&gt;Here is the basic schedule - All times are aprox. and everything usually runs a bit late. If you or your friends do not have a canoe partner we will find you a paddle buddy. We pair several people up that morning and it can actually be more fun to be put in a canoe with people you do not know.  No guest will get stuck alone (unless you want a single kayak).  If we have an odd number of paddlers I will paddle solo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SATURDAY July 11th &lt;br /&gt;8:15am to 9am Continental Breakfast - Bagels, Juice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:45am Buses arrive at Wedeln. (10:15 at Maks)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1pm - Lunch on the river: sandwiches and snackfood&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4pm Takeout: be patient it can take a while.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm - BBQ&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30pm - Bonfire, beer and wine included.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>come up on Friday night</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1247784669000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240961757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SACO River Canoe Trip </name><id>10289492</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247317200000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/10289492/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/7/global_5139335.jpeg</photo_url></item>