<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Medford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.414890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-646-4849</phone><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I am a huge roller derby fan, and to help kick off the new season, our local roller derby league, the Boston Derby Dames, is sponsoring a screening of this 2001 documentary on the modern rebirth of roller derby.

Woohoo! Roller Derby!!! 

[b]How to Find Me[/b]

I'll be in the lobby with my red meetup hat starting at 6:30 and I'll send in some folks to grab seats at 6:45. I'll send out my cell number to those who RSVP yes and maybe. 

[b]About the Theater[/b]

The Regent is in Arlington Center, and as such is not on the T, but you can take the #77 bus from Harvard Square, or several buses from Alewife, or possibly a bus from Lechmere. 

If you are driving, there's a huge parking lot behind the stores on Mass Ave.  There's a small driveway opposite the Regent that leads into it.  There's also an entrance off Rte 60.

I'm also told there's lots of resteraunts to choose from, so I'll just find one that is appropriate and we'll head there afterwards.

Special thanks to alert members Bari and Jared for giving me all that helpful info!

[b]From the Sponsor[/b]

BDD is proud to sponsor a screening of Hell on Wheels--a documentary of the birth of modern day roller derby in 2001 in Austin, Texas--at the historic Regent Theater in Arlington.

What began with plans of creating a circus-like spectacle on skates has spawned more than 200 skater-run leagues in North America and Europe, as entrepreneurship and serious athleticism have become just as big a part of the roller derby revival as campy pseudonyms and sassy uniforms.
 
Catch scenes of BDD's recently relocated General Lee Feisty in her days with TXRD's Rhinestone Cowgirls. Read more about the movie at the Hell on Wheels site: &lt;a href="http://www.hellonwheelsthemovie.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hellonwheelsthemovie.com/&lt;/a&gt;.

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/_GTS8BPTNZY&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See meetup description for how to find me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238939234000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232542356000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hell on Wheels: Texas Is the Reason</name><id>9569786</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235174400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/9569786/</event_url></item>