<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Court St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.761859</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Court Street Theatre</name><city>Nashua</city><id>1136896</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.464458</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Correction on the prices and time:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will hold a block of seats for us under the name &amp;quot;Neil's meetup group&amp;quot; until 7:30 PM, so we all need to pay for our tickets by then. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we get 10 people for the group rate, it will be $14 per ticket.&lt;br /&gt;If we don't qualify for the group rate, you can use the discount code (I'll email you that after you RSVP) for $16 per ticket.&lt;br /&gt;The regular price is $18 per ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm listing this event with 4 meetup groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See www.madco.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's their description of this show: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live from Hollywood! It’s Christmas Eve and Judy Garland has invited a star-studded list of celebrities to ring in the holidays – Ethel Merman, Bing Crosby, Liberace, Joan Crawford – and more! But Judy’s outrageous comeback special enters a twilight zone when a mysterious stranger crashes the party – taking one and all on a mystical journey beyond legends and legacies….&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Magical! A Side-Splitting Musical Parody…Wickedly Funny!” – Los Angeles Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A Non-Stop Hoot!&amp;quot; – Backstage West&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This award-winning original musical was developed in New York, premiered in Los Angeles and performed in Chicago and other cities around the country. Music and Drama Company's special holiday presentation is a New England premiere, directed and choreographed by Portsmouth’s multiple-Spotlight award winner, George Hosker-Bouley. &amp;quot;JUDY&amp;quot; will light up the Court Street Theatre for five performances only! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JUDY'S SCARY LITTLE CHRISTMAS&lt;br /&gt;a holiday special&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;written by Jim Webber and David Church&lt;br /&gt;music and lyrics by Joe Patrick Ward (TV's &amp;quot;Sordid Lives&amp;quot;)&lt;br /&gt;musical direction by Jed Holland&lt;br /&gt;directed and choreographed by George Hosker-Bouley&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Wonderfully Strange!…A True Holiday Treat!” – Hollywood Reporter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Hilarious! A surreal snow globe highball; a Hollywood Christmas card from beyond the grave!” – Portland Mercury&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hilarious, Outrageous, Nostalgic, and even a bit Spooky, JUDY'S SCARY LITTLE CHRISTMAS is “A Glistening Christmas Gift!” (Frontiers Magazine), “An Instant Holiday Classic!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Woe to your Holidays if you miss it!&amp;quot; - Burbank Leader&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;50% profits from this production donated to BRIDGES domestic and sexual violence support organization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ACCESSIBLE SEATING: All Row AA seating is fully accessible for patrons with accessible seating requirements. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Restrictions: &lt;br /&gt;Some material may be inappropriate for young audiences.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let me know if you don't already know me and I'll think of something.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>NeilL</member_name><member_id>3034835</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260836466000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260226303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedic Musical Theatre </name><id>12039072</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260663300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/12039072/</event_url></item>