<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Values are extremely important because errrrr... they are the abstract ideas of that which is important to us!  Is that a tautology, i.e. a mere redundancy?  Well, the problem with values is that they do involve some redundancy because at some point it is said that 'x' is a value because it is valuable.  Let's consider the mother of all values: &lt;em&gt;monetary value&lt;/em&gt;.   The value of a U.S. dollar in relation to the value of an ounce of gold has fallen more than  tenfold since Nixon took us off the gold standard in the 1970s (I believe this is fairly accurate).  Is this, perhaps, because the dollar no longer possesses a workable basis for valuation?  But why should gold be the standard?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This discussion will not be about economics, but it will concern the basis of valuation, and in that sense I think there is some commonality between ethical value and monetary value on at least a couple of levels: a) The deflation of monetary value affects our general notions of worth and worthlessness, and b) Any valuation must be reliant upon a process.  The relative success of some versions of the gold standard in the past compared to our current system of determining currency value by bidding,  like bidding on the price of a barrel crude oil, says something about the nature of reasonable (or crazed) valuation and devaluation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethical standards such as the "utilitarian standard" or the "categorical imperative," while philosophically interesting and excellent stimuli for ethical reflection, are dismal failures as practical mechanisms for deciding moral conundrums and, by extension, for the weighing of ethical values.  It has long been my view that the sub-discipline of ethics has lost its way or, perhaps, has never really gotten started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will discuss monetary and ethical value and the deeper processes that make values valuable.  This should be a particularly creative discussion on the meaning of what is arguably the most important thing in conscious life: value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the spirit of creating new values, this meeting will  take place in a different venue.  Good meeting places are valuable commodities!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298941085000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292732426000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Value: From the Monetary to the Ethical</name><id>15770189</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296864000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/15770189/</event_url></item>