<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Purchase Tickets:&lt;/b&gt; $5.00 &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Tickets now on sale&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; at the Harvard Bookstore site on the bottom of the page at &lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2516" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvard.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Harvard Bookstore site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2516" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvard.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome pre-eminent biologist and naturalist E.O. WILSON as he reads from his first novel, Anthill, a book equally inspired by his scientific passion and his boyhood in Alabama.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Anthill follows the adventures of a modern-day Huck Finn, whose improbable love of the 'strange, beautiful, and elegant' world of ants ends up transforming his own life and the citizens of Nokobee County. Battling both snakes bites and cynical relatives who don’t understand his consuming fascination with the outdoors, Raff explores the pristine beauty of the Nokobee wildland. And in doing so, he witnesses the remarkable creation and destruction of four separate ant colonies, whose histories are epics that unfold on picnic grounds, becoming a young naturalist in the process. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An extraordinary undergraduate at Florida State University, Raff, despite his scientific promise, opts for Harvard Law School, believing that the environmental fight must be waged in the courtroom as well as the lab. Returning home a legal gladiator, Raff grows increasingly alarmed by rapacious condo developers who are eager to pave and subdivide the wildlands surrounding the Chicobee River. But one last battle awaits him in his struggle. In an ending that no reader will forget, Raff suddenly encounters the angry and corrupt ghosts of an old South he thought had all but disappeared, and learns that 'war is a genetic imperative,' not only for ants but for men as well&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... The storyline sounds sketchy, but T.J. Maher wants to be able to see Edward O. Wilson ever since he heard him on RadioLab. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting outside the Brattle Theatre at 5:30 pm and will be attempting to save seats at 5:40 pm. If we can't sit next to each other, let's group up after the event outside the theater and go grab dinner. T.J. is five foot seven, wish short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Edward O. Wilson:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2516" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvard.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Edward O. Wilson grew up in south Alabama and the Florida Panhandle, where he spent his boyhood exploring the region’s forests and swamps, collecting snakes, butterflies, and ants—the latter to become his lifelong specialty. Regarded as one of the world’s preeminent biologists and naturalists, he is the author of more than twenty books, including the Pulitzer Prize-winning &lt;i&gt;The Ants&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;The Naturalist&lt;/i&gt; as well as his first novel &lt;i&gt;Anthill&lt;/i&gt;, Wilson, a professor at Harvard, makes his home in Lexington, Massachusetts&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Listen to E. O. Wilson on Radiolab (9/23/2008):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.wnyc.org/radiolab/2008/09/23/chasing-bugs/" target="_blank"&gt;http://blogs.wnyc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Remember the first time you ever saw an ant hill? That parade of black insects pouring in and out of a small sand mound…most of us stopped, looked and then moved on to other parts of the playground. E. O. Wilson is the kid who never took his eyes off the mound. He grew up to revolutionize the fields of entomology, sociobiology and conservationist thought. E. O. (E is for Edward, O is for Osborne) got a nod from Time Magazine on their list of the 25 Most Influential People in America and picked up a few Pulitzers along the way. But before all that he was just an eight-year-old boy in the South whose nickname was 'Bugs.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Ed and Robert Krulwich spoke a few years ago at the 92nd Street Y in Manhattan about Ed’s early insect-philia and how it blossomed. Ed tells Robert about the time he figured out how to make hundreds of ants trace his name and the time he convinced an ant colony one of their ants was dead when it was anything but&amp;quot;. (20 minutes, &lt;b&gt;Radiolab&lt;/b&gt; podcast by WNYC, &lt;i&gt;also downloadable in iTunes and in MP3 format&lt;/i&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... E.O. Wilson was also interviewed for Radiolab's show back in 2/18/2005 called &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Emergence&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;What happens when there is no leader? Starlings, bees, and ants manage just fine. In fact, they form staggeringly complicated societies, all without a Toscanini to conduct them into harmony. How? That’s our question this hour. We gaze down at the bottom-up logic of cities, Google, even our very own brains. Featured: author Steven Johnson, fire-flyologists John and Elizabeth Buck, biologist E.O. Wilson, Ant expert Debra Gordon, mathematician Steve Strogatz, economist James Surowiecki, and neurologists Oliver Sacks and Christof Koch&amp;quot;. &lt;a href="http://www.wnyc.org/shows/radiolab/episodes/2005/02/18" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wnyc.org/s...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About E. O. Wilson, according to Wikipedia:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/E._O._Wilson" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Edward Osborne Wilson (born June 10, 1929) is an American biologist, researcher (sociobiology, biodiversity), theorist (consilience, biophilia), naturalist (conservationist) and author. His biological specialty is myrmecology, a branch of entomology.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Wilson is a two-time winner of the Pulitzer Prize for General Non-Fiction. He is known for his career as a scientist, his advocacy for environmentalism, and his secular-humanist and deist ideas pertaining to religious and ethical matters.[1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As of 2007, he is Pellegrino University Research Professor in Entomology for the Department of Organismic and Evolutionary Biology at Harvard University and a Fellow of the Committee for Skeptical Inquiry. He is a Humanist Laureate of the International Academy of Humanism&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Wilson, along with Bert Hölldobler, has done a systematic study of ants and ant behavior, culminating in their encyclopedic work, &lt;b&gt;The Ants&lt;/b&gt; (1990). Because much self-sacrificing behavior on the part of individual ants can be explained on the basis of their genetic interests in the survival of the sisters, with whom they share 75% of their genes (though the actual case is some species' queens mate with multiple males and therefore some workers in a colony would only be 25% related), Wilson was led to argue for a sociobiological explanation for all social behavior on the model of the behavior of the social insects. In his more recent work, he has sought to defend his views against the criticism of younger scientists such as Deborah Gordon, whose results challenge the idea that ant behavior is as rigidly-predictable as Wilson's explanations make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Edward O. Wilson, referring to ants, once said that 'Karl Marx was right, socialism works, it is just that he had the wrong species', meaning that while ants and other eusocial species appear to live in communist-like societies, they only do so because they are forced to do so from their basic biology, as they lack reproductive independence: worker ants, being sterile, need their ant-queen to survive as a colony and a species and individual ants cannot reproduce without a queen, thus being forced to live in centralised societies. Humans, however, do possess reproductive independence so they can give birth to offspring without the need of a 'queen', and in fact humans enjoy their maximum level of Darwinian fitness only when they look after themselves and their families, while finding innovative ways to use the societies they live in for their own benefit&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The building is shared with Algiers Cafe, Casablanca Restaurant, and Harvard Square Optical, and the theatre entrance is on the left side of the building—look for our sidewalk poster case and marquee. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;On-Street Parking&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Metered parking spaces are available throughout Harvard Square, however spaces are limited and competition for them can be difficult and time consuming. We recommend use of public transportation when possible, or choose one of the discount parking garages above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Charles Square Garage&lt;br /&gt;At the Charles Hotel, 5 Bennett Street, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Contact the garage at 617 491-0298 for current rates and hours of operation, or visit www.harvardsquareparking.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;University Place Garage &lt;br /&gt;124 Mt. Auburn Street, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;$2 Discount with box office validation. Contact the garage at 617 491-0801 for current rates and hours of operation&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272665245000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270063461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Edward O. Wilson reads from his first novel, "Anthill" @ Brattle Theatre</name><id>13050467</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272492000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13050467/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/c/global_14049468.jpeg</photo_url></item>