<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1175A Soldiers Field Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02163</zip><lat>42.366479</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781.648.0066</phone><name>The Charles River - Lot #4</name><city>Brighton</city><id>1026365</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132339</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/3/a/event_5560506.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BOSTON DRUM CIRCLE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A high-energy, FUN, celebration of &lt;span&gt;drum&lt;/span&gt;ming and community. For beginners wanting to try something new, friends, experienced &lt;span&gt;drum&lt;/span&gt;mers, dancers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We celebrate the traditions - rhythms that have built energy for hundreds of years for celebration, dance, ritual - just plain FUN! As well as whatever you bring to it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll have &lt;span&gt;drum&lt;/span&gt;s to share, and support for newcomers, and energy for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT! We will be at Parking Lot #4 (the larger Publick Theater lot).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1175 Soldiers Field Rd, Brighton, MA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; a folding full-height chair, your drum, water, fruit, a hat and a jacket. On a hot day, it can be 7-10 degrees cooler at The Charles. Parking should be easy in the huge lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAIN PLAN:&lt;/strong&gt; If it rains we will try it the following Saturday, Sept 22nd - same time. Call 781-316-8068 if you are unsure of inside/outside. There will be a recorded message or maybe you get ME!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extra Info:&lt;/strong&gt; If you have an extra chair and/or an extra drum, please bring, if you can. If you have dunun (Mandingo Bass Drums) please bring with stands, or use some chairs and straps. Sticks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Drum?&lt;/strong&gt; We'll have some so don't let that stop you. We'll even have extra chairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Ideas:&lt;/strong&gt; Bar-B-Que! For the last few years we've been holding a BBQ. If anyone would like to volunteer to get a grill down there and get some help setting it up, we will ask people to bring food stuffs for it. Or, we can do cold food stuffs and that will work fine. Whatever's clever! Just let me know if you want to do the BBQ volunteer duty. Free pass into drum circle for that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; We will start at 4 and end at 6, however folks may stay and make a night of it! All chairs we bring will have to leave at 6 but other chairs and drums you bring stay till you want the party to end! Party on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recent accolade!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This Drum Circle is a great stress reliever after a long week of work and I wish it were every Friday night!! Boston Drum Cirlce attracts a wonderful , eclectic group of people that share the common bond of hand drumming. It is always wonderful to have the multi talented Fanta leading the Circle. Her singing, dancing, and drumming are all 5 star. Thank you for a great night of Drumming!&lt;/em&gt; Carla (thanks Carla - love you too and all)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're the nice folks with the Drums!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alan</member_name><member_id>1328052</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347988121000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Drummers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>DrumConnection</urlname><id>886763</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>The Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347596088000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drum Circle on The Banks of The River Charles</name><id>82345942</id><headcount>27</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347739200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/DrumConnection/events/82345942/</event_url></item>