<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list. A yes list will be provided as soon as possible. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Criteria: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;NO WHINING, COMPLAINING&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;ETC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; All hikers must be able to maintain a minimum pace of three miles an hour for a minimum of four hours. All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website. &lt;br /&gt;starting at Webster-Jackson Trailhead  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.10 mi/5 min/+67 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;The trail, blazed in blue, leaves the east side of US 302 between the Crawford Depot and the Gate of the Notch. It runs through a clearing, enters the woods, and passes the side path leading right to Elephant Head.  &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Elephant Head Spur  &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.50 mi/29 min/+466 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;The main trail climbs along the south bank of Elephant Head Brook, well above the stream, then turns right, away from the brook. Angling up the mountainside roughly parallel to the highway, nearly level stretches alternating with sharp uphill pitches, it crosses Little Mossy Brook, and a side path leads right 60 yd. to Bugle Cliff. This is a massive ledge overlooking Crawford Notch, where the view is well worth the slight extra effort required; if ice is present, exercise extreme caution.  &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Bugle Cliff spur  &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.80 mi/39 min/+329 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;The main trail rises fairly steeply and crosses Flume Cascade Brook. Within sound of Silver Cascade Brook, the trail divides, the left branch for Mt. Jackson and the right for Mt. Webster.  &lt;br /&gt;hike 1.20 mi/1 hr 15 min/+1265 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;The Jackson (left) branch ascends gradually until it comes within sight of Silver Cascade Brook, then begins to climb moderately. Above the junction, it crosses three branches of the brook in quick succession. A short distance below the base of the rocky summit cone, it passes Tisdale Spring (unreliable, often scanty and muddy). The trail soon swings right and ascends steep ledges to the open summit.  &lt;br /&gt;to Mt Jackson  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Totals  &lt;br /&gt;Distance 2.60 mi  &lt;br /&gt;Time 2 hr 28 min  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2338 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -210 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +2128 ft  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions &lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth &lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.30 mi/52 min/-250 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail  &lt;br /&gt;From the summit of Mt. Jackson, the Webster Cliff Trail descends the steep, ledgy cone before swinging west to cross numerous wet gullies. It descends to the junction of the Webster branch of the Webster-Jackson Trail, leading to US 302 near the Macomber Family Information Center (Crawford Depot).  &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.10 mi/4 min/+67 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail  &lt;br /&gt;The trail ascends to the jumbled, ledgy summit of Mt. Webster.  &lt;br /&gt;to Mt Webster (Beans Grant)  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Totals  &lt;br /&gt;Distance 4.00 mi  &lt;br /&gt;Time 3 hr 24 min  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2602 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -656 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +1946 ft  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions &lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth &lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.10 mi/4 min/-67 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail  &lt;br /&gt;The trail then descends north, and the Webster branch of the Webster-Jackson Trail from US 302 near the Macomber Family Information Center (Crawford Depot) enters left.  &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;hike 1.00 mi/1 hr 2 min/-1016 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;From the Webster Cliff Trail, the trail goes down steadily north. It goes steeply down the bank, bears right, and then crosses it just below a beautiful cascade and pool. The Webster (right) branch immediately ascends steeply from Silver Cascade Brook.  &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.80 mi/39 min/-329 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;The trail merges within sound of Silver Cascade Brook. The main trail crosses Flume Cascade Brook and falls fairly steeply.  &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Bugle Cliff spur  &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.50 mi/29 min/-466 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;A side path leads left 60 yd. to Bugle Cliff. After crossing Little Mossy Brook, there will be nearly level stretches alternating with sharp downhill pitches, angling down the mountainside roughly parallel to the highway. The main trail turns left, towards the stream, and descends along the south bank of Elephant Head Brook.  &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Elephant Head Spur  &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.20 mi/9 min/+60 ft on the Elephant Head Spur  &lt;br /&gt;to Elephant Head  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Totals  &lt;br /&gt;Distance 6.60 mi  &lt;br /&gt;Time 5 hr 47 min  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2975 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -2848 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +127 ft  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions &lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth &lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.20 mi/9 min/-60 ft on the Elephant Head Spur  &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.10 mi/5 min/-67 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail  &lt;br /&gt;It passes the side path leading to Elephant Head, then emerges from the woods, and runs through a clearing, ending at the east side of US 302.  &lt;br /&gt;to Webster-Jackson Trailhead  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Totals  &lt;br /&gt;Distance 6.90 mi  &lt;br /&gt;Time 6 hr 1 min  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3016 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -3016 ft  &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change 0 ft  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#65279;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the AMC Highland Centers' Common Room across from front desk.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1304284157000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Why not?</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303478307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT JACKSON &amp; MT WEBSTER</name><id>17395956</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304170200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/17395956/</event_url></item>