<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The time will be updated closer to the meet up. Please check back for changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UPDATED: The movie starts at 7:50. Please meet in the lobby at 7:20. If this effects your ability to attend please update your RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone will be responsible for their own ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the movie:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A retired pugilist transitions to the business side of the ropes after human boxers are replaced by robotic ones in director &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/shawnlevy/filmography/p42162"&gt;Shawn Levy&lt;/a&gt;'s feature-length adaptation of the &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/thetwilightzone%5Btvseries%5D%5B19591964%5D_v133223/plotsummary"&gt;Twilight Zone&lt;/a&gt; episode "&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/thetwilightzone:steel_v198403/plotsummary"&gt;Steel&lt;/a&gt;." Charlie Kenton (&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/hughjackman/filmography/p269258"&gt;Hugh Jackman&lt;/a&gt;) was fighting for the title when the sport of boxing was changed forever. Now, instead of humans duking it out for the masses, huge, powerful steel robots trade blows in the ring. As a result, former gladiator Charlie has been forced into the role of two-bit promoter, piecing together cut-rate fighting bots from scrap metal as he makes the rounds on the underground boxing circuit. Just when it seems that Charlie has sunken to the nadir of his career, his estranged son, Max (&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/dakotagoyo/filmography/p651749"&gt;Dakota Goyo&lt;/a&gt;), offers him the once-in-a-lifetime opportunity at a comeback by constructing and training a true champion. Now the stakes are higher than ever before, and Charlie is fully prepared to coach his robot to victory so that he can finally leave an indelible mark on the sport he once dedicated his life to.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the lobby to the right of the ticket booth.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle</member_name><member_id>2132838</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318621455000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317519335000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Real Steel</name><id>35769942</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318546800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/35769942/</event_url></item>