<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>INTRODUCING A *NEW* MEET-UP SERIES: Monday Funday! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(As if Mondays aren't bad enough, right? Well, let's add some fun to them - something to look forward to come Sunday eve, when the sun is setting and you start to dread the next day, Monday. Besides, isn't it time Mondays got a make-over?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, let's all meet on Monday, Sept 28th. Deal? Deal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While it may be far for some, this location by any OTHER name would still entice us to visit. That's because it's suppose to be one of the coolest places in Back Bay to hang out, grab a brew and chat with friends. Ah, perfect. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, let's do just that - hang out, grab a brew and chat with friends. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to one Yelper: &amp;quot;Definitely one of the best beer selections in the Back Bay. The have so many different breweries represented- even ones not on the East Coast! But beyond the delicious beer is a menu that provides the best selection of everything. Breakfast served 24 hours is, and always will be, a temptation, pulling me away from their delicious sandwiches and wraps.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YUM. I want breakfast for dinner, don't you?&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be inside, wrestling for a table. (wink)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alicia</member_name><member_id>8353321</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254590093000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>beer buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CraftBeerCrew</urlname><id>1469154</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Craft Beer Crew</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252678910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Funday: The "Far" Side</name><id>11346750</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254178800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CraftBeerCrew/events/11346750/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/d/global_9049101.jpeg</photo_url></item>