<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>836 Brooks Rd.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.533666</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.301.0204</phone><name>Stephanie Borrelli</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1482803</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.602483</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>There will be a full day workshop presented by Norton Berkowitz, Ph.D.  If the subject of PAST LIFE IS OF INTEREST TO YOU, THEN THIS IS THE PLACE TO BE.  He is one of the world's leading experts on reincarnation and past life regression. He is an internationally known educator,lecturer and past life facilitator.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has lectured and facilitated workshops for various foundations, universities and organizations throughout the US.  He has also appeared on national radio and television programs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the past fifteen years, Dr. Berkowitz has been a practicing hypnotherapist and is a participating member of the International Hypnosis Hall of Fame, the National Guild of Hypnotists and the Association of Past Life Researchers and Founder/Director of the Life Memory Recall Research Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Berkowitz workshop consists of:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Speaking about Past Lives and how Life Memory Recall works&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Group Past Life Regression, where all attendees of the workshop will explore the significance these past lives play in this lifetime personally&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A sharing session will be held, during which the group will discuss their experiences of these past lives they regressed into&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;One full past life regression demonstration will be performed by Dr. Berkowitz.  Everyone is able to hear and participate in the experience of this past life and its significance to the individual.  These are often very exciting stories which include tremendous personal revelations.  This person will be chosen by a lottery system.  If there is time, Dr. Berkowitz will conduct additional Past Life Regressions for both the whole group as well as individuals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;There will be time allotted for discussion and Q &amp;amp; A's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a bag lunch and beverage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-registration and payment is a MUST.&lt;br /&gt;... Can be sent to Stephanie Borrelli, 836 Brooks Rd., Middletown, CT, 06457&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to contact Stephanie with any questions at 860-301-0204.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jo-Ann Blanchette-Silverio</member_name><member_id>9921229</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297723067000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296091726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PAST LIFE REGRESSION WORKSHOP</name><id>16201644</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297522800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/16201644/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/2/b/global_12747883.jpeg</photo_url></item>