<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>(The February meetup has been rescheduled to the 19th in order to avoid conflicting with Ignite Boston 5, which is on the 12th: &lt;a href="http://upcoming.yahoo.com/event/1503424/" target="_blank"&gt;http://upcoming.yahoo...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For our February meetup, we'll be doing a mixture of group code reviews and lightning talks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CODE REVIEWS are a chance to get group feedback on a django project or idea.  Bring some code that feels unnecessarily hairy, and we'll see if a roomful of django hackers can help clean it up, or set you on a path to a simpler, cleaner, and better solution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LIGHTNING TALKS are ultra-short talks, under 5 minutes, on any topic of interest to the group.  You can take this time to introduce a new library, give a quick demo, or just discuss an interesting question.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU'RE INTERESTED in either a code review or lightning talk, please let us know either by email or by responding to the question in the RSVP form.  Advance notice is highly appreciated, so we can better publicize the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming by car, you can park in the Green Street garage for $5. If coming by T, take the Red Line to Central Square and walk two blocks to 13 Magazine St. Buzz suite #2 and then walk up the stairs two flights.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shimon Rura</member_name><member_id>409933</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236901996000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Djangonauts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>djangoboston</urlname><id>1289145</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Django Boston Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231463368000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Django February Meetup</name><id>9481105</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235088000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/djangoboston/events/9481105/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/9/global_5640505.jpeg</photo_url></item>