<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 King Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.320358</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Coolidge Park Cafe</name><city>Northampton</city><id>9071492</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631332</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join fellow Hidden-Techies and Hidden-Tech board members to usher in the fall season with good cheer and conversation at the Hotel Northampton. This social also marks the 10th anniversary of the founding of Hidden-Tech, so we'd love to have you there to thank you for all the good discussions, projects, and events that have happened this last decade. If you’ve never been to a Hidden-Tech event before, this is the perfect opportunity to introduce yourself and get to know your neighbors. Due to the inevitable scheduling logistics, there is at least one other social in Northampton on September 12, but we have made sure to allow for enough time to swing by. Look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When: Wednesday, September 12, 5:30 to 8:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: Hotel Northampton, Coolidge Park Cafe, 36 King St., Northampton, MA (MAP)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Refreshments: Cheese, fruit, crackers, and vegetable crudite with herb dip will be served--drinks and sandwiches can be purchased at Coolidge Park Bar and Cafe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested donation: Complimentary--bring your good cheer and money for drinks. NO reservation needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking: Ample free parking behind the Hotel Northampton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information: www.Hidden-Tech.net&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347529146000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346792478000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HIDDEN-TECH PRESENTS: OUR FALL KICK-OFF SOCIAL</name><id>80833462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347485400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/80833462/</event_url></item>