<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>318 7 Bridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01523</zip><lat>42.464493</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bolton Fair</name><city>Lancaster</city><id>6810482</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.658348</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;June 3, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

11 a.m. to 3 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;

Admission: free &lt;br /&gt;

Benefiting: Shelters and rescues throughout NE &lt;br /&gt;

What's a Whisker Walk you Ask? View our 30 second commercial at &lt;a href="http://youtu.be/zRBxoL3Ce7o" class="linkified"&gt;http://youtu.be/zRBxoL3Ce7o&lt;/a&gt; Well its a lot of things ... but mostly its a FREE, fun day for families and their dogs PLUS a dog walk-a-thon fundraiser to benefit animal shelters and rescue groups throughout New England. The 2011 Whisker Walk brought in 100+ animal rescue groups, pet related vendors/manufacturers and sponsors for the first of its kind “event not to be missed” for pet lovers. The 2012 Whisker Walk is sure to be bigger and better! Held at the Lancaster Fairground (Home of the Bolton Fair) there are 50+ acres for Pet owners and animal lovers to walk, visit vendors, see, do and buy PLUS they can lend a paw for the animals shelters and pet rescues they love and support! Come see exhibits, demonstrations, educational programs, special attractions, product giveaways, entertainment, auctions/raffles, food, fun and things for adults and kids to see, do and buy – both human and pet related! Check back often to see participants, events and attractions Top off your exciting day and join us for the Walk - a leisurely (almost) ONE mile stroll on shaded, flat, grassy trails with your well behaved dog (sorry other pets must stay home) &lt;br /&gt;

For more information, please call 978 422 8585 or email leigh13@Ix.netcom.com. &lt;br /&gt;

Coming from out of town? Get a discounted rate on pet friendly hotels in Lancaster, or call 877-411-FIDO to speak with one of our pet travel experts!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338817080000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335025361000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whisker Walk 2012</name><id>61531092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338735600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/61531092/</event_url></item>