<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Wattaquadock Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.430644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>http://www.nashobawinery.com</phone><name>Nashoba Valley Winery</name><city>Bolton</city><id>731361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.614016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Wedelns at Nashoba Valley Winery for their best fall festivals that highlight their hand-crafted micro-brews. Relax, sit back, and enjoy some bluegrass music. Snack shack sells cider donut and caramel apples, full barbecue menu under pavilion provided by the chef&amp;rsquo;s from thier restaurant. Tour the winery or simply taste their our award winning wines (to sign up for winery tours, visit info table at front of wine shoppe). Free parking, free entry, BBQ meals for sale (or bring your own picnic). Bottles of wine for sale in shoppe (they will open it for you to enjoy outside), and many beers on tap, of course! Just bring blanket or beach chairs, picnic items, and look for Wedeln logo on our hats or fleeces! Southern Rail&amp;rsquo;s music is high energy exuberant fun, with riveting harmonies, irreverent humor and sparkling banjo and mandolin solo work. Their songs have graced Bluegrass Unlimited&amp;rsquo;s Top Thirty Singles Chart receiving heavy national airplay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Helpful Hints!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Here are some helpful tips:&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Get there early so you can buy wine, browse the gift shoppe, take a tour, etc. Because it will be mobbed later on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Their BBQ is really tasty, but lines get long and they always run out of food so buy early - especially things like their cornbread and caramel apples (yummy!) BBQ prices may seem high, but remember that it's a FREE event so NO charge to park, no cover charge for live band :-)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you have a small folding table, it might come in handy since we've asked everyone to bring a dish to share and can't hog all the picnic tables.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you bring a dish, please try to remember plastic forks, plates, or whatever you will need to serve with it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you can't bring a dish, and you want to eat other people's dishes, I suggest contributing wine to the general pot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you plan to buy wine to bring home, I suggest you put it right in your car so there's no confusion over what's community and what's not :-)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you're drinking wine, they will give you plastic cups inside the winery but it's always good to bring some. You can always buy their logo'd wine glass in a pinch. If you take the winery tour, it includes a souvenir glass.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can buy chilled bottles inside the shop.&amp;nbsp;I usually buy bottles early, and put them into a cooler so I don't have to keep going in. Plus, you get a discount for bulk purchases (when I left a year ago, deal was 5% off 6 bottles, 10% off case - can be mixed assortment)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Beer can be bought on tap outside only, and in bottles inside. I recommend tap - bottled stuff isn't as great. Although they do make decent hard cider that they bottle. Always good for bellinis and mimosas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Campfire" style chairs are highly recommended but blankets work well too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jenn V</member_name><member_id>6144735</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319565422000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>65</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316388215000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brews &amp; Blues Festival at Nashoba Valley Winery</name><id>34045532</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319385600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/34045532/</event_url></item>