<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Rt. 9 Westbound-behind Chuck E. Cheese)</address_2><address_1>3 Vision Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.300643</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitney Place Assisted Living</name><city>Natick</city><id>766030</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354550</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;We are very excited to announce a &lt;u&gt;FREE&lt;/u&gt; concert with children's singer Charlie Hope.  Bring your children and enjoy the show!  We are very close to full right now with official members, but visitors from Meetup are welcome. We'd love to have you!   Please note that I will close off rsvp's as soon as we reach maximum, so be sure to rsvp right away if you would like to attend.  Once this event is full, I will take a waitlist.  Please only attend if you have confirmed spots, and if you rsvp, please be committed to attend or let me know with as many days notice as possible should you need to cancel so that someone from the waitlist can attend.  It's very important to include the number of adults and children in your party with your rsvp. Thanks!&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;A Concert with Charlie Hope&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link to Charlie Hope's Video (if it doesn't work, copy and paste it into your browser window and be sure there are no spaces between the words) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HKlHABc8HTE&amp;amp;feature=channel" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and Charlie Hope's Facebook Page    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Challenge-Fun/93833754268?ref=ts#/pages/Charlie-Hope/86485971115?ref=ts" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie Hope spent her childhood in Toronto and Boston harmonizing with her sister and in her school choirs. As she grew she discovered the joys of writing music as well, and it became a powerful outlet for her to express her feelings. For Charlie, music should empower not only the creator, but also the listener. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her fresh approach to children’s music stems from the many years she has spent with children – from receiving her degree in Art Therapy with Children to the preschools and private homes she has become an integral part of as a trusted caregiver. From all her experiences Charlie believes that music is vital to a child’s overall well-being. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On her debut album, “I’m Me!”, she created music that is relevant to children’s lives; reflecting and respecting their experiences. Elements in the album include a positive take on naptime, learning about the joys of having a new child in the family and discovering the limitless possibilities we all have inside of us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I’m Me!” has been followed-up by the lullaby album “World of Dreams.”  This original album gently lulls children (and adults) to sleep with images of balloons, teddy bears on boats, the gentle rain, and more.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie Hope children's music is melodic, interactive and sing-able! Whether you’re a parent or kid, you’ll find an opportunity to stomp your feet, become a train or roar like a lion!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanya</member_name><member_id>7153030</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252971204000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251220880000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPECIAL EVENT-  LIMITED SEATS **CHILDREN'S CONCERT!!</name><id>11196790</id><headcount>79</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251727200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/11196790/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/a/global_8459978.jpeg</photo_url></item>