<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>315 Huntington Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.340954</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>617-536-3577</phone><name>Boston Shawarma</name><city>Boston</city><id>604090</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.087640</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Boston magazine deemed the falafel at Boston Shawarma the &amp;quot;Best of Boston&amp;quot; in 2006. If falafel's not your thing, there are plenty of other tasty Middle Eastern dishes on the menu at this Huntington Avenue &amp;quot;cheap eats&amp;quot; favorite, including--you guessed it!--shawarma, plus several vegetarian options. Afterward, we'll take the short stroll down the street to the Museum of Fine Arts and drink in the masterpieces. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RESTAURANT DETAILS: &lt;br /&gt;Let's meet outside the restaurant at 5:45. It's a small, informal place with counter service, and they don't accept reservations. Seating is limited, so we'll want to arrive before the dinner rush to secure some tables. No website, but you can find favorable reviews online.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MUSEUM DETAILS: &lt;br /&gt;Admission is free on Wednesday nights (donations are encouraged). Special exhibits are extra. The museum stays open until 9:45, giving us plenty of time to roam the galleries after dinner. For more information, visit mfa.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LATECOMERS/MUSEUM ONLY:&lt;br /&gt;If you already know you can't make dinner, but would like to join us at the museum, please contact me in advance by emailing me at dessertandcoffee@aol.com, and we'll plan to meet you in the ticket area at approximately 7pm (or as soon as we arrive from dinner). After we've received our tickets, we will wait for exactly five minutes, and then we're off to the galleries. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it's a last-minute kind of thing, I (Laura, your host for this evening) don't own a cell phone, so if you're running late or can't find us, my suggestion is to exchange phone numbers with another group member beforehand, so that you can get in touch with us at the last minute if need be. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRANSPORTATION/DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Public transportation is strongly recommended. Luckily, the Red Sox will be away, so the T shouldn't be too bogged down. Take the Green Line E-branch to either the Northeastern University or Symphony stop. If you get off at Northeastern, the restaurant is a five-minute walk traveling east on Huntington; if you get off at Symphony, the restaurant is a five-minute walk traveling west on Huntington. For more information, visit mbta.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************&lt;br /&gt;RULES OF ENGAGEMENT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow foodies' time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES afterward and you have not attended, it will count as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours, without an explanation, it will count as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, to those on the wait list, to the organizer, as well as the restaurant whose staff size is based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're removed and have extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so rate the event by completing the survey afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-four hours from the event and you are not &lt;br /&gt;able to attend, you MUST call or text Tonya at (617) 445-7549. &lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or less than &lt;br /&gt;twenty-four hour RSVP change from YES to NO, is an expected &lt;br /&gt;courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in front of the restaurant at 5:45. If you arrive late, look for the chatty group inside (it's a small place, so you can't miss us).</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212184267000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>We are a welcoming group of folks from all ages and backgrounds who enjoy good food, conversation, and (tonight), fine art.</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210281868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Budget Delight: Falafel and Free Fine Art!</name><id>7901181</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212011100000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/7901181/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/a/7/global_4066007.jpeg</photo_url></item>