<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 9.6 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Elevation Gain:&lt;/strong&gt; 2,191 feet &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Estimated Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 7 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Please check this meetup on Monday...unfortunately, with the muggy summer, long hikes may be rescheduled several times. Right now, there's a 30% chance of showers for Wednesday, June 6th. Note: the Orange carpool is now 8 AM.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/c/e/event_125330382.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/3/2/event_125330482.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CARPOOL INFO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8:00 am SHARP, Rts 2 and 202, Orange, Mass.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;There's a small dirt parking area on the right, 100 feet after going under Rt 2 from the South. If coming from the East on Rt 2, the parking spot is directly across from you from Exit 16. There's also a gas station/convenience store within a stone's throw of the parking spot in case people need last minute provisions. &lt;strong&gt;Please give your driver $10 for gas!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If there are other carpools, they may want to meet us here, too.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please indicate in your RSVP "Orange Carpool" if you'll join us. (Or say if looking for other carpool.) When you RSVP there's a text box for comments. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DESCRIPTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The hike:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start from the parking area on notch Road a short distance from the Bellows Pipe Trail. We'll make a loop with the Bellows Pipe, Appalachian, and Bernard Farm Trails, with a nice ridge hike almost to Mount Williams. I'm thinking I'd rather go &lt;strong&gt;up&lt;/strong&gt; the &lt;em&gt;ridge&lt;/em&gt; and down the Bellows Pipe, but I'll defer to other hikers on this...it is my first time hiking Greylock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is about 1 mile of steep section before the Bellows Pipe hits the Appalachian; not sure if that's easier going up or down...but I love the idea of going up the ridge with all the lovely views along the way. On the other hand, going down the ridge we could take a 1/2-mile detour to Mt Williams summit (then back onto our route) if we feel like it...that would add 1 mile altogether. We will also encounter the wreckage of a private plane on our route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The drive:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drive on the Mohawk Trail has always been my favorite part of any trip to Mount Greylock! After passing through scenic, midwestern towns such as Erving, Gill, and Turners Falls, you get to the good stuff. Charelemont must be the prettiest town in the state! You have entered the sharp ridges of Western Mass, but are driving through narrow green valleys of rivers and farmland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then the best part: 10+ miles winding through a sharp, narrow gorge alongside the river, with vertical mountains closing in from every side! After travelling uphill though the gorge, you emerge on the mountaintops, with several summits on the eastern and western sides. The climax is downhill through the hairpin turn, where the restaurant/gift shop has amazing views of Mounts Greylock and Williams, North Adams at the foot, a beautiful valley between you and the mountains, and parts of New York and Vermont.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will be coming back the same way...don't do this drive with bad brakes. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT MOUNT GREYLOCK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"At 3,491 feet, Mount Greylock is the highest point in Massachusetts. Rising above the surrounding Berkshire landscape, dramatic views of 60-90 miles distant may be seen. It spans the Massachusetts towns of North Adams, Adams, Lanesborough, Cheshire, Williamstown and New Ashford." (DCR website.) The tower that was closed, then torn down, years ago was rebuilt several years ago and has been open for quite some time. I only found this out from Kevin. (Otherwise, there would be no view from the top, due to tree cover.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Official Website:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/mtGreylock/"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/mtGreylock/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visitor Center:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 30 Rockwell Road &lt;br /&gt;

 P.O Box 138 &lt;br /&gt;

 Lanesborough, MA 01237 &lt;br /&gt;

 413-499-4262&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note that the DCR considers both distance and difficulty when doing their "ratings" which is confusing because the difficulty should be seperate. They rate this "aggressive" but I trust hiker's opinions more.&lt;/strong&gt; (Also, the guide says 6 hours, but I estimate 7, considering it's a little longer than the Pumpelly Trail to Mt. Monadnock. We have 11 daylight hours to hike!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PREPARING FOR THIS HIKE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check the weather the day before and plan your gear accordingly. It is best to dress in &lt;strong&gt;light&lt;/strong&gt; layers (no cotton) and bring plenty of water, as well as a raincoat (just in case) and a few emergency supplies. We will take one or two longer breaks for lunch/snacks, and pause along the way as needed. We will hike at the pace of the slowest member of the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water (1-2 liters)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raincoat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sturdy shoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flashlight or headlamp (even though this is a day hike, prepare for emergencies)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Batteries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Light layers (prepare for cool weather, but probably you'll be down to one light layer very quick)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insect repellant (especially "deep-woods"-type with DEET or Pemethrin)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I also recommend a camera!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I will have basic first aid with me...bandages, gauze, tape, antibiotic...I don't see the need for everyone to have such supplies, as long as someone does, but use your best judgement.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I DON'T HAVE TIME TO CHECK EMAIL FREQUENTLY AND IT GETS BACKED UP...IT IS MUCH BETTER TO POST QUESTIONS AND COMMENTS DIRECTLY ON THE MEETUP ITSELF (at least for mine).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus. (When we choose carpool locations, it will be posted!)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342978362000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335446507000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Greylock "Thoreau's Footsteps" (Bellows Pipe and Appalacian Trails)</name><id>62220842</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>25200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338991200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/62220842/</event_url></item>