<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Boylston St. and Dartmouth St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350093</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Copley SQ</name><city>Boston</city><id>1090276</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077332</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Boston Book Festival 2009, presented by State Street Corporation, which will take place on Saturday, October 24 from 10 a.m. - 6 p.m. in Copley Square. More than 75 top authors and presenters will be on hand for this FREE inaugural event. It's a great excursion for book groups, families, and anyone who loves to read.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The list of authors includes Nobel Prize winner Orhan Pamuk, Richard Russo, Anita Diamant, John Hodgman, Dennis Lehane, &amp;quot;Heroes&amp;quot; creator Tim Kring, Cornel West, actor Alicia Silverstone, Michael Patrick MacDonald, Barbara Lynch,Jill Lepore, and children's book author and illustrator Chris van Allsburg.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is something for everyone:&lt;br /&gt;Fiction and Poetry&lt;br /&gt;Current Affairs and Memoir&lt;br /&gt;Future of the Book technology panels and demonstrations&lt;br /&gt;Photography and Food Writing&lt;br /&gt;Children's Program&lt;br /&gt;Exhibits and Booksellers&lt;br /&gt;Music and Contests&lt;br /&gt;Workshops and Open Mic&lt;br /&gt;Book Signings and More&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, it's FREE and open to the public!&lt;br /&gt;Read all about it at www.bostonbookfest.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Book Festival events have no fee or reservation requirements with the following exceptions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be two special ticketed events in the evenings. The Festival will open with a song and word-filled kick-off event on Friday night, October 23 at 7:30 p.m. at Trinity Church (tickets $12 available 10/1). On Saturday, October 24 at 6 p.m., the Boston Book Festival will go out with a bang with the launch party for Boston Noir, a new collection of short stories edited by Dennis Lehane (tickets $15, 21+, available now).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grub Street is leading two events for writers that require pre-registration: Jumpstart Your Writing and Writer Idol. Free. Reservations open 10/1.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the Boston Book Festival site at www.bostonbookfest.org for more information or to buy tickets and make reservations for ticketed events.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Official Site: &lt;a href="http://bostonbookfest.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonbookfest...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256566312000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255229786000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Book Festival - Copley SQ</name><id>11598853</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256392800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11598853/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/1/global_11149745.jpeg</photo_url></item>