<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/u&gt; Rain date will be the next day, Sun. 11/7/10. We hope it doesn't rain, but if you can't make Sat. please consider stopping by on Sunday. This is an easy-breezy project and the tulips will bloom in spring for years to come!! Your friends and family are welcome too!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;WE REMEMBER LAUREN TISBERT:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  We have done our best to console and support our friend Susan Tisbert following the passing of her beloved daughter, Lauren, in September.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE PLAN:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; Lauren's favorite flowers are tulips. It would be lovely to create a garden of tulips ringing around a favorite tree on Susan's lawn.  After a long cold winter will come the warmth and color of Spring! How nice to look forward to the blooming of tulips planted by friends, in honor and rememberance of Lauren!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;WE NEED:&lt;/u&gt; PEOPLE to participate, give advice, and have fun!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Consider inviting family and friends as your guests!! Please bring a bag or two of tulips bulbs, and/or a bag of topsoil. Both of these items can be purchased at Home Depot or Lowes.  Not expensive, and we need plenty of both!&lt;br /&gt;If you have a bulb planter, bring that too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE REST:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; Susan needs help with raking her leaves, so we want to do this too.  Have a rake or a leaf blower?  Bring them!  (ps...I'm trying to keep up with them, so shouldn't be bad, suz ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE FUN:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; We will have a potluck day, so please bring something to share.  Susan will have her BBQ available.  A bonfire may be possible, weather permitting and she has a horseshoe pit.  (I will supply beer/water/soda, pizza and salad...suz)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; Park in Susan's driveway or along Keyes Hill Road but on-street parking is only allowed on Susan's side of the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) A chair&lt;br /&gt;2) Tulip bulbs or topsoil or BOTH.  A bulb planter or small spade, if you have one.&lt;br /&gt;3) Food to share and BYOBeverage please.&lt;br /&gt;4) Rake, leafblower.&lt;br /&gt;5) A pretty garden ornament? Little statues, pretty stones, any creative touches you may wish to add.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'M ALMOST DONE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  Please come even if you only have an hour to spare, or can stay longer.  &lt;br /&gt;Post any ideas because SUGGESTIONS and FEEDBACK are welcome!  &lt;br /&gt;And remember:  &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;MANY HANDS MAKE LIGHT WORK&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain date will be Sunday, November 7th between 10-11am arrival so we can watch the Pat's game at 1pm.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jill</member_name><member_id>3473807</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289230139000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287341611000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's create a Tulip Garden for Lauren!</name><id>15138056</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289052000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/15138056/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/6/global_18812166.jpeg</photo_url></item>