<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Berkshires</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06757</zip><lat>41.679958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Club Getaway</name><city>Kent</city><id>684911</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.490791</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Fun, Sports, Relaxing&amp;amp;Socializing! Don't miss our FINAL Weekend Getaway Event of the Year / Fun Meetup Getaway&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fun, Sports, Relaxing and Socializing! Don't miss our 2010 / Annual Fun Meetup Getaway , Book Today by calling Greg at 917-868-4268 to Join us and Reserve Your Spot !! THE FINAL Getaway Weekend usually sells out 1-2 weeks in advance and will fill up soon, DON'T GET CLOSED OUT, Sign up TODAY (Mid-sept.) /ASAP by calling 917-868-4268&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call Greg @ 917-868-4268 if interested, &lt;br /&gt;Book Today and Mention FUN MEETUP to save $ off the weekend &amp;amp; Get a FREE DRINK Book !!! (Type Fun Meetup in the How did you hear about box) call me @ 917-868-4268 if any questions ! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Getaway Weekends typically sell out in advance, Advance Reservations are required , call 917-868-4268 if questions, Usually sell out weeks before the event !!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fun Meetup Presents Fun Meetup Getaway, Fun Getaway Weekend !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us in Kent , CT, for the summer Weekend ! Bus leaves friday at 5:30pm from the upper east side, NYC, or meet us up there ! &lt;br /&gt;Weekends sell out in advance (up to 1-2 weeks before we leave) and &lt;br /&gt;reservations are required! call me @917-868-4268 if questions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this amazing weekend !!! (make sure to mention &lt;br /&gt;Fun Meetup if booking by phone or type Fun Meetup in the comment box &lt;br /&gt;if booking online to get the discount and some free drinks !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hottest sports, adventures and parties are at Club Getaway this &lt;br /&gt;Fall Weekend! In addition to all the cool Getaway stuff like &lt;br /&gt;the flying trapeze, tennis, mountain biking, volleyball &lt;br /&gt;and rock climbing, we've got a weekend packed with great special &lt;br /&gt;events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this great weekend, Don't get closed out, Book &lt;br /&gt;Today , call me @ 917-868-4268 if questions !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Choose any weekend and mention Fun Meetup when reserving for your FREE FUN MEETUP DRINKS BOOK !!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sample Schedule, we'll get the official schedule Friday Night upon check in or saturday morning!!! &lt;br /&gt;Saturday Afternoon/Night &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:00 pm Tennis Tournament &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Basketball Clinic with Hollis Copeland &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Rock Climbing &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Intermidiate Road Biking - 10 miles &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Mountain Bike II - Single Track Trails Intermediate &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Archery Class &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Co-ed Volleyball Tournament &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Latin and Swing Dance Class 2:00 - 3:30 pm Walk to Kent for Shopping or Ice Cream &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 4:00 pm Advanced Trapeze &lt;br /&gt;2:30 - 4:30 pm Mountain Bike II - Single Track Trails Intermediate &lt;br /&gt;2:30 - 4:30 pm Arts &amp;amp; Crafts &lt;br /&gt;3:00 - 4:30 pm Fly on the Bungee Trampoline &lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 5:00 pm Advanced Road Bike &lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 5:00 pm Swing Dancing with Lucky &lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 5:00 pm Wine Tasting with Wine Expert Horst &lt;br /&gt;4:00 - 5:30 pm Co-ed Keg Softball &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 5:30 pm Bike Trip to Town for Ice Cream &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 5:30 pm Yoga with NYC's OM Yoga &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 5:30 pm Collage Art Class &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 7:00 pm Lakeside Happy Hour: Live Music, Complemantary BBQ Grill and Drink Specials &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 6:00 pm Texas Hold'em Poker &lt;br /&gt;8:00 - 9:30 pm Restauratore Italiano under the Tent followed by Rob and The River Boys Live &lt;br /&gt;9:30 pm The Out of this World Party at the Boat House Lounge with DJ . Haunted House. Dancing till the wee hours. &lt;br /&gt;12:00 am Midnight Campfire with Live Music and S'mores &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fall Sports Weekend Events Include:&lt;br /&gt;Tailgate Party&lt;br /&gt;Pumpkin Carving&lt;br /&gt;Haunted House&lt;br /&gt;Club Getaway's Famous Costume Party!! ((Bring up a costume with you))&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You Can Do It All...Or Nothing At All&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get Active &lt;br /&gt;Meet your match in basketball, volleyball or tennis. Hit the road with one of our Specialized road bikes. Share a keg at our co-ed softball game or team up for an action packed game of dodgeball. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seek Adventure &lt;br /&gt;Climb the Berkshire Mountains and rappel down a rock ledge. Hike along the Appalachian Trail or around camp. Discover the rush of soaring through the air on a flying trapeze or the 350-foot aerial zip line. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be Creative &lt;br /&gt;Stimulate your senses with the arts, food and wine. Become a salsa sensation in dance class. Let chefs from the Connecticut Culinary Institute show you how to cook up delicious dishes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just Relax &lt;br /&gt;Take a short walk to the charming town of Kent, Connecticut to enjoy an ice cream cone and browse through the antique shops. Lounge by the lake with a good book. Take a yoga , massage or wine tasting class. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Party On &lt;br /&gt;Share the day’s adventure at Happy Hour by the lake with live music, great drinks, and a complimentary BBQ. Dance in the Boat House Club. Play volleyball under the stars. Join strumming guitars and s'mores around the campfire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As the only facility of its kind on the East Coast. The club is leading the way in sports, adventure, fitness, and feeling-good vacations…The bottom line at Club Getaway is that everyone has a good time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- New York Post&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;BOOK Our Last 2010 Weekend CAMP / Getaway WEEKEND and Mention FUN MEETUP to save $ &amp;amp; Get FREE DRINKS , Join us this season!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the final Getaway of 2010 !((Halloween Theme weekend, the 10/1 weekend always closes out in advance, Don't get closed out, JOIN US, call 917-868-4268 if questions/ to signup)) ((RSVPing yes or maybe is not enough, you must book your spot in advance with credit card, call 917-868-4268, FunMeetupGetaway , Don't miss this Great Weekend !))&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>call Greg @ 917-868-4268 meet at dinner Friday Night !!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>8121708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285973487000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonMeetup</urlname><id>1477254</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>#1 Meetup - BOSTON MEETUP,  Travel&amp; Events, BOSTONMEETUP.org</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>100</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284562630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fun, Sports, Relaxing&amp;Socializing! Don't miss our FINAL Weekend Getaway Event !!</name><id>14779004</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285968600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonMeetup/events/14779004/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/c/global_17984108.jpeg</photo_url></item>