<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purgatory Chasm is a great place to explore and since it's only open seasonally until the end of November we had to fit it in.  The park is located about 1 hour southwest of Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time:  It takes about half hour- one hour to walk so we'll head over to nearby Douglas State Park for another hour or so.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terrain: Please wear sturdy shoes or hiking boots as the trails are slippery even when it is dry out.  This is a moderate walk but it is very rocky. &lt;br /&gt;While Douglas State Park is easy with broad trials and little elevation.  Bring water and snacks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A unique natural landmark, Purgatory Chasm runs for a quarter of a mile between granite walls rising as high as 70 feet. Popular with picnickers and rock-climbers alike, the Chasm is believed to have its origin in the sudden release of dammed-up glacial meltwater near the end of the last Ice Age, approximately 14,000 years ago.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails lead to a wide variety of rock formations, with such romantic names as The Corn Crib, The Coffin, The Pulpit, Lovers' Leap and Fat Man's Misery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the east &amp;amp; west: Take Mass Pike to Exit 10A, take Rt.146 south into Town of Sutton, take Purgatory Road Exit, take right at end of ramp onto Purgatory Road, park is 1,000 feet up the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/purg.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.  Douglas State Park - Park Directions&lt;br /&gt;Douglas State Forest is located on the southern border of central Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;From east or west: MA Turnpike (Rte. I-90) to exit 10, Rte. 395 south to exit 2, Rte. 16 east 5 miles, turn right on Cedar Street for .5 mile, go straight on Wallum Lake Rd. 1 mile&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/doug.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later we'll head to late lunch:&lt;br /&gt;Waterfront Mary's &lt;br /&gt;103 Birch Island Road&lt;br /&gt;Webster, MA 01570-1550  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.waterfrontmarys.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waterfront...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196471975000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194305497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Purgatory Chasm/Douglas State Park</name><id>6683896</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196010900000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6683896/</event_url></item>