<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>274 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371369</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center for Digital Imaging Arts at Boston University</name><city>Waltham</city><id>723446</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236903</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>ASMP NE Chapter presents: &lt;br /&gt;Who? What? Where?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who is buying Photography? What are they looking for? Where are they finding it? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This panel discussion with top industry creatives and moderated by Louisa Curtis of Chatterbox Enterprises, is destined to be revealing as well as informative. In a time of economic uncertainties, where is our industry headed and how do photographers adjust to stay in business? Louisa has invited a diverse panel of six industry creatives ranging from large international ad agencies, to the boutique and niche, with a group that includes creative directors, art buyers and producers as well as a graphic designer, all of whom are willing to share their insights and thoughts on our industry now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After introductions to the panelists, their backgrounds and visual examples of their agencies’ work, Louisa will ask the type of questions that are so pertinent today, such as:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the big challenges for creatives and photographers in the current climate?&lt;br /&gt;What type of work are you looking for, and has it changed in a significant way this year?&lt;br /&gt;What new trends are you seeing and what has become passé?&lt;br /&gt;What makes a photographer stand out from the crowd in today’s saturated market? &lt;br /&gt;How do you find new talent? &lt;br /&gt;What type of photographer’s promotion appeals to you and do you have a preference? &lt;br /&gt;What makes you bookmark a website? &lt;br /&gt;Do you use stock and if so, how often and where do you go to find it?&lt;br /&gt;Do you prefer dealing with an individual photographer or an agent?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And there will also be ample time for the audience to ask questions during the discussion. &lt;br /&gt;Read the biographies of the participating panelists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please register early  so we can make sure to have enough food and beverage for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Boston University’s Center for Digital Imaging Arts, 274 Moody Street, Waltham. - directions&lt;br /&gt;Time:  Social hour &amp;amp; Food: 6:00; Program: 7:00&lt;br /&gt;Cost (Food, beverage provided)&lt;br /&gt;Pre-registered:  Members: $1; Students: $10; All Others: $25&lt;br /&gt;At the door:  Members $5; Students: $20; All others: $35&lt;br /&gt;From Points North/South to the CDIA Waltham Campus (274 Moody Street, Waltham, MA.)&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 128/I-95 to Exit 26 (Route 20). Follow Route 20 East for 2 miles. Turn right onto Moody Street. CDIA is located 1/4 mile down on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points East/West&lt;br /&gt;Take the Mass Pike to exit 14 (Route 128/I-95). Take Route 128/I-95 to Exit 26 (Route 20). Follow Route 20 East for 2 miles. Turn right onto Moody Street. CDIA is located 1/4 mile down on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION&lt;br /&gt;Train: Fitchburg (Fitchburg Line) commuter rail to Central Square Waltham - CDIA is located two blocks up on Moody Street.&lt;br /&gt;Bus: Oak Park - Dudley via Central Sq bus #170 or Cedarwood bus #70/70A &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING&lt;br /&gt;There are two public parking lots within a short walking distance of CDIA. The Embassy Parking Lot is located two blocks down Pine Street behind the Embassy Landmark movie theatre and is located one block away from CDIA. The Crescent Street Lot is another option, located on Crescent Street between Moody and Adams. In both cases look for the parking signs when you reach Moody street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS &lt;br /&gt;Enter your starting address in the following format to receive driving directions to CDIA. &amp;quot;123 Main Street, Anytown, State 01234&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ASMP Members $1.00&lt;br /&gt;Students $10.00&lt;br /&gt;Non-members $25.00&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Scott will be wearing a big old grin...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236899734000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235080543000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ASMP Meeting About Who What Why When Where and How</name><id>9778649</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236726000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9778649/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/1/3/global_7379651.jpeg</photo_url></item>