<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of Coddington and Spear Street</address_2><address_1>8 Spear Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.252351</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Bethany Congregation Church</name><city>Quincy</city><id>861252</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.000549</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Space still available!!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stretch, breath, relax at our afternoon Hatha Yoga class. Join members of the South Shore Fitness Meetup Group and their Guests for our own private Hatha Yoga Class taught by our own Group Member, Elaine! The class is being held at the Real Life Yoga Studio in the Bethany Congregational Church in Quincy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During Hatha Yoga, the poses are held for 2-3 breaths. The class is suitable for is beginner to moderate.  Almost anyone can participate. Wear loose clothing. Bring water and a mat if you have one (there will be mats available at the studio). Yoga is best done on an empty stomach.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive at 3:50 PM so that we can start the class right at 4 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please Note: To ensure that the room rental and instructor fee is covered, we are requesting that you mail your money in prior to the class. You should RSVP to the Wait List and once your money is received, your RSVP will be changed to a YES. If the class is canceled due to min number of people not met, you will receive a refund.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday Afternoon Hatha Yoga Class   &lt;br /&gt;October 4 @ 4PM  &lt;br /&gt;The Bethany Congregation Church  &lt;br /&gt;8 Spear Street  &lt;br /&gt;Quincy, MA 02169 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: Inside Yoga studio on the 2nd floor. Plenty of parking in lot.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class Cost: $10pp due by Friday, October 2nd. Fees must be received from at least 8 people by October 2nd in order for this class to take place.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: Org Team and Annual Members - None. Members and Guests: $2 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note about Cost and Fees: Elaine will be collecting the money but your class fee can be paid at any meetup event as long as you let the Event Organizer know which event this is for. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers:  Elaine  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Fees must be received from at least 8 people by October 2nd in order for this class to take place.   &lt;br /&gt;Max of 16 total attendees. Guests are welcome!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Church is across from College Next to Thomas Crane Library.  &lt;br /&gt;Yoga Studio up stairs on Second Floor.  &lt;br /&gt;Elevator and handicap accessible.  &lt;br /&gt;Door will be open. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rte. 3 From North and South  &lt;br /&gt;Take the Quincy Center T station exit, follow Burgin Pkway. for about 3 miles staying to the right.  &lt;br /&gt;At intersection of Granite St. take a right (Burger King is on left at this intersection) into Quincy Center, stay left around island, takes you to the right  &lt;br /&gt;Go straight through this light at (intersection of Washington st.)  &lt;br /&gt;This is Coddington st., Bethany Church is on right. Take the first right onto Spear st.  &lt;br /&gt;Parking is in back of Church &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- From 3A South  &lt;br /&gt;Follow 3A, Washington st, towards Quincy Center.  &lt;br /&gt;Take right, at light at Thomas Crane Library, intersection of Washington and Coddington st.  &lt;br /&gt;Church is on right  &lt;br /&gt;(post office will be on left) Take Right onto Spear st.  &lt;br /&gt;(Parking is behind Church) or on Coddington st. in front of Church &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please use mapquest.com for door-to-door directions.read less&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1254969838000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252379886000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Afternoon Hatha Yoga Class</name><id>11315050</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254686400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11315050/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/9/b/global_10601275.jpeg</photo_url></item>