<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>800 Boylston St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02199</zip><lat>42.348541</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Prudential Center Food Court </name><city>Boston</city><id>4498902</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082581</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for our &lt;a href="http://mgn.cardsconversation.org"&gt;eleventh Mega Game Nite in Boston on February 1st&lt;/a&gt;. MGN continues to be a great way to mix and mingle with old friends and meet new people! So grab your favorite board or cards game for an early night on the town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Like our event last year&lt;strong&gt;, MGN XI&lt;/strong&gt; will actually be divided up into different sections, specializing in certain themes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Party Palace&lt;/strong&gt; will have the main playing area for party games and for those who just want to socialize with other attendees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Card Room&lt;/strong&gt; will be for those who rather play card games (&lt;strong&gt;Poker&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Spades&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Hearts&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Bridge&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Cribbage&lt;/strong&gt;, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Strategy Bunker&lt;/strong&gt; is a separate area for those who want to play more serious strategy games (such as &lt;strong&gt;Settlers of Catan&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Risk&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Blokus&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Ticket to Ride&lt;/strong&gt;, etc.) We have a lot of people interested in these types of games, so we wanted to provide a special location for those to congregate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;??? (it's a secret!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is hosted by Tony, group organizer for the popular Cards &amp;amp; Conversation group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What to bring? Well, any card and board games are welcome. &lt;strong&gt;Apples to Apples&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Catch Phrase&lt;/strong&gt; are always popular. Up for some strategy games? You'll see &lt;strong&gt;Settlers of Catan&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Ticket to Ride&lt;/strong&gt;, and other board games being played. Unsure?  We'll have a set of volunteers who will be supervising to assist you in finding a great crowd of people to play with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come for dinner and some drinks, or just games and socializing! Since this is an open event, come early, come late, stay for a bit, stay for the whole event, anything goes! The event is held until 10pm. Afterwards, many attendees go out for drinks and food at &lt;strong&gt;Legal Sea Food&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Cheesecake Factory&lt;/strong&gt; after the event...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is held in the rear of Food Court next to &lt;strong&gt;Pizzeria Regina&lt;/strong&gt;. Look for the Meetup Game Nite sign.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>MGN is held in the rear of the Prudential Center Food Court, next to Pizzeria Regina and Cheeseboy. Go to the MGN Information Booth.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tony</member_name><member_id>977510</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359772424000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359081663000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mega Game Night: Huge Joint Event at Prudential Center</name><id>101276652</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359761400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/101276652/</event_url></item>