<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let’s dance away the close of summer and welcome the fall aboard the Provincetown II “Don’t Let the Summer End Party Cruise.”  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boat has 3 decks to dance on, multiple live bands (on the covered decks) and a DJ, spinning on the large top deck for dancing under the stars.  Free Airbrush Tattoos and Body Painting and contests will also be going on throughout the night.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I went on one of these several weeks ago and had a great time.  The views of Boston Harbor at night are beautiful.   &lt;b&gt;The boat leaves at 7:30PM and docks at 10:30PM&lt;/b&gt;.  For those looking to take the T, you can leave immediately after.  For those looking to stay out later, according to the website there is a free afterparty nearby from 10:30PM-1AM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If as great and as lively of a group shows up as the one who came out to Noir, this should be a great event!  Right now tickets are only $10, so sign up before 9/11 when the promotion ends.  After 9/11, tickets become $25 (link below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mcssl.com/SecureCart/ViewCart.aspx?sctoken=d07543d4b52b4db1a928a22f61b5727d&amp;amp;mid=D95F4FEE-72AA-4912-9C02-D4692E2849F6&amp;amp;bhcp=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mcssl.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please only RSVP “Yes” after buying your ticket so I have a proper head count.  &lt;b&gt;We’ll be meeting at 7PM in front of the doors to the 7-11 on the corner of the pier on Seaport Blvd.&lt;/b&gt;   Click on the map: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;q=&amp;amp;sourceid=navclient-ff&amp;amp;rlz=1B5GGGL_enUS316US318&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will leave 7-11 and get on the boat by 7:15PM, so be on time or find us onboard. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get there: &lt;br /&gt;By T: From South Station, take the Silver Line to the World Trade Center stop and walk 2 blocks to the Commonwealth Pier. The boat is halfway down the pier.&lt;br /&gt;By Car: Park at Anthony's or in any one of the surrounding lots.  Walk past the Seaport Bar, then take an immediate left before the World Trade Center onto the Commonwealth Pier. The boat is halfway down the pier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boat is the MV Provincetown II at Bay State Cruise Co. located at 200 Seaport Blvd on the Commonwealth Pier.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be standing outside the 7-11 on the corner of the pier</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>6966003</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255126713000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252375748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Don’t Let the Summer End Party Cruise!</name><id>11314508</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253228400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/11314508/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/d/2/global_10599026.jpeg</photo_url></item>