<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From the Brattle website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some Like It Hot at 4:30, 9:30   &lt;br /&gt;(1959) dir Billy Wilder w/Marilyn Monroe, Tony Curtis, Jack Lemmon, George Raft [120 min] &lt;br /&gt;Double Feature w/THE APARTMENT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A buddy comedy with a twist, Joe (Curtis) and Jerry (Lemmon) are two musicians who witness a mob hit during the St. Valentine's Day Massacre. They are found out and quickly need to wrangle enough cash to get out of town, however, the only paying gig around is in an all-female band. Mustering up their courage (and their pantyhose), the two dress - and, amazingly, pass - as women, securing their place in the band and their salvation from the mob. However, things become more complicated when Joe falls for their gorgeous band mate (Monroe), and Jerry finds himself with his own problems after he catches the eye of a male suitor who won't take no for an answer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Apartment at 7:00   &lt;br /&gt;(1960) dir Billy Wilder w/Jack Lemmon, Shirley MacLaine, Fred MacMurray [125 min] &lt;br /&gt;Double Feature w/SOME LIKE IT HOT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The great Billy Wilder made 10 pictures under the United Artists banner and this is one of the sharpest. Lemmon, as the low man on the corporate ladder, sells his morals for a higher rung by lending the use of his Upper West Side bachelor pad to his superiors for extra-marital trysts. Complications ensue when he falls for the office's favorite elevator girl (MacLaine) who happens to be his boss's mistress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be seeing Some Like It Hot at 4:30 and then The Apartment at 7:00.  As you can see, Some Like It Hot is also playing at 9:30.  When you RSVP, pleases let me know which movie(s) you'll be attending.  Then I can look for you so we can all sit together.  Hope to see you there.  Susan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will hold up a meetup sign near the front.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210884111000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>It's a double feature - what a deal.  Two movies, "Some Like It Hot" and "The Apartment,"  for the price of one!!!!</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210250938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Double Feature of Billy Wilder Films at the Brattle!!</name><id>7897983</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210710600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7897983/</event_url></item>