<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This will be a 6 mile loop hike that should take not more than 5 hours. There are plenty of ups and and an interesting trail. We will meet at 10:00 AM at the Rte. 77 parking area for the Mattabesett Trail (on rte. 77, 4.6 miles south of Durham or 4.3 miles north of Rte. 80 in Guilford - see location below). This will be both our starting location and our ending location. We will road walk about 2/3 mile to the start of the trail. The group will hike on the Lone Pine Trail for 3 miles west to north-west and up onto Totoket Mountain. This is a traprock mountain of altitude 720 ft. We join the Mattabesett and hike 3 miles to the south-east, past Bluff Head and its associated cliffs overlooking Myerhuber Pond and the three preserves in the valley. We reach the endpoint back at the cars.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equipped we should come in earlier than estimated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to go should have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* A daypack - To carry trail food, water, and any extra items.  &lt;br /&gt;

 * Hiking boots advised  &lt;br /&gt;

 * 2 quarts water&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate/directions&lt;/strong&gt; (dirt parking lot off Rte. 77, roughly 4510 Durham Rd., Guilford, CT)&lt;span&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://mapq.st/13ZsleH"&gt;http://mapq.st/13ZsleH&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 [lat 41.408, lon -72.6962]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt; are in "&lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Walk Book: Eest&lt;/strong&gt;" 19th ed., by Connecticut Forest and Park Association as map &lt;strong&gt;MB-5b&lt;/strong&gt; on page 24 and map &lt;strong&gt;MB-5c&lt;/strong&gt; on page 25. They can also be found in &lt;span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Walk Book: West&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;" 19th ed., by Connecticut Forest and Park Association as map&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;MB-5b&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;on page 108 and map&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;MB-5c&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;on page 109.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Ford Escape SUV, CT plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365425346000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365220589000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking Lone Pine Trail to Mattabassett Trail Guilford CT</name><id>112958272</id><duration>18000000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365343200000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/112958272/</event_url></item>