<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mountain Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.475981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-464-2987</phone><name>Wachusetts Mountain State Reservation</name><city>Princeton</city><id>761189</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.883362</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A slight change in this day.  We will now be helping with the Department of Conservation and Recreation's Park Serve Day.  We will still be at Wachusett Mountain State Reservation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Name: Wachusett Mountain State Reservation &lt;br /&gt;Park Serve Activity: Participants will assist with Trail Restoration on the Pine Hill Trail, adjacent to the Visitor Center parking lot as well as trail clean-up and flower planting. &lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place/Time: Hitchcock Visitor Center at 9:00 a.m. - 1:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the East/Northeast/Southeast&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take I-495 to exit 29, Rt. 2 west. &lt;br /&gt;Take Rt. 2 west to exit 25, Rt. 140 south. At the top of the exit ramp take a right onto Rt. 140 south. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 2.1 miles on Rt. 140 south and take a right onto Mile Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road, take left fork onto Mountain Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd. Park entrance is on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OR&lt;/b&gt; Take 1-90 (MA PIKE) west to exit 10, I-290 north. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 7.3 miles on I-290 north to exit 19, I-190 north. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 9 miles on I-190 north to exit 5, Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 9.3 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left onto Mile Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road, bear left at fork onto Mountain Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd. Park entrance is on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the West/Northwest&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-91 to Exit 27, Rt. 2 east. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 31 miles on Rt. 2 east to exit 25, Rt. 140 south. &lt;br /&gt;Take Rt. 2 east to exit 25, Rt. 140 south. &lt;br /&gt;At the top of the exit ramp take a left onto Rt. 140 south. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 2.1 miles on Rt. 140 south and take a right onto Mile Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road bear left at fork onto Mountain Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd. Park entrance is on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Southwest&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take I-90 (MA PIKE) east to Exit 10, I-290 north. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 7.3 miles on I-290 north to exit 19, I-190 north. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 9 miles on I-190 north to exit 5, Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 9.3 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left onto Mile Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road, bear left at fork onto Mountain Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd. Park entrance is on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes, Gear and Attire:   This is an outdoor project suitable for adults or families with older children (10 or older). Long pants and long- sleeve shirts and work gloves are strongly recommended. Loppers are helpful if available.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>7626345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272423023000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270242179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate Earth Day with Greater Worcester Humanists!</name><id>13071255</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272114000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/13071255/</event_url></item>