<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>800 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02199</zip><lat>42.348690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Prudential Center: Terrace Food Court</name><city>Boston</city><id>833924</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082520</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/6/0/event_62028992.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Anyone in the mood to play some Cribbage? How about Scopa? What about Catan? If you answered yes to any of these, come on down to the Pru on Thursday, May 16, and pull up a chair! Spring is in full bloom, and it's time to get out of the house. But before you venture out on your weekend hikes and sailing trips, try warming up by playing a few games in a really cool food court, or if you're really daring, the Prudential's outdoor terrace! This will be a joint meetup with a few groups, so come on down and meet a few people!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/6/5/4/event_62030772.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your brand new to playing games, relax. We can teach you almost any game you want to play, and we're great with newbies. The only requirement is that you arrive with a desire to socialize. So hop on the green line and come join us! Just head toward the back of the food court on the right and tell anyone playing a game that you're new - you'll be pointed in the right direction!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO GET THERE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be in the rear of the Terrace Food Court at &lt;strong&gt;Prudential Center&lt;/strong&gt;.  We will be in the back of the food court, to the right and behind Pizzeria Regina.  &lt;em&gt;The food court is large, so if you do not remember this information, you won't find us!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Street parking on Bolyston Street and the surrounding streets are available, but it is very limited.  Your best best will be to park at the &lt;a href="http://www.prudentialcenter.com/parking/parking_map.php" target="_blank"&gt;Prudential Center garage&lt;/a&gt;, $12 with validation at any store or food vendor.  For more information about parking at Prudential Center, visit their &lt;a href="http://www.prudentialcenter.com/parking/rates.php" target="_blank"&gt;parking rates&lt;/a&gt; page.  A map showing the parking garage entrances is &lt;a href="http://www.prudentialcenter.com/parking/parking_map.php" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are coming in via the subway, you have a number of great options:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Green Line: For 'E' trains only, please use &lt;strong&gt;Prudential Station&lt;/strong&gt;on Huntington Avenue.  For all other Green Line trains, please use &lt;strong&gt;Copley&lt;/strong&gt; on Boylston Street at Dartmouth Street (next to the Boston Public Library) or &lt;strong&gt;Hynes Convention Center&lt;/strong&gt; on Massachusetts Avenue at Newbury Street.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Orange Line or Commuter Rail:  There's a direct underground connection between Copley Mall and &lt;strong&gt;Back Bay&lt;/strong&gt; Station on the Orange and Purple Lines.  From Copley Center you can cross the Copley Bridge into the Prudential Center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the people playing games to the right of the Pizzeria Regina.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rakesh Khetarpal</member_name><member_id>13468661</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368754304000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368193638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday Night Cards @ the Pru</name><id>118725802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368743400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/118725802/</event_url></item>