<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Valley Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.608825</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-777-1245 </phone><name>Connors Farm</name><city>Danvers</city><id>750154</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.937395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;center&gt;Welcome to Connors Farm Corn MaiZe!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Danvers, MA - September 2009: The Connors Farm family will join forces with Fox Licensing &amp;amp; Merchandising to unravel the mystery as they bring the MAiZE, an intricate network of twists and turns carved into 7 acres of corn, back to the North Shore on September 12, 2009.  The Connors family and maze designer Brett Herbst - the world's leading designer of 600+ corn mazes worldwide -- hope to challenge the wits of those seeking to find the one exit from their mind-boggling puzzle -- a unique source of good farmin' fun for adults and children alike. Though the correct pathway can be walked in only 20 minutes, most wandering maize-goers will require about one hour to travel through more than four miles of twists, turns and decision points.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When/Where:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MAiZE will give Massachusetts residents the chance to &amp;quot;get lost&amp;quot;. Special days of operation are Singles Night (Friday, October 9, 6:00 PM to 10:00 PM), featuring live music, a bonfire, marshmallow roasting, and apple cider.  Champions BBQ will also be on site, and there is also a great country store to shop or browse around in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did this event last year with another meetup group and it was a lot of fun, come out and let’s get lost in the MaiZe!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be updated as the date gets closer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special Event:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Singles Night - Friday, October 9th - 6-10pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a flashlight and try to find your way through our 7 acre maze in the dark with other singles.  After going through the MaiZe, come and hang out by the pond, around the bonfire, roasting marshmallows, while listening to live music, all for the admission into the MaiZe!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get a $1.00 off your visit go to &lt;a href="http://www.connorsfarm.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.connorsfar...&lt;/a&gt; on the bottom of the screen hit Corn Maize on the right side you will see the “Get a Maize Coupon, just fill out some information and print the coupon right from your printer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Were to meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in front of the Connors Farm Sign facing the street, if you are not able to make it at the meetup time go into the MaiZe and come around back to the pond and find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to bring:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A flash light and marshmallows only if you want to toast them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There is a lot of parking around the front of the farm/store or if you need to parking on the street is allowed.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside by the Connors Farm sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255302535000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250640277000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Night @ the 7 ACRE Corn Maize!</name><id>11143177</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255129200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/11143177/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/d/global_10274989.jpeg</photo_url></item>