<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187114</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>Richard Tosti Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>826225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236877</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>New Years Celebraton!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, party is on for tonight. Bring your own wine or beer, catered food buffet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members do not have to bring food for the Holiday season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional:Casual professional dress code.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This evening will be special to celebrate our optimism for the future.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Past members who have found the love of their lives are invited to this special celebration. Sharing your joy with others will be truly inspirational.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite a gentleman you know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our energy will soar again! And our hope will be renewed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Values of this group:  To be nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and to be respectful to everyone.  We utilize private dance parties as a vehicle to meet other singles personally.  Purpose is to socialize with similar people of our age (30-65) who are searching for a lifetime partner.  Have fun meeting old and new friends.  Circulate, talk to everyone.  If someone is alone go up to them and say hi!  Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite other friends, particularly men.  Our objective is to have an equal amount of men and women.  We are very close on equal numbers of men and women.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable dance party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***The entry fee is $30.00.  Paid in advance. Bring your own wine/beer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location is in a warm, loving and relaxing environment.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dress code - &amp;quot;professional casual&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;7:30PM - 12:30pm- optional- stay as long as you want, feel free to leave early&lt;br /&gt;Friday-Dec. 31, 2010&lt;br /&gt;My residence, 36 Woodridge Road, Westwood, MA 02090&lt;br /&gt;Maximum attendees 40-----minimum 20 attendees&lt;br /&gt;Dancing is optional - CDs-bring your favorite&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions&lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road &lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128-Exit 16B/Route 109 toward Westwood &lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles left on Pond Street, just past the middle school on left. If you go by Dunkin Donuts on right, you missed it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go 1 mile, then left on Oak Street (Google search says go right; this is wrong.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go 1.5 miles to end and turn right on Brook Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 100 feet, take a right on Woodridge Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My home is the 3rd house on the left, cream colored, number 36.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on Friday, Dec. 31st., 2010 at 7:30pm----&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30pm Party begins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food served at 8:00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be!&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293952029000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283820009000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Years Eve Party 30-65</name><id>14677912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293841800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/14677912/</event_url></item>