<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1037 Silvermine Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06840</zip><lat>41.151524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-966-9700</phone><name>Silvermine Guild Art Center</name><city>New Canaan</city><id>718617</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.450615</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;Artist Talk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6:00pm &lt;br /&gt;

Silvermine Galleries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;Join us for an informal talk with exhibiting artists Jocelyn Braxton Armstrong and Marilyn Richeda who will discuss their work in their current exhibits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;Jocelyn Braxton Armstrong&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/0/e/event_97688462.jpeg" width="292" height="229" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;That's Life # 2, translucent porcelain, plexiglass, wall hung pedestal, halogens, 23" x 26" x 11"&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;Modernist ceramic sculptor, Jocelyn Braxton Armstrong's exhibition "I AM SHE," features recent figurative sculpture and installations. In this exhibition she examines issues relating to feminism, exploring the causes of gender based violence and inequality, from both a domestic and global perspective. Throughout the exhibition, she aims to inspire curiosity, thought and dialogue, to raise awareness and incite positive action that promotes feminism worldwide. Jocelyn's work is, for the most part, unglazed white porcelain. Her elegant figurative sculptures appear to be covered with delicate line drawings. These lines are used in an illustrative effect and sometimes the lines can express meaning. Her sculptures have a fresh sophistication and modern aesthetic that link fine art with craft. Of her work, Ms. Armstrong states, "Gesture is what interests me. Body language is beguiling. Gesture naturally conveys movement but can also be passive or submissive, playful or seductive, regal and proud. Gesture can tell a story. Some sculptures are motivated and methodically planned, while others are spontaneous and come from within. My most recent sculptures are more conceptual in nature, influenced by my life experiences now. I am exploring the emotions of relationships, conflict, love, and family, particularly how these emotions relate to women."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marilyn Richeda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/8/event_97689032.jpeg" width="200" height="298" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Mystified, Ceramic, 38" x 10" x 7"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;"Whispered Warnings" is an exhibit of sculptural works by Marilyn Richeda of other worldly figures, creatures not found in forests, on the street or in encyclopedias. Some figures are robot-like, non-speaking, noiseless and still. Others stand confident, perhaps hiding something. Birds are portrayed as enchanting, but often showing a darker side such as feelings of loss, helplessness and being marooned. The combination of strangeness and familiarity reveal human concerns and behaviors as portrayed by the birds. "I rarely start to work with a clear visual image of what I will create. I do, however, have an idea of what I want to explore or a feeling I want to express and keep on working until I feel it's right," says Ms. Richeda of her work. "Like all my work, they explore pattern and color. In many ways, color is the most important part of every piece I make. Color is what seduces me. Even the names of the glazes affect which ones I select." Marilyn gets her inspiration for her colors from looking&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>will wear the bw scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332960442000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330536467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jocelyn Braxton Armstrong and Marilyn Richeda - Artist Talk</name><id>54353492</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332884700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/54353492/</event_url></item>