<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Westminster st</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822720</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-421-3300</phone><name>Tazza Caffe</name><city>Providence</city><id>700461</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.412926</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Providence Collective Monday Meetup series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar and restaurant scenes in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Tazza - on Westminster St. in downtown Providence&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tazza is a perennial favorite of P-Collective members and was requested for this Monday Night BECAUSE the windows along Westminster street will be lined with pumpkins carved by RISD students! The Plan: Gather at Tazza and around 6:30 we can make our way down the street to view the pumpkins and return to Tazza afterward. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tazza has everything and is a super versatile place with lunch, dinner and breakfast as well as different events, live music, etc. almost every night of the week. Its trendy yet cozy, and always a good time. If we're lucky they also might be playing some great movie on the big screen, aka the wall next to the bar. So if you haven't been, this one is worth knowing about - you'll be back. So let's check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.&lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not sure what scarf I'll be wearing - but we're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288048232000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287889066000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup  - Tazza and pumpkins too!</name><id>15208090</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288044000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/15208090/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>