<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; beginner-to-moderate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length:&lt;/strong&gt; estimated 4 miles, on well-used paths and dirt roads, with some hills. Maybe 2 hours plus picnic/sightseeing time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enfield Overlook is a very popular spot at Quabbin Reservoir. It's a great place to spot bald eagles, and has spectacular views of all 3 branches of Quabbin Reservoir plus Mount Monadnock. We will park here and start our hike on a trail that goes downhill to the shore. (Someone told me you can get birds to eat out of your hand not far off the road, where they have built birdhouses...maybe the same chickadees that visit the orchard?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/f/0/event_73253232.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/b/6/event_73246262.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From there, the trail follows the shore (I can't wait to see this!) to Hank's Meadow, a nearly half-mile long meadow stretching from the shore to the park road. The meadow has a beach, picnic tables and an outhouse with sanitizer. During apple season, deer and other creatures are frequently seen feeding. It's also another bird/eagle-watching spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directly across the road from Hank's Meadow is an old dirt road (formerly Webster Road). We'll follow this (about a mile), then a couple sections of trail (another half-mile) to the Lookout Tower on top of Quabbin Hill. They may not have the tower open yet (they didn't last year), but the hill is open on the reservoir side, and you will love the view!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we take a trail through the woods to the orchard. Immediately after the orchard is the rotary. We can either take the main park road .25 miles back to Enfield Overlook, or backtrack a little and take the trail to Enfield Overlook. (It's about the same distance.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FYI, if anyone has a time/distance limitation, we can take the paved road directly from the tower (instead of the trail) to the orchard and cut off .5-.75 miles.&lt;/strong&gt; (Then the entire hike would be 3.25-3.5 miles. As planned, I estimate 4 miles.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending how much time we spend picnicing and taking pictures, I'm guessing we'll get done between 12:30-1pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lunch, snack, drink. We'll picnic...maybe even twice, there's lovely spots on this hike!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera highly recommended!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No special equipment or clothing is needed, just dress for the weather that day. These are well-traveled areas, and there's no snow or ice on the trails. Right now, the forecast is for sunny skies, probably in the 40s at the time we're hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quabbin Reservoir Rules:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading; it's a public water supply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals, for the same reason.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Carry-in, carry-out": take your trash with you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove items from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please remember to set your clocks ahead 1 hour Saturday night!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Worcester and points east:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware, you will ascend two long-steep hills with climbing lanes. At the bottom of the 2nd hill, on the right,&amp;nbsp; is a dirt pull-off with wooden gate; go past it. After a long curve, take the East Entrance on the right. The white sign says, "Quabbin Reservoir East Entrance." (If you pass marsh on both sides of Route 9, you've gone too far. That's okay, take the middle entrance and follow directions from the West.) After about 3 miles, park on the right at Enfield Overlook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Amherst and points west:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 through Amherst and Belchertown, past the intersection with Route 202. You'll see the West Entrance in about 2.5 miles; go past it, you cannot get to Enfield from there. The Middle Entrance is a little over 1.5 miles further on the left, with a white sign saying, "Quabbin Reservoir Middle Entrance." After almost 2 miles, go through the rotary (not uphill), and Enfield Overlook will be .25 miles on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points north/northeast (Athol, Orange, Fitchburg, Leominster):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can take Routes 56 or 31to Route 9 and follow directions as from Worcester. Or Route 122 south to 37A south to Route 9, and pick up those directions from Ware to the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are near Route 2, it makes the most sense to take Route 2 west to exit 19. From there, take Route 202 south for about 20 minutes. Turn left onto Route 9 east, and follow directions as from Belchertown/points west.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>From the East Entrance, drive 3 miles and park at Enfield Overlook on the right. From the Middle Entrance, go almost 2 miles, through the rotary (but not uphill), and Enfield Overlook is about .25 miles on your left..</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331965464000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331233751000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday @ Quabbin: Enfield Overlook/Hank's Meadow/Tower/apple orchard loop.</name><id>55538302</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331474400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/55538302/</event_url></item>