<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>395 River Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01001</zip><lat>42.056824</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413 789-1917</phone><name>Michaels Pasta In The Pan</name><city>Agawam</city><id>988061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.605049</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thank you all for voting for May's two books. The winners for May are Petropolis &amp;amp; Sarah's Key. Please read one book and join us for the May Discussion. Please remember to &lt;i&gt;include in your R.S.V.P&lt;/i&gt; what book you are reading. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you all at the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Petropolis – Anya Aulinich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sasha Goldberg is a biracial, Jewish, socially maladjusted&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;child of the intelligentsia&amp;quot; from the Siberian town Asbestos&lt;br /&gt;2. Sasha's father takes off for the U.S., leaving Sasha to&lt;br /&gt;navigate adolescence under the shadow of her overbearing&lt;br /&gt;mother. At fourteen, Sasha falls in love with an art school&lt;br /&gt;dropout who lives in a concrete half-pipe in the town's dump.&lt;br /&gt;When following her heart gets her into trouble at home, Sasha&lt;br /&gt;leaves Russia as a mail-order bride and, with the help of the&lt;br /&gt;Kupid's Korner Agency, lands in suburban Arizona. Soon, she&lt;br /&gt;escapes her Red Lobster- loving fiance and embarks on a&lt;br /&gt;misadventure-filled journey across America in search of her&lt;br /&gt;father.PETROPOLIS is a satire and a love story. It's also about&lt;br /&gt;racism, academic art training, cross-cultural confusion,&lt;br /&gt;religion (and lack thereof), sex, class conflict, overweening&lt;br /&gt;charity, and three different kinds of mothers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Sarah’s Key – Tatiana de Rosnay&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;De Rosnay's U.S. debut fictionalizes the 1942 Paris roundups&lt;br /&gt;and deportations, in which thousands of Jewish families were&lt;br /&gt;arrested, held at the Vélodrome d'Hiver outside the city, then&lt;br /&gt;transported to Auschwitz. Forty-five-year-old Julia Jarmond,&lt;br /&gt;American by birth, moved to Paris when she was 20 and is&lt;br /&gt;married to the arrogant, unfaithful Bertrand Tézac, with whom&lt;br /&gt;she has an 11-year-old daughter. Julia writes for an American&lt;br /&gt;magazine and her editor assigns her to cover the 60th&lt;br /&gt;anniversary of the Vél' d'Hiv' roundups. Julia soon learns that&lt;br /&gt;the apartment she and Bertrand plan to move into was acquired&lt;br /&gt;by Bertrand's family when its Jewish occupants were&lt;br /&gt;dispossessed and deported 60 years before. She resolves to find&lt;br /&gt;out what happened to the former occupants: Wladyslaw and Rywka&lt;br /&gt;Starzynski, parents of 10-year-old Sarah and four-year-old&lt;br /&gt;Michel. The more Julia discovers—especially about Sarah, the&lt;br /&gt;only member of the Starzynski family to survive—the more she&lt;br /&gt;uncovers about Bertrand's family, about France and, finally,&lt;br /&gt;herself. Already translated into 15 languages, the novel is De&lt;br /&gt;Rosnay's 10th (but her first written in English, her first&lt;br /&gt;language). It beautifully conveys Julia's conflicting&lt;br /&gt;loyalties, and makes Sarah's trials so riveting, her innocence&lt;br /&gt;so absorbing, that the book is hard to put down.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275238435000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268588050000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Discussion Place Holder</name><id>12873580</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274824800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/12873580/</event_url></item>