<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.407211</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>Online</city><id>4355392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.382439</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Worcester Alliance of Photographers and the Gallery at City Hall&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;EXHIBITION OPPORTUNITY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Worcester Alliance of Photographers was approached by the city and asked to contribute photographs to a rotating gallery space in Worcester’s City Hall. WAP agreed to take on the project and manage the shows and space. We have had many successful shows over the years. So- we are pleased to announce our next theme for the space and welcome you to join in by submitting images to be shown in the gallery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Landscapes and…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Many landscape photographs are featuring subjects such as strongly defined landforms, weather, and ambient light. As with most forms of art, the definition of a landscape photograph is broad, and includes urban settings, industrial areas, and nature photography. Waterfalls, coastlines, seascapes and mountains are especially popular in classic landscape photography. But in fact most places and things can be photographed as a landscape, a kitchen, a lamp, a wall, or even the human body. Contemporary Landscape photography has made a notable shift from being about nature and the environment towards being more about the direct relationship between man and nature and where they come together. This is open to your interpretation. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Important Dates:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To apply for the exhibition opportunity, please send &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;up to 3 jpegs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;to donna@erbphoto.com by March 2, 2013. Please make the Jpegs small enough to email to me and under 1 MB. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please please please - use your name as the file name when submitting them!! I need to know who’s images are who’s. Example: donnadufault_landscape1.jpg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Notifications of selected artists will be made by March 6th, 2013.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Framing Party will be March 23rd, 2013 and Installation will be March 28th, 2013.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be juroring them since we only have 25 frames for the space. You must be able to attend the framing party on March 23rd at the library so you can frame your chosen image.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Where to submit?&lt;/span&gt; You must email your photos to me. Put "Landscape and…" in the subject line so I know these are your submissions. &lt;span&gt;Please please please - use your name as the file name when submitting them!! I need to know who’s images are who’s. Example: donnadufault_landscape1.jpg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Submissions need to be made on or before 7pm March 2nd, 2013. We will notify you on March 6th, 23013 if your image is chosen for the show.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Who? A trio of city folks do the jurying but this may vary due to deadlines, but typically it is Erin Williams of the Worcester cultural commission, Howard and Anne, who run Worcester windows program throughout the city. And other guest jurors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What? If your image is included in the show you must print it and get it matted with a white mat that will fit into a 16x24 frame. 16x24 is the frame size your matted print must fit into. That's 16x24.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Any questions?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Worcester Windows is funded in part by the Worcester Cultural Coalition, the City of Worcester, the Greater Worcester Community Foundation and Worcester State University Gallery.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Online! This submission process takes place online but the framing party is March 23rd.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362316789000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361290162000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WAP and the Gallery at City Hall:  EXHIBITION OPP Landscapes</name><id>105334162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362268800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/105334162/</event_url></item>