<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>795 Central Avenue</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.213017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wentworth Home</name><city>Dover</city><id>5403062</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.875801</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;[Merci &amp;agrave; Jim qui organise les Soir&amp;eacute;es Cin&amp;eacute;ma &amp;agrave; la Wentworth Home ! &lt;span style="color : #111111"&gt;La Wentworth Home est une maison pour des personnes&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #111111"&gt;&amp;acirc;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #111111"&gt;g&amp;eacute;es, &amp;agrave; c&amp;ocirc;t&amp;eacute; de l'h&amp;ocirc;pital.&lt;/span&gt; Il y a pas mal de vieilles dames qui parlent fran&amp;ccedil;ais qu&amp;eacute;becois, et Jim organise un petit groupe de conversation francophone l&amp;agrave;-bas le jeudi matin. Il me dit que la maison a une belle salle pour regarder les films, donc si la situation nous arrange, on y passera un film fran&amp;ccedil;ais un de ces week-ends pour notre group. This series of public events are not really Meetups, but Jim and I both thought that group members might be interested in attending. You certainly are encouraged to look for each other at the venue!]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All who are interested in the French language, good film, and an entertaining evening are invited to attend a new film series at the Wentworth Home. All films will be shown in French with English subtitles and will begin promptly at 6:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wednesday, April 11: &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0091288/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jean de Florette&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;Yves Montand, G&amp;eacute;rard Depardieu, and Daniel Auteuil star in this timeless tale of greed, survival and fate which won four British Academy Awards, including Best Picture. Set in the rugged, arid countryside of Provence, the film is a feast for the eyes and an unflinching critique of rural village culture. 1986, 121 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please park in front of or to the left of the building (as you face the building). If necessary, additional parking is available at Wentworth-Douglass hospital next door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be in the Gage Room, which is at the very back of the building on the first floor. Enter through the covered walkway and walk straight to the back (one jog left then right in the hall).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the the Gage Room (instructions in the description).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Verschueren</member_name><member_id>31053912</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334186654000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastNHFrench</urlname><id>63967</id><group_lat>43.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>Seacoast NH French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327790558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Language Film Series at the Wentworth Home: Jean de Florette</name><id>50032342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334181600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastNHFrench/events/50032342/</event_url></item>