<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: RonPaul2012.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;Ten Million Dollars. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; That's how much establishment candidate Mitt Romney raised in one day a couple of weeks ago from well-heeled party bigwigs for his 2012 White House bid. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; So today, I'm writing to personally ask if you are up for a challenge. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;My campaign's grassroots supporters are holding another Money Bomb &lt;span&gt;next Sunday&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span&gt;June 5th&lt;/span&gt;, and I believe it offers us an excellent chance to make some headlines of our own.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; You see, the Romney campaign thinks no one else can touch their accomplishment. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; But honestly, I don't need 10 million dollars to match Mitt Romney.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; After all, I don't have to defend a liberal record as governor of &lt;span&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; I don't have to defend against passing a bill just as bad as ObamaCare.&amp;nbsp; Mitt Romney does.&amp;nbsp; So it's ok if he has a bit more money than we do. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; He's going to need it! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;But it is absolutely critical I have the financial backing to build a first-class operation in early caucus and primary states and show the pundits and press that I am a serious candidate&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; I know these so-called "gate keepers" are part of the &lt;span&gt;Washington&lt;/span&gt; problem, but the fact is their either dismissing of candidates or praising them makes a difference to many undecided voters. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; An overwhelming showing &lt;span&gt;on June 5th&lt;/span&gt; would force the establishment pundits to realize you and I are in this to win it! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; So please, visit &lt;a href="http://paracom.paramountcommunication.com/ct/6031542:8901934754:m:1:261457602:EB862AC67D5934949C790DC713D2EF38" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.RonPaul2012.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on June 5th and contribute whatever you are able.&amp;nbsp; I know times are tough, but each and every dollar will go toward implementing our plans to run a first-class, winning campaign to restore America now. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Support for my Presidential campaign is growing every day, and I'm hopeful that we are in time to save America, rebuild our economy, and hand our children an even better country than the one we inherited. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;And on June 5th, we can demonstrate the strength of support for our freedom message&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; If you can help my campaign really take off now with a contribution at &lt;a href="http://paracom.paramountcommunication.com/ct/6031542:8901934754:m:1:261457602:EB862AC67D5934949C790DC713D2EF38" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;www.RonPaul2012.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on June 5th, I'd certainly appreciate it. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Your donation will allow us to ramp up our efforts in all the key primary states right away.&amp;nbsp; That's why political experts say that $1 now is worth as much as $5 later on. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;And it would prove that our campaign doesn't need fat cat bankers and rich elitists to compete&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; When our R3VOLUTION comes together, there is no limit to what we can accomplish, and it is a great source of encouragement to know I can count on you. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Thank you for all your support!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;And we're going to show them! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; For Liberty, &lt;br /&gt; Ron Paul&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;barbara g.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's Show Them We're Serious Money Bomb</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>barbara g.</member_name><member_id>7156348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307250992000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306641111000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Show Them  We're Serious Money Bomb</name><id>20117471</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307246400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/20117471/</event_url></item>