<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Tillman Story starts at 4:10&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I had to post &lt;b&gt;The Tillman Story&lt;/b&gt;  on Labor Day weekend as I'm busy the following weekend and even though I think this one is going to be around for awhile, well , you just never know.&lt;br /&gt;Heres a link to the trailer: &lt;a href="http://tillmanstory.com/site/media/" target="_blank"&gt;http://tillmanstory.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What soldier, anticipating his death in combat, wouldn’t want to be remembered as a fallen hero who gave his life for his comrades? What grieving family wouldn’t accept the official account, however fraudulent, of a son or daughter’s heroism, stifle their doubts, keep their mouths shut and be content to find some comfort in the ritual honors? NY Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pat Tillman gave up his professional football career to join the Army Rangers in 2002—and became an instant symbol of patriotic fervor and unflinching duty. But the truth about Pat Tillman is far more complex, and ultimately more heroic, than the caricature created by the media. And when the government tried to turn his death into war propaganda, they took on the wrong family. From her home in the Santa Cruz mountains, Pat’s mother, Dannie Tillman, led the family’s crusade to reveal the truth beneath the mythology of their son’s life and death. Featuring candid and revelatory interviews with Pat’s fellow soldiers as well as his family, Amir Bar-Lev’s emotional and insightful film not only shines a light on the shady aftermath of Pat’s death and calls to task the entire chain of command but also examines themes as timeless as the notion of heroism itself. Kendall description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Tillman Story&lt;/b&gt; is a probing examination of truth, decency and the American way. It also explores deception and military propaganda and lays bare the ravages of grief.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intensely dramatic, filled with elevated heroism, crass self-interest and blatant stupidity, it's a paradigmatic narrative of our tendentious, turbulent times. LA Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;86% rating on Rotten Tomatoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you are in town over the holiday weekend you may want to include &lt;b&gt;The Tillman Story&lt;/b&gt; in your weekend plans. I imagine there will be quite a lively discussion at the restaurant afterward. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, &lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When the film is over Tom will be holding a bright red sign near the front row and then its off to a nearby eatery for our group discussion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282778682000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Tillman Story at Kendall</name><id>14543396</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283716800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14543396/</event_url></item>