<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rte. 5</address_2><address_1>125 Reservation Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.266956</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mount Tom State Reservation</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>798301</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.634781</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>By request/suggestion, let's hike/walk/stroll around the trails and forests of the Mt. Tom reservation.  I have not been to this venue, but the trail maps look pretty well marked and I am sure that the group members who suggested this place will be happy to help show us around!  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/laughing.gif' border='0' alt='laughing' /&gt; Let's plan to spend about 2 hours, of course if anyone wants to make it a longer outing, that's OK too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I recommend that we start out with our canine companions on leash, to see how everyone gets along before letting them off lead.   It also looks like we will want to bring water for ourselves and our doggies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Tom boasts an unparalleled view of the Connecticut Valley north and south, the Berkshire mountains to the west and the Pelham hills to the east. This 2,082 acre facility offers 20 miles of hiking and walking trails; picnicking; canoeing and fishing on Lake Bray; and cross country skiing and ice skating in the winter. Mt. Tom also offers a children's play area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today the Reservation includes about 47 of the 80 tree species found naturally in Hampshire County. Mt. Tom is one of the premier hawk watching spots in New England. Each fall, thousands of hawks and other birds fly past the mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to Holyoke entrance:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the south: Rte. 91 north, take exit #17-A to Rte. 5 north. Travel 4 miles, reservation entrance is on your left.&lt;br /&gt;From the north: Rte. 91 south, take exit #18 to Rte. 5 south. Travel 4 miles, entrance is on your right&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at Holyoke entrance I have a black lab with a blue leash &amp; white PT cruiser</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristi</member_name><member_id>7010444</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230995906000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225038600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>By request: Mt. Tom Reservation</name><id>9034089</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226257200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/9034089/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/9/global_6032489.jpeg</photo_url></item>