<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello fellow members of the Greater Boston Internet Marketing Meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On October 2nd at 1:30 pm BIMM will conduct an on-air broadcast reporting live from three different locations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our objective is to give you, the viewer, the chance to see a Google Hangout in action and to give you all a sense of how easily you can use this FREE TOOL to expand your internet marketing prowess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only way to participate is to tune into YOUTUBE and watch the less than 30 minute presentation and shoot us messages via twitter @BOSTIMM  or #Bostimm  or email keithspiro@kendall-press.com during the meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a registered GOOGLE PLUS (g+) user - you can look for keith at Kendall PRess or Bruce Jones BJ Design and the top entry at 1:30pm will be BIMM TUESDAY GROUP.  Click and watch our brief demonstration of this powerful and free tool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also have a short roundtable where Lew, Bruce and Keith will present their TOP TIP for how to overcome any fear of broadcasting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do tune in and engage us with twitter or email during the broadcast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our next regular live and in-person MEETUP is scheduled for Weds Oct 17th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will have a chance at the Oct 17th meetup to create your own 30 day challenge to put out a live broadcast on the internet for fun and profit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This will be an ONLINE MEETUP. Tune in on You Tube or if you are on g+ look up BJ Design see below</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>lew</member_name><member_id>10673992</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>bruce jones</member_name><member_id>11668980</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Keith</member_name><member_id>12427891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349203419000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>53</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315597563000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Internet Marketing Meetup's Thirty Day Challenge - GOOGLE HANGOUT ON AIR</name><id>32924372</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>1800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349199000000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/32924372/</event_url></item>