<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>GOING TO THE GYM : WEB-MEDIA &amp;amp; SEARCH - GOOGLE, YAHOO AND MICROSOFT HEAD EAST - TAKING ADVANTAGE OF THE BOSTON/CAMBRIDGE UNIVERSITY AND PROMINENT CAPITAL SCENE?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the last few years three of the country's west-coast based technology giants, Google, Yahoo and Microsoft, have established a significant presence in the Boston/Cambridge area through both acquisition and expansion. Microsoft now has research and start-up labs in Kendall Square and Google has their Development Center in Kendall Square while Yahoo has set up a presence via acquisition. The groups’ investments and acquisitions of Groove Networks, SoftGrid, VMware and Maven Networks speaks favorably about Boston’s area's rich technology ecosystem, established entrepreneurial community and significant angel, VC and institutional capital providers which have supported, nurtured and invested in new ideas and start-up companies for over three decades…and the pace continues.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this EntreTech Forum session, we will delve into this newly established presence and investment of Google, Yahoo and Microsoft in the Boston area by addressing the following questions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why have they committed such a strong presence in the Boston area? &lt;br /&gt;Has their local presence accelerated company creation, partnering, acquisition, and investment in the Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;What do they view as their relationship to the Boston area universities and innovation community? &lt;br /&gt;What particular areas of technology and what market needs are they emphasizing in their Centers and Labs? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jerry Katzke, Principal, JK Associates&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investor:  Dayna B. Grayson, Principal, North Bridge Ventures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google:  Steve Vinter, Director, Boston Development Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yahoo:  Bob Hammond, Vice President of Engineering&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Microsoft:  Sara Spalding, Senior Director, New England Research and Development Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;University:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David R. Kaeli, Professor, Director of the Northeastern University Computer Architecture Research Laboratory&lt;br /&gt;Neena Buck, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Office of Corporate Relations, Industrial Liaison Program&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234917477000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225198124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Going to the GYM - Web Media &amp; Search</name><id>9046388</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232494200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/9046388/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_4560057.jpeg</photo_url></item>