<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>770 Campbell Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06512</zip><lat>41.279713</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Saray Turkish</name><city>West Haven</city><id>1464121</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.955229</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>By request....Saray Authentic Turkish cuisine Campbell Ave West Haven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a long day of workish...why not join us for Turkish! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets end another long work week and kick-off the weekend with some great food, good friends and nice wine....&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In meeting with the restaurant owner, I have worked out 3 different options for our group for that night. ******When you RSVP, please indicate whether you wish option 1, 2, or 3 so they can plan accordingly.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Option 1 (&lt;b&gt;and the best deal&lt;/b&gt;!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) A 3 course meal (appetizer, entree and dessert) off a broad prix fixe menu for $19.99 plus tax tip and any alcohol ordered . This choice includes soda if desired. There are many manychoices and it is not restrictive. This is the same menu and price they offered for restaurant week in October...very gracious of them to offer it to us as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Option 2) Same 3 course offering as above...except you can choose any 1 appetizer, entree and dessert of their full regular menu of your choosing. Comes with soda if desired. This price option is $29.99 plus tax, tip and any alcohol ordered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Option 3) You can order anything you would like at full cost plus tax, tip, and any alcohol if ordered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This restaurant is BYOW!!...Bring Your Own Wine... if you choose. For those not sure what to pair with dinner, here are my suggestions....Turkish food tends to be rich, have wonderful spices and flavors, therefore a red would be your best best at cutting through and pairing with these types of dishes. As Greece is near turkey and similar flavors...you might try an underestimated and often overlooked wine from Greece. A spanish red , etc. For those who prefer whites...no problem, bring what you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a recommendation from one of our members:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My boss turned me on to this great Turkish restaurant in West Haven on Campbell Ave. I am very picky when it comes to eating out,,,let me tell you,,this place is fantastic,,the service excellent, the food excellent, if you like hummus, kebabs, grilled eggplant, and lots of exotic spices,,,and oh, the waiter looks like Leonardo DiCaprio,,,the desserts a must have as well,,, &lt;br /&gt;SARAY is the name of this great restaurant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****Please keep in mind our group rule of bringing enough&lt;u&gt; cash&lt;/u&gt; to cover your &lt;u&gt;food, drink, TAX AND TIP&lt;/u&gt;*** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saray Turkish Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;770 Campbell Ave&lt;br /&gt;West Haven, CT 06512&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*There will be a $2.00 Meetup fee collected at the restaurant.&lt;span style="color: black"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rena</member_name><member_id>5082966</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296426390000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294415017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>After workish...why not join us for Turkish!!! ....and BROW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</name><id>15957901</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296257400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/15957901/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_3095463.jpeg</photo_url></item>