<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 William T Morrissey Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.309647</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Savin Hill Yacht Club</name><city>Dorchester</city><id>1527219</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043594</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;November 15th – “Preparing Your Blue Water Cruise” by Joel Stern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of us dream about it, but are we really ready to go Blue Water cruising? According to Joel Stern, we’re less prepared than we want to believe. In Joel’s talk he will take us through preparing the boat, the crew, and most of all, ourselves, for a blue water cruise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joel Stern bought his first boat at age 7; a quarter plywood boat, 12 foot in length. Spent summers in Winthrop water skiing and fishing. Discovered sailing in 1981 while visiting San Diego, CA. In 2001, purchased s/v “Culzean” a Vagabond 47 ketch; 54’ overall, 13’5” beam, displaces 22 tons and draws 5 1/2ft. In 2007, Joel got his 50 ton merchant marine captain’s license and on October 29, 2007, with a crew of 5 left San Diego as a participant in a popular West Coast rally that had Cabo San Lucas, Mexico as its destination. After that trip, Joel traveled about 20,000 sea miles and visited 18 countries returning on October 16, 2010 to be with his ailing mother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pelagic Sailing Club meets at Savin Hill Yacht Club, Dorchester, MA, on the second floor at 6:30pm for social hour and pizza, 7:30pm for meeting, 8:00pm guest speaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information check out our website at: pelagicsailingclub.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dedicated to bringing together competent skippers and competent crew for their mutual sailing benefit!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests welcomed. Just let me know so we order enough pizza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: this meeting is one week earlier than scheduled to due Thanksgiving.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robin G. Coles</member_name><member_id>10488766</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353075201000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352733017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>“Preparing Your Blue Water Cruise” with Joel Stern at Pelagic Sailing Club</name><id>91045782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353022200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/91045782/</event_url></item>