<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Cheryl Dutton&lt;br /&gt;Experiences with Live Product Searches &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the major changes that has occurred for the independent inventor has been the method of getting their new product ideas in front of manufacturers and companies.  A dozen years ago,.  companies did not want their competition to know that they would look at products from outside their own research and development arms. They also found that a great deal of time was wasted dealing with inventors who did not understand the ‘rules’ of non-disclosures and who wanted to show products that did not match their needs.  Inventors at shows such as the Minnesota Inventors Congress and the Yankee Invention Exposition complained bitterly about how difficult it was to get in the door of companies. Frustration ran high on both sides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Flash forward to 2009 and times have changed. Many companies now actively seek outside products (Proctor and Gambel’s goal for the last few years has been to identify 50% of their new products from outside.) and new media opportunities have changed the way to get attention to new products. IRN member Cheryl Dutton will talk about her experiences with Edison Nation’s product submission process. Cheryl is an inventor, real estate agent and gold member of Edison Nation. Many may recognize her EN screen name &amp;quot;Just Cheryl&amp;quot; At the request of Inventor's Digest, Cheryl held a mirror to Edison Nation in her article in the June 2009 issue of Inventor's Digest which gives an unvarnished look at the site that hosts Live Product Searches, linking inventors with retailers and manufacturers. Cheryl has had several innovations make it to the finalist stage with EN and be presented to retailers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Cormier</member_name><member_id>6323188</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260322398000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258676491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>IRN December Public Meeting</name><id>11915408</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259797500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/11915408/</event_url></item>