<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hickory Hill Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03053</zip><lat>42.873760</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Musquash Conservation Area</name><city>Londonderry</city><id>1178579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/c/e/event_13965262.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Musquash Conservation Area: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The term Musquash comes from the Algonquin word for muskrat. Today it describes a forest block of over 900 acres in the western part of Londonderry. The area is made up of forested, rolling hills dotted with wetland areas that provide natural habitat for moose, deer, beaver, and painted and Blanding’s turtles to name just a few species. This landscape also provides an enjoyable place for outdoor recreation for the citizens of the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to a trail map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://londonderrytrails.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/musquashtrails_2010-final-final-draft.pdf"&gt;PDF &lt;br /&gt;

 file of the Musquash Conservation Area Trail Map&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting on part of the Landing Trail, we will hike part of the Deer Trail, all of the Porcupine Ridge Trail, part of a different section of the Landing Trail, almost all of the Betty Mack  Loop Trail, and part of the Overlook Trail to get back to the Landing Trail to finish this loop hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are over 4 different entrances to the Musquash Conservation Area so please use the correct address above for where the hike will start.&lt;/strong&gt; Once having turned off of High Range Road onto Hickory Hill Drive simply go to the end of the road (about 0.2 miles) where the parking lot with the trail head sign is located.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any adult guest you want to bring should sign up on the meetup site as a member so they will be covered by the liability waiver. A minor would need a written waiver signed by a parent or guardian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359395446000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357599071000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Musquash Conservation Area - 5 mile hike</name><id>98448272</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359212400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/98448272/</event_url></item>