<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Ashburton Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.359028</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Suffolk University</name><city>Boston</city><id>9456932</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062805</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the opportunity to meet and greet with Jonathan Klein, co-founder and CEO of Getty &lt;br /&gt;

Images. Jonathan will spend the day at Suffolk University of Boston mentoring professors &lt;br /&gt;

on the education of innovation. In the evening, he will give a talk to the public and business &lt;br /&gt;

leaders on global leadership and innovation. He is the recipient of the The Global Leadership in Innovation and Collaboration (GLIC) Award, which was developed by the Center for Innovation &amp;amp; Change Leadership (CICL) to recognize organizations whose innovation and collaboration practices have influenced their industry and stakeholders globally. Getty Images powers the communications of businesses around the world in more than 100 countries and is the first place creative and media professionals turn to discover purchase and manage images and other digital content. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

All are welcome to the event. Registration is free and online at &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.suffolk.edu/54012.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.suffolk.edu/54012.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Leadership in Innovation and Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday, November 5, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 Event Starts at 4pm with reception to follow &lt;br /&gt;

 C. Walsh Theatre &lt;br /&gt;

 55 Temple St. Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The Center for Innovation and Change Leadership is recognizing Jonathan Klein, CEO and cofounder of GettyImages, as the recipient of its 2012 award for Global Leadership in Innovation and Collaboration. GettyImages is a leading creator and distributor of still imagery, footage, music, and premium content, offering the best in news, sport and entertainment, and archival imagery. The company targets four main markets: advertising and graphic design firms; editorial organizations, such as newspapers, magazines, and online publishers; corporate communications departments; and film and broadcast producers. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://glic2012.eventbrite.com/"&gt;Registration is required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For questions, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:bizevents@suffolk.edu"&gt;bizevents@suffolk.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352175398000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348584591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet and greet with Jonathan Klein, co-founder and CEO of Getty Images</name><id>84003052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352149200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/84003052/</event_url></item>