<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Mount Snow </address_2><address_1>Mt Snow Rd</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05356</zip><lat>42.967121</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(802) 464-2196</phone><name>Mount Snow </name><city>West Dover</city><id>783580</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.891433</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;October 6 – October 7 &lt;br /&gt;

Mount Snow is excited to bring you their 15th annual Oktoberfest celebration. This fall festival is designed for the enjoyment of both adults and children. Enjoy a day packed with children’s activities, adult games, arts and crafts, and of course delectable foods &amp;amp; GREAT Beer. This outdoor event provides scenic tours of the mountainside and breathtaking views of the colorful fall foliage. &lt;br /&gt;

Oktoberfest boasts an array of German activities for you to enjoy throughout the weekend. As you walk the festival grounds you’ll enjoy a constant serenade of German music to get you in the mood. At the base of the mountainside in the Main Lodge you’ll find over 40 artisans and craftsmen from across New England. &lt;br /&gt;

This Vermont Oktoberfest features kid’s activities that include arts and crafts, pumpkin painting, face painting, a hay pile, and the new favorite “schnitzel toss.” &lt;br /&gt;

Here the adults won’t feel left out of the celebration! Adults will compete in the entertaining Keg Toss, Horseshoe Tournament, and Stein Holding. Make sure to check out the new event of the one man saw. A favorite festival event that will also be returning is The Apple Sling Shot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349566760000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345654675000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oktoberfest &amp; Harvest Art &amp; Craft Festival</name><id>78872362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349539200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/78872362/</event_url></item>