<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>475 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.367938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 894-8755</phone><name>Little India</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739937</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.237468</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A bit of beach reading!  Hindi-Bindi Club by Monica Pradhan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link on Amazon:  &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Hindi-Bindi-Club-Monica-Pradhan/dp/055338452X/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1245520885&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Booklist&lt;br /&gt;Like Amy Tan's Joy Luck Club (1988), Pradhan's first novel, which features six alternating narrators, speaks to the cultural and generational tensions between immigrant mothers and their Westernized daughters. Recently divorced Kiran Deshpande, a family doctor who longs for a family of her own, is finally willing to admit that her Indian parents might have been right to disapprove of her marriage to a musician with a wandering eye. She's come home after a long estrangement to discuss with her parents her wish to consider an arranged marriage. Her mother, recently diagnosed with breast cancer, is more than willing to play peacemaker between her authoritarian husband and her headstrong daughter. The narrative also encompasses two other young women, childhood friends of Kiran, and their individual struggles with their parents, including battles with clinical depression and anorexia. Although Pradhan's novel is much lighter than Tan's, her pages are alive with the sights, sounds, and smells (recipes included) of a vibrant Indian culture. In addition, her young characters speak with fresh but cutting humor about the difficulties of assimilation. Joanne Wilkinson&lt;br /&gt;Copyright © American Library Association. All rights reserved&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the room with the buffet, book on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249143728000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245521019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July - Hindi Bindi Club</name><id>10695873</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247328000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/10695873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_5395668.jpeg</photo_url></item>