<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crowd Funding&lt;/strong&gt;: The Power of Alternative Financing for Entrepreneurs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crowd funding for your venture provides a powerful means to directly access large groups of potential investors and capital without the burden of middlemen costs and complexities. Crowd funding has successfully funded projects, products and ventures from startup companies, to film makers, and Rock Bands like Marillion to the most successful +$10m fund raising for a smartwatch from Pebble Technology. Crowd funding tools are an essential resource to any entrepreneur who seeks to leverage the latest in a formidable alternative finance strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our next Entretech Forum, we will identify some of the leading crowd funding players and discuss how to use crowd funding, creating a pitch, successes, pitfalls and what the future holds in store. Please join us for this exciting topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfjune2012.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panelists include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/Pierson,%20David_web.jpg" width="100" height="130" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;David R. Pierson, Partner, Foley Hoag Emerging Entreprise Center&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;David chairs Foley Hoag’s Venture Capital/Emerging Companies Practice Group. He represents a broad range of emerging companies, including companies in the software and technology, life sciences, cleantech and other industries. David also represents U.S. and foreign venture capital firms in connection with their investments throughout the U.S. His practice at the EEC focuses in particular on start-up companies, and includes providing advice regarding corporate formation, founder arrangements, angel and venture capital financings, equity incentive plans, mergers and acquisitions and other strategic transactions, contract negotiations and general corporate matters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/June2012Mtg/cohen.jpg" width="100" height="101" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jed Cohen, RocketHub.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jed was born in one of the few geographical areas shaped like a piece of clothing, Michigan, but moved to NYC at the age of 12 to pursue his career as an actor. Jed made his feature film debut as Rod McCallister in Home Alone, and his Broadway debut as Dickon in the Tony Award-winning musical The Secret Garden. Jed is a graduate of Harvard University, where he earned his degree in Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, and now lives in NYC with his wife Kate and their little dog Sophie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/June2012Mtg/schlesinger.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Joseph Schlesinger was trained as an electrical and computer engineer at Worcester Polytechnic Institute, and has worked across many fields, with a passion for robotics. A serial entrepreneur since a young age, he is the founder of the non-profit educational tech shop, MakeIt Labs. Joseph is currently working on his company ArcBotics, which develops and sells open, low-cost robotics platforms for hobbyists, education and research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/June2012Mtg/jack.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Jack Kelly is CEO of Adva Mobile, a technology and mobile marketing company focused on the music industry. Jack leads the strategic, product, and Artist Relationship initiatives of his firm, which provides more than 1,500 Artists with tools and services that help musicians like Natalie Stovall, Glen David Andrews, Jimmy Mack, Dumpstaphunk and Laurie Krauz connect with their fans on mobile phones. Prior to Adva Mobile, Jack led sales and marketing activities at public, venture backed, and bootstrapped communications technology companies and has rewarded stakeholders and investors with more than $650 million of value. Jack has raised more that $25 million through venture capital, private equity, SBA grant, angels, friends and family, and most recently a crowd funding campaign using Indiegogo. Jack has degrees from Boston University and New England School of Law and is the chair of the MIT Enterprise Forum Digital Media Special Interest Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 - 9:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;

Location: Emerging Center at Foley Hoag the Bay Colony Corporate Center, Waltham, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting Cost: $25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Grumer</member_name><member_id>12792562</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340156733000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314976499000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crowd Funding: The Power of Alternative Financing for Entrepreneurs</name><id>qnlkbcyqjbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340145000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/32004932/</event_url></item>