<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Brattle Theater is hosting a week-long Looney Tunes Film Festival!  Come join us in the balcony to watch the Tasmanian Devil larger than life!  There's 3 different features, so check the calendar and join us for all three!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movie:&lt;/b&gt; Looney Tunes: A Devil of a Time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movie time: &lt;/b&gt; 7:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; $9.75 or one of your Brattle membership passes &lt;a href="https://www.vendini.com/service/tickets/viewEvent.html?e=592c8b4e776d865573eadf8eebf97209&amp;amp;entry=1" target="_blank"&gt;(buy tickets online - make sure to pick correct date and time)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be waiting outside the main entrance to the movie theater in line against the wall.  I have shoulder-length blonde hair and I'll be wearing a big purple coat with a Meetup logo button on it.  Once they let us in (usually about 15 mins before), I'm heading in out of the cold and making a bee-line for the balcony for seats.  If you come after they let people in, come find us there.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The theatre entrance is on the left side of the building - look for our sidewalk poster case&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Parking in Harvard Square is DIFFICULT.  The theater validates parking at a couple locations (see their website for details) but expect to spend extra time looking for parking.  Or just take the T!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Brattle Theater:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle shows the best in classic, cutting-edge, foreign, and art-house films. We also show first-run films and new releases of classic films, but our specialty is a repertory programming format consisting of films from a particular director, genre, or subject shown over the course of a week, or on the same weekday throughout the month. Visit our Series Archive to learn more about past repertory programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Movies have been shown at the Brattle Theatre since 1953, when Bryant Haliday and Cyrus Harvey Jr. started things off with a screening of the German film, Der Hauptmann von Köpenick (The Captain from Köpenick). Haliday and Harvey later founded Janus Films for the purpose of distributing foreign films nationwide&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266506679000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265820378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Looney Tunes Film Festival: A Devil of a Time</name><id>12570926</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266451200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12570926/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/5/a/global_13034650.jpeg</photo_url></item>