<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>799 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363407</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-8356</phone><name>Bertucci's </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>754675</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097389</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am pleased to announce this new meetup on Self-Sabotage. Again, another meetup in conjunction with Boston's Freeing Our Space Time Meetup, run but 
&lt;strong&gt;Judy Stitt&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am also very pleased that that I will be sharing this meeting with 
&lt;strong&gt;Barry Harris&lt;/strong&gt;, an expert on the new paradigms of Health and Well Being and the creator of the " 
&lt;strong&gt;Beggars at God's Banquet&lt;/strong&gt;" program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;(Meeting starts at 7pm.&amp;nbsp; Come at 6:30 if you want to order food.)&lt;/em&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Come and learn about self sabotage and how to stop it!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;WHY&lt;/em&gt; do we sabotage ourselves ... and how can we stop doing so?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;Self-sabotage is often not conscious. It can range from subtle nervousness and discomfort to more overt, destructive behaviors like anger or rage ... usually surfacing just as you're about to succeed in something - a relationship, career or job, or otherwise financially. Have you been trying to accomplish something significant (or even trivial), yet obstacles keep coming up just before you can complete it? This well may be self-sabotage.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;Why do we do such things?! The reasons are myriad, often fear-based and not even seemingly logical. Why would anyone fear 
  &lt;em&gt;success&lt;/em&gt;, for example? Often success entails responsibility or has other consequences that we may resist at a deep, unconscious level....&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;Let's discover more reasons for self-sabotage - and learn techniques to alleviate or eliminate them: especially, 
  &lt;strong&gt;when we can see something from a different&lt;/strong&gt; 
  &lt;strong&gt;perspective&lt;/strong&gt; 
  &lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; 
  &lt;strong&gt;often&lt;/strong&gt; 
  &lt;strong&gt;we notice new things&lt;/strong&gt; 
  &lt;strong&gt;that might serve us better&lt;/strong&gt;. This is certainly true of self-sabotage, which might involve blockage of sorts, including clutter- metaphysical (thoughts) as well as physical (manifested thoughts).&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;A number of our members have made profound discoveries together over dinner while learning about NLP and experimenting with its techniques to change feelings at a deep level. While our achievements might be longer-lived if followed up by more NLP work, 
  &lt;em&gt;alternate&lt;/em&gt; approaches could require months, if not years, of much more expensive therapy and drugs - for possibly no greater benefit. And while clutter 
  &lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt; be vanquished through sheer determination alone, most of us have experienced difficulties with such: "discipline" is easier said than done ... which is why clutter confounds so many of us. So, we welcome opportunity to meet periodically and celebrate progress, then consider next steps to consolidate and increase our gains. We welcome 
  &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; thoughts on clutter and NLP, however diverse the viewpoints might be: do bring them to the table for us all to consider their basis in truth and respond.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;Having facilitated many positive changes with NLP, Kevin knows with certainty that neurolinguistic programming offers great value to many.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the group to the side</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310691334000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309954161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Self-Sabotage: Why We Do It and How to Stop-- FAST</name><id>24729331</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310423400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/24729331/</event_url></item>