<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can join me or not, i plan on doing this since this is what i do prior to posting an event with all the specific data needed to provide a FULL EXCURSION event later..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This LOCAL to the Hartford area event is in replacement of the paddling trip to Sachems Skull Island because of some rain, winds above 10 mph and no sun on one or both days.(Not worth paddling without it being a good Beach Day...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am doing this particular event to obtain some data for our Halloween Paddling and Hiking event on the weekend either prior or after HALLOWEEN.....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ie measuring the exact walking distance and time vs expectations to the entrance..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few of us already know whats inside but i want to still time the event..etc...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its Unprecedented Uniqueness is something you will talk about for years to come and only a few of us have ever been there.. Ready to find out what and where it is ???&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember the movie "The Fantastic Voyage" ...and the game "OPERATION" ??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah the inside of the GUTS of HARTFORD...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if ya forgot it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fantastic_Voyage"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fantastic_Voyage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NO kayaks needed on this event (we will use our kayaks at a different time), (unless you want to take a ONE WAY trip and we send you to Hartford's Anus )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THIS IS a real event and "NO JOKE EVENT", YOU WILL SEE SOMETHING NOT MANY WILL EVER SEE IN A LIFETIME AND YOU WILL BE ASKED QUESTIONS ABOUT WHAT YOU SAW IF YOU TELL PEOPLE YOU TOOK THE "&lt;strong&gt;VOYAGE&lt;/strong&gt;".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, we are going into the Body of Hartford ----&amp;gt; remember the diagram below, its the only map i will give ya on this event, bring a light and a camera:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WEAR YOUR WATER SHOES OR GETTING WET SNEAKERS, ITS PRETTY WET WHILE stomping around IN THE GUTS with all those digestive juices sloshing around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DUE TO OUR PHYSICAL SIZE AND MODE OF TRAVEL in the guts-- WE WILL NOT BE ABLE TO EXIT FROM THE ANUS on this event -- SO ITS BACK UP STREAM TO THE ESOPHAGUS..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/d/c/event_135184572.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get to the transport canal processing station prior to entry:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use #20 Wellington  Street,  Hartford in your GPS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or-- use the link below for your own specific directions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bing.com/maps/?FORM=MLOMAP&amp;amp;PUBL=GOOGLE&amp;amp;CREA=userid1743gobroadfphumem2khvlw7ml8dkb3h3kcgsoxz1369#JnE9LndlbGxpbmd0b24lMmJzdCUyNTJjaGFydGZvcmQlMjUyY2N0JTdlc3N0LjAlN2VwZy4xJmJiPTQxLjc4MjQwMjU2MDYzNDMlN2UtNzIuNDk3ODU5NDc3OTk2OCU3ZTQxLjc2OTIzMjczODExNTMlN2UtNzIuNTIwMzkwMDMzNzIxOQ=="&gt;http://www.bing.com/maps/?FORM=MLOMAP&amp;amp;PUBL=GOOGLE&amp;amp;CREA=userid1743gobroadfphumem2khvlw7ml8dkb3h3kcgsoxz1369#JnE9LndlbGxpbmd0b24lMmJzdCUyNTJjaGFydGZvcmQlMjUyY2N0JTdlc3N0LjAlN2VwZy4xJmJiPTQxLjc4MjQwMjU2MDYzNDMlN2UtNzIuNDk3ODU5NDc3OTk2OCU3ZTQxLjc2OTIzMjczODExNTMlN2UtNzIuNTIwMzkwMDMzNzIxOQ==&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(its adjacent to the I-84 underpass on Hamilton St Hartford.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park on the side of Wellington STREET where we all meet prior to going into the epoglotus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by-pass opening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From there its through the Mouth  into the &lt;span&gt;esopogus tube into the Stom-ache&lt;/span&gt;..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once inside of the stomache there is also an appendix where the overflow goes..then there is 2 sets of intestines, the left and right intestine.. the left intestine is constanly growling and the right intestine has special trapped doors and side passages of interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AGAIN -- REMEMBER:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOU MUST BRING A HEADLAMP OR FLASHLIGHT.... WEAR WATER SHOES BECAUSE YOU WILL BE STEPPING IN WATER -- BE ABLE TO ROLL UP YOUR PANTS LEGS UP TO YOUR KNEES ONCE WE ENTER THE STOM-ACHE..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GETTING TO THE MEETING SPOT:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GPS USE APX #20 Wellington  Street Hartford AND PARK ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ITS BY THE OLD CITY WELDING Place AND I WILL STICK A ORANGE CONE ON MY CAR ROOF ALONG WITH WEARING MY ORANGE HAT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A simple Pot Luck BBQ and fire can be had at my home afterward or someone else's home where we can wash our feet..etc..Details discussed at the event ending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;al-r&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>#20 Wellington  Street Hartford -- prior to the Miniaturization Process, I will wear my ORANGE Hat..</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344868075000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341257570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*Hartford's PARK RIVER UNDERGROUND TUNNEL(s) HIKE*  --- 12:00 pm SUNDAY AUG 12</name><id>71685412</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344744000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/71685412/</event_url></item>