<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Fellow Snake Charmers,        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, welcome back!  After a February hiatus we are ready for our next Meet-up.  This month we will  for the first time conduct &lt;b&gt;Python POWERPOINT KARAOKE.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So you have heard of Karaoke - when you sing along to the soundtrack of pop songs. The idea behind PowerPoint Karaoke is similar. Presenters present, but to slides they have never seen before.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will conduct two 35 minute sessions.  In the first we will use an Intro to Python presentation.  It will be presented in some sort of order that will make sense to people new to Python.  This is a easy way to get familiar with Powerpoint Karaoke.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a break, in the second session we will use a randomizer tool that will grab open source PPTs from the web, so presenters will really be challenged and surprised by the Python presentation slides that have to present.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So all we need are volunteers to sign up to be at bat for 5 minutes.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is how it works.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. I will be in charge of matching the presentations, calling speakers and keeping time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Presenters sign up on the list and come to the stage when their name is called.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. A presentation is put up on screen. The presenter DOES NOT get to look at it prior to it being projected on screen.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. The timer goes off and the presenter starts giving the presentation. You're pretending this is your presentation and trying to actually give it, not necessarily make fun of it, or just blast your way through it. Take your time and read the slides as if you really want to communicate the information. Most of the time, the presentations give you plenty of stuff to work with, so be sure to ham it up and go off on tangents.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Presenter continues presenting for 5 minutes (or until you run out of slides or decide you've had enough)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Audience applauds.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. Next victim arrives on stage...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So are you game!  Send me an email or mention it in your RSVP if you are willing to join in the fun. We need you all-knowing Pythoners! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pizza and soda will be served.  Donations are appreciated as usual to pay for Meetup and the food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter        &lt;br /&gt;617 620 3071 Cell  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are new to this Meetup drop me an email for directions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Marquez</member_name><member_id>4000314</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206140925000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Great Content and Community.</why><group><who>Pythonistas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonpython</urlname><id>469457</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Python User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203555845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cambridge Python March Meeting</name><id>7374450</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205967600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/events/7374450/</event_url></item>