<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 JFK St., Harvard Square, Cambridge, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373215</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-0101</phone><name>Z Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>352351</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119598</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thanks to those (9) who showed up for our November meeting, we had a typicaly animated discussion about brain science and responsibility. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;December Topic: Time and Free Will&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Radio Lab production with science reporter Robert Krulwich called &amp;quot;Against Time,&amp;quot; the section on &amp;quot;No Special Now,&amp;quot; [please listen, it's great, link below] explores the somewhat discomfiting implications of the Einsteinian 4-dimensional &amp;quot;block universe&amp;quot; for free will.   Courtesy of physicist Brian Greene, who questions the idea that the future is open, and neuroscientist V. S. Ramachandran, who discusses the famous Libet experiments on the timing of readiness potentials, Krulwich discovers that he isn't perhaps quite &amp;quot;in charge&amp;quot; the way he thought he was.  Greene is sympathetic to Krulwich's concerns, but can't honestly reassure him about free will, and tries to distract him with multi-verse cosmology.  But Krulwich doesn't buy it; he wants his free will back.  Ramachandran is trenchantly definitive: the unconscious readiness potential precedes the conscious choice to move one's finger by .5 seconds, so consciousness can't be in control the way we thought.  No solace for Krulwich.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;        Green talks about time in his terrific book The Fabric of the Cosmos, chapter 5, &amp;quot;The Frozen River,&amp;quot; and chapter 15, &amp;quot;Teleporters and Time Machines,&amp;quot; (see pp. 451-8 re free will).  Each moment we experience as flowing from future to past is actually &amp;quot;an eternal and immutable feature of spacetime,&amp;quot; so past, present, and future co-exist in the block universe.  Time as a dimension is simply there, just as up/down, left/right and forward/back are all there, laid out in front of us.  This means all our past, present and future actions co-exist as well, strange as it may seem.  But this can be understood as a time neutral re-statement of what science, from our (illusory) time-bound conscious perspective, describes as causal relations over time.  The way one moment effortlessly gets transformed into the next ? no hindrance or obstacle, just a smooth transition ? suggests the next moment was (is) simply there, waiting for the mind to experience.  Naturalist attorney Bob Gulack explores time and free will in one of his talks for the Ethical Culture Society of Bergen County, New Jersey, see link below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;twc  at  naturalism.org&lt;br /&gt;617-480-8846&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Radio lab episode on time: &lt;a href="http://www.wnyc.org/shows/radiolab/episodes/2005/03/04" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wnyc.org/s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;re block universe: &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eternalism_(philosophy_of_time" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bob Gulack's paper on time: &lt;a href="http://www.ethicalfocus.org/index.php?mpage=33/land_of_now.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ethicalfoc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google &amp;quot;block universe Einstein&amp;quot; and see the book excerpt from &amp;quot;Space, time and Einstein&amp;quot; by Kennedy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197504591000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194916115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Time and free will</name><id>6730080</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197331200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/6730080/</event_url></item>