<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;
    &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Come into the Hub for some food, some birthday cake, and a play from the pen of the Bard. Jeanne is moving far, far, far away (to North Attleboro), and before she does she wants to get a few of you suburbanites into the city she&amp;rsquo;s loved for a long time. Jeanne is also celebrating a birthday, not her 29th -- so don&amp;rsquo;t ask. Come join her for a picnic on the Boston Common &amp;amp; then for the comedy "All&amp;rsquo;s Well That Ends Well." The picnic and the performance take place at the Parkman Bandstand on the Boston Common.&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;This year&amp;rsquo;s play staged by the Commonwealth Shakespeare Company is a globe-trotting adventure story of how far one woman will go to win the heart of her beloved. Helena loves Bertram, but marriage is the last thing on Bertram&amp;rsquo;s mind. With wit and tenacity, Helena pursues Bertram from Paris to Florence, through a maze of obstacles thrown at her by chance, circumstance, and her fiance&amp;#769;&amp;rsquo;s recalcitrance, but she finally emerges victorious. till is. For more information, see the following link:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.commshakes.org/shows/current_show/Othello/shows_current.html"&gt;http://www.commshakes.org/shows/current_show/Othello/shows_current.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Bring a beach blanket and/or a low-to-the-ground lawn chair and, if you can, a dish to share. (You can also rent lawn chairs.) You may need insect repellent. Jeanne will plan to get to the Common extra-early, to park one or two blankets in a prime location, so we can sit together. Look for her in the area right in front of the stage.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Taking the T is advisable. Take any train on the Green Line to the Arlington Street stop, or, if coming via the Red Line, get off at Park Street Station.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;If you drive, there is some parking in the Common Garage on Charles Street, but it may fill up. Take Soldiers Field Road to the Back Bay area, turn onto Arlington Street, then left onto Boylston Street. At the first light, turn left onto Charles Street for the underground parking garage.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;The circle marked no. 11, which looks like a wagon wheel and is inside a red box, is the Parkman Bandstand, where the play takes place.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;If the weather is cloudy and rain is expected, call Jeanne on her cell phone. She will track information at the Parkman Bandstand.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you RSVP "yes", Jeanne will send you her cell phone number.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marie A</member_name><member_id>4623326</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne Smith</member_name><member_id>8341850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312263254000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310355809000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE - Shakespeare on the Common</name><id>25284571</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312146000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/25284571/</event_url></item>