<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Generation Obama will welcome Ben Affleck and Jennifer Garner to Rumor Nightclub (21+) in support of Barack's candidacy -- 7 PM Pre-Party ($250); 7:30 PM Main Party ($50).&lt;br /&gt;----------&lt;br /&gt;how many of you know...&lt;br /&gt;Zbigniew Brzezi&amp;#324;ski - a member of the CFR who is also Obama?s foreign policy advisor (as well as the Chief Executive Officer on the Trilateral Commission of the Bilderberg group).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;January 15, 1998: Former National Security Adviser Has No Regrets Giving ?Arms and Advice to Future Terrorists?&lt;br /&gt;Edit event  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In an interview, Zbigniew Brzezinski, President Carter?s National Security Adviser, admits that it was US policy to support radical Islamists to undermine Russia. He admits that US covert action drew Russia into starting the Afghan war in 1979 (see July 3, 1979). Asked if he has regrets about this, he responds, ?Regret what? That secret operation was an excellent idea. It had the effect of drawing the Russians into the Afghan trap and you want me to regret it? The day that the Soviets officially crossed the border, I wrote to President Carter: We now have the opportunity of giving to the USSR its Vietnam war.? Then he is asked if he regrets ?having given arms and advice to future terrorists,? and he responds, ?What is most important to the history of the world? The Taliban or the collapse of the Soviet empire? Some stirred-up Muslims or the liberation of Central Europe and the end of the Cold War?? The interviewer then says, ?Islamic fundamentalism represents a world menace today.? But Brzezinski responds, ?Nonsense! It is said that the West had a global policy in regard to Islam. That is stupid. There isn?t a global Islam?.? [Le Nouvel Observateur (Paris), 1/15/1998] Even after 9/11, Brzezinski will maintain that the covert action program remains justified. [Nation, 10/25/2001]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205881891000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204945649000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Ben Affleck &amp; Jen Garner//Generation Obama</name><id>7488273</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205708400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7488273/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>