<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The organizer's invite you to a winter gathering to be held in the Common Room at Ashton Mills in Cumberland, RI.  Where we'll spend from 6pm to 10pm socializing, playing games and generally just experiencing a warm, friendly winter (well, pre-winter technically) evening.  Between the amenities of the space we've secured and the entertaining antics of your organizers and newest friends, a good night is all but guaranteed&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among the amenities of the space are a pool table, couches, bistro tables and chairs as well as a fireplace and big screen television.  Please feel free to bring games!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Food and Drink&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While not specifically a potluck, we are asking attendees to bring some sort of finger food (mini-quiches, veggie platter, cheese and crackers, etc.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be BYOB (please limit to beer and wine).  Matt is planning to bring a batch of home made eggnog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We ask that all attendees drink responsibly, especially if they are driving.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Activities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pool&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Games (whatever you bring! - Cranium, scrabble, pictionary?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;White Elephant/Yankee Swap (optional! More info below.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the White Elephant Exchange&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you wish to participate in the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_elephant_gift_exchange" target="_blank"&gt;White Elephant Exchange/Yankee Swap&lt;/a&gt;, bring one small gift wrapped item that is worth less than $10.  Everyone who brings a gift will be eligible to participate in one of the most interesting and potentially fun gift exchanges ever seen.  Examples of good items:  DVD, book, gift cards, novelty bottle openers, (almost anything from Oop!), small toys.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A $5/person fee will be collected at the door to cover the cost of renting the space and providing cups, plates and napkins, and a selection of finger foods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions and Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 295 take exit 10 &lt;br /&gt;Go left onto Mendon Rd./Route 122&lt;br /&gt;Go through three sets of lights (the second being a blinking light)&lt;br /&gt;After the third light, go right onto Store Hill&lt;br /&gt;Go right at the stop sign&lt;br /&gt;Cross the railroad tracks&lt;br /&gt;Arrive at&lt;a href="http://www.ashtonmill.com/templates/template_ashtonmill/location.asp?w=riverloftsatashtonmill&amp;amp;t=template_ashtonmill&amp;amp;siteid=1250029" target="_blank"&gt; Ashton Mills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available on both sides of the tracks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will provide an access code to attendees to enter the main lobby.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230815731000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227996920000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Party</name><id>9248032</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229209200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/9248032/</event_url></item>