<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Empire St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821484</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-331-2695</phone><name>Perishable Theatre</name><city>Providence</city><id>502103</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415960</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>And now for something a little different..... Excerpts from works-in-progress at &lt;a href="http://www.perishable.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Perishable Theatre &lt;/a&gt;with a talkback following, pay what you can (suggestion donation is $5).  General seating.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna M is organizing this one. This is a Sunday show and starts at 3 p.m. Meet Donna in the lobby at &lt;b&gt;2:30 pm&lt;/b&gt; -- she'll be wearing an orange plaid scarf.  After the play, those who want to can go next door to &lt;a href="http://www.as220.org/about/2008/03/taqueria-pacifica.html" target="_blank"&gt;AS220's Mexican restaurant&lt;/a&gt; for eats/drinks/conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP so Donna knows who to look for. Questions? Email Donna through our site, or post a message for her.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here are the details:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perishable Theatre Resident Artists Tom Hurdle and Rick Massimo are showing excerpts of their works-in-development on a double bill. Their showing is a part of the RAPT, or Resident Artists at Perishable Theatre, Program, which supports the development of projects over 1 to 3 years by mid-career theatre artists. Work in Progress showings throughout the development process provide invaluable feedback to the artists as they work toward full production.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hurdle and Massimo, residents of North Providence and Providence respectively, have different approaches, but are united in their reliance on sound as a story-telling element. Tom Hurdle’s piece Mortal Sins is a play being written as a chamber piece for actors, singers and musicians. It uses a ghost story to detail the disintegration of a woman's life. Massimo’s Madame Bovary is a theatrical mash-up and remix of Flaubert's novel, the creation of that novel and the evolution of people's responses to it. While Hurdle’s piece is a collection of songs, Massimo’s work relies on the juxtaposition of a recorded soundscape and spoken text. Each artist will be presenting up to 30 minutes of material, followed by an informal salon-style talkback.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Donna M will meet you in the lobby. Look for her orange plaid scarf.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232758156000</updated><rating><average>2.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231603604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>And now for something a little different -- Perishable Theatre</name><id>9491468</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232307000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/9491468/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/3/global_6879667.jpeg</photo_url></item>