<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/0/7/event_11469991.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Herb is throwing a free and unique Halloween party for his friends and colleagues! He has invited us to attend. The party goes from 7:00pm until midnight and you are obviously welcome to arrive and leave whenever you feel like during that time period. So, when you are done trick or treating feel free to come to this awesome event! This will be a great alternative to the crowded and loud parties being held at bars and clubs. Herb&amp;rsquo;s party will be fun, with a quiet and intimate setting where you have a chance to have a conversation with the people around you. Instead of bar drinks, enjoy lots of candy and junk food (the true spirit of the holiday).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Herb encourages people to come dressed as their Enneagram Type, the type you want to be, or wear a costume from the dark side! The party is also an optional potluck so if you can please bring a vegetarian dish/snack or candy! Herb is open to answering questions about the Enneagram during the party, particularly typing ghosts, vampires, monsters and other haunted visitors (both visible and invisible).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327704744000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318977654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Unique Halloween Party</name><id>37883232</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320102000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/37883232/</event_url></item>