<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The familiar saying “We are what we eat” can certainly apply to more than our physical state of wellness. Is diet a mirror of...well, is it a mirror of something more than taste or cultural conditioning? Dietary restrictions in one form or the other are common to many religions. The Jewish and Muslim religions prohibit the eating of pork. Jewish dietary laws also prohibit the mixing of dairy and meat in the same meal. Both the Muslim and Mormon faiths prohibit the drinking of alcoholic beverages, and Mormonism also prohibits the drinking of coffee and teas. Some Buddhist sects are vegetarian, as is the Seventh Day Adventist Christian denomination. And there are, I’m sure, many other religious dietary restrictions of which I am quite ignorant. (If there are any errors in the above, please accept my apologies and let me know so that I can correct my statement. Although, the remark about my ignorance is not debatable).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the ethics of diet goes far beyond religious restriction. The environmental health and the personal health of dietary choices are issues of world significance. If diet can make you sick, then your bad choices increase heath care costs, and also touch upon the ethical significance of trying to stay healthy. And if eating meat, for example, expends about ten times as much energy as grains and other vegetables to produce, and destroys forested areas that produce environmental havoc, it is a vital ethical issue as well. So spiritual issues aside, dietary choices  may be one the most significant class of choices that a person may make. &lt;span&gt;And what about the spiritual implications of diet? If there are spiritual implications, what are they?&lt;/span&gt; As someone coming from a vegetarian perspective I would like to quote Schopenhauer: "The assumption that animals are without rights and the illusion that our treatment of them has no moral significance is a positively outrageous example of Western crudity and barbarity. Universal compassion is the only guarantee of morality." (ref. &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arthur_Schopenhauer" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ar...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The meat eaters may not become vegetarians after this discussion, and the vegetarians are not likely to go running for a Big Mack, but in this discussion we might just edge closer to an understanding that goes beyond the mere advancement of a particular agenda. And we may learn something about the diversity of dietary choice that, by increasing the depth of perspective we may increase the understanding of each others' religious, spiritual and philosophical points of view. As with all of our conversations, mutual respect for our various points of view is required.     &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people).   After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.  It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.  And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!  While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt; expenditure of $12 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill for food and/or drink plus tax and tip is under $12 the balance will be added to the gratuity).  Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks. To simplify, many folks just round off to $20 and add and adjust if they order drinks. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.  However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*****************************&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP for one of our events it is expected that you have every intention of attending. Please refrain from impulse reservations and impulse cancellations!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351434777000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346346042000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concerning the Ethics of Diet</name><id>80097242</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351292400000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/80097242/</event_url></item>