<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Parking Lot</address_2><address_1>300 Elm St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.442524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-395-8492</phone><name>Flynn Rink/Fells Reservation</name><city>Medford</city><id>1231135</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094414</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's super early - but I know there are other early bird hikers out there...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who are addicted to hiking and need a mid-week fix, join me for an invigorating early morning hike in the Fells. A friend of mine once said that the Fells look, feel and sound different in the early morning hours - once you experience it, you'll be hooked. &amp;nbsp;He's right!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;What's the plan?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're switching it up a bit to visit the other side of the Fells. We'll do an approx.&amp;nbsp;4 mile loop of the Rock Circuit&amp;nbsp;Trail.&amp;nbsp; While the terrain is not nearly as challenging as the Whites, this trail is rough and rocky and there are some steep ascents to rocky outcrops&amp;nbsp;that&amp;nbsp;provide&amp;nbsp;nice views of the surrounding area - we'll get a bit of elevation and do some climbing. We also plan to hike at a relatively 
&lt;strong&gt;fast pace - 3+mph&lt;/strong&gt;, when we're not scrambling up the climbs - and hope to finish in about 
&lt;strong&gt;2 hours&lt;/strong&gt;. The terrain of this hike makes it take longer than you might think for the distance... so realize this hike will take a bit longer than the usual trail we do on the western side of the fells. You don't need to be an experienced hiker to join, but you should have some reasonable level of aerobic fitness. &amp;nbsp;So you know what to expect - we're out to get exercise, not take a leisurely, relaxed stroll in the woods.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Where will we meet?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're meeting&amp;nbsp;
&lt;span&gt;at Flynn Rink on Elm St/Woodland Rd&amp;nbsp;- just past the round-about.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Please be on time - most of us have to get to work eventually and if we start late, we'll finish late and mess up our schedules. I'll leave the lot promptly at 5:35am.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;What should I bring?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water (24 oz - 1 Liter), good hiking shoes/trail runners, bug spray&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;More Info:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain will cancel - I'll send out an email (with my cell phone number) to confirmed participants the night before the hike to confirm details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will likely bring Della, my well-behaved dog, with us.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more information about the Fells here:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.fells.org/visit/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.fells.org/visit/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And you can print out free maps here: 
&lt;a href="http://www.fellsbiker.com/maps"&gt;http://www.fellsbiker.com/maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312204794000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311249527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Early Morning Hike at Middlesex Fells (Rock Circuit)</name><id>26523791</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311845400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/26523791/</event_url></item>