<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>146 Front St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02066</zip><lat>42.195965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 545-3999</phone><name>Mill Wharf Restaurant &amp; Pub</name><city>Scituate</city><id>242422</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.724846</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for a delicious jazz brunch at Chester?s at Mill Wharf, overlooking Scituate Harbor.   They offer a buffet brunch with all the breakfast options as well as seafood, chicken, roast beef, etc.  The band has been there for years, keeping people entertained throughout the brunch. &lt;br /&gt;Time/Date:  11:00 AM Sunday, April 1st, 2007 (We?re not foolin?!)&lt;br /&gt;Location:  Chester?s Mill Wharf, 146 Front St, Scituate, MA 02066&lt;br /&gt;Web: www.millwharf.com&lt;br /&gt;Minimum/Maximum: Attendance is unlimited.&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place:  11:00 AM in lobby of Chesters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: Jazz-brunch is $22.95, which includes the meal, tax, tip, and juice.&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees:  $ 2.00 pp&lt;br /&gt;Other Costs: alcoholic beverages, coffee, etc. to be paid at end of meal&lt;br /&gt;Please Note:  &lt;br /&gt;1. Total Cost of Brunch and Fees is $25.00 which will be collected at check-in.  Anything additional will be collected at the end of the meal when the bill arrives. &lt;br /&gt;2. RSVP Deadline: Friday, March 30th @ 6pm ~ The Restaurant has asked us to finalize our reservation by Friday night.  Here?s how this will work.&lt;br /&gt;A. The Event Organizer(s) will put in a maximum number of whatever the total Yes RSVP?s are on Friday night when they call in the reservation.  (This will, in effect, close the RSVP?s unless there is a cancellation.)&lt;br /&gt;B. If there are any openings then someone can RSVP Yes &lt;br /&gt;C. If anyone needs to cancel they have until 4pm Saturday, March 31st to do so w/o penalty.  &lt;br /&gt;D. RSVP Update Deadline: Saturday, March 31st @ 4pm [We are expecting a large crowd, and if our numbers decrease we need to let the restaurant know so they can adjust accordingly.]&lt;br /&gt;E. If anyone changes their RSVP after 4pm on Saturday, March 31st w/o emailing one of the Event Organizers as well then they will be considered a ?no-show/no-call/no-email/no-follow-up? for this event and may be asked to pay their event fee if the spot is not taken.&lt;br /&gt;Organized by:  Jen E. &amp;amp; Angela N.&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather:  Event takes place rain or shine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 3:  Take exit 13 ? Rt. 53 North.  Travel one mile to Junction of Rt. 123.  Get onto Rt. 123 East.  After crossing Route 3A, bear right onto Driftway.  Continue to Front Street and Scituate Harbor.  Mill Wharf Restaurant is located behind the Welch company Gift Shops.&lt;br /&gt;Lost?:  Call restaurant at 781-545-3999&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177936888000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173404205000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jazz Brunch at Mill Wharf</name><id>5551194</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175439600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5551194/</event_url></item>