<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Wattaquadock Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.430644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>http://www.nashobawinery.com</phone><name>Nashoba Valley Winery</name><city>Bolton</city><id>731361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.614016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Okay, folks, I know this is short notice, so if we can't make it happen this Saturday, we'll reschedule. But let's give it a shot!  The Nashoba Valley Winery in Bolton has been known for its fabulous fruit wines for many years, but I only recently learned that they now produce more conventional wines as well. Not to mention beers and distilled fruit liquors (or should that be &amp;quot;liqueurs&amp;quot;?). They also have a restaurant where you can pre-order a picnic lunch for about $10. This strikes me as a delightful way to spend a Saturday afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winery tours -- which cost $6 -- start at 11 and take about 45 minutes. I'm thinking if we plan to meet at 12, we will have the flexibility to decide if we want to dive into the next tour or enjoy our picnic first. The time can also be pushed back a bit if members prefer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was hoping for a big turnout so as to touch base with as many members as possible and get some direct feedback on the kind of meetups you'd like to see in future. However, the weather forecast for Saturday is now gorgeous, high 70s with a mix of clouds and sun, very little chance of rain. Another date might not be as fortuitous. So I'm going to extend the R.S.V.P. time till tomorrow night -- maybe we can pick up a few more people!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow signs for "winery tours" and look for me waving a Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243202355000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241488883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winery Tour and Picnic Lunch at Nashoba Valley Winery</name><id>10339461</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241884800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/10339461/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/1/global_8127057.jpeg</photo_url></item>