<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is Thanksgiving and I'll be cooking the Turkey with all the trimings. If you have no where to go, plan on coming on over and celebrating Thanksgiving with me. I've changed the time to 4pm but if you want to come on over earlier please do so - I always love to have the company.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do have a place to go but can't stand your family once they start bickering, come on to play games after you have dinner with them. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll have Soda, left over liquor from the previous events but other than that, it's BYOB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are an equal opportunity game playing group - We play Euro and party games as well as card games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring the $1.00&amp;nbsp;for Nina our awesome organizer to help pay for the cost of the meetup group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking logistics: Please park in the CVS or Funeral home parking lots or along the sideof the road without blocking people from getting in or out of their designated parking spots. Please do not park in the front or side of my house - Cranky neighbor issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allergy alert: I have a long haired shedding machine (dog) named Princess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to hosting and&amp;nbsp;playing games with all of you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>163 S Main St. Colchester CT. 06415</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret </member_name><member_id>5111537</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322493949000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320531427000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thanksgiving Game night at Margariiiiittttaaaasss</name><id>chkhxyppbgc</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322168400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/40094222/</event_url></item>