<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Certification on Mastering Law of Attraction will be given at the end&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn how to and start immediately attracting a wonderful life, one you might have believed in or "knew" of but never knew how to have, attract or become...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicole has studied with the Leading Edge Consciousness Law of Attraction and has learned how to Master the Law of Attraction... She has manifested many "new" realities based on ones that have been seen only in her dream state...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with her coach and clients and through her active awareness of LOA, and teaching her classes, Nicole has manifested a wonderful romantic relationship with her Twin Flame- Soul Mate, living in a beautiful beach house on the water, doing work she loves, moving to a new state, driving her convertible Mercedes, trips to Australia(in 3 weeks), Travel to London, Italy and all over the world/country, Studying with amazing teachers, attracting friends of like-mind, better relationships, healthier ways of being, a spiritual soul, family community, a new body, hundreds of people in her law of attraction meetup groups, a passionate career, wonderful clients, wellness and holistic center in the works - leaving a dead end corporate america "job", large sums of money, gifts, opportunities beyond her wildest dreams... etc...She is a powerful manifestor and can show anyone how it is done...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be getting into the nitty gritty of manifesting for a full day...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the topics discussed and worked with will be: &lt;br /&gt;

What is Manifesting through the Law of Attraction really mean? &lt;br /&gt;

and How is it done? from the simpliest process to more complex ones... &lt;br /&gt;

What are the Steps in becoming a Deliberate Creator? &lt;br /&gt;

What is the Art of Allowing and how it is Key... &lt;br /&gt;

Identifying past programming, limited false beliefs... &lt;br /&gt;

Really understanding the contrast in our lives and using it to propel us forward... &lt;br /&gt;

The processes of Pivoting, Segment Intending, Creating a Powerful Vortex, Setting Intentions, Visualizing &amp;amp; Imagining, The key to awareness and really shifting perspective so the silver cloud can be dissolved...and what you want can and will show up...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicole will use proven skills &amp;amp; techniques that have helped her and her clients shift from limited, stuck consciousness to one that's leading edge, empowering and freeing and allowing all things to come to you...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once etched in your brain and your being, the law of attraction will truly become easy and the value of your existence and life will take on new meaning... Things will work out, you will see things differently, any negative "electrical" charge that people, places and events have on you will no longer exist... Positive things, people, places, and relationships will naturally be attracted to you.. Your true self will emerge... one that's destined to live a life that feels good...You will recognize life beyond the mundance and unsatisfying and instead of being bored and feeling unfulfilled you will start to have a sense of peace, knowing and joy that has never been felt before... Life will get really good and you will see miracles unfold that you didn't even know existed or were possible for you...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicole will take you through various exercises, processes and activities that will literally shift you into alignment with your inner being and all that you desire even if you do not know what that is... that actually is a perfect time in life to experience this one day workshop because when you leave, you will be creating a new life, one filled with positive expectations and a joy that is immeasurable...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are tired, worried, fearful, done, spent, on the verge of giving up, depressed, sad, unhappy OR you have hope, know a little of LOA and know it's just around the corner but don't know how to get there... This workshop will be most beneficial as it will be the connector to all the dots, all the questions of HOW will be answered ... all the cooperative components will be understood... all workshop participants will have the opportunity for a one on one coaching session with Nicole during the day, helping to gain clarity on any perceptions of being stuck, not moving forward, and identifying the next steps in manifesting from that place...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Invest $111 in yourself... in creating a better life... in truly making a difference in your world, the world of those you love and as a gift to humanity... when you take that first step, your life will never be the same... This workshop will propel you forward because you will have shifted, you will be in your Vortex of Creation and you will start to live your dreams!!! This day will be a day of High Vibrational Manifesting and Attracting!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make a committment to your life, your self and your journey to experience the best life possible... Please let Nicole know your desire to attend and RSVP by October 12th, send your deposit of 55.50 to Nicole to reserve your spot, this will be a full event, materials will be bought/brought, room has to be set up and preparation will be done so an accurate head count would be much appreciated... thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, This will be the last opportunity this year to hear and participate in one of Nicole's seminar's as she is getting ready to embark on yet another one of her dreams ~a trip to Australia to be with the man of her dreams for a couple of months to start and create a new life... you won't want to miss this and you will be glad you came!! &lt;br /&gt;

Here's a few testimonials on Nicole's coaching and classes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicole's energy is amazing! Her insight and intuition is so accurate and she easily guides me back into feel-good mode when I get off track. By the time we end our coaching session, I am excited to take inspired action - getting me ever closer to my goals and dreams. Thank you, Nicole!Mair Hill, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicole is awesome! Great energy and great group! Love it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a last minute decision to go to this meetup, and I only knew about the subject matter from a quick read on Wikipedia. lol However, this was such a great group of people, eager to see others in the group do well and grow. I didn't feel like an outsider or unwelcome even a little. I still do not claim to really know anything at all about the Law of Attraction, but I got such a great feeling from this group of people and will be going back again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just being able to find yourself through the law of attraction is amazing, not to mention what lies ahead in my life. Great Job Nicole&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are ready for change in your life and are interested in learning more about the Law of Attraction this is a great place to learn. It is a group of very friendly and helpful people that are willing to share experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>8953582</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350258846000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Magnificent Manifestors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors</urlname><id>1552727</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>South Shore Law of Attraction  Manifestors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348513284000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Day Seminar on Law of Attraction ~ Manifest NOW</name><id>83880522</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350225000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors/events/83880522/</event_url></item>