<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Long Hill Estate)</address_2><address_1>421 Wadsworth St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.541404</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wadsworth Mansion</name><city>Middletown</city><id>319656</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.675021</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TODAY: My &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; MeetUp is CANCELED DUE TO POOR WEATHER... If YOU are still interested in attending, please contact the venue (after 2pm) on their website: www.WadsworthMansion.com and/or their voicemail at 860-347-1064) as to whether the concert is &amp;quot;officially&amp;quot; canceled, or not.  Even if it's not &amp;quot;officially&amp;quot; canceled, it'd not be a great picnic environment today, unfortunately.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As such... I'll be gathering up a group of friends to attend this evenings Funny Bone Comedy show - please see that posting for full details.  All are welcome!    &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; gathering at the Funny Bone Comedy Club in Manchester's Buckland Hills Mall (must be 21+).  This weekend's headliner &amp;quot;Jimmy Dore&amp;quot; will be performing.  Buy a promo Tee-shirt at the Box Office for only $15 and get in for this, and EVERY WEDNESDAY, for FREE... for the rest of your life (whether attending with us or not).  We typically have @ 6-20 people gather from my combined Single Event &amp;amp; MeetUp groups!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** disregard the following ***  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: Gather @ 6:00. (Show starts @ 6:30).   &lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Look for me/us under three shiny BLUE STAR-shaped BALLOONS (may or may not be fully inflated/deflated) attached to a white stick w/ red reflector - LOW TO THE GROUND so as not to block the view of those behind us! At concerts, I traditionally stake out an area with 2-4 large blue-on-blue U-Haul moving blankets, likely fairly in the center, or farther, from the stage, not too close to loud speakers. If in doubt, call my cell# from an easy-for-me-to-spot-you location and I can direct you to us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; BYO picnic dinner/snacks and beverages of choice. As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; We typically stay till after the crowd disperses enjoying the company of old and new friends.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; This event is also being posted on the &amp;quot;Singles Event&amp;quot;, but without RSVP's, so likely several more people joining us than post on MeetUp. For Hartford County concerts we typically gather 12-24... C'mon MIDDLESEX COUNTY - come out to meet new local friends and have fun!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;  Please check back here Wednesday after 3:00PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob Pudney, organizer  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;C: (860) 690-9595  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, July 18 - Gathering @ 6:00 - FREE Concert begins at 6:30 p.m.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Prelude&amp;quot; - (in-demand wedding band as well as show/dance band!)  &lt;br /&gt;The most versatile band this summer has been together 20 years and performed all over the Northeast. This six person band plays a wide variety of music that can be enjoyed by listeners of all ages.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional parking will be available at Snow School.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: please MapQuest directions or see web site.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Wadsworth Mansion  &lt;br /&gt;421 Wadsworth Street (Long Hill Estate)  &lt;br /&gt;Middletown, CT 06457   &lt;br /&gt;860-347-1064  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184847935000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184070865000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FINAL UPDATE: "Prelude" - Wadsworth Mansion - Middletown</name><id>6000850</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184796000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6000850/</event_url></item>