<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Weather permitting: We need good weather for this hike. If forecast for greater than 30% chance of rain for most of the day, we will postpone this great hike for the next available Sunday. Wet boulders create a safety hazard for this +5000ft Mountain hike.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This incredible hike features two beautiful waterfalls, two mighty mountains, a world of fantastic views, and a large A.M.C. hut to rest in! The Ammonoosuc Ravine Trail is the nicest way up to the &amp;quot;rockpile&amp;quot;. Stop at Gem Pool to see a wonderful waterfall pour into the emerald pool. A quarter mile more sees two spectacular cascades drop more than 500' into the foot of a gorge!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At only 3.1 miles to the Lakes of the Clouds, the hut &amp;amp; crew welcome hikers to eat, rest, get some shade and spend the night at the foot of Mount Monroe.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is just .3 of a mile, 20 minutes to summit Mount Monroe (5372') and only 1.5 miles in 90 minutes on Crawford Path, cut in 1819, to summit Mount Washington (6288') from the hut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://inlinethumb10.webshots.com/5577/1467583229079256950S500x500Q85.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part way up Mt Washington looking back at Monroe, lower lake, &amp;amp; the hut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This full day round trip is a moderate, yet spectacular 9.0 miles, 3800' of elevation gain in a hiking book time of 6 hours 30 minutes, not including photo ops at the cascades and the 80+ mile 360 degree views on top of both summits. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember that it is usually windy up here and colder than the base. Pack for changes in weather. Pack a ski cap, fleece pullover, windbreaker and light gloves even for summer hikes. Gloves are also protective against the rough summit rocks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's have a tailgate party after the hike. Pack your icy cooler with what ever you like (remember you still have to drive home). You can't claim a tag until you've finished the hike!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217125929000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><why>Will it be summit #48 for Diane! Long awaited, postponed many times, lets celebr</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214006739000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mounts Monroe &amp; Washington!  </name><id>8182022</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215952200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8182022/</event_url></item>