<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>West Roxbury</address_2><address_1>1732 Centre Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02132</zip><lat>42.287252</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-323-4199</phone><name>West on Centre</name><city>Boston</city><id>826323</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.149726</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Yes, we're having our first real snowfall of the season and our brunch is still on as of Sun Dec 7th at 9:30 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're welcome to join us even without an RSVP, just call or text me 617 445-7579 to be included.&lt;br /&gt;Come out for a relaxing meal with your fellow friendly foodies. Safe travels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What a lovely wintry morning... here is a cool poem which seems apropos:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOLIDAY SNOWFALL&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;they're falling &lt;br /&gt;drifting down&lt;br /&gt;big beautiful snowflakes&lt;br /&gt;covering the ground&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;they're evoking gleeful feelings&lt;br /&gt;nods to holiday expectations&lt;br /&gt;those of generous intention&lt;br /&gt;filled with heartfelt expressions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;they're proclaiming seasonal greetings&lt;br /&gt;times of reverence and thankfulness&lt;br /&gt;days enjoyed with family and friends  &lt;br /&gt;times of love and happiness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;they're falling&lt;br /&gt;sacred offerings of pristine white&lt;br /&gt;big beautiful snowflakes&lt;br /&gt;covering everything within sight&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copyright © 2008 by Gwen Dickerson&lt;br /&gt;All rights reserved.&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fellow foodie, Nicole suggested having brunch here.&lt;br /&gt;Since she mentioned it, I've heard nothing but good reviews.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is an intimate group, you will not be allowed to invite guests.&lt;br /&gt;Your guest is welcome to join our group, here &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; , so they can RSVP for themselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://www.westoncentreboston.com/html/home.html"&gt;http://www.westoncent...&lt;/a&gt; for the menu, directions, and parking details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with comment about your circumstances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. *If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change your RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's which are staffed based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call me on my cell (617) 445-7549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to me, &lt;a href="http://brunchclub.meetup.com/107/members/3389565/"&gt;Tonya&lt;/a&gt; explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229878631000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228326669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch at West on Centre - It May Be Snowing But We're Still Going</name><id>9273512</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228669200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/9273512/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/6/0/global_6503472.jpeg</photo_url></item>