<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>So Decembers event was a great success.  The January event will also be Janice's birthday party.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need to talk about food.  I guess we are all spoiled from last year's great efforts.  Trust that Decemeber's event was marked with some great stuff like pizza, subs, chili dip, stuffed mushrooms, and meatballs.  I am asking for folks to try not to bring chip, salsa, hummus and crackers.  I have a large quantity of unopened items from this event that will be shared.&lt;br /&gt;Think more substancial items like pasta, stew, rice dishes, chicken wings, salads.  Since it will be a birthday, the dessert will be make your own brownie ice cream sundaes.  Of course other desserts are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This was such a hit last year that we've decided to again have a game night and party each month during the winter (and this is the 2nd of 3). This helps break up the long nights and to socialize with lots of fun! This event will be held at Janice's condo complex clubhouse (a.k.a. clubhousel) in South Windsor. We'll have a large fireplace with fire, music, tables &amp;amp; chairs, bathrooms, and full kitchen available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Food&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Supplied already: &lt;br /&gt;* Paper and glass products &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please plan to bring to share any of: &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Small entree&lt;/b&gt; (plan to feed &lt;b&gt;8&lt;/b&gt; people!) &lt;br /&gt;* Drinks &lt;br /&gt;* Finger food &lt;br /&gt;* Snacks &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Games&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the games we have already: &lt;br /&gt;* Pictionary &lt;br /&gt;* Picture Picture &lt;br /&gt;* Worst Case Scenario &lt;br /&gt;* Trivial Pursuit &lt;br /&gt;* Scrabble&lt;br /&gt;* Fact or Crap &lt;br /&gt;* Jenga (well a knockoff version) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd like to see someone bring these as well as anything else: &lt;br /&gt;* Bolderdash &lt;br /&gt;* Cranium &lt;br /&gt;* Cards (for various card games)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring any other game you might think 4 - 6 people at least could play at the same time. Team games would be great too. Note this is an indoor game night. We are not doing horseshoes or lawn darts! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hall Rental Donation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would appreciate donations of any amount (maybe $3 - $5 each person?) to help offset the cost of the hall rental. Donations can be made at the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is at a hall at a condo complex in South Windsor. The &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;address will be sent to those who respond &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; about a couple days before the event.&lt;/span&gt; If you sign up last minute be sure to e-mail Janice or Kevin for directions. Limitation on RSVP's is due to parking limitations. We all hope you can attend and enjoy a warm evening with great people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year this was a hit with over 60 people going each time and people brought great food and drinks to share! The next and last Game Night and Party of the season will be Feb. 5th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and later can't go, please remember to change your RSVP so someone else can go!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>13</waitlist_count><updated>1295197435000</updated><rating><average>4.84999990463</average><count>20</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>59</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291572829000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Game Night and Janice's Birthday Extravaganza</name><id>15648282</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294527600000</time><rsvp_limit>66</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15648282/</event_url></item>