<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.409340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Amherst</name><city>United States</city><id>1538940</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.146873</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/4/3/1/event_33993841.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
NOFA Summer Conference attendees register for an entire weekend of keynote speeches, over 225 workshops, a country fair, farmers&amp;rsquo; market, over 100 exhibitors and vendors, a children&amp;rsquo;s conference, a teen conference, live entertainment and silent auction.&amp;nbsp; Over the years, NOFA has presented a wide array of thoughtful, engaging and important keynote speakers, including Wendell Berry, Joel Salatin, and others.&amp;nbsp; The 2011 Friday evening keynote will be given by perennial-edibles expert and award-winning author, Eric Toensmeier, from Holyoke, MA.&amp;nbsp; The 2011 Saturday evening keynote will be given by Biology professor and anti-GMO activist Dr. Ignacio Chapela, from UC Berkeley.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This year, the 2011 NOFA Summer Conference is proud to feature the Northeast Animal Power Field Days (NEAPFD); a special collection of workshops and hands-on activities for those interested in using draft animals to facilitate farming and logging activities.&amp;nbsp; Local farm tours and most Animal-Power workshops will be held at offsite locations in the Pioneer Valley, for those interested in daytime excursions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Workshop topics for 2011 include: Alternative Energy and the Environment; Animal Power; Animals, Crops, Farm Economics and Management, Farming and the Community, Food and Family, Food and Farm Education,&amp;nbsp; Food Preservation and Cooking, Fruits, Nuts, and Trees; Garden and Greenhouse, Herbs, Land Care, Nutrition and Health, Of the Spirit, Politics and Policy, Practical Skills, Soil and Fertility, and Urban Agriculture. Most workshops are held in and around the UMass Amherst campus.&amp;nbsp; Participants generally select on-campus housing, and reside in the UMass dormitories for the duration of their stay.&amp;nbsp; Camping on the UMass property is also available.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Online registration available now. Go to: www.nofasummerconference.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;For information on registration, contact registration@nofasummerconference.org, or call Kathleen or Siedeh at the registration hotline:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;(413) 230-7835.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can't go to the entire conference? No problem. Go for one day, or one night. It's well worth a nice drive out to Western Mass. About an hour and 45 minutes from Boston. Lots of folks heading out there...carpools are available. You can preregister or walk in on the days of the conference! Discounts for early registration. Check the NOFA conference website for details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>6980975</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313162559000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308681584000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northeast Organic Farming Association 2011 Summer Conference</name><id>23002661</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313157600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/23002661/</event_url></item>