<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I know what you're thinking......what does a guitar concert have to do with Ethnic Dining? Well, I'll tell you.........Michelle is the organizer of the Ethnic Dining Group.......and besides being a self-described &amp;quot;fabulous&amp;quot; vocalist, also happens to be an accomplished violinist and guitarist! Michelle thought everyone should know about this event. There won't necessarily be a coordination of the event by EDEMG however, Michelle thought it would be a good idea to post the event for your convenience and planning efforts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Late Summer Classic! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Event &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 9, 2006 3:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;(Rain Date: Sunday, Sept. 10, 3:00 PM) &lt;br /&gt;Riverfront Plaza, Hartford &lt;br /&gt;Admission: FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Handicapped Accessible &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;an annual invocation to the guitar's glory&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;- The Hartford Courant &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come celebrate the start of our new season as guitarist Daniel Salazar, Jr. takes the evening stage accompanied by the Hartford Festival Orchestra in this signature concert featuring Spanish, Latin, and World Music. In addition, several of New England's top guitarists will perform a variety of music styles throughout the afternoon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a terrific atmosphere of music and fun, pack up the kids and a picnic for a great day?free to the public! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festival is supported in part by The National Endowment for the Arts, The Hartford Financial Services Group, The Greater Hartford Arts Council, The Connecticut Commission on Culture &amp;amp; Tourism, and media sponsor Beethoven Radio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, call The Connecticut Classical Guitar Society at (860) 249-7041 or Riverfront Recapture at (860) 713-3131. Riverfront Plaza is fully handicapped accessible. Click for directions, map of Hartford, and handicap accessibility. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been very fortunate to always have wonderful weather for this event, but in case of rain the concert will take place the following day on Sunday, September 10. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This annual event has now become an end-of-summer tradition for thousands of music lovers. Presented by The Connecticut Classical Guitar Society, the afternoon festivities will include several of New England's best guitarists, performing an exciting variety of musical styles. The evening will feature internationally acclaimed guitarist Daniel Salazar, Jr. performing with the Hartford Festival Orchestra, conducted by Brian Sparks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guitar Under the Stars founder and internationally acclaimed classical guitarist Daniel Salazar, Jr. will perform selections from his exciting repertoire that fuses Spanish guitar with Latin and World rhythms. Joining him will be The Daniel Salazar Ensemble, a group consisting of guitars, bass, keyboards, and world percussion, accompanied by the 35-piece Hartford Festival Orchestra conducted by Brian Sparks. The program will also include a selection of Spanish classics, including flamenco-inspired music by Falla, Albeniz, and Lecuona especially arranged for guitar and orchestra. Guest vocalist Sylma Pagan will be a featured artist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To start this special day, The Connecticut Classical Guitar Society will present an afternoon of great guitar music featuring several of its professional members performing an array of guitar styles. Performers include The Hartt Suzuki Guitar Ensemble, Kevin Gallagher, Val Ramos, and The Alturas Duo. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.ccgs.org/events06-07/gus06.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ccgs.org/events06-07/gus06.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ccgs.org/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1157560730000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Sound of International Music - Guitar Under the Stars!</name><id>5115600</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1157828400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/5115600/</event_url></item>