<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For those of you who have not overdosed on fun and frivolity during the raucous that is the Victory Day Holiday, we have a treat for you!  INTRODUCING! The Very First Annual - End of Summer BBQ Bash Extravaganza!  The debauchery will be hosted by our very own bow-tied attorney, Mike Doyle.  This event will prove to Rhode Islanders, new and old, that sometimes it is worth taking a bit of a drive...even if it is not to visit mom or New York City.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those not in the know, Mike recently moved to the fair hamlet of Warren, despite the tireless and pugnacious struggle by local officials hell bent on keeping him out.  He thinks they said something about &amp;quot;standards&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;no nudity&amp;quot;, we’re not really sure.  Regardless, in bow-tied domination he prevailed, and the Collective now reaps the benefits!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So….Saturday, August 28th, starting at 3pm, come on down to his wee little cottage by the coast and scarf down a burger/dog and an ice-cold adult beverage.  There will be games, cornhole, bocci and perhaps some old-fashioned Lawn Darts (yeah that’s right the good kind, not the ridiculous re-release of the game with lame poofy nerf tips).  Mike will provide the burgers, dogs, cold beer, and a few bottles of soda for the weak.  For those interested in something more - no problem!  If your last name  begins with  A-M, then bring a &amp;quot;savory&amp;quot; - chips, veggies n dip, etc.  If it begins with N-Z, then bring a &amp;quot;sweet&amp;quot;!  What’s that you say??  What if it rains?? Party tents are also in the offing, so weather is noooo problem.  What’s that more questions??? Yes you can stay the night, but be sure to bring your own &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; tent - unless you are lucky enough to win one of the few coveted spots in the house (let the jello wrestling begin!).  Now quit asking stuff and junk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh yeah and there’s more!!  Mike’s five year old nephew, Henry, is celebrating his 5th year of survivorship.  And since helping others feels great, as part of the Extravaganza, Mike is taking donations for the Leukemia &amp;amp; Lymphoma Society (LLS), this will go to the Light The Night Walk in October, LLS's evening walk and fundraising event.  If you can't make the Extravaganza, then feel free to go here and make a donation:  &lt;a href="http://pages.lightthenight.org/ct/NewLondn10/MDoyle" target="_blank"&gt;http://pages.lightthe...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK so enough talking about myself in the third-person...I truly look forward to spending the day laughing and generally enjoying life with such good friends.  I hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;41 Bradford Street&lt;br /&gt;Warren, RI  02885&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cell:  401.787.4930.  (Texting is great!)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's my house. duh</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>9780319</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283173277000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>43</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280873816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Very First Annual - End of Summer BBQ Bash Extravaganza!</name><id>14309413</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283022000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/14309413/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>