<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi,&lt;br /&gt;  I hope you are fine. I have another exciting announcement. We are continuing this exciting new season with another  popular and timely presentation by Jay Wallus. What everyone wants to know about marketing, specifically, how to get sellers and buyers to hear your message. This is an information packed exposition, by the an expert on marketing and sales,he also has a very extensive bio.His Company &amp;quot;Street Smarts&amp;quot;,helps companies and individuals find unique ways to gain and keep the attention of their subject audience.He has worked this magic for investor's in Mass. and in other states. You won't want to miss this informative, timely, valuable revelation of many unknown and mostly unexplored ideas that could make you wealthy, beyond your wildest dreams. &lt;br /&gt;  This event will fill up fast. If you are interested, please respond now. I don't want you to be disappointed, by being shut out. dale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. Several of us who have profited from this material, will be on hand to tell our stories.&lt;br /&gt;P.P.S. I will forward another email with his full bio&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PPPS. Networking can be the most valuable part of these meetings. Unfortunately, I have promised to be out of the room by 9pm. Those folks who have arrived early to meet people, can tell you of the value of coming early.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>dale</member_name><member_id>3116571</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199923612000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New Normal RE Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>GreaterBostonREIClub</urlname><id>320990</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Real Estate Investing Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196730702000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston Real Estate Investing Club January Meetup</name><id>6850809</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199750400000</time><rsvp_limit>99</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/GreaterBostonREIClub/events/6850809/</event_url></item>