<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>(approx.) per person</description><amount>82.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>*** The raft is reported to be full! 8/15/06 ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Reservation has been made... make your reservation w/company ASAP to get with our group. Use Martha Sanders as party name.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Meetup time has been updated to reflect the reservation**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fun, Easy Whitewater! This 10 mile trip is the perfect outing and would be a day-trip and includes lunch on the river. The cost is about $80 bucks. You could say this is a &amp;quot;hike&amp;quot; on the water. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first half of the day offers fun, easy rapids such as &amp;quot;Freight Train&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Pinball.&amp;quot; Calm sections allow your guide to fill you in on local history and enjoy the breathtaking scenery. About half-way through the trip, the rafts approach &amp;quot;Zoar Gap,&amp;quot; the day's biggest rapid. After safely navigating this exciting stretch, we serve a hearty riverside picnic lunch. The second half of the trip has fun spots such as &amp;quot;Roger Rapid&amp;quot; and opportunities to get out of the boat and float. This trip is the perfect introduction to whitewater rafting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: &lt;br /&gt;Crab Apple on the Deerfield - Charlemont, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one is Martha (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2559645/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;) so please direct questions to her.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Please register your intent ASAP so we can make the reservation.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Do not pay via PayPal. Payment will be made to the outfitter.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time:&lt;br /&gt;This trip starts at different times - Check confirmation for your trip time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***We'll make the reservation and send out an e-maill to all the hiking meetup members. You will have only a **7 day window** to make your reservation/payment yourself with the company and get in our group. See the Message Board for more information and to ask questions (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/boards/view/viewthread?thread=1764327&amp;amp;pager.offset=30).***"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is your responsibility to arrive on time. The trip cannot wait for latecomers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip Itinerary:*&lt;br /&gt;* Check-in at appropriate trip time &lt;br /&gt;* Lifejacket and helmet fitting &lt;br /&gt;* Safety lecture and paddling instruction &lt;br /&gt;* Bus ride to Fife Brook dam &lt;br /&gt;* Raft 5 miles in Class II whitewater &lt;br /&gt;* Zoar Gap Rapid Class III &lt;br /&gt;* Hearty riverside picnic lunch &lt;br /&gt;* Continue 4 miles in Class II whitewater &lt;br /&gt;* Take out and ride back to Crab Apple &lt;br /&gt;* Slide presentation of trip &lt;br /&gt;* Trip itinerary could be altered to accommodate dam release time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Bring: &lt;br /&gt;Bathing suit or shorts &lt;br /&gt;Footwear - sandals w/straps, watershoes (flip-flops not recommended) &lt;br /&gt;Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;Towel &lt;br /&gt;Change of clothes and shoes for after trip &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Items for cool/rainy days:&lt;br /&gt;***Avoid cotton clothing-it cools the body when wet! &lt;br /&gt;For feet: wool/fleece socks. &lt;br /&gt;For torso and legs: wool, fleece, capilene, polypropylene &lt;br /&gt;Outer layer: wind jacket and pants are great for shedding water and can be worn over a wetsuit or fleece &lt;br /&gt;Wetsuits&lt;br /&gt;Clean, comfortable wetsuits and wetsuit boots will always be available for rent. Fleece and synthetics are extra warm under wetsuits and wetsuit boots. Wind jackets and pants can be worn over wetsuits to shed water and add warmth. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$$$:&lt;br /&gt;Crab Apple on the Deerfield houses a fun store where you may purchase photos of your trip, a fine selection of apparel and souvenirs. A snack bar is also available with ice cream, snacks, soda, beer and wine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medications:&lt;br /&gt;Always bring medications which you may need on the river i.e. asthma inhaler, bee sting kit, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deerfield River Fife Brook Section Prices: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weekday Weekend Non-Guaranteed &lt;br /&gt;Adult $77pp $82pp $72pp &lt;br /&gt;Child under 16 $62pp $67pp $57pp &lt;br /&gt;Includes:&lt;br /&gt;Pre-trip safety instruction, guide, equipment, transportation to and from river, riverside picnic lunch and photo presentation of your adventure&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.crabappleinc.com/massachusetts/deerfield-fife_brook.shtml"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crabappleinc.com/massachusetts/deerfield-fife_brook.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crabapplei...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1151942412000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Martha's White Water Rafting on Deerfield R. Fife Brook Section, Charlemont MA</name><id>5006492</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1156080600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5006492/</event_url></item>