<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>96 Fair St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06437</zip><lat>41.287177</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 458-6699</phone><name>Women &amp; Family Life Center</name><city>Guilford</city><id>759422</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.686208</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Networking&lt;/b&gt; over coffee and tea from 8:30 to 9:00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Program from&lt;/b&gt; 9:00 to 10:00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business Brainstorm:&lt;/b&gt; “Established Business” – anyone 1-3 years in business will get a mini mentoring session from members.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speaker&lt;/b&gt; – Lisa Kennally&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Topic:&lt;/b&gt; Lisa will discuss Becoming an Entrepreneur in the Skin Care Industry as well as provide tips and information on skin care. &amp;quot;It's time for a little pampering and learning wrapped into one! Come and learn how to make your own lip balm and other body care products. I'll share my tips for using what you have in your own kitchen and also the challenges and successes I've had as a 'solopreneur.'  I'll also share with you my recent success story regarding the Spa at Norwich Inn!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Lisa Kennally is the creator of 'lisa ann skincare' and studied consumer affairs in college. “I have always been concerned with ingredients in products and how they affect all of us. I have never understood or agreed with why there are so many chemicals in our skin care products and foods. After spending some years in publishing and packaging I decided it was time to put my love for creating &amp;quot;as natural as possible&amp;quot; skin and body care products skills to good use.  Careful attention has been put into all the ingredients I use to make my products. Fair Trade unrefined shea butter, olive oil, cocoa butter, pomegranate, green tea are all ingredients that have amazing benefits for your skin and are in many of my products. You can find my products in spas, boutiques, health food stores and online.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New and prospective members enjoy their first meeting free.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cheryl Roby</member_name><member_id>10682494</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258724532000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Association-of-Women-Business-leaders</urlname><id>1543671</id><group_lat>41.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>AWBL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257778323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November 18 AWBL Meetingg</name><id>11831709</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258551000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Association-of-Women-Business-leaders/events/11831709/</event_url></item>