<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03878</zip><lat>43.263596</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dat's Pizzeria &amp; Sports Pub</name><city>Somersworth</city><id>8321402</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.863861</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;*** This month we'll be at Dat's Pizzeria &amp;amp; Sports Pub in downtown Somersworth!  ***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site used to be Station 319, a legendary Somersworth haunt, and after a few years as Joe's Pizza is now under new management.  Literally, they are having their Grand Opening while I type this!  If *this* one doesn't get us an investigation, I need to hang up my stirrups!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anecdotes include moving objects, appearing and disappearing objects, and several reports of two different apparitions!  Seriously!  I'm excited they're back open!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;t's easy to find once you're on Main Street - it's just off of downtown and the old Station 319 sign is still hanging by the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The monthly dinner meetings are primarily non-mandatory networking events. Although we talk business updates for half an hour and occasionally play evidence clips, these events are for discussion, event/investigation planning, asking questions, telling your own stories, etc. They're so we can all have a little unpressured time as a group. Because our regular place has closed down we are going back to our roots and will be choosing a different reportedly haunted location to meet at each month. Keep your eye on the meetup post for details. We look forward to you joining us!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Valerie Roy</member_name><member_id>4599203</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>andy</member_name><member_id>5342211</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343310820000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342741935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>kgjdnyqkbhc</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343255400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/74095822/</event_url></item>