<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Gorham Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04106</zip><lat>43.636547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borders</name><city>South Portland</city><id>863730</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.332540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Girl With The Dragon Tattoo by Stieg Larsson.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://z.about.com/d/bestsellers/1/0/F/6/-/-/Girl_Dragon_Tattoo.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a brief synopsis from Barnes and Noble of The Girl With The Dragon Tattoo:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s about the disappearance forty years ago of Harriet Vanger, a young scion of one of the wealthiest families in Sweden . . . and about her octogenarian uncle, determined to know the truth about what he believes was her murder.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s about Mikael Blomkvist, a crusading journalist recently at the wrong end of a libel case, hired to get to the bottom of Harriet’s disappearance . . . and about Lisbeth Salander, a twenty-four-year-old pierced and tattooed genius hacker possessed of the hard-earned wisdom of someone twice her age—and a terrifying capacity for ruthlessness to go with it—who assists Blomkvist with the investigation. This unlikely team discovers a vein of nearly unfathomable iniquity running through the Vanger family, astonishing corruption in the highest echelons of Swedish industrialism—and an unexpected connection between themselves.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the cafe at the table by the windows</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248900570000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240691988000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June Book Club - The Girl With The Dragon Tattoo</name><id>10266460</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245884400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/10266460/</event_url></item>