<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Is it time! Are you starting over again. Or do you feel stagnant, like you are just spinning your wheels.  &lt;br /&gt;Well here it is! Something that could change your life. This Vision Voice and Message workshop is designed to help you create your New Year, Your New Beginning starting now! Let work together and start now to put your best year ever into ACTION. This is a free event so nothing is stopping you from your GOALS in life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you have been here before and created a Vision Board please bring it with you. If you have not don't worry about it, this workshop is about creating it and writing it down, making it part of your everyday life and to work it into your New Morning Routine (NMR) and your New Evening Routine. We shall create together a seven sentence statement that will keep you focused on your dreams in life and work on getting it to appear daily. So make that step, get in touch with me and say &amp;quot;YES I am Ready&amp;quot;!&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Mindful Wealth Seminar reveals the most powerful laws in the universe.   &lt;br /&gt;The knowledge of these laws have run like a golden thread through the lives and the teachings of all the prophets and through the lives of all truly great men and women.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All that they have ever accomplished or attained has been done in full accordance with this most powerful law  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ The Law of Attraction.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hello Folks, YES! WE are back! Anthony Pasquale will be holding This Vision Board/Statement Workshop! Specializing in &amp;quot;how to put it into action&amp;quot; workshop. Finding the Purpose within!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All are welcome! If you have attended these events in the past, it was such a success we had to book four other workshops&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have been to one of these workshops, Bring your Vision Board and either finish it or update it with new goals in your life. If this is your FIRST time, WELL you are in for an amazing life changing event.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also Anthony J. Pasquale will be there to teach you his Five Pillars to Mindful Wealth Everyday!   &lt;br /&gt;Anthony will be sharing his Goal Setting Vision Statement processes that he says &amp;quot;will put your life on course&amp;quot; and help you find your CHIEF AIM in life.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be held November 7th 1:30pm to 5:00pm for the workshop PLUS: from 445pm to 500pm we may have a special guest drop by.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do Not Wait to book your space we only have 25 seats and six are already taken.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to change your life!!! Things to Bring to this Visioneering Workshop   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Imagination   &lt;br /&gt;2. Desire  (write it out)  &lt;br /&gt;3. Your &amp;quot;Why&amp;quot; in Life (write it out)  &lt;br /&gt;4. Persistence   &lt;br /&gt;5. The life style you want. (write it out)  &lt;br /&gt;6. Where and with who. (write it out)  &lt;br /&gt;7. What you are willing to give in return for your goals. (write it out)  &lt;br /&gt;8. The Date that you want your goals done by! (write it out)  &lt;br /&gt;9. 5 x 8 index cards, Markers. Glue stick (mini Vison Board) &lt;br /&gt;10. Any decorative items you may want to put on your board. Most importantly anything that, &amp;quot;Speaks to you!&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;11. Open Mind to Adunance and Wealth.   &lt;br /&gt;12. Sense of Humor.   &lt;br /&gt;13. A willness to be coachable.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some of the things that will be covered:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Awakening, Voice, Vision, Message!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Seven Daily Steps through Mindful Wealth Living.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creating your Vision. (Your Vision Board)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creating your Voice. (Your Vision Statement)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creating your message in life. (Your Vision Symbol)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Vision in life will determine your decisions in life!  &lt;br /&gt;(You will do this excerises for the rest of your life!)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sifu Anthony Pasquale   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AJP Enterprise   &lt;br /&gt;United Martial Arts Center  &lt;br /&gt;Osanna Seminars  &lt;br /&gt;Mindful Wealth Group  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Live with purpose and passion everyday&amp;quot; !&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.umachealth.com   &lt;br /&gt;www.danversmartialarts.com  &lt;br /&gt;20 Locust Street, Suite 100   &lt;br /&gt;Danvers MA 01923   &lt;br /&gt;(978) 836-6501   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's remarkable, how much mediocrity we live with, surrounding ourselves with daily reminders that the average is acceptable. Our world suffers from terminal normality. Take a moment to access all the things around you that encourage you to remain &amp;quot;average&amp;quot;. These are the things that keep you powerless, unable to go beyond a limit you have arbitrarily set for yourself.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will introduce myself at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sifu Rita Rose </member_name><member_id>7503567</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257791779000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Practicers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-732</urlname><id>1196018</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Danvers " The Secret  "Vision Board Workshop Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252946620000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vision, Voice and Message! Learn to develop your Vision in Life! </name><id>11368546</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257618600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-732/events/11368546/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/e/b/global_4551819.jpeg</photo_url></item>