<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>146 Front St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02066</zip><lat>42.195965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 545-3999</phone><name>Mill Wharf Restaurant &amp; Pub</name><city>Scituate</city><id>242422</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.724846</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Join SSDOMG Members and their Guests as well as the FunFunFun.org Singles Club for a delicious and favorite jazz brunch at Chester's at Mill Wharf, overlooking Scituate Harbor. They offer a buffet brunch with all the breakfast options, inlcuding but not limited&amp;nbsp;to a variety of salads, waffles,&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;eggs,&amp;nbsp;as well as seafood, pasta, chicken, roast beef, etc. The band has been there for years, keeping people entertained throughout the brunch. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;The SSDOMG and FunFunFun.org Singles Club invite all singles and a friend to join us for this combined event as we introduce each other to both groups.&amp;nbsp; After Brunch we may go for a walk, depending on the weather.&amp;nbsp; Plan to join us for 1.5-2 hours as this is a very social Brunch as both Groups have discovered.&amp;nbsp; To learn more about the FunFunFun.org Singles Club please visit their website at &lt;a href="http://www.funfunfun.org"&gt;www.funfunfun.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Singles Jazz Brunch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, May 15th @ 11am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mill Wharf Restaurant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;146 Front Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scituate, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;781-545-3999&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.millwharf.com"&gt;www.millwharf.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.funfunfun.org"&gt;www.funfunfun.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Please meet outside the front door. Once most of us have arrived we will go in to be seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Carpool&lt;/em&gt;: Meet @ 10:15am&amp;nbsp;@ Braintree Town Hall @ 1 JFK Memorial Drive directly across the street from the Thayer Public Library and next to Thayer Academy.&amp;nbsp; We will wait 5 minutes and then depart as I need to be at the restaurant 5-10 minutes early.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;Please note in your RSVP Comments if you will be carpooling so we can be on the lookout for you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please Note&lt;/em&gt;:  &lt;br /&gt;1. We&amp;nbsp;will be separated into two or three tables.  &lt;br /&gt;2. This is for Singles Only.&amp;nbsp; That&amp;nbsp;means you are not married or engaged.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. The cost of the Brunch is $17.95 including coffee for parties of up to 14 people and $23.00 per person which includes coffee, tax, and tip for parties of 15 or more people.&amp;nbsp; All other beverages are additional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.&amp;nbsp;The SSDOMG is&amp;nbsp;charging $5 per SSDOMG Member and their 1 Guest.&amp;nbsp; This is the Monthly Special Rate for the FunFunFun.org Singles Club, the least expensive Event Fee option.&amp;nbsp; The FunFunFun.org Singles Club generally requires advance payment and registration via their website.&amp;nbsp; SSDOMG Members and their Guest will be able to pay in cash at the event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizers&lt;/em&gt;: Angela and Chris G. of the FunFunFun.org Singles Club&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: $5 per person - Members and their 1 Guest pay the same Event Fee; You can become a 2011&amp;nbsp;Annual Member for $12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: No minimumor maximum.&amp;nbsp; However, the rate we have procured for our groups is for a minimum of 15 people which we are confident we will get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: One per member.&amp;nbsp; If anyone else wants to join us please direct them to the funfunfun.org website to register for the event there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: 4pm on Saturday, May 14th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions to Mill Wharf:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview&lt;/em&gt;: Tucked in behind some shops right on Scituate Harbor.&amp;nbsp; Please watch for landmarks as it's easy to miss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Rt. 3&lt;/em&gt;: Take exit 13 - Rt. 53 North. Travel one mile to Junction of Rt. 123. Get onto Rt. 123 East. After crossing Route 3A, bear right onto Driftway. Continue to Front Street and Scituate Harbor. Mill Wharf Restaurant is located behind the Welsh Company Gift Shops after CVS and before TK O'Malley's.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lost?:&lt;/em&gt; Call restaurant at 781-545-3999.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Approximate Drive Time from Braintree: 1/2 hr&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions to Braintree Carpool @ Braintree Town Hall @ 1 JFK Memorial Drive&lt;/em&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Meet us in the parking lot between the Water/Sewer building (closest to the street when you pull in) and Town Hall.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview&lt;/em&gt;: Located near South Braintree Square, directly across from the Thayer Public Library and next to Thayer Academy, Town Hall is a short walk from the BRaintree T and a short drive from Route 3.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Routes 95/128/93:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Head towards Route 3 South/Braintree/Cape Cod.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route &lt;/em&gt;3: Take Exit 17/Union Street/Braintree&amp;nbsp;(it will be your 2nd exit on Route 3 South), take the 1st right off the exit ramp (from Route 3&amp;nbsp;southbound/3rd right&amp;nbsp;from Route 3&amp;nbsp;northbound) keeping Motel 6 on your left.&amp;nbsp; Get in one of the middle lanes and go straight thru the 1st set of lights going under the overpass and keeping the T on your left.&amp;nbsp; Take a left at the light at the top of the hill and get in the right lane.&amp;nbsp; Take a right at the next light and an immediate left into the Town Hall parking lot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the Braintree T on foot&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Exit the T heading towards Union Street and South Braintree Square.&amp;nbsp; Leave the front door, take a left and head towards the street (it's a one way so you may see a bus or taxi heading your way), then go down the steps and take a left heading under the underpass up the hill.&amp;nbsp; At the top of the hill at the light round the corner to your left heading towards The Fire Station.&amp;nbsp; At the next light if you walk diagonally across the street you will be at Town Hall.&amp;nbsp; Basically, cross the street in front of the fire station and then use the signal to cross Washington Street, or use the signal to cross Washington Street and then cross Central Street.&amp;nbsp; You will be at the Town Hall Mall once you have crossed the street(s).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the front door or at our table after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306204617000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>It's a favorite Brunch with the SSDOMG and the FunFunFun.org Singles Club.  We thought this would be the perfect combined event for these two groups.</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301259814000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Jazz Brunch w/ the FunFunFun.org Singles Club</name><id>17077337</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305471600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/17077337/</event_url></item>