<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Broadmoor Wildlife Sanctuary &lt;br /&gt;280 Eliot St. &lt;br /&gt;Natick, MA &lt;br /&gt;(508) 655-2296 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a $4 admission fee to the sactuary (kids $3).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Broadmoor?s nine miles of walking trails guide you through a variety of field, woodland, and wetland habitats. A quarter-mile, handicap accessible trail and boardwalk along the bank of Indian Brook and over the marsh offers great opportunities for birdwatching, photography, and sketching. To enjoy this site in the winter, bring your snowshoes or cross-country skis. Stroll along the edge of Indian Brook, which flows into the Charles River at the sanctuary, and look for wood ducks and signs of beavers and otters from the 110-foot-long bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Need a ride?  I can pick you up at 10 at the Riverside T stop, in the pick up/drop off area.  You should also consider posting a messase with your RSVP asking for a ride from from your neighborhood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you offer a ride?  Consider putting a message in with your RSVP, or email me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By car: From Boston: Take the Mass. Turnpike (Rt I-90) west to exit 16 (West Newton/Wellesley). Follow Rt 16 west for 7 miles to South Natick Center. The sanctuary is 1.8 miles ahead on the left. From the east: Take Rt 9 west to Rt 16 in Wellesley. Follow Rt 16 west for about 5 miles; the sanctuary is on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the west: Take Rt I-495 to Rt 9. Follow Rt 9 east to Rt 27 in Natick. Follow Rt 27 south for 4 miles to Sherborn. Turn left onto Rt 16 east and follow for 1.6 miles; the sanctuary is on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north and south: Take Rt I-95 to Rt 16 (exit 22). Follow Rt 16 west for 7 miles; the sanctuary is on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will go for lunch at:&lt;br /&gt;TENNESSEE'S REAL BBQ-REAL FAST&lt;br /&gt;341 COCHITUATE RD&lt;br /&gt;FRAMINGHAM,  MA  &lt;br /&gt;(508) 626-7140&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy M</member_name><member_id>3233594</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199115639000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198441816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Broadmoor Wildlife Sanctuary walk, then BBQ</name><id>6959834</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198942200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6959834/</event_url></item>