<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>268 College St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.306969</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Owl Shop</name><city>New Haven</city><id>885482</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928973</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Owl Shop was originally opened on Wall Street in 1934 by Joseph St. John who came to America from Greece in 1925. Beginning originally as a bookstore, he was also selling tobacco and mixing his own blends. In 1937, a second store on College Street was opened by Joseph and his wife Catherine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greg Sherrod has been entertaining audiences in the New England region for 22 years, playing music in the best venues in the area. Greg was selected to Michael Bolton’s New Haven Choir on Clash of The Choirs. Clash Of The Choirs was a reality special shown Live Dec, 17 thru 20th of 2007 on NBC. . 5 celebrities went back to their home towns to select a 20 person choir and take them to NYC to compete live on national T.V. Greg was also selected to The special sight reading and fast study group hand-picked from each choir to perform live on an NBC "The Today Show" which featured Gloria Estefan. Greg sang on stage with Patti LaBelle, Kelly Rowland of Destiny's Child, Nick Lachey, Blake Shelton, and Michael Bolton. Greg also performed as a back-up singer for Michael Bolton's performance of When a Man Loves a Woman.. Greg is now enjoying great success in residence at the critically acclaimed Blues Night at The Owl Shop on The Yale University Campus every Tuesday night for the past 18 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew will be hosting this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Text: 508-524-9988&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew</member_name><member_id>32462702</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354299333000</updated><rating><average>1.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353870037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greg Sherrod Band at The Owl Shop</name><id>92746462</id><duration>10800000</duration><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354068000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/92746462/</event_url></item>