<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>One of our most popular speakers is returning to make a presentation to us this next Wednesday July 15th.  Please RSVP early as this will fill up quickly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joe Burns&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;the founder of Burns Investment Group and The BigEdgeReport.com  will present his unique formulas for both fundamental and technical analysis and give us his current watch list and outlook on the market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who are not already familiar with Joe, he was a former National Speaker for IBD* and traveled the globe giving seminars for them for nearly ten years and, aside from being a tremendously knowledgeable speaker, he is always entertaining.  Joe now has his own company and provides education for individual investors around the world.  On Wednesday the 15th he will cover his own EDGE Investing System.  This means that he will discuss how to narrow your watch list to the very strongest stocks fundamentally and then how to use both traditional base patterns and entry points and then also his Early EDGE Entry strategies to buy stocks at a point that gives you the best chance to maximize gains and protect yourself from unnecessary losses in your portfolio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;*Joe Burns and Burns Investment Group are not affiliated or endorsed by Investor’s Business Daily or William O’Neil &amp;amp; Co.  Joe Burns and the Burns Investment Group do not utilize or lecture on CANSLIM investing.  CANSLIM is a registered trademark associated with William O’Neil and Investors Business Daily. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248321969000</updated><rating><average>3.25</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>74</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247094489000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Speakers Meeting: Joe Burns</name><id>10833811</id><headcount>88</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247698800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/10833811/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>