<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please read the details of this posting before attending this hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My cell # if you need to reach me is: (413)559-0192 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;I'm re-posting this hike for when I can make it and leaving the old posting up to for anyone who wants to explore this on their own so here's the new time and date for when I'll be there(and hopefully have the chance to explore it before then too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;New news&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;I was just told this trail has been re-routed so unless someone knows the old trail this route is no longer in use. I will explore this before we hike so I can suggest a new route to take...Currently from what I know, we could either start at the Tully Lake Campground and head to Royalston Falls from there or combine the two by carpooling from one trail head to another and still do Tully Mountain too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This is a hike I have not done yet and would like to check out. Anyone up for some exploration with me? I saw the sign saying it was 10 miles to Royalston Falls so I need to check it out. I'd like to spot a car (at least) at Royalston Falls and come back to start the hike at Tully Mountain which is going to be less than 1 1/2 miles for the mountain hike(according to the guide) then connect to the trail heading to Royalston Falls which is 10 miles according to the sign.I have done the Tully Mountain hike many times but had no way to know how far it was.I don't have a GPS. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.thetrustees.org/assets/documents/places-to-visit/trailmaps/Tully-Trail-Map.pdf"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/assets/documents/places-to-visit/trailmaps/Tully-Trail-Map.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Please bring a headlamp just in case it's needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/1723755200050492932723/img/smileys/biggrin.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;This hike will be for intermediate hikers at least who can hike at good pace of 2-3 MPH for the entire approximately 12 mile trip.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;You must be able to physically handle this hike. if anyone has a medical condition that I should be aware of, please let me know ahead of time along with other information on your emergency treatment plan, contact information, etc....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will plan short breaks as needed only and one longer break to rest at the approximate half way point  so communicating is also essential if you want to stop for any reason...ie: I'm hungry, need to find a tree, hang on...gotta blow my nose or find my headlamp, etc;-).... Alright, hope that made you smile;-).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/45"&gt;http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/45&lt;/a&gt; Photo: Tully Mountain, photo by David Brothers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photo: Tully Mountain, photo by David Brothers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tully Mountain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain Rd., Orange, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The focal point of the Tully Trail and of the Tully Mountain Wildlife Management Area, Tully Mountain rises 1,163 feet above sea level and humps dramatically above the relatively flat land around it. Geologically, it is a remnant of ancient mountain building that upthrust the northern Appalachians 400 million years ago. From the northwest it also shows the effect of the glaciers—the northern face ground smooth, the southern face left much more irregular by deposited debris. A loop trail of about 1½ miles leads to outcrops near the summit that afford magnificent views of the surrounding land and waters and of more distant mountains. And Tully Mountain not only offers peace and pleasure to people but also—because of its numerous types of habitats—provides a home for a rich array of plants and animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The focal point of the Tully Trail and of the Tully Mountain Wildlife Management Area, Tully Mountain rises 1,163 feet above sea level and humps dramatically above the relatively flat land around it. Geologically, it is a remnant of ancient mountain building that upthrust the northern Appalachians 400 million years ago. From the northwest it also shows the effect of the glaciers—the northern face ground smooth, the southern face left much more irregular by deposited debris.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A loop trail of about 1½ miles leads to outcrops near the summit that afford magnificent views of the surrounding land and waters and of more distant mountains. And Tully Mountain not only offers peace and pleasure to people but also—because of its numerous types of habitats—provides a home for a rich array of plants and animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Rte. 2 take Exit 18 and go west on Rte. 2A into Athol center. Turn right (north) at the traffic light onto Exchange St. Turn left onto Pequoig Ave. just across the bridge and go 3.1 miles to Royalston Rd. Turn right and then take a quick left onto Mountain Rd. (Note: Pequoig Ave. becomes Pinedale Ave. and then Tully Rd.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Image of globeClick for a Map&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/central-ma/royalston-falls.html"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/central-ma/royalston-falls.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Royalston Falls Photo Gallery Royalston Falls Royalston, MA Bird Watching Cross-country skiing/Snowshoeing Fishing Horseback Riding Hunting Picnicking Walking/Hiking (Strenuous) Regional Trail Link Key To Symbols&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Royalston Falls &lt;br /&gt;

 Regulations &amp;amp; Advisories &lt;br /&gt;

 Directions &amp;amp; Contact Info &lt;br /&gt;

 Admissions &amp;amp; Fees &lt;br /&gt;

 History &lt;br /&gt;

 Volunteer Opportunities &lt;br /&gt;

 Conservation &amp;amp; Stewardship &lt;br /&gt;

 Maps &amp;amp; Resources &lt;br /&gt;

 Planning Your Visit &lt;br /&gt;

 Tell Us About Your Visit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E-Newsletter Sign Up Explore events, news, &amp;amp; more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Royalston Falls 217 acres&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow a descending trail that leads to a deep, ancient gorge carved by prehistoric glacial meltwater to falls that plunge 45 feet into a basin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes Royalston Falls a special place? &lt;br /&gt;

 We think it’s the remote location of the waterfalls – well worth the 0.8-mile descent to the edge a half-hidden ravine! Carved over the ages by Falls Brook, the boisterous cascade plunges 45 feet into an icy pool, sending up a misty spray through the thick forest hugging the gorge. A shelter on the trail offers a great resting spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you make your way into the ravine, the dramatic falls remain hidden within an emerald cloak of dense forest and ferns. The flume appears suddenly, as if to offer a sensory reward for your exertions. In winter, freezing spray creates a fantastic landscape of ice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note: The trek is not an easy one – and can be very wet in places, so you should use extreme caution when walking here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Forest’s Comeback &lt;br /&gt;

 From the time of the first wave of European settlers in the 17th century, much of the Massachusetts forest was cut down for agricultural fields and pastures, firewood, and timber. Such wholesale land clearing continued into the 19th century until New England farmers abandoned their fields and headed west in search of richer, less rocky soil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, the resurgent forest continues to slowly erase all remnants of human activity from more than a century ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But at this reservation, the forces of nature manifest themselves in ways other than just flora reclaiming its own; Falls Brook not only carved the flume but also fashioned a series of natural bridges through the bedrock just upstream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A large group shelter, which overlooks Falls Brook, is available for overnight hikers. The shelter is located on the reservation near the intersection where the Metacomet-Monadnock Trail diverges from the Tully Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Tale of Two Trails &lt;br /&gt;

 The primary access route to the falls is along a short stretch of the Tully Trail, a 22-mile loop encircling the scenic Tully Valley. But this 0.8-mile pathway down to Falls Brook is also part of the much longer Metacomet-Monadnock Trail. The M-M Trail extends for 117 miles from the border with Connecticut near Springfield to Mount Monadnock in southwest New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trails &lt;br /&gt;

 1.5 miles of trails. Moderate hiking, strenuous in places. The trail is rugged and wet in places, so use extreme caution when hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reservation is a link in the Tully Trail and the Metacomet-Monadnock Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When to Visit &lt;br /&gt;

 Year-round, daily, sunrise to sunset. Allow a minimum of 1 hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facilities &lt;br /&gt;

 Interested in camping near Royalston Falls? Check out the Tully Lake Campground, also in Royalston.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a Meetup sign. Terry &amp; I are spotting cars so may not be there when you arrive if you are early.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370132419000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363356758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tully Mtn to Royalston Falls Explorative Hike(Appr 12miles), Rescheduled</name><id>109397432</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370092500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/109397432/</event_url></item>