<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>522 Amherst Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.794567</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-882-6026</phone><name>Sky Lounge</name><city>Nashua</city><id>845678</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.526093</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE 7/22/2010:  The 7/29speed Dating event is being postponed until August 26, the main reason is due to lack of signups especially of the male persuasion.  All you men out there, lets get signed up for the August 26, 2010 event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you signed up for the 7/29 event and have already sent your payment but will be unable to attend the August 26 event, please let the organizer know and and they will reach out to Susan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all, espcially you men at the Aug 26th event&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan Tisbert from Meeting &amp;amp; Greetin in so. NH is having a speed dating event, her last one was very successful.  The details are below, if you are interested in attending follow the directions as she has stated by mailing her a check and including which age group you will be attending, then RSVP on this site that you have sent the check and which age group you will be attending.  Hope to see you all there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh and by the way, Susan Tisbert is an awesome Realtor, so if you are looking to buy or sell give her a buzz.  She just assisted me in buying my first home and she was a godsend.....Janet&lt;br /&gt;Hi there,&lt;br /&gt;I thought I would let you know of my new venture, in case you're single and would like to try &amp;quot;suzie's speed dating&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;fun events by suz&amp;quot;...someone help me with the name please  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;My first party was in Dracut, MA last month, and was very successful, with over 50 people attending.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you'd like to spin the wheel of fate, and maybe find your sweetie, I am having a second party in Nashua, NH at the &amp;quot;Sky Lounge&amp;quot; restaurant and pub, on Thursday, July 29th.  The Sky Lounge is a real classy, big &amp;quot;open air/concept&amp;quot; place at 522 Amherst Street , even though from the street, it looks like a small bar.  It's in the same plaza as Gold's Gym.&lt;br /&gt;The owners/managers let me use the entire upstairs lounge for the party :)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;They have a good menu you can check it out at SkyLoungeNH.com, and of course there's a cash bar.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To attend, please mail your check, for $15, to my address below.  There will be no refunds, a week before the party.&lt;br /&gt;Here is the schedule:&lt;br /&gt;46-58 years group starts at 6:00pm&lt;br /&gt;33-45 years group starts at 8:00pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please include in your correspondence the following information:&lt;br /&gt;Age/category you'd like to be included in, and your Name, Address, Phone and Email address.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If anyone is interested in a 55+ group please let me know, I will get a list together&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the lounge beginning at 6pm</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282923057000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278671816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Speed Dating - Come meet your honey</name><id>14049499</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282860000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/14049499/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>