<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>877-269-7289; PIN 15059&lt;br /&gt;6pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Washington, D.C.) - U.S. Senator Jeanne Shaheen today announced that she will host a telephone town hall discussion on health care this Thursday, August 6th from 6:10 p.m. to 7:10 p.m. As the health care debate continues in Washington, Shaheen wants to hear directly from people across New Hampshire about the type of health reform they'd like to see. Shaheen will open the discussion with short remarks and then will take questions from constituents for the remainder of the call.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Reforming the nation's health care system so that coverage is more affordable and accessible has been and continues to be one of the greatest challenges of our lifetime,&amp;quot; said Shaheen. &amp;quot;Everyone has a personal stake in this important debate, and I'm looking forward to speaking directly with New Hampshire residents to update them on the progress we've made and answer any questions they may have.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The discussion will focus on the Senate's progress on health care reform, how Shaheen will evaluate proposed legislation, and why Congress must act now to change the status quo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Hampshire residents that would like to participate in the call should contact Shaheen's Manchester office at 603-647-7500 to obtain the call information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members of the media are welcome to join the teleconference to listen to the discussion, though we ask that the limited number of questions Shaheen will be able to take during the hour-long call be reserved for non-media participants. Reporters wishing to join the call should RSVP to Nell McGarity for the call information at (202) 224-5553 or nell_mcgarity@shaheen.senate.gov.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249769368000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249504296000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>US Senator Shaheen Healthcare Town Hall</name><id>11044214</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249596000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/11044214/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>