<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Mt. Holyoke Range State Park is a little North of Springfield with 3,000 acres! The exact length and path covered on this hike will depend on the weather conditions. If there is little or no snow ***we'll do a traditional hike.*** If there is something like 6 inches or more of snow we will either hike, try snowshoeing. We'll hike no more than approximatly 6 miles with less being the case if conditions require more effort given a 5 hour window for hiking. Most of the hike would be moderate in difficulty with some limited opportunity for high-moderate exertion. Streams, forest, and quiet solitude will dominate the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go need to have: &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots or comfortable winter boots (no sneakers!) - There could be snow or it could be wet/muddy! &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Gators or snow pants - Suggested, as there could be snow on the trail and you want to keep it out of your boots! &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too. &lt;br /&gt;* Gloves - MUST have &amp;amp; warm ones too! &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket - BRIGHT color best given hunters (not advised to wear white, dark green, brown, tan, dark grey, or black if possible -see vest below if must wear). &lt;br /&gt;* Hat - You loose 20% of your heat through your head! Protect those ears too. &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water - MUST bring! &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food/lunch - (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.) &lt;br /&gt;* Snowshoes and poles - Advised if there is 6 inches or more of snow.&lt;br /&gt;* Orange vest/bandanna, or something bright orange, bright yellow, or bright red to wear -suggested, just in case, so hunters don't make a mistake. I'll have 2 vests in the party already.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 9 AM at the Notch Visitors Center at the west side of the park (see the park map). Directions are below. We'll likely relocate to another parking location for the hike (south or north side of the park). We will hike (with rest stops and sightseeing) about 4 hr. and get back to the vehicles at about 2 PM. Then the plan is to head out to eat a late lunch together back down MA-116 in South Hadley. There are plenty of good places to eat in one place near Holyoke College. We would finish up eating at about 3:30 PM and head home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor ***leaving*** at a 8 AM for those interested. There will be a blue Dodge Grandcaravan Sport. Please chip in for gas and the drive is an hour. Return at about 4:30 PM. It is advised to call Kevin (number in RSVP) so he knows you plan to carpool. Directions for the carpool meet-up can be found at: &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?searchtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;searchtab=home&amp;amp;formtype=address&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=69+Prospect+Hill+rd.&amp;amp;city=East+Windsor&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General park information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/hksp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/Holyoke.gif" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location to meet at park (can get directions from here):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=1540+West+St.&amp;amp;city=Amherst&amp;amp;state=MA" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Can meet me in E. Windsor to join in a carpool or to follow up to hike location. Can also meet at hike location at Visitor's Center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200874952000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><why>A winter hiking experience without too much difficulty!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198729310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at Mt. Holyoke Range SP in Amherst MA</name><id>6974534</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200146400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6974534/</event_url></item>