<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>271 Pine Nook Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01342</zip><lat>42.543167</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Eaglebrook School</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>6975382</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.588030</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/e/2/event_115618082.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We will meet on Pine Nook Road in Deerfield after Eaglebrook School. The road turns to dirt after the school entrances and there are several pull-offs to park at. We can then walk down the road to meet up with the trail. Since this is still a road used occasionally by both on and off road vehicles, we should keep the dogs on leash until we walk on the trail - it is not far at all to the trail. We will walk on the Fridge section of the Pocumtuck Ridge Trail. It is a well defined footpath that is a moderate to slightly difficult trail. We will walk for 45 minutes and then turn back. We may reach Rice's Ferry Road which is an Off Road vehicle trail. We then have the option to continue on the footpath.  The website for this entire trail system is &lt;a href="http://pocumtuck.org/"&gt;http://pocumtuck.org/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions from Greenfield center are to head south on Bank Row, which is also Route 5 and 10, into Deerfield for about 3 miles. Pine Nook Road is on the left at a 4 way intersection. Look for a red house at that intersection. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions from Northampton are to head north on route 91 and take exit 24 to Route 5&amp;amp;10. Turn right to head north on Route 5 and 10 for about 5.5 miles. Pine Nook Road is on the right. Look for the red house at a 4 way intersection - it is across from Pine Nook Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Pine Nook Road and go under the archway.  Continue past the Eaglebrook School entrances until the road turns from tar to dirt.  The road has a few sharp curves.  Once the road has turned to dirt, start looking on the right or left for parking areas.  The path starts just as the road turns from tar to dirt.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336999306000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335834134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Fridge section of Pocumtuck Ridge Trail</name><id>62849432</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336831200000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/62849432/</event_url></item>