<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$10.00 pay at the door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have you resolved to "do more" in 2011? Want to make progress on your goals?&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Join Socializing for Justice for a Skillshare on Overcoming Procrastination February 7th, 6:00 - 8:30 PM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SoJust hosts events that draw progressives of all stripes that share common values but may work on different issues. We create social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections and run a Skillshare Series, hosted by The NonProfit Center*, which builds our individual capacity to make a difference in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're very excited that Hillary Rettig, author of &lt;em&gt;The Lifelong Activist: How to Change the World Without Losing Your Way&lt;/em&gt;, is returning to facilitate this training. Copies of her book will be available - $20 cash/check, proceeds shared with SoJust. "If I had but one book to spend hard-earned cash on this year, [The Lifelong Activist] would be it, hands down." &amp;ndash; Daily Kos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overcoming Procrastination, Perfectionism, Blocks and Fears&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This workshop helps under-productive writers overcome procrastination and blocks, and productive writers increase their writing tempo. We characterize the specific nature of procrastination, under- and blocks, and explain why people have trouble overcoming these problems. We also discuss the key procrastination symptoms of perfectionism, negativity and fear of failure/success. After precisely characterizing the problem, we discuss solutions, and keys for living a happier and more productive life. We also discuss mentors as a crucial component of success, and how to locate and cultivate them. After the workshop, participants typically feel energetic and empowered and eager to go home and make some of the changes we&amp;rsquo;ve discussed. Many later report making more progress on their goals than they have in a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE  &lt;br /&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing - bring your own dinner  &lt;br /&gt;6:30-8:00 Training  &lt;br /&gt;8:00-8:30 Q &amp;amp; A and more socializing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT OUR PRESENTER  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hillary Rettig&lt;/strong&gt; is a writer, coach and workshop leader who specializes in helping people:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) increase their productivity (especially, writing productivity), and overcome blocks  &lt;br /&gt;2) improve their time use  &lt;br /&gt;3) find jobs, and build more meaningful and satisfying careers, and  &lt;br /&gt;4) start and grow businesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hillary has spoken before hundreds of audiences across the nation in the activist, arts, community, small business and corporate realms; and in each realm finds wisdom and insight to bring to the others. She has also appeared on national and local television and radio programs, and been quoted in many national and local newspapers.You can read more about her and her work at &lt;a href="http://hillaryrettig.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.hillaryrettig.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 7th Skillshare:&lt;/strong&gt; Grassroots Fundraising aka How to Make the Ask by SoJust's Co-Founder Robbie Samuels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*&lt;a href="http://www.nonprofitcenterboston.org/site/c.ddKGIQNuEmG/b.1363373/k.5381/About_Us__Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt; - The NonProfit Center&lt;/strong&gt; is located one block from South Station at 89 South Street. The Center is accessible through the main lobby to people who have restricted physical abilities.   &lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this "Movement Moment". Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With almost 1600 members and 4+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298232505000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294078830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Overcoming Procrastination</name><id>15899136</id><headcount>37</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297119600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/15899136/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/b/global_20596251.jpeg</photo_url></item>