<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>~~&gt; Use the dirt driveway to the tree</address_2><address_1>20 Hartford Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06070</zip><lat>41.847504</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Sickomoore Tree Put In</name><city>Simsbury</city><id>405792</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.806230</lon></venue><fee><label>Kayak Rental Doughnation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per Kayak/canoe Rented</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>ALL KAYAKS ARE NOW TAKEN&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Farmington River Paddle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, May 25, 2008 at 12:00 PM 20080622T160000Z&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where&lt;br /&gt;Sickomoore Tree Put In&lt;br /&gt;20 Hartford Road Use the short north driveway before Bridge&lt;br /&gt;Simsbury , CT 06070&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who should come&lt;br /&gt;Those that have a kayak (their Own or one of mine) and want to paddle this short portion of river to the Terriffville Gougre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why&lt;br /&gt;Its a kayak trip on a nice day...(Hopefully)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to find the organizer(s)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I will have the Blue Toyota Avalon with a kayak trailer and the customary orange traffic cones.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;--AL-r (The Kayaking Honcho)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the shortened trip from the one we have done in the past on this river.&lt;br /&gt;I know most of you need some conditioning to get to those 25+ mile paddles..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location(s) allows for an easy in and out loading, along with a fast car transport between locations (most of you know the drill on this one..its not difficult) ...some have to stay, some go to the end and drop off cars..then some have to take us back..then some take those who drove us to the beginning get a ride back to their cars,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(i dont want to hear any complaining about this...everyone will end up just about driving the same amount), those who have kayaked with us here know its pretty easy and fair to all..&lt;br /&gt;those that don't want to do this can paddle back up stream and meet us at the end when we finish..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The put in location, THE PLACE WHERE WE MEET FIRST, unload etc.....&lt;br /&gt;is at the Giant Sickomoore tree in Simsbury CT,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford i use&lt;br /&gt;I 91 north, to exit 35..take a left onto rte 218..follow it past Copaco, till it runs into rte 185, take a right onto rte 185 follow till you get to the bridge..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use 20 Hartford Road (rte 185) Simsbury for a GPS, mapquest location (always compare the info to my directions, if not close, then forget Mapquest and look at a different map..or better yet...get a GPS)..&lt;br /&gt;thay cost about the same as one night and a few drinks at even lower quality restaurants.. HINT..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Giant SickoMoore tree is at the traffic light intersection of Nod Road and rte 185, before the light take a north entry into a small driveway that leads down to the river. I dont know if its open yet, if not take a left at the light and you will see us in the dirt turnoff area next to the bridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be going to Curtis Park BY THE RIVER as out take out point and pot luck pickonick, rest, conversation, fire pit area for the rest of the afternoon. So bring some food and beverage.&lt;br /&gt;I dont like food lists..so surprize us...&lt;br /&gt;I dont even know what im briging yet..maybe a fishin pole and we have fish..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The TAKE OUT AND PICkONICK spot.&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;~~&amp;gt;&amp;gt; From the Sicko Moore Tree,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get back onto rte 185 (heading to Hartford) but take the very first left, this is Weatogue Rd, follow Weatogue Road till it intersects with Terrys Plain Road, stay on Terrys Plain Road to the end, it intersects with another road and turns left so stay on Terrys Plain Road till it intersects with Rte 315 right at the bridge..&lt;br /&gt;take a right onto 315, Curtis park is on the right and a smaller part of the park on the left..take the first left dirt road into smaller part of Curtis park, go all the way to the end,,this is our take out point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details to follow if necessary..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available:&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub= Pungo 12'= AL-r and Aelene&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= Gary&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', with Paddle Pants included= Jill&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= BILL&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenland= NDK Greenlander Pro 18' with Greenland paddle= KATHY~G&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Hotub= Canoe 18' this one can hold 3 people pretty easily..maybe more..= Alex and Deanna, Holly and Son..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I  have enough safety equipment and paddles for the above boats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK if you know which kayak fits your paddling style and know its characteristics say so in your comments..&lt;br /&gt;I can only rent kayaks to full yes RSVP's..(limited carry capacity and none can be left on the trailer)..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211923466000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211228691000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Combined Meetup Groups..Farmington River Paddle---Slow Flat Water---</name><id>7969669</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211731200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/7969669/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/c/global_3264476.jpeg</photo_url></item>