<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>244 Thayer Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02912</zip><lat>41.828294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-863-3168 </phone><name>Brown University Bookstore</name><city>Providence</city><id>1030388</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.400684</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>David Hurlehy, Author of The Lost Cyclist will be talking about his book as well as be participating in discussion and Q&amp;amp;A for this Rhode Island Bicycle Coalition event. I'm sure the author would be happy to sign copies if you have already read or are interested in this book. Mr Herlihy is also the author of Bicycle: The History, regarded as one of the best histories of the development of the modern bicycle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lost Cyclist recounts the life and final adventure in the 1890's of Frank Lenz, a bicycle racer and tourer from Pittsburgh, PA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Free Event courtesy of the Author and Rhode Island Bicycle Coalition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Amazon product synopsis (Best Books of June 2010):&lt;br /&gt;[ul]&lt;br /&gt;In the late 1880s, Frank Lenz of Pittsburgh, a renowned high-wheel racer and long-distance tourist, dreamed of cycling around the world. He finally got his chance by recasting himself as a champion of the downsized &amp;quot;safety-bicycle&amp;quot; with inflatable tires, the forerunner of the modern road bike that was about to become wildly popular. In the spring of 1892 he quit his accounting job and gamely set out west to cover twenty thousand miles over three continents as a correspondent for Outing magazine. Two years later, after having survived countless near disasters and unimaginable hardships, he approached Europe for the final leg.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He never made it. His mysterious disappearance in eastern Turkey sparked an international outcry and compelled Outing to send William Sachtleben, another larger-than-life cyclist, on Lenz's trail. Bringing to light a wealth of information, Herlihy's gripping narrative captures the soaring joys and constant dangers accompanying the bicycle adventurer in the days before paved roads and automobiles. This untold story culminates with Sachtleben's heroic effort to bring Lenz's accused murderers to justice, even as troubled Turkey teetered on the edge of collapse. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>On the first floor of the bookstore is a "community" room adjacent to childrens books.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292285798000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290520402000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Author David Herlihy speaking at Brown Bookstore</name><id>15535740</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292281200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/15535740/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/0/global_12002896.jpeg</photo_url></item>