<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Men that share experiences and wisdom to support self-awareness, positive change and transformation. We examine the destructive aspects of the &amp;quot;modern man&amp;quot; and our own personalities that limit us from embracing life fully. We form a community of peers who take risks to improve our lives and help others. All kinds of men are involved. Non-religious and non-profit. Any man ready to follow some simple ground rules and take responsibility for himself is welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This work can have profound positive impacts on families, friendships and communities. Better health, more happiness, less anger, closer relationships with loved ones! Make the change you've been dreaming of. Become more the man you want to be. Create trusting and open relationships with men.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The way we see it, the world really needs men who have courage (heart) enough to get real with one another and work together as brothers. Dominating, chest pounding, 'tough it up' or 'laugh it off' masculinity is a facade that often covers up the truly effective, powerful, compassionate, nurturing, mature man.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosted and facilitated by men from the ManKind Project of New England. Fourth Thursday each month. www.openmen.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Blue and Silver Subaru Legacy</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boysen </member_name><member_id>7527796</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220390712000</updated><rating><average>2.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Men</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>openmen</urlname><id>1200732</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5500030518</group_lon><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216908747000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's a wake up call - improve your life - find community</name><id>8403221</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219962600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/events/8403221/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/d/global_4591725.jpeg</photo_url></item>