<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi to All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some say there are signs the bottom is being reached in some battered markets, especially CA and NV and AZ.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The question I have is, Are We Hitting Bottom Here Yet?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For our next meetup I will research the trends in pricing, sales, time on the market in various communities, as we have done before.  We can compare the results against those of 4 months ago, and 8 months ago, to assess where some markets are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In my short sale work, I can see strong evidence that the effects of the subprime meltdown are abating.  More of those defaulted early.  What I am seeing now is a spread to other markets for preforeclosures.  Because those defaulters are both earning steadily in most cases, and because the programs and options for workouts have grown, more and more are able to save their homes from foreclosure.  That does not have much effect for investor property.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some cannot.  And some are not sure they want to...the values are way down and they may be able to get in for less money in a year or two.  Unemployment is rampant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also have to see the impact of the economic stimulus package as it gets passed, when it gets passed, and how quickly and effectively it will slow the job loss and recession.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These are all subjects we will be exploring at the February 2 meetup.  Please bring your ideas, and the results of your own research and reading.  We should have a GREAT conversation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7-9 PM.  New Horizons in Woburn.&lt;br /&gt;Best regards,&lt;br /&gt;Annie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come in and go down the stairs to our meeting room on the lower level.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236037756000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New Normal RE Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>GreaterBostonREIClub</urlname><id>320990</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Real Estate Investing Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231204410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston REI  Meetup- Are We Hitting Bottom?</name><id>9453833</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233619200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/GreaterBostonREIClub/events/9453833/</event_url></item>