<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;The Harvard Film Archive will be screening two films this month by Kar Wai Wong, the first Chinese director to win the  best director award at Cannes. In The Mood for Love will be the first film I've seen by this director- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wong Kar-wai is undeniably an auteur of striking and salient cinema, standing apart from much mainstream Hong Kong cinema.The sense of history and nostalgia that pervades In the Mood for Love is a signature of Wong?s style and reminiscent of filmmakers such as Alain Resnais, Jean-Luc Godard and Krzysztof Kieslowski. The notion of time is a pervading concept in all of Wong?s films. His preoccupation with capturing time is constantly evident, his camera doting on specific moments and intent on finding difference in repetition. Music is also a prominent and strategic element in all of Wong?s films. Musical repetition is often employed to articulate that which is unsaid or that which cannot be expressed via words and dialogue.  Senses of Cinema&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;In The Mood for Love&lt;/b&gt; 2000 97 minutes&lt;br /&gt;For his first film since the 1997 Hong Kong handover, auteur filmmaker Wong Kar-wai directs this moody period drama about unrequited love that, like his earlier work, swoons with romantic melancholy. Set in a Shanghaiese enclave in Hong Kong in 1962, the film centers on two young couples who rent adjacent rooms in a cramped and crowded tenement. Li-zhen (Maggie Cheung) works as a secretary in an export company while her husband's job at a Japanese multinational keeps him away on extended business trips. Across the hall, Chow (Tony Leung Chiu-wai) works as a newspaper editor and is married to a woman who is also frequently out of town. Neither respective spouse is ever shown in full, instead they are shot from the back or obscured by walls and furniture. Li-zhen and Chow soon strike up a cordial ? if tenative ? friendship. Chow begins to suspect that his wife's long absences are not entirely business related when he stops in unannounced at her office to discover that she is not there. Later, a colleague tells him that he saw his wife with another man. The icing on the cake comes when Chow notices that Li-zhen's handbag is identical to his wife's while Li-zhen discovers that Chow is wearing a tie that she gave her husband; it doesn't take long for them to realize that their spouses are sleeping together. Drawn together by shame and anger, Chow and Li-zhen reveal nothing of their discoveries to their partners. While working through their guilt by imagining how their adulterous spouses first hooked up and rehearsing interrogations, the pair slowly fall in love in spite of their determination to uphold their end of their marital vows. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a review: &lt;a href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/films/2000/10/24/in_the_mood_for_love_2000_review.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bbc.co.uk/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well since you read this far, its only fair to tell you that the HFA is presenting this film for free and its open to the public.  Yahoo!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As is our custom, Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then its off to a local restauarant to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200702527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>In the Mood for Love at the HFA</name><id>7146917</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202256000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7146917/</event_url></item>