<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Landmark Kendall Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>4178182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090599</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Revenge Of The Electric Car&amp;quot; follows 4 larger-than-life entrepreneurs at the forefront of the electric car race. First, there's Bob Lutz -- Mr Detroit himself, the cigar-smoking vice-chairman of GM, who has been making gas-guzzling cars his entire career. He is challenged by Elon Musk (surely you've heard of him!), the young dot-com maverick billionaire who thinks that he can show Detroit how to build cars with his Silicon Valley-based, Linux-driven Tesla Motors. Carlos Ghosn of Nissan-Renault, the desperately smart and ruthless businessman who singlehandedly rescued Nissan from ruin, wants to flood the market with affordable mainstream electric vehicles. And lastly, &amp;quot;Gadget&amp;quot; Abbott, a reverend/designer/engineer is one of thousands of electric car DIY-ers who together may be a force big enough to change the auto industry - and the world - forever. The movie opens at Kendall Sq on November 4 More information can be found at www.RevengeOfTheElectricCar.com PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION: Take the Red Line towards the Kendall/MIT stop. Upon exiting the stop you will see the Marriot Hotel. Go through the lobby of the Marriot Hotel to Broadway. With the Marriot behind you facing Broadway St., make a left and walk down Broadway until you pass over the train tracks. After crossing the train tracks stay on your right until you see Kendall Square on your right. Walk all the way across the Kendall Square courtyard, passing the Blue Room and UPS Store through an arch at which time you will be on Binney St. At that time you will be facing the Kendall Square Garage. We are to the left of the garage.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glenn P DeRosa</member_name><member_id>4460952</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320442877000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Energy Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1402</urlname><id>654497</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Green Business Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319756776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Revenge Of The Electric Car". November MeetUp</name><id>38995852</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320438600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1402/events/38995852/</event_url></item>