<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Old Sturbridge Village Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01566</zip><lat>42.107005</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-347-3362</phone><name>Old Sturbridge Village</name><city>Sturbridge</city><id>669375</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.091484</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The largest outdoor history museum in the Northeast, Old Sturbridge Village portrays the daily life of a rural New England town from 1790 to 1840, with 40 original buildings allowing visitors to get an authentic look at post-colonial America. Bulk up your historical knowledge by roaming into the village's sawmill, law office, district school, and more, while demanding answers about the absence of a historical used horse-and-buggy dealership. Inquirers can listen to the historical interpreters that make the town bustle each day, from the rugged blacksmith to the farmer cultivating the fields. Along with admission to the past, there is a stagecoach ride and riverboat ride. Check the Old Sturbridge Village WEBSITE: &lt;a href="http://www.osv.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.osv.org/...&lt;/a&gt; There are some pretty cool-looking crafting classes that people might be interested in taking. Feel free to sign up and enjoy! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are several restaurants, such as the early New England cuisine at the Oliver Wight Tavern, and picnic tables are also set up for those who prefer to nibble on homemade sandwiches. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're invited to join the fun: play baseball the way early New Englanders did, make a craft, join a game of French &amp;amp; English (left), meet the young oxen in training, try your hand at marbling paper, watch a toy fire-balloon flight, visit the Freeman Farm, stop and see craftsmen at work, and much more.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, September 5: Members of WGBH or WGBY get 2-for-1 adult admission and two kids free. Please show your WGBH or WGBY member card at the Visitor Center.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We may or may not stay together as a group depending on what we want to do and see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTES: Only pouring rain will cancel this event. Cost is $20 unless you bought the recent Groupon. Sturbridge Village is open 9:30 am-5 pm. Sturbridge Village is 59 miles from Boston; if you don't have a car it's probably best that you don't sign up, unless you make your own transportation arrangements. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture and will wear a Meetup button, will be near the entrance at 9:30 am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anna</member_name><member_id>404606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283732342000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281120108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sturbridge Village, Stagecoach Ride, and Riverboat Ride</name><id>14342013</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283693400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14342013/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/d/global_16986189.jpeg</photo_url></item>