<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>306 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.348064</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-888-HARPOON</phone><name>Harpoon Brewery</name><city>Boston</city><id>669000</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.037100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's almost that time of year again! Time for the drinking and the wearing of the green at the Harpoon St. Patrick's Festival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Harpoon:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Kick off the St. Patrick's Day Holiday season in Harpoon style!&lt;br /&gt;-What better place to begin the season than inside the largest brewery in Boston?!?!?!&lt;br /&gt;-Food vendors selling Corned beef &amp;amp; cabbage along with other delicious food&lt;br /&gt;-Cash bars offering a selection of fresh Harpoon and UFO beer featuring Celtic Ale&lt;br /&gt;-Featuring live Irish and Rock and Roll bands from the Boston area&lt;br /&gt;-Come dance the jig, enjoy Harpoon beer, and celebrate St. Patrick!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where is it?&lt;br /&gt;-At the Harpoon Brewery, 306 Northern Ave., Downtown Boston.&lt;br /&gt;-Inside The Brewery amongst the tanks and outside under huge circus tents&lt;br /&gt;-Free shuttles from the South Station area. Departs from behind the Federal Reserve along the Fort Point Channel off Summer Street. Look for the Shuttle Sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Band Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 – 7:00 PM Dicey Riley  (Celtic Rock and Irish Pub Songs)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 – 8:00 PM Colum Cille Pipes &amp;amp; Drums  (Bagpipes &amp;amp; all) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:20 – 10:20 PM Joshua Tree  (Boston’s Premiere U2 Cover Band) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details:&lt;br /&gt;-Cover charge $20.00 and includes a souvenir Pint Cup and one (1) drink ticket (does not include food or additional beers)&lt;br /&gt;-Must be 21 or older and have proper I.D.&lt;br /&gt;-Cash bars serving a selection of fresh Harpoon beer for $5.00 per 16 oz. cup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's usually a coat check (a few $$) so you don't have to lug your coat, etc. around all night. Bathrooms are spot-a-pots, so be prepared!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**I recommend taking the T and leaving your car at home, especially if you're going to drink.  Some say that the beer is stronger than normal, since it comes fresh from the brewery.  Personally, I say it just tastes more fresh!!  Either way, be safe, and plan ahead.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet between 5:30 and 6:00 outside Clarke's. Then we'll head over using the shuttle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP updated so that I know who to look for.  And please also indicate if you plan on meeting us at the Brewery instead of at Clarke's.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299432324000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295985943000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harpoon St. Patrick's Festival 2011</name><id>16182421</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299277800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/16182421/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/3/6/global_12923430.jpeg</photo_url></item>