<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Folks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can join us for an all-day hiking adventure at Bear Mountain in Salisbury, CT, which has a scenic, looping trail and spectacular views! We will meet at 7:45 in Orange.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLAN: The hike will be 6 miles, and should take 4-5 hours.  The Bear Mountain trail has a gradual incline on the way up, then we will stop along the trail to chat and have lunch.  On the way back, we will have to scramble down the mountain, and from there the trail is level.  The hike will be somewhat challenging, and you should have some hiking experience.  The group is planning to go out to eat after the hike.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Meet at 7:45 a.m. (we will converge at the commuter parking lot on Route 34 in Orange). We plan to leave from there, and expect to arrive by 9:45, at the trail entrance in Salisbury. We will stretch, and start hiking at 10 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING: A lunch to eat on the trail, plenty of water and snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.berkshirehiking.com/hikes/bearmt_salisbury.html" target="_blank"&gt; Click here for information on Bear Mountain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dot/LIB/dot/Documents/dtravelroad/orange.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Location of Commuter Parking Lot in Orange, where we will meet at 7:45&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=CT-34+%26+Abbey+Ct,+Orange,+CT+06477&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;dirflg=&amp;amp;daddr=salisbury,+ct&amp;amp;f=d&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=41.308745,-73.03638&amp;amp;sspn=0.007962,0.019312&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=9" target="_blank"&gt;Google map and directions from Orange (commuter lot) to Salisbury&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact us via our &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hiking-575/messages/boards/thread/5584668"&gt;message board&lt;/a&gt; with any questions or concerns, especially if this is your first time hiking with the group. If you need to carpool, are available to drive others, or wish to drive up to Salisbury on your own and need help with directions, please leave a note on the message board.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at Park and Ride commuter lot in Orange, Ct  for carpool/convoy</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah </member_name><member_id>7903956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225724249000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hiking-575</urlname><id>1282762</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Walks in the Woods</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224550312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Haven Early-bird Hiking Meetup</name><id>8999692</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225548000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hiking-575/events/8999692/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/4/global_5981220.jpeg</photo_url></item>