<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&amp;nbsp; we have changed the meeting location to the Walgreens parking lot to avoid parking headaches.&amp;nbsp; Once we all arrive we will place our chairs for the parade, proceed to Captain Carlos for a bite to eat.&amp;nbsp; After dinner we can watch the parade, walk around for awhile then attend the fireworks display.&amp;nbsp; Please keep in mind, that we will be doing ALOT of walking, so please dress the piggies appropriately.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Remember, if you are running late, get lost or can't find us please call the MU cell phone at 978-304-2811.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's go out to Gloucester for a fun night of Horribles in the parade....and maybe some tootsie rolls (yum) and then stay for the fireworks over the Harbor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet in St. Peters square in front of Cape Ann Brewery, walk around, grab a bite to eat and then find our spot for the parade.&amp;nbsp; Once the parade is over we can locate a good place to watch the fireworks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will celebrate our Independence, socialize with friends and I am sure there will be a lot of laughter, joking and fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So grab that bag chair and come on out to Gloucester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember if you get lost, are running late or can't find us, please call the Meetup Cell phone at 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet us at St Peters Square in front of Cape Ann Brewery</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309871384000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308274396000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gloucester Horribles Parade &amp; Fireworks</name><id>22507341</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309723200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/22507341/</event_url></item>