<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>395 River Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01001</zip><lat>42.056824</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413 789-1917</phone><name>Michaels Pasta In The Pan</name><city>Agawam</city><id>988061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.605049</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Below are the fiction and non-fiction selections for October's Meetup.  When you RSVP, please write in which book you think you might read!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fiction:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Life of Pi, Yann Martel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yann Martel's imaginative and unforgettable Life of Pi is a magical reading experience, an endless blue expanse of storytelling about adventure, survival, and ultimately, faith. The precocious son of a zookeeper, 16-year-old Pi Patel is raised in Pondicherry, India, where he tries on various faiths for size, attracting &amp;quot;religions the way a dog attracts fleas.&amp;quot; Planning a move to Canada, his father packs up the family and their menagerie and they hitch a ride on an enormous freighter. After a harrowing shipwreck, Pi finds himself adrift in the Pacific Ocean, trapped on a 26-foot lifeboat with a wounded zebra, a spotted hyena, a seasick orangutan, and a 450-pound Bengal tiger named Richard Parker (&amp;quot;His head was the size and color of the lifebuoy, with teeth&amp;quot;). It sounds like a colorful setup, but these wild beasts don't burst into song as if co-starring in an anthropomorphized Disney feature. After much gore and infighting, Pi and Richard Parker remain the boat's sole passengers, drifting for 227 days through shark-infested waters while fighting hunger, the elements, and an overactive imagination. In rich, hallucinatory passages, Pi recounts the harrowing journey as the days blur together, elegantly cataloging the endless passage of time and his struggles to survive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Non-Fiction:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Endurance, Alfred Lansing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The astonishing saga of polar explorer Ernest Shackleton's survival for over a year on the ice-bound Antarctic seas, as &amp;quot;Time&amp;quot; magazine put it, &amp;quot;defined heroism&amp;quot;. Alfred Lansing's scrupulously researched and brilliantly narrated book--with over 200,000 copies sold--has long been acknowledged as the definitive account of the &amp;quot;Endurance's&amp;quot; fateful trip. of photos and maps. Nationwide traveling museum exhibition. This is a stunning account of the 1914 Antarctic expedition gone to hell. It is clear that the author did an incredible amount of research, and though this book doesn't read like a novel, its presentation is much more powerful this way, giving a panoramic view of the whole terrible and desperate situation of these men.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meagan</member_name><member_id>6521348</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah</member_name><member_id>8272134</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288454495000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279760169000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October's Discussion: Life of Pi and  Endurance</name><id>14175425</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288132200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/14175425/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/b/global_18704395.jpeg</photo_url></item>