<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Possibilities 13 week Group Coaching Program&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;to experience greater harmony, happiness and success and connect to your greater Self &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399 ; font-size : small"&gt;Thursday evenings, October 20th through February 2nd, (excluding 11/24,12/22, 12/29), 7:15 -9:15pm,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399 ; font-size : small"&gt;Roots and Wings, Natick, MA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399 ; font-size : small"&gt;(&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Please do not rsvp through this site. &lt;em&gt;Registration and payment directly with Ann is required to participate in this program&lt;/em&gt;. Registration will close after the first session; and since registrations have been directly with me, it will not show on this site.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Has trying to resolve your problems and find greater happiness on your own been as successful as you&amp;rsquo;d like? Are you reading this book and that book, or listening to this CD or watching that DVD, or listening to large impersonal teleseminars that essentially leave you on your own? Somehow, these aren&amp;rsquo;t as effective as really engaging and learning with others.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly meetups are great for a little of this and a little of that, getting a boost, and staying in the learning game. But if you&amp;rsquo;re still not getting the results and changes you desire, then maybe it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider more.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Can you relate to any of these questions?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Have you settled for resigned acceptance or complacency for how things are, even though you&amp;rsquo;re not fully happy about it?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;If you practice Law of Attraction principles, do you feel like you&amp;rsquo;ve been doing everything you &amp;ldquo;should&amp;rdquo; to get results you want, yet still find yourself frustrated, wondering, &amp;ldquo;Why is this so hard?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Why isn&amp;rsquo;t this working?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Or maybe you know how you&amp;rsquo;re holding yourself back, but you still can&amp;rsquo;t seem to make the necessary changes on your own, no matter what you try.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Would you like to expand in new ways for continued growth and personal evolution, and to open up new possibilities in your life? Life can get better and better!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;If you can relate to any of these, we invite you to join us in our 13 week New Possibilities Group Coaching Program to immerse yourself in a dedicated, comprehensive, over-time learning program led by experts in personal change, combined with the caring support of a consistent, intimate group of peers.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;If you've been to any of our meetups, you've heard us say many times that the way to manifest what you want is to find inner harmony and happiness first. And, being happy is the point of it all, anyway!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Our New Possibilities Group Coaching Program is a comprehensive program that is guaranteed to provide you with proven beliefs and skills for leading a life with harmony, happiness and success.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;We use the powerful model and processes of NLP (Neurolinguistic Programming) to create deep changes you don't have to keep working at, and we integrate it with Law of Attraction principles and spirituality. You'll get personal changes and growth in the areas of your life that matter most to you (work, self-esteem, family, relationships, health, etc.). As Mark likes to put it, it will allow you to easily flow into the future you care about.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Participating in an in-depth personal growth program like this could be one of the most stimulating, happy, fulfilling, expanding times of your life! It has certainly always turned out that way for us. Little compares to the in-person, experiential, embodied learning and changes that can take place for you in this kind of environment. This is what we are offering you.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;It was SO fulfilling to see the positive changes people made in past programs:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Like the two women who firmly believed (and thus experienced) that there were no more good men in their age range or that any man worth wanting wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be interested in them. By the end of the program they were both going out on dates with desirable men and having a great time.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;People began to experience greater peace &amp;ndash; with themselves, in their relationships, and even within potentially very stressful times (like house and money problems).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;They began to get more of what they wanted because they learned how to ask more effectively!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;They made easy behavioral changes, like eating habits, when they learned how to easily reveal and release resistance to change.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;People busted through limiting beliefs, like "I don&amp;rsquo;t have what it takes", that were holding them back in their careers.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;One woman said that how she was when she began the program felt like a different lifetime. She could barely express how much better and freer she felt at the end of the program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Some comments from participants weekly preparation forms:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The most amazing thing about loosening up my stem belief and beginning to see that it isn&amp;rsquo;t true, is a feeling of freedom&amp;mdash;something I have never really felt before. At first I was shocked that I have lived my life based on a false belief, but then I just began to enjoy the freedom. I&amp;rsquo;m sensing a paradigm shift as I am beginning to find myself in moments of great peace, joy, and contentment and see/feel the expanded version of myself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;"I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m gliding along these days, feeling a lot of joyousness and appreciation, and things have been remarkably easy. I&amp;rsquo;d asked for ease and grace, and here it is. Thank you! Occasionally there are some &amp;ldquo;moguls&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; challenging bumps to maneuver, but I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve got momentum and my attitude about the bumps is &amp;ldquo; Ok, let&amp;rsquo;s see how well I can do this one! &amp;ndash; Woohoo!&amp;rdquo; And then I&amp;rsquo;m on to the next."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;"Regarding my work, I have become much more relaxed &amp;ndash; and way more efficient! My brain chatter used to make me so stressed out about tasks I had to do for work. Now I&amp;rsquo;m viewing myself as part of source energy, and not as this powerless worker-ant. I am more confident about my work, and for some reason, I&amp;rsquo;m able to set limits with clients (but not in a bad way, in a way that satisfies everyone). I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting more challenging jobs, and I&amp;rsquo;m tackling the creative piece with more confidence"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;"I'm still enjoying this new underlying sense of stillness and ease (or "harmony!"). I'm discovering a new freedom with respect to others. I feel much less dependent on what others say and do in order to feel good. (YAY!) I feel like I'm really becoming ME -- and that's a huge thing to celebrate."&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;"I feel excited about my future! I feel empowered and capable. I feel smarter and wiser. I feel confident. I love waking up in the morning and feeling that I get to start a new day all over again! How awesome is that?!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;In the largest sense, what has opened up for me is my potential. No longer feeling defective, no longer feeling less than everyone else, no longer afraid to express my voice and be seen, I feel as if the world has opened up for me. I see it as my blank palette upon which I am going to create the most magnificent grand finale of life that anyone has seen yet. Before the class I felt as if I had very few choices; now I feel joyfully overwhelmed by the number of choices available."&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;So what would &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;you&lt;/span&gt; like? Really like. Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to ask, and don&amp;rsquo;t think too small. Mark and I believe you can have all the harmony, happiness and success that you desire; and we would love to partner with you on that path!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;For more curriculum details, testimonials, logistics and current rates ( &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;discounts and a limited number of bonuses for early sign-ups&lt;/span&gt;), go here:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com/programs.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Group Coaching Program&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com/programs.html"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;We restrict the size of the group, so we strongly recommend signing up and setting your commitment now. As you've probably experienced, it's also way too easy to slip into the land of "some day".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;If you're interested, contact Ann at annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com to arrange for a phone call to determine if this is right for you, and, if so, to register directly through her. You must make the full program commitment to participate (recordings of each session will be sent to you in case you have to miss an occasional one); and people will not be allowed to join once we begin. This is part of what will allow the results you desire!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Hope you'll join us to create lasting new possibilities for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Joy to you,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the Wings studio on the first floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323393769000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321026853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Possibilities Group Coaching Program</name><id>pcrpxypqblb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323389700000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/40805792/</event_url></item>