<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>corner of arlington and boston common</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373623</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Arlington st and boston Common</name><city>boston</city><id>7523802</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.178040</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You asked for it so here it is... ice skating on the Common...  &lt;span&gt;Outdoor ice skating at one of the oldest parks in the United States.  After skating we can find a warm bar with warm drinks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT:  We need an assistant organizer for this event as I will be out of town that week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only reserve a space if you plan to attend and have purchased the Groupon below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://s3.grouponcdn.com/images/site_images/2799/0340/RackMultipart20121126-9690-1pk7ufu_grid_6.jpg" alt="Rackmultipart20121126-9690-1pk7ufu_grid_6" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.groupon.com/deals/boston-common-frog-pond?utm_campaign=UserReferral&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=uu4440570" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.groupon.com/deals/boston-common-frog-pond?utm_campaign=UserReferral&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=uu4440570&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since its invention, ice skating has brought us countless thrilling hockey games, scores of inspiring figure-skating routines, and one unforgettable NBA season. Be like Darryl Dawkins in the '82-'83 season with this Groupon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose Between Two Options&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$14 for admission and skate rental for two (up to a $28 value)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$28 for admission and skate rental for four (up to a $56 value) 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prices vary based on age.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Common Frog Pond&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the heart of Boston Common, one of the oldest and most treasured public parks in the US, sits the Boston Common Frog Pond. Although it’s named for the melodious creatures that once dotted the site, today, the pond’s placid surface is the natural habitat of visitors from around the world. The pond changes with the seasons; during the winter, park officials replace the water with ice for skating school and public sessions. During the spring and the fall, visitors cast pensive looks into the reflecting pond; in the summertime, those looks are trumped by the squeals of laughter from children cavorting around the spray pool and carousel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No matter the season, the Frog Pond Café stays open, serving hot cocoa and soups to warm up winter guests, as well as year-round snacks including burgers, hot dogs, iced tea, and juice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359728364000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>40-plus</urlname><id>1222683</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2699966431</group_lon><name>40/50 Something Year Olds - Men &amp; Women Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357099830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ice Skating at Boston Common Frog Pond followed by warm drinks!</name><id>97416192</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359300600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/40-plus/events/97416192/</event_url></item>