<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Southbridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.261272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>877-571-7469</phone><name>Hanover Theatre</name><city>Worcester</city><id>840605</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.803322</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Pecha Kucha is happening at the Hanover Theater in Worcester MA on Sept 26th. It is a free event and involves 8 very talented presenters who share ideas and creative concepts. Check out the web site and please think about coming out and supporting your local artist friends! Disclosure: I happen to be presenting some of my personal photography work at this particular event. So I am hoping folks will come out and support me! I'm very nervous and want to look out into the crowd and see familiar faces!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s the link to Pecha Kucha RSVP - again it's a free event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventsbot.com/events/eb662036061" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eventsbot....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please use this link when inviting your friends and family, and promoting online. It will help us plan for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info you may need:&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available all around the area: Franklin Garage is right across the street, and the Worcester Public library parking lot is right behind the building. We recommend the library parking as there’s plenty of spots and will be free and well lit at that time of night.&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 7:20 for and hour of drinks and mingling- &lt;b&gt;GREAT Networking Opportunity!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presentation start at 8:20&lt;br /&gt;There will be a cash bar and light refreshments served.&lt;br /&gt;This event is co-sponsored by ARTSWorcester and The Hanover Theatre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are some really fun and interesting events happening in Worcester in Sept and I hope you'll check them all out.... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285603335000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283262004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What is Pecha Kucha? Come and Find out!</name><id>14603013</id><headcount>180</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285542900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/14603013/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/5/9/global_17620441.jpeg</photo_url></item>