<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>An informative, fun and free evening is planned! A variety of complementary therapies will be discussed in an informal setting. These therapies may be used for relaxation, stress management, problems with pain, anxiety, attention, control of habits and more.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Energy therapies including Reiki, Yoga as therapy, meditation and Pranic Healing will be discussed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, learn about the many applications of hypnosis including weight loss, smoking cessation, control of habits and more.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6-9 pm  THERE IS NO COST FOR THIS EVENT - BRING A POTLUCK DISH TO SHARE. &lt;br /&gt;Soda, hot tea and cookies will be provided. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Thomas School of Hypnosis,  50 Bridge St., Manchester, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming from the North or South&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming from the north into Manchester take 293 South. If you are coming     from the south, take 293 North. From 293, take Exit 6 (Amoskeag Bridge). Follow signs that say “to Bus. Dist. 3”. This will bring you to Elm Street. Take Right onto Elm. Continue down Elm Street.  You will pass Orange street on your left. You will notice green parking lot signs.  Next street is Pearl.  Turn Left unto Pearl and it will bring you into the parking area.    Park on the South side of the lot.  You will see the back of 50 Bridge Street. Take stairs or elevator to 3rd floor.  We are in Suite 303.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming from the seacoast or Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take 93 to exit to 101/293 north. After the bridge (over the river), you will continue right unto 293 north. From 293, take Exit 6 (Amoskeag Bridge). This will bring you to Elm Street (Bus. Dist. 3). Take Right onto Elm. Continue down Elm Street.  You will pass Orange street on your left. You will notice green parking lot signs.  Next street is Pearl.  Turn Left unto Pearl and it will bring you into the parking area.   Park on the South side of the lot.  You will see the back of 50 Bridge Street. Take stairs or elevator to 3rd floor.  We are in Suite 303.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297210102000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>travel-575</urlname><id>418980</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Old and Not so Old Ladies Travel</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294711171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Complementary Healing Therapies</name><id>16001968</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297206000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/travel-575/events/16001968/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/2/global_20742722.jpeg</photo_url></item>