<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>So, folks,  here's the intro to our current project,  It's very much a work-in-progress for most of us!  Some of us have only begun, others are in the midst of the creative process, and some are just beginning, so feel free to join us.  You'll be able to start your box, and be inspired by the possibilites!  You can continue on your own, or come to the next Meetup...This project will probably continue for another month or two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'We're exploring the possibilities of altered boxes...come and join the excitement! Think Joseph Cornell, or Michael DeMeng; think altered shrines, museums, theatres, antique stores...or create something new...whatever you can imagine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our studio group has acquired a generous supply of old wooden boxes, formerly used to sort buttons in a retail store. These are roughly 14&amp;quot; long, by 6&amp;quot; across, by 3&amp;quot; deep...(I haven't actually measured them, but will later today...then we'll see how accurate my estimate is!) There are also many small cardbard boxes that fit inside as dividers. A few of the wooden boxes are already gessoed, and ready to work on; many are still in their original unfinished state. We'll make one of these available to you at the meetup, along with the space, and some additional shared tools and supplies, and lots of shared inspiration, discussion and laughter! (Additional boxes may be available for a reasonable fee.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, gather up all those bits and pieces that you've saved ... bring your own supplies, ideas and creativity, and come share the fun.'&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the side door, it should be propped open. We are at the top of the stairs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pamela</member_name><member_id>1042340</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>emelengy</member_name><member_id>4250560</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256246281000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Creative Types</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>assemblageart-29</urlname><id>748373</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Altered Art and Assemblage Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236019580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wooden Boxes...continuing to explore the possibilities!</name><id>9861300</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237741200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/assemblageart-29/events/9861300/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/1/global_4071601.jpeg</photo_url></item>