<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;...[this] film will make you think twice about spending money you don't have.&amp;quot; - Robin Clifford, Reeling Reviews &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Maxed Out doesn?t really offer solutions, probably because there are none. But it does a great job of showing how the rich get richer and the poor foot the bill, plus interest.&amp;quot; - Richard Roeper&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Given that James D. Scurlock's documentary Maxed Out is a resolutely uncinematic progression of talking heads -- and they're talking about a subject most of us would rather not even think about -- it's a remarkably entertaining film.&amp;quot; - Andrew O'Hehir, Salon.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maxed Out is a documentary about the consumer debt crisis made up of interviews with creditors, debtors, academics, and others. The main premise of Maxed Out is that banks and other creditors deliberately market to people who are more likely to have problems paying and that the creditors benefit from connections to government, the debt collection industry, and from lawmaker apathy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is directed by James Scurlock in an effort to raise awareness about the ways credit and lending issues are affecting out society. Americans for Fairness in Lending (AFFIL) was consulted in the making of this film and has organized screenings of the film around the country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maxed Out has gotten mixed reviews, but I think this is a particularly timely topic given the state of the US economy. I'm looking forward to the discussion afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is about an hour and a half long, meaning that we will get out at 7:30. This means that we can go out for tea or Thai food (depending on what people are in the mood for) and still be done by 9.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a meetup sign at the front of the theater when the movies over.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216332405000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214533837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maxed Out: Serious Matters of Life and Debt</name><id>8225117</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216159200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8225117/</event_url></item>