<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>HBA Boston- A Conversation with John Maraganore: Crossing boundaries – across an IPO and from bench to CEO&lt;br /&gt;When:              Thursday, January 20, from 5:30 p.m. to 9:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:             Alnylam Pharmaceuticals&lt;br /&gt;                        300 Third Street&lt;br /&gt;                        Cambridge MA 02142&lt;br /&gt;Website:           &lt;a href="http://www.hbanet.org/home.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hbanet.org...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This year Healthcare Businesswomen’s Association (HBA) Boston general programming will explore the boundaries of our healthcare industry via a set of four programs that highlight dramatic personal and organizational stories where boundaries are successfully crossed.   The “Crossing Boundaries” season begins with the story of a CEO who took a company from privately held to publicly traded. This is a great opportunity for HBA members to engage in a conversation with John Maraganore, CEO of Alnylam Pharmaceutical.  After receiving his Ph.D. from the University of Chicago, John Maraganore went on to work as a scientist at The UpJohn Company, ZymoGenetics, Inc., and Biogen, Inc.    At Biogen, Dr. Maraganore invented and led the discovery and development of Angiomax™.  After joining Alnylam in 2002 as CEO, John successfully maneuvered the intricacies of taking Alnylam from a privately held start up therapeutics company to a publicly traded company at the forefront of RNAi therapeutics.  John will discuss his journey in taking Alnylam public, including the challenges, surprises and benefits encountered along the way.  In addition, John will also discuss his career path that led him from bench scientist to CEO.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295567376000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292990317000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Crossing boundaries – across an IPO and from bench to CEO</name><id>15796134</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295562600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15796134/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>