<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>943 Namquid Drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02888</zip><lat>41.741898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-572-3390</phone><name>Game On!</name><city>Warwick</city><id>1111698</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405803</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Bring your friends and join in the fun as we celebrate the return of the beloved fan-favorite world Dark Sun, a campaign setting of harsh survival and savage enemies in a blasted land.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dark Sun release features three products designed to give you a wealth of new options for your Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons game to get immersed in the world of Athas, whether you’re a player or a DM. The Dark Sun Campaign Setting gives you new character options and background on the Tyr Region, including two new playable races (mul and thri-kreen), new class builds and themes, and a host of setting-specific feats, equipment, and magic items. The Dark Sun Creature Catalog features hundreds of new monsters ready for battle and information on the dreaded sorcerer-kings that control the civilized lands. Marauders of the Dune Sea introduces you to the world of Dark Sun with a 32-page adventure taking you on a journey through the desolation of the Tabelands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just for participating you’ll take home the pregenerated character sheet of the character you played. If you DM the game, you’ll take home the adventure itself, a poster map of the encounter areas, and the tokens used in the adventure. To satisfy your curiosity, here’s a quick description of the adventure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lost Cistern of Aravek &lt;br /&gt;A remarkable device has been discovered in the wastes near the city-state of Tyr – a magical cistern created by a long-dead preserver named Aravek. You are charged to journey through the harsh desert lands, brave fierce monsters, and retrieve the cistern before your enemies can claim it for their own cruel master. Can you bring a font of live-giving water to a parched populace? Or will you succumb to dangers beyond the gates of Tyr? A Dark Sun adventure for 4-6 pregenerated 4th-level characters.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanios</member_name><member_id>4187193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282744052000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280376258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worldwide D&amp;D Gameday:  Dark Sun</name><id>14249243</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282410000000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/14249243/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/f/global_6578223.jpeg</photo_url></item>