<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>256 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 647-4000</phone><name>Watch City Brewery</name><city>Waltham</city><id>669403</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236840</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Been a member of this Meetup but never attended any events? Here's a great opportunity to change that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We really want to meet all the folks whose names and pictures we see on our Meetup, but whom we have yet to meet in person. The &lt;a href="http://www.watchcitybrew.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch City Brewing Company in Waltham &lt;/a&gt;is a great informal location, ideal to mix and mingle and relax at the end of the week. So come along and have a fun and friendly Friday evening with everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Watch City:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 128 North/South, take Exit 26 (Rt 20 East). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Rt 20 East for approximately 1 1/2 miles (7 lights) through downtown Waltham until you see Sovereign Bank on your right. Take that right onto Moody Street. Follow Moody Street until the second set of lights. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch City is directly on the left at the intersection of Moody and Pine. There is parking (free after 6 PM) behind the restaurant. Just take the left at Pine Street and the second left after the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you prefer public transportation, the Waltham Commuter Rail Station is just off Moody Street, approx. 2 blocks away from Watch City [&amp;quot;staggering distance&amp;quot; according to some of the locals ? :)].&lt;br /&gt;Waltham is on the Fitchburg Commuter Rail line, fourth stop after leaving from North Station in downtown Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: &lt;br /&gt;Be careful where you park in Waltham. &lt;br /&gt;Make sure you park in one of the Municipal Parking lots, or in the Watch City parking lot (which is FREE from 6pm onwards). &lt;br /&gt;If you happen to park in the lots in front of or behind the Enterprise Car Rental Agency on Moody Street, your car WILL be towed. It is big bucks and a lot of hassle to retrieve your card from the Tow Yard (I speak from personal experience!).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn L</member_name><member_id>3649230</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marie A</member_name><member_id>4623326</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216591432000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>The beer is great, the food is great &amp; the company is great!</why><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215279273000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mix &amp; Mingle at Watch City Brewing Co.</name><id>8281621</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216418400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/8281621/</event_url></item>