<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In December we’ll meet on the third Thursday of the month at Chaibo in Fitchburg to discuss &lt;i&gt;The Other Boleyn Girl&lt;/i&gt; by Philippa Gregory.  By then it may no longer be pumpkin whoopie pie season, darn it – but they’re sure to have other holiday treats like eggnog latte, spiced hot cider and maybe even gingerbread whoopie pies, along with their many other coffees, teas, baked goodies and yummy gelato flavors. Take a break from your holiday shopping and hang out with us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a description of the book from Publisher’s Weekly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Sisterly rivalry is the basis of this fresh, wonderfully vivid retelling of the story of Anne Boleyn. Anne, her sister Mary and their brother George are all brought to the king's court at a young age, as players in their uncle's plans to advance the family's fortunes. Mary, the sweet, blond sister, wins King Henry VIII's favor when she is barely 14 and already married to one of his courtiers. Their affair lasts several years, and she gives Henry a daughter and a son. But her dark, clever, scheming sister, Anne, insinuates herself into Henry's graces, styling herself as his adviser and confidant. Soon she displaces Mary as his lover and begins her machinations to rid him of his wife, Katherine of Aragon. This is only the beginning of the intrigue that Gregory so handily chronicles, capturing beautifully the mingled hate and nearly incestuous love Anne, Mary and George (&amp;quot;kin and enemies all at once&amp;quot;) feel for each other and the toll their family's ambition takes on them. Mary, the story's narrator, is the most sympathetic of the siblings, but even she is twisted by the demands of power and status; charming George, an able plotter, finally brings disaster on his own head by falling in love with a male courtier. Anne, most tormented of all, is ruthless in her drive to become queen, and then to give Henry a male heir. Rather than settling for a picturesque rendering of court life, Gregory conveys its claustrophobic, all-consuming nature with consummate skill. In the end, Anne's famous, tragic end is offset by Mary's happier fate, but the self-defeating folly of the quest for power lingers longest in the reader's mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be sitting at the big couches closest to the door. See you there!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292636998000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290366017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - The Other Boleyn Girl by Philippa Gregory</name><id>15517649</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292544000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/15517649/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/8/global_19784744.jpeg</photo_url></item>