<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Orange St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304375</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-772-2709</phone><name>ARTSPACE</name><city>New Haven</city><id>227951</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.925056</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>5-8 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CWOS Grand Opening Reception&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     We'll be kicking things off the right way with an opening bash for our Festival Exhibit at Artspace, 50 Orange Street, New Haven!&lt;br /&gt;    Wine and light refreshments will be provided, and DJ Nate Dizzy of EULA  will provide a soundtrack as eclectic as the works and installations on display. We're especially grateful to our reception sponsor, the Opici Wine Company of Connecticut.  Artspace -  In Gallery 3, Bernd Krauss has constructed his Hortus Conclusus, a situational site-specific installation comprised of materials culled from our basement. In Gallery 4 contains Deploy Black, a new series of works by Meredith Nickie exploring scenes of subjugation. Dwell by Ilona Anderson is a series of drawings assembled into fragmented wall installations intended to simultaneously disorient and engage the viewer; it is on view in Gallery 5. Finally, in Gallery 7, Taryn Wells' Inbetween Worlds uses the self-portrait to explore themes of race and identity. These exhibits will be on display until October 30.&lt;br /&gt;    And in case you missed them, there are still two exciting installations on display from this past summer. Particular Heights is an interactive, site-specific installation in the Lot at Chapel and Orange, developed by artists Paul Theriault and Siebren Versteeg. Tag and Repeat X2 is the collaborative project of master artist Cat Balco and the Summer Apprentice program, and it is on display in both the Lot and the Long Wall of gallery. These will be on display until October 30, too!&lt;br /&gt;    While you're in the neighborhood, be sure to check out two exciting satellite events. The first is Micro-Fest!, hosted by our neighbors at &lt;b&gt;Project Storefronts&lt;/b&gt; where demonstrations and musical performances will be ongoing from 5 pm - 8 pm. The second is &lt;b&gt;WPKN's ArtFest 2010 Preview Party at Erector Square&lt;/b&gt;, from 7 pm - 10 pm. ArtFest 2010 takes place at Erector Square in tandem with City-Wide Open Studios' first weekend.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285598398000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283389728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>City Wide Grand Opening Reception</name><id>14626424</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285362000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/14626424/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/2/d/global_17650141.jpeg</photo_url></item>