<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ok, Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;I hope you are ready to hit the water for real..&lt;br /&gt;I already have with the ConnYak'ers&lt;br /&gt;This is event is especially made for the Recreational and Beginner Paddlers. Experienced paddlers are welcomed and would inspire the beginners..&lt;br /&gt; All we are going to do is introduce paddling to the beginners, teach a few rescue routines, paddle float entry, a T rescue, and maybe something else..&lt;br /&gt;then padle around the lake and see whats new on the lake..&lt;br /&gt;The other thing is to socialize on the beach and water, try out each others kayaks to see what might be a better fit to us..etc... Maybe the Shady Glenn Rest for their Famous Cheeze Burger, I never had one yet in 30 years..but i like their ice cream..anyway thats something to talk about then...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I chose both and or one day because Kevin may have a hike that i want to go to or some of you might want to go on too..&lt;br /&gt;I like doing both and would like to integrate both if possible...&lt;br /&gt;The bolton notch (5 minuts away is a good place  for a hike) before the event..or after for that matter...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update the event details as the time gets closer.. rain ..exact time etc.. but i like to hit the water about 10:30/11:00 am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;There is a easy to reach boat launch right off of rte 44 in Bolton that has plenty of parking and PortaPotties at the parking lot (they should be there by then). Further to the east on the lake is a beach area that would be an excellent place to sit in the sun eat some snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;Rte 384 E to Bolton Notch &lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (left part of fork) rte 6 is to the right &lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light. &lt;br /&gt;The next light has the boat launch to the left and a church to the right. &lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area. &lt;br /&gt;I carry my kayak on a old sailboat trailer so im easy to spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case of moderate rain, It might be best to wait till a better weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be safe and bring your Personal Floatation Devices if you have some...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have some cheap ones and a few  different kinds of kayaks for those who dont have one...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178549230000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176403845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Recreational Paddle Event of the Season, BOLTON LAKE Apr 5 and/or 6</name><id>5663755</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178376300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5663755/</event_url></item>