<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;5:30-6:50 Premeeting - Daytraders Group led by Eric from Vermont&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 7:10 Announcements and Polls, led by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;7:10 - 8:45 Macro Trends by Harlan &lt;br /&gt;8:45 - 9:00 One Indicator by Herb&lt;br /&gt;9:00 - 9:30 Prospecting Using Investors.com led by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;Special Talk by Harlan on Macro Trends&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     We are now in the midst of an unprecedented upheavel in our economy. Many people have lost a great deal of money. Many are confused.  &lt;br /&gt;           There are numerous opinions about how we got here and who is responsible. Even more questions about what the future will look like. The environment going forward will be quite different from the one we all know and it is imperative to plan properly in order to survive the coming economic challenges.&lt;br /&gt;              Harlan has been studying this debacle in great detail and will give his insight on the situation. Harlan will explain how we got here, where we are currently, and where we are most likely headed. He will also talk strategy and investment ideas for the coming decade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members value discussion highly. We try to pack as much discussion as possible. Expressing ideas and sharing knowledge is paramount to our members.&lt;br /&gt;All levels of expertise are welcome. No question is too simple - as a matter of fact the simplest question often evokes the best discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newcomers gather at the podium during the 8:00 break to learn about the group. Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you talk stocks with someone then bring them with you!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Virtual Trading game is up and running!&lt;/b&gt; Directions are at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/browse_thread/thread/ff5e030eb15a6c7c/7dab7a5592adbc28?lnk=gst&amp;amp;q=simulator#7dab7a5592adbc28" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Please be sure to choose a name that we can identify with you! Otherwise it is anonymous!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own investment decisions! Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232313978000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>72</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229908860000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Business Daily Tuesday Meetup</name><id>9373750</id><headcount>104</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231891200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9373750/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>