<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>34 Hanover St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.078057</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 431-5904</phone><name>High Hanover Parking Garage</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1004792</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.758043</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Hello Everyone, Please come and join us for a beautiful ride from Portsmouth NH, to the Nubble Light in Cape Neddick, Maine then over to Mount Agamenticus and back to Portsmouth...&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave Portsmouth at approximately 10:30 am go over the Memorial Bridge past Badgers Island and through Kittery.. Passing by the historic Portsmouth Navy Ship Yard as we go... We will then ride up Rte 103 past many historic landmarks riding through York Village along the Maine seacoast... At this point we will see the Historic Nubble light in the distance to our right...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When we arrive at Nubble light you can stop and walk around a bit if you like, but then we will go up the hill so I can introduce you to one of my very favorite Ice Cream Stands...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From there we will ride through the famous York Beach (watch for traffic) and ride towards Mount Agamenticus.. Those of you up for a challenge can ride to the top... those of who want to skip the challenge will wait...it's about two miles up and back...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From there will head back towards Portsmouth on the beautiful back roads of York, Elliot, and Kittery....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The average speed of this ride is 12-15 miles per hour. The terrain is mostly small rolling hills (Except for Mount A).  If it's Windy it can be difficult to push against the wind.  Road bikes are highly recommended, I do not recommend the use of mountain bikes on this route. Helmets are required. Please be sure to bring plenty of water and sunscreen.&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;****Please contact Cyndi if you can be a co-leader on this ride, I would love to have someone go out with the faster riders, and a sweep with the slower riders. My email is cpariseau81@hotmail.com*****&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since I'm sure we will all work up an appetite, after were through we will go to the Weathervane on Badgers Island for a bite to eat.  They have a beautiful deck right on Portsmouth Harbor. The meeting time for this ride is 10am leave promptly at 10:30 am.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please only sign up for this ride if you are sure you can go.. If you are unsure and you sign up you are preventing other members who can go from signing up.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We shall meet outside the main entrance of the Hanover St parking garage, there is a restroom inside and it costs 75 cents an hour to park in the garage.  I would not recommend parking on the street since most of the meters are two and four hour meters and Portsmouth Parking police are terrible.  If the ride is cancelled, I will post it on the meetup website by 8:45 am.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Portsmouth, NH  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take Interstate 95 heading North   &lt;br /&gt;2. Take Exit 7 from Interstate 95.   &lt;br /&gt;3. Turn east toward the ocean on Market Street. Downtown Portsmouth is one mile. (At the fork, the Sheraton Portsmouth, stay to the left.)   &lt;br /&gt;4. For the main parking garage, the High-Hanover Garage, turn right at Hanover Street.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also that evening there is a Fireworks cruise leaving from Portsmouth Harbor at 6pm... I run another meetup and there are many of doing that cruise... I will post another page about that. too.. with more details..&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting all of you and enjoying this great day! Thanks, Cyndi  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will congregate to the right of the main entrance/ my # is 781-856-2933</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cyndi</member_name><member_id>3604417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278522130000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277436584000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portsmouth, NH to Nubble Light and Mount Agamenticus, 35-38 miles</name><id>13905574</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278165600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/13905574/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/3/global_15948851.jpeg</photo_url></item>