<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rt 125</address_2><address_1>1250 Osgood St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01845</zip><lat>42.718580</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-531-0500</phone><name>Beijing Restaurant</name><city>North Andover</city><id>288058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.112320</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE 1/21/2011:  Here in North Andover/Haverhill the snow has stopped, the sun is shining and the roads are fine.  With that said, this event is still on.  If you feel that you will make the decision not to attend please change your rsvp as soon as possible so we can finalize the reservation.  If you were not planning on coming but would like to come, you are more than welcome please rsvp. Hope to see everyone at the Beijing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: black"&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE 1/20/2011:  Snow is a coming and MeetupStormCast245 is on the lookout!!!!   No seriously, as of right now we are keeping this event on the calendar.  Around 2pm tomorrow we will be going out to see the conditions on the local streets and will make a decision whether to cancel or not.  We will email an update no later than 4 pm tomorrow on whether this event will take place or not.  So please, before leaving for the event, please check your email for the event update.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's go out to North Andover and check out the New Beijing Restaurant.  The Beijing was taken over by new owners, they added a buffet and a Teppanyaki Grill.  The food is great and reasonably priced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can either take in the buffet, sit at the Teppanyaki grill or sit at a regular table.  It will be a good time to socialize and enjoy some really good Chinese Food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be taking in the Karaoke after dinner, please go to that event to RSVP separately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming for dinner, watch their website and local coupon books as they frequently have very good coupons to bring in business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be closing this RSVP on January 19, so that we can make a reservation.  Please include in your RSVP whether you want to sit at the Teppanyaki grill or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, its that time of year, bad weather will cancel this event.  The organizers will make every attempt to do so early enough so that you can plan accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember if you have to cancel at the last minute, get lost or are running late, please call the meetup phone and let us know.  The meetup phone number is 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change and don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at the New Beijing&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup Table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295878069000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292979434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner @ the New Beijing Restaurant</name><id>15794496</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295654400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15794496/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/f/global_20408383.jpeg</photo_url></item>