<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The New Haven Hiking Group is helping to clean up the Invasives at Hammonasset.  Its good to give back to the trails and this system is really lovely at all times of the year.  I believe Hartford Area Hiking could lend a hand.  I am told that there is good food (I do not know if there is a fee for food) and the opportunity to meet like minded hikers.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Help us &amp;quot;Free Willy!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, January 4th, 2009, 10 a.m. – 12 noon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hammonasset Beach State Park&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Willard's Island (&amp;quot;Willy&amp;quot;), at Hammonasset Beach State Park, is being taken over by invasive plants! Oriental bittersweet is crowding out the native trees, reducing valuable food sources for birds and other wildlife. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Menunkatuck Audubon Society is hosting a work party!&lt;br /&gt;BYO: Loppers, Hand Saws, and Work Gloves&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Willard's Island trail entrance, located at the far left end of Nature Center parking lot, at 9:45am.&lt;br /&gt;Hot Drinks, Chowder &amp;amp; Chili will be available at the Meigs Point Nature Center for all volunteers afterward, and Door Prizes will be awarded!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a repeat event that was very successful and rewarding for all last year!  Hope you can come help.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231252693000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230827537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Invasive Plant Clean up, Hammonasset Beach State Park, Madison, CT</name><id>9418687</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231079400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/9418687/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>