<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>563-565 Broad Street </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.761799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>the Studio @ Billings Forge</name><city>Hartford</city><id>846300</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.686790</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I went to one of these events this past Monday and really thought it was wonderful!  The event begins with an open mic and then showcases guest readers. There are refreshments served, socializing, and a lot of talent.  And it is free!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taken directly from the Word Forge site &lt;a href="http://wfreadings.blogspot.com/:" target="_blank"&gt;http://wfreadings.blo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday June 14, 7pm—Suzanne Frischkorn and John Surowiecki&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suzanne Frischkorn is the author of Girl on a Bridge (2010) and Lit Windowpane (2008) both from Main Street Rag Publishing. In addition she is the author of five chapbooks, most recently American Flamingo (2008). A 2009 Emerging Writers Fellow of The Writer’s Center, her honors also include the Aldrich Poetry Award, and an Artist Fellowship from the Connecticut Commission on Culture &amp;amp; Tourism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.suzannefrischkorn.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.suzannefri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Surowiecki is the author of three collections of poetry, Barney and Gienka (CW Books, 2010), The Hat City after Men Stopped Wearing Hats (Word Works, 2007) Watching Cartoons before Attending a Funeral (White Pine Press, 2003), as well as five chapbooks. His Tapeworm Comics, a narrative poem in comic book form, has recently been published by Ugly Duckling Presse. In recent years, John has won the Poetry Foundation Pegasus Award for verse drama, the Pablo Neruda Prize and took the silver in the last Sunken Garden National Competition. He is presently working on a new collection called The Catbird as Robert Browning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus Open Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;For more information, contact:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jim Finnegan&lt;br /&gt;JforJames@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;860-508-2810&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://wfreadings.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://wfreadings.blo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WordForge Readings: A poetry reading series featuring local poets along with an open mike. Many readings will have a theme. All events will be scheduled for Monday nights, with a 7 p.m. start time. Location: The Studio @ Billings Forge, 563 Broad Street, Hartford, CT 06106. Parking available next to Firebox restaurant or along Broad Street. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly S</member_name><member_id>2538500</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276694216000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274362889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Poetry Reading at Billings Forge</name><id>13541754</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276556400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13541754/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/d/global_6743869.jpeg</photo_url></item>