<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 E Hollis St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.757860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 595-2222 </phone><name>Giant of Siam</name><city>Nashua</city><id>485419</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463500</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The membership has voted! The July Restaurant of the Month is Giant of Siam. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Korapin Sueksagan, who co-owns Giant of Siam with her husband Sawat, states that Thai food is light, and ranges from not spicy to very spicy. People need to try it and understand. The food has been misrepresented.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To that end, Korapin stresses the nutritional value of Thai food and the fact that they will customize any entrée for the customer's health needs or taste desires. There is very little oil in Thai cooking and absolutely no MSG at Giant of Siam. Broths, herbs and spices are used for flavoring, rendering a very healthy meal. Korapin and her staff of family only use the finest of ingredients, there are no powders, and the basil, mint and other herbs are all fresh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Korapin Sueksagan came to the United States in 1980 in order to pursue a career in economic planning. When she found that she wasn?t particularly enamored with the field, she chose to indulge in her lifelong interest of cooking Thai food. She became employed at New England?s first Thai restaurant, ?Bangkok Cuisine? in Boston. There, she met the owner?s brother, Sawat, who later became her husband.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Korapin and Sawat, along with Korapin?s cousin, Chai Senabunyarithi, decided to try their hand at opening a Thai restaurant in Nashua. Thus, Giant of Siam opened in January of 1988. Korapin?s cousin eventually left the business, but her two sisters, nieces and nephews who help to cook, serve and operate the business continue to make it a family affair. Korapin and Sawat also offer the same wonderful food, service and atmosphere at their popular Manchester restaurant, Lakorn Thai.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Preparing food and serving it to family and friends is second nature to the Sueksagans. They want all of their customers to feel that Giant of Siam is a second home. There is nothing that is too much trouble for the staff to accomplish. They will cook to order - well-done, very mild, spicy, you name it. Vegetarians make up approximately 20% of their customer base, and they enjoy the creativity that serving vegetarians allows. Anything on the menu, anything, can be made vegetarian, stresses Korapin. All that they need to do is to let us know. She notes that tofu is a wonderful substitute for meat, vegetable broth is a great flavor additive and that there is a large variety of mixed vegetables to tempt the vegetarian palate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The seafood dishes at Giant of Siam are out of this world. The prices, as with all of the entrees, are more than reasonable, and the fish is the finest available. If I see a good piece of fish and it's expensive, I buy it. I don't make money off of it, but I make the customers happy and they will come back. Hot and Sour Soup is the signature soup of Giant of Siam. It has a wonderful variety of flavors that warms even the soul.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Korapin would also like to make her customers aware that their 140-seat restaurant can accommodate small parties, business meetings and luncheons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again, there is enough on the menu to please all and a relaxed atmosphere to make a business meeting flow smoothly. Everything on the lunch and dinner menu is also available for takeout.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To those who are still afraid to try Thai, Korapin stresses that if you like Chinese, you will love Thai. It's lighter, healthier, and at Giant of Siam, with all of the options open to you, it's a lot of fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eating &amp;amp; Drinking: Open for lunch and dinner.Alcohol is not served. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nashuatelegraph.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/20030301/SECTIONS010503/31223011/-1/SECTIONS0105" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nashuatele...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Menu:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.menupix.com/nashua/menu.php?id=610096" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.menupix.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next Month: To Be determined by the poll&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216681990000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215297487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dining Event: The Southern New Hampshire Restaurant of the Month Club July Meetu</name><id>8283137</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216508400000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8283137/</event_url></item>