<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>After doing an amazing job introducing us to the Enneagram of Personality, Herb Pearce will teach us about the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description of the workshop from Herb: &amp;quot;Learn about the 16 types of the Myers-Briggs. Learn whether you are an introvert or Extravert; Sensor or iNtuitor; Thinker or Feeler; and Judger or Perceiver. This system gives as much information as the Enneagram to understand personality differences and improve relationships.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it. Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit has been set. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce ******&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce, M.Ed., has been teaching personality systems for 20 years and has been a psychotherapist for 30 years, having worked with thousands of individuals, couples andfamilies, as well as teams in corporations and agencies.  Author of The Idiot's Guide to the Enneagram, he has also taught the Myers Briggs to unlock keys to the mystery of our uniqueness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239406697000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236711474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Myers-Briggs</name><id>9924722</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238799600000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/9924722/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/0/4/global_7624356.jpeg</photo_url></item>