<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Auburn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.345868</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newton/Auburndale Park and Ride</name><city>Newton</city><id>774415</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.246553</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For those not heading out of town for the Columbus Day weekend, we'll be fleeing Beantown Saturday and Sunday in exploration of the Fall Fair(e)s north and south of the city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today it's Topsfield, the oldest Agricultural Fair in America.  It's State Fair-ing at it's best, complete with a chick hatchery, oxen pulls, and the infamous &amp;quot;Birds of Prey&amp;quot; show.  Seriously, with all due respect to the Big E, nothing screams state fair like pig races, and you'll be able to get your fill come Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the events at their website: &lt;a href="http://www.topsfieldfair.org/tour%20the%20fair.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topsfieldf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out Saturday's schedule at: &lt;a href="http://www.topsfieldfair.org/2008%20Daily%20Schedules/day%208.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topsfieldf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $12.00 for admission, and there is a $8.00 charge per car for parking.  Hence, we'll be doing some carpooling, and will plan on meeting at the Newton Auburndale Park and Ride just off the Mass Pike and 95.  Scroll down to the Newton/Auburndale Park and Ride for directions off this website: &lt;a href="http://www.masspike.com/pdf/maps/pnr-maps.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.masspike.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For any of our northern positioned folks, my car will also be making a stop at the logan express Peabody lot for pick-up.  The positive is, less driving and more company for the ride.  Negative is, $11 per day, which is slightly more than fair parking.  If you are interested in meeting us, please email me directly at doclmeet@yahoo.com.  You're going to need to mapquest directions, but here's the site:&lt;a href="http://www.ctps.org/proto/7_links/1_getting_around/1_park_and_ride/p/peabody.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctps.org/p...&lt;/a&gt;  We'll probably be arriving there between 10:30 and 11 depending on how fast we make it out of Newton.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There may be some discounts for advance purchases, but best I can tell, it involves a trip up there to the ticket office.  Lemme know if you're going:-).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at 10 a.m. at the park and ride, and then plan on traveling up 95 to Topsfield en masse :-).  Will send out my cell phone closer to the date so any interested North Shore members can meet us there, and to facilitate finding each other in Newton.   There are only 35 spots available at the park and ride, so we may do a little pre-fair carpooling to the West Newton Park and Ride.  We'll see:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Jeff Corwin show that morning was not part of the plan, but if folks are really interested, contact me directly and we'll see about adding it in.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, contact Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223993434000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222512732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Topsfield Fair Day</name><id>8843669</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223733600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8843669/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>