<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>690 Asylum Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.772090</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>The Hartford Financial Services Group Plaza</name><city>Hartford</city><id>243433</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.699715</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the 25th anniversary Walk Against Hunger and we hope you can join us to make it the biggest and best Walk ever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can sign up online by doing the following:&lt;br /&gt;--Go to &lt;a href="http://www.foodshare.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.foodshare.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Click on the Walk Against Hunger logo&lt;br /&gt;--Click on &amp;quot;join us&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;--Fill out the walker registration page (be sure to remember your user name and password so you can come back later to check progress!)&lt;br /&gt;--Click on &amp;quot;join an existing team&amp;quot; and look for &amp;quot;Gloria's Glorious Gang&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now you can create your own personal web page as part of the event and use it to send e-mails out to friends and family asking them to support you, which they can do right on the web site with a credit card.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also raise money the old fashioned way with checks and cash.  If you need a paper brochure, send me an e-mail with your snail mail address and I'll get one out to you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that, although I usually organize dog-friendly hikes, dogs are NOT allowed at the Walk Against Hunger.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, feel free to e-mail me through the site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gloria's Glorious Gang team will be made up of a mixture of Hiking and other Meetup friends, Tall Club friends, and other friends and family.  I hope you will join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+++++++++++++++++++&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the registration table first and sign in and then look for us on the hill between registration and the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212951879000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>With every $30 raised, Foodshare can provide enough food for a hungry person for an entire month!  If you can raise $600, the Chase Family Foundations will match it, doubling your money!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205958626000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk Against Hunger</name><id>7564976</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209920400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7564976/</event_url></item>