<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Eliot St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138-5706</zip><lat>42.372280</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(617) 354-0999</phone><name>International House Of Pancakes</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>282500</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121800</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The actual marathon starts on Saturday, April 5th at 10:00pm and runs until Sunday at 11:00am.  All survivors can join us back the IHOP for more coffee, pancakes, and discussion if you are still awake and sane!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THESE ARE THE &amp;quot;BOMBS&amp;quot; THAT HAVE BEEN DROPPED ON US AS OF MARCH 24TH: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE BIG BIRD CAGE (1972) dir Jack Hill w/ Pam Grier, Anitra Ford, Candice Roman, Teda Bracci, Carol Speed, Karen McKevic, Sid Haig&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though not a sequel to Jack Hill's 1971 The Big Doll House, this entertaining women's prison epic plays all the same cards as the original drive-in hit and helped cement the clichés that similar films went on repeating for years. The Big Bird Cage is more dramatically sound than most WIP (Women In Prison) films, and while it isn't quite as sadistic as some, there's no lack for feral action and its tastelessness is tongue-in-cheek. -Fred Beldin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more of the Fred Beldin review, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.allmovie.com/cg/avg.dll?p=avg&amp;amp;sql=1:5371~T1" target="_blank"&gt;The Big Bird Cage Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GALAXINA (1980) dir William Sachs w/ Dorothy Stratten, Stephen Macht, Avery Schreiber&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Galaxina is definitely worth 80 minutes of your time. It's a pleasant surprise in the sense the film is as witty and disarmingly silly as it is. -Joseph Bensoua&lt;br /&gt;For more of the Joseph Bensoua review, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.dorothystratten.com/Galaxina_Reviews.html" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxina Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LITTLE RED RIDING HOOD AND THE MONSTERS (1962) dir Roberto Rodriguez / K. Gordon Murray &lt;br /&gt;(also known as:  CAPERUCITA Y PULGARCITO CONTRA LOS MONSTRUOS)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LITTLE RED RIDING HOOD AND THE MONSTERS is a treasure of dark fantasy. CAPERUCITA Y PULGARCITO CONTRA LOS MONSTRUOS is more bizarre, imaginative, harrowing and grotesque than any other film ever made expressly for children. -kgordonmurray.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more of this review, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.kgordonmurray.com/f09.html" target="_blank"&gt;Little Red Riding Hood and the Monsters Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE MANITOU (1978) dir William Girdler w/ Tony Curtis, Susan Strasberg, Michael Ansara, Stella Stevens, Ann Southern, Burgess Meredith&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 1978 adaptation of a popular Graham Masterson novel is one of the most genuinely bizarre films to emerge from the late-'70s horror boom. Sadly, it is also one of the most unintentionally humorous and dull films from that era.- Donald Guarisco&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more of the Donald Guarisco review, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.allmovie.com/cg/avg.dll?p=avg&amp;amp;sql=1:31325~T1" target="_blank"&gt;The Manitou review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POOR WHITE TRASH (1957) dir Harold Daniels w/ Lita Milan, Peter Graves, Timothy Carey&lt;br /&gt;(also known as: Bayou)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No reviews for this film at this time. I?m sorry.  For a synopsis, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.allmovie.com/cg/avg.dll?p=avg&amp;amp;sql=1:31325~T1" target="_blank"&gt;Poor White Trash synopsis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;SPICE WORLD (1997) dir Bob Spiers w/ The Spice Girls, Alan Cumming, Richard E. Grant, Hugh Laurie, Stephen Fry, Elvis Costello, Elton John, Bob Geldof&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the late '90s, the Spice Girls not only became an international pop sensation, but they decided to star in their own movie like the Beatles before them. Even though Spiceworld: The Movie lacks a coherent plot and structure, it is still an energetic and mildly amusing parody of fame, fortune, and the music industry. -Adam Goldberg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more of the Adam Goldberg review, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.allmovie.com/cg/avg.dll?p=avg&amp;amp;sql=1:160114~T1" target="_blank"&gt;Spice World review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INCOMING!!!! YET ANOTHER &amp;quot;BOMB&amp;quot; DROPPED UPON US JUST IN TIME FOR APRIL FOOL'S DAY!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE BLOOD OF DRACULA'S CASTLE (1969) dir Al Adamson &amp;amp; Jean Hewitt w/Alexander D'Arcy, Paula Raymond, Gene Otis Shayne, Jennifer Bishop&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I must admit, I adore most of Adamson's &amp;quot;so bad it's good&amp;quot; cinema, but BLOOD OF DRACULA'S CASTLE is so bad, it's just plain bad. A really boring film that makes you wonder if they were aiming for comedy with the sub-Munsters dialog and stereotypical horror characters. -George R. Reis&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more of the George R. Reis review, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.dvddrive-in.com/reviews/e-h/horriblehorrors2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;The Blood of Dracula's Castle Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about this event in general, click here: &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/080405.html" target="_blank"&gt;Schlock Around the Clock 2008 information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The above list is only a fraction of what we are seeing during this marathon. There will be other films posted, I am sure.  I will let you fine people know when I know. Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walter&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be sitting at a table with a pot of coffee in one hand and meetup sign in the other.  If you can not make it to IHOP, I'll raising the sign at the Brattle.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Walter</member_name><member_id>3779246</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207615264000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205362037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bad Movie Marathon at the Brattle</name><id>7520449</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207441800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7520449/</event_url></item>