<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Parking charge</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>There is a level walk from the parking area on Cherry Hill Road, off Route 157, to the brink of the falls. A trail system connects the falls with the main swimming/picnicking area and other scenic areas of the park. From a stone bridge used by the Colonel, the trail passes through densely wooded areas, the Little Falls and several meandering streams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There appears to be a $7.00 parking fee. Not sure as I have never been there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet in the parking area at 10:00 am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Driving Directions:&lt;br /&gt;    From Hartford area: take I-91 south onto Route 9 south. Follow Route 9 south to Middletown. Take Middletown – Meriden Exit 15 onto Route 66. Stay on Route 66 through Middletown for 6-7 traffic lights – look for the signs Wadsworth Falls State Park and Route 157 at a traffic light near a Walgreen’s Pharmacy. Take a left onto Route 157. Stay on Route 157. Wadsworth Falls State Park will be on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    From New Haven area: take I-91 north onto Route 66 (Middletown – Meriden Exit 15). Follow Route 66 towards Middletown. Look for the signs Wadsworth Falls State Park and Route 157 on the right. Follow Route 157 to Wadsworth Falls State Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    From Westbrook/Shoreline areas: take Route 9 north onto Route 66 (Middletown – Meriden Exit 15). Follow Route 66 through Middletown for 6-7 traffic lights. Take Route 157 off Route 66 near a Walgreen’s Pharmacy. Stay on Route 157 to Wadsworth Falls&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/wadsworth.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/wadsworth.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1131559672000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wadsworth Falls</name><id>4797383</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1131894000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4797383/</event_url></item>