<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This trail leaves from the Downes Brook parking area just east of Passaconaway Campground and 13.5 miles west of Conway on the Kancamagus Highway. The trail takes you to the summit of Mt. Hedgehog (2520'). The grade is moderate and only the final sections require a little extra effort. The advantage in taking the loop in a clockwise direction is to view the Presidential Range and Mt. Washington as you reach the summit from the South. &lt;br /&gt;Hedgehog is strikingly shaped with Allen's Ledge on the north, and the huge East ledges on Little Hedgehog. The vantage point from Allen's Ledge, located 1.1 miles up the west fork of the trail, affords remarkable views of Mt. Passaconaway, Mt. Chocorua, the Moats, the presidential Range, the Carrigain Range, and many other eastern peaks. On a clear day even the observatory on top of Mt. Washington is visible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essential Info &lt;br /&gt;Mileage: &lt;br /&gt;4.8 miles compete loop &lt;br /&gt;east ledges 2.0 miles &lt;br /&gt;Hedgehog summit 2.9 mile &lt;br /&gt;Difficulty: Easy to Moderate &lt;br /&gt;Loop elevation range: 1250'-2532'&lt;br /&gt;Estimated time: 5 hours&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be prepared for winter conditions.  No cotton clothing is allowed.  Some type of foot traction is required (e.g. crampons, microspikes, etc).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in a black four door Toyota Echo with Maine plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232982570000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228318890000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOUNT HEDGEHOG</name><id>9272806</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232809200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9272806/</event_url></item>