<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Charles and Beacon St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>681695</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069439</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;CROSSLISTED WITH BOSTON HAPPY HOUR and SOCIAL FUN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time to take a break from all the trivia nights and drink fests to give a little back over the Memorial Day Holiday.  The &lt;strong&gt;Massachusetts Military Heroes Fund&lt;/strong&gt; is planting 33,000 flags at the Soldier and Sailors Monument on the Boston Common to represent every brave Massachusetts service member who gave his or her life defending our country since the Civil War.  There are opportunities to help with their festivities throughout the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOWEVER,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this MeetUp is to help &lt;strong&gt;TAKE DOWN&lt;/strong&gt; the flags beginning at 6pm on Monday, May 28th.  With enough volunteers, this shouldn't take much time at all.  We could all pitch in and then go somewhere nearby for some food and drink after we are done.  PLEASE RSVP here AND also fill out a Volunteer Registration Form at &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massmilitaryheroes.org/community-building-events"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;http://www.massmilitaryheroes.org/community-building-events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;You can list MeetUp as the organization with me (Isabel Bourelle) as team captain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, there are opportunities to volunteer with the Massachusetts Military Heroes Fund throughout the weekend, including planting the flags on Weds 5/23, attending the name reading ceremony on Thurs 5/24, and to help with shifts to watch the flags over the weekend.  Information on their entire weekend events can also be found on the above link.  I also have an email that I can forward to interested parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance for any help you can lend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll figure out a way for us to meet once the date nears</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338297640000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335983019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Help Massachusetts Military Heroes Fund AFTER Memorial Day Weekend festivities</name><id>63119892</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338242400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/63119892/</event_url></item>