<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Columbus Av</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.872567</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-724-7300</phone><name>McCoy Stadium</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>1184423</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.371834</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>11.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!  THIS IS A JOINT MEETUP.  A fantastic game to watch!  www.pawsox.com I bought 8 tickets.  They are in Section 6 Red Seats second level behind home plate! I am in Row BB (2nd row) Seats 5-8 and the ones up for grabs are in Row CC (3rd Row) Seats 5-8.  How cool is that!  And to boot the tickets are only $11 each plus $2 to park.  Very limited free parking near the stadium.  And yes I said only $2 to park.  UNBELIEVABLE!  But it is true!  I remember going to a game and it turned out it was just before Ellsbury and Paplebon got called up to Boston.  Who will be next?  Could be someone from this game.  You never know :)  HOW TO GET TICKETS: RSVP yes.  Then send me an email to see if the tickets are still available.  (I have this posted to 3 meetup groups).  If I email you back with a yes, then you must PROMPTLY send me a check or money order for the tickets.  Chris Lorant PO Box 3581 Edgartown, MA 02539-3581.  They are face value.  I am eating the cost of the service charge.  I will in turn mail you the tickets.  FAILURE TO DO SO WILL RESULT IN ME CHANGING YOUR RSVP TO A NO AND REOPENING THE RSVP TO OTHERS.  SORRY TO BE THIS WAY, BUT I HAVE GOTTEN STIFFED ONE TO MANY TIMES. THE FIRST 3,000 FEMALES TO ENTER THE PARK GET A FREE T-SHIRT.  Park opens 2 hours before game time.  We will meet at our seats.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at seats</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Slammer</member_name><member_id>9179551</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281291555000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265568593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paw Sox/Yankee Tickets!</name><id>12543992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281286800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/12543992/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/7/global_12983319.jpeg</photo_url></item>