<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Actual address is 550 but wrong on Google</address_2><address_1>550 Peverly Hill Rd.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.049259</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 431-2334</phone><name>Seacoast Family YMCA</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>874846</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.778389</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I have reserved the Seacoast YMCA pool in Portsmouth NH for 3 Sundays in a row starting November 22nd from 3 - 6pm. These kayak pool sessions will provide you an opportunity to practice or learn safety skills including wet exiting, self and assisted rescues, bracing and rolling techniques. This is a self paced &amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;learn on your own&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot; format there will not be any formal or professional instruction however there will be others there to give you tips and assistance as well as spot people practicing rolling. Cost is $25 per person based on a minimum of 12 people attending. If less then 12 people attend the cost will be slightly more. I do need to collect the money in advance to insure full attendance for each session. I'd also like to keep the number of people between 12 - 15 per session. If anyone wants to attend as a spotter and helper without your kayak you can do so free of charge. However if you want to participate in the session as well as bring your kayak you'll have to pay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will bring your own kayak, PFD, Paddle etc.. Please be sure your kayak is very clean inside and out.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Once again the dates are..&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Sunday November 22nd&lt;br /&gt;    Sunday November 29th&lt;br /&gt;    Sunday December 6th&lt;br /&gt;          &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP for each date to let me know which dates you'd like to attend and please send a check for $25 per session made payable to me at my address below. Either write on the check or send a note with check indicating which date/dates you plan to attend. I'll be sending out more info as well as directions to those who sign-up.&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Neil Sheehan&lt;br /&gt;    763 Ocean Boulevard&lt;br /&gt;    Hampton, NH 03842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in parking lot 15 minutes before session begins</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259445670000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258143523000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Kayaking Safety, Bracing &amp; Rolling Skills - Portsmouth YMCA 3-6pm</name><id>11868357</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258920000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/11868357/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/c/6/global_7263782.jpeg</photo_url></item>