<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>325 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01940</zip><lat>42.511207</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-592-1010 </phone><name>Bostonville Grille</name><city>Lynnfield</city><id>731588</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.008321</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let’s meet up at the Bostonville Grill to watch what might be a NLDS or NLCS preview.  The game starts at 7:10 pm est. so let’s aim to meet at 7pm.  I will be wearing my cubs hat and be by the bar which is to your left as your enter the Bostonville Grill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For information on Bostonville Grill please visit their web site at &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonvillegrill.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonvill...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to my work schedule it will be difficult for me to pick anyone up at the T before the game, but if you need a ride and want to watch the game with other Cub fans please email me as I am sure there is someone you can carpool with or pick you up at a T station. After the game I will be happy to get people back to a T line if needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let’s go cubs!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Sox fans are welcome)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bostonville Grill is located on the northbound side of Rt1 in Lynnfield.&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming south on Rt1 from the Danvers area, you will have to turn around and head back north at the Walnut Steet Exit (take Walnut Street exit towards Lynn).&lt;br /&gt;Heading northbound on Rt1 beyond the Walnut Street exit, The Bostonville Grill is located before the next Rt1 exit.&lt;br /&gt;While heading north on Rt1 you will pass Polcari's, Dunkin Donuts, the Naked Fish and then you will be very close.&lt;br /&gt;There driveway is just beyond the Kelly Nissan dealership.&lt;br /&gt;Print out a map on their website or use the &amp;quot;driving directions&amp;quot; link on their web site for further help.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223587415000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Chicago Sports Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Chicago-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1195793</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Chicago Sports Club of New England</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221710948000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cubs vs. Mets</name><id>8781270</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222383600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Chicago-Sports-Club/events/8781270/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/8/global_4543928.jpeg</photo_url></item>