<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>As I usually host this event in January, I would LOVE to be able to just get together and talk over some delicious chinese/thai food/drinks and get to know everybody. I also thought an &amp;quot;unloved&amp;quot; elephant yankee gift swap would be a fun idea for the group as of course, everybody LOVES presents!!!! (who doesn't, right????)...... So here are the details: &lt;br /&gt;        A. We will play the traditional yankee swap gift exchange game the same way, HOWEVER, this time around it will be the present you received this past holiday that was &amp;quot;NOT&amp;quot; your favorite pick.&lt;br /&gt;        B. The gift range MUST be 10.00-15.00 minimum (okay to go a little more if necessary). &lt;br /&gt;        C. Also, the gift must be something a guy/girl can appreciate. &lt;br /&gt;        D. Please have the gift either wrapped or in a gift bag as of course we don't want it to be visible during the game. &lt;br /&gt;        E. If you don't feel you have an &amp;quot;unloved&amp;quot; gift from the holidays, I am sure there is that &amp;quot;unloved&amp;quot; present somewhere you got for your birthday or another occasion.       &lt;br /&gt;     I personally have done this type of gathering in the past with my own set of friends and you would really be in for a treat as there WILL be a lot more trading going on at this swap as everybody would traditionally go for that Borders gift card!!!!!, right????....... &lt;br /&gt;     I had made arrangements with the restaurant to have the gifts placed in an area for when it is time for us to play the game.       &lt;br /&gt;       If people did want to continue hanging out afterwards, there is the Charles Play House  very close by as they do have karioke available, however of course I will leave that optional. &lt;br /&gt;     There is plenty of parking around and the location is very T accessable if you are coming by public transpertaion. &lt;br /&gt;     Also the limit is 20 attendees. If the list is full, please write a note in the &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; section saying you would like to attend if there is an opening and I will see what I can do. &lt;br /&gt;     Lastly I would appreciate it if you are going to sign up as a &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to please be 90 percent sure you are going to attend. (as I did have RSVP'ing problems in my Scrabble group) (Please read my note on the message board explaining)....   &lt;br /&gt;     I am looking foward to a fun evening and meeting everybody!!! My e mail is always open if any more questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please meet at the hostess area as I will have balloons/red meet up shirt on</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>krista</member_name><member_id>3604506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265589561000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1958</urlname><id>1096649</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge and Boston Singles Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264879341000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PF Changs friday night dinner/Unloved Elephant "Unloved" Yankee Swap </name><id>12468378</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265416200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1958/events/12468378/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/8/global_3699192.jpeg</photo_url></item>