<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>USNH</name><city>Hamden</city><id>180814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us Saturday, September 29 at 4PM when Henry Auer will speak on global warming. Henry will give an informal presentation open for discussion with participants. This meeting is intended especially for those without a scientific background. Henry will introduce the greenhouse effect and discuss whether recent warming is man-made. In addition to talking about the causes of global warming, Henry will cover economic consequences of rapid warming. The meeting will include questions and answers and a group discussion. Henry believes it is important to act to overcome the bitter political stalemate that immobilizes the federal government on this and related issues. Henry is a seasoned scientist with many years in research and development, both in the biotechnology industry, and earlier, as a medical school faculty member. Most recently, until he retired in 2010, he was a patent agent focusing on biotechnology. Since 2010, Henry has become active in global warming and related environmental issues, including publishing his Global Warming Blog at &lt;a href="http://warmgloblog.blogspot.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://warmgloblog.blogspot.com/&lt;/a&gt; . Henry has an A.B. in chemistry from Princeton, and he earned his Ph.D. in biochemistry from Harvard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start with coffee and snacks from 4PM until 4:30PM, which will be followed by Henry’s presentation and a group discussion. You are encouraged to bring a snack to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sholem</member_name><member_id>445389</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348962970000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347278926000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Global Warming: The Facts And The Issues--A Discussion With Henry Auer</name><id>81694702</id><duration>9000000</duration><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348948800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/81694702/</event_url></item>