<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Daniela Stark &lt;br /&gt;KidknowsTM Outdoor Thermometer&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, June 3, 2009&lt;br /&gt; Daniela is the inventor and developer of the Kidknows™ Outdoor Thermometer, a thermometer that empowers kids to choose the right clothing for various outdoor temperatures even if they are not old enough to recognize numbers and understand the concept of measuring the outdoor temperature. As they continue using their thermometer, kids can learn to read numbers and to understand the concept of measuring the outdoor  temperature. One advantage is the elimination of the morning power struggle between parents and  children over appropriate clothing by providing parent and child with a pictorial reference of how cold or warm it is outside. &lt;br /&gt;Daniela is using the experience she acquired as she worked for years as an independent consultant for various medical and consumer products companies from her home in Andover MA.  Before staying home with her kids, Daniela was an IDSA Award winning industrial designer working for Product Genesis Inc. and Arthur D. Little Inc. She founded DHS Design LLC, an industrial design consulting, product development company, and owner of the Kidknows trademark in early 2009.&lt;br /&gt; Daniela will describe the steps and the decision-making processes she has taken in developing her product and making the transition to selling it.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the SEC Education Room 1st Level</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Cormier</member_name><member_id>6323188</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249510454000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238629776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Innovators' Resource Network June Meetup</name><id>10092629</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244069100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/10092629/</event_url></item>