<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Woodbury Ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.074732</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-431-8000</phone><name>Holiday Inn</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>688110</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.778262</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event will be the staging of a fake picket line to protest Shaheen's support of the new &amp;quot;card-check&amp;quot; union law that would make it much easier to intimidate fellow employees into joining a union...the ballots would go from secret, private voting to the &amp;quot;card-check&amp;quot; method preferred by union thugs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Water, coffee, small sandwiches and even cigarettes will be provided to anyone wishing to join the picket line.  The focus of this particular event is on the labor issue and signs will be provided, but you are free to protest her other issues such as (&amp;quot;Tax Machine Shaheen&amp;quot;, her signing of the state-wide property tax, her support of the income tax, etc.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is expected that the media will be present at this event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further information please contact &lt;a href="mailto:aedemers@gmail.com" target="_blank"&gt;Andy Demers&lt;/a&gt; at 603.703.1633.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Employee Free Choice Act (EFCA)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;What is the Employee Free Choice Act?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Employee Free Choice Act (EFCA) is a bill that labor unions are working to make into federal law in 2009. It would rewrite the rules of union organizing to get rid of employee private-ballot voting. These rules would unfairly favor organized labor without regard to the true preferences of employees or employers ? all to help unions bolster their sagging membership numbers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If EFCA becomes law:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Union membership will swell nationwide. Andy Stern, head of the Service Employees International Union (the fastest-growing union in the country), says of his Change to Win union coalition: &amp;quot;If we pass the Employee Free Choice Act, these unions will grow by 1.5 million members a year, not just for five years but for 10 to 15 straight years.&amp;quot; Explosive growth for unions means economic stagnation the likes of which the United States has not seen in decades.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to talk about EFCA:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;First, mention that the name &amp;quot;Employee Free Choice Act&amp;quot; is actually a misnomer, as this legislation would actually encourage the use of FORCE and INTIMIDATION in union elections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mention that private voting is an essential part of our democracy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring to the readers' attention that the politicians who oppose private ballots were themselves elected by a private ballot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some employers voluntarily allow &amp;quot;card-check&amp;quot; unionization. Where this has occurred, employees suffer from the same intimidation and coercion from union officials that union officials accuse employers of perpetrating.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Many Democrat politicians are taking pro-union and pro-labor PAC money in return for their support of this legislation, which would empower unionization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214168836000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213907408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Picket Line Protest for Jeanne Shaheen</name><id>8174704</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213995600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/8174704/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>