<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>January 19, 2010 When Angels Speak: Understanding the Angel Financing Process&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston angel investing scene has become remarkably sophisticated in the past decade. Not only has it grown absolutely as individual wealth has been created locally, but it has also become more organized. While one can only guess at the number of active individual angel investors, there are well over 20 self-described angel investing groups in the Metro Boston area representing hundreds of members. Nonetheless, the idiosyncrasies of the angel investing world guarantee that there is no single protocol that governs the angel investing process, and no first-time entrepreneur can be faulted for being somewhat confused at the often conflicting criteria, styles, personalities, and philosophies that define the angel investing landscape.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The January 19th EntreTech Forum will focus on understanding the local angel investing landscape and how and why angel investors make the decisions they do. The EntreTech Forum will also bring together entrepreneurs who have actually raised angel funding and get their take on the steps they took as they attempted to raise the capital they needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;Hambleton Lord – Angel Investor &amp;amp; Managing Director: Launchpad Venture Group&lt;br /&gt;Joe Caruso - Angel Investor &amp;amp; President, Bantam Group&lt;br /&gt;John Martino, Independent angel&lt;br /&gt;Mark C. Terrell - President and CEO, SepSensor&lt;br /&gt;Ann Raider, CEO, InStream Media&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hambleton Lord – Managing Director: Launchpad Venture Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hambleton (Ham) Lord has over 25 years experience in the software industry founding and building industry leading companies. Currently, Ham is the Managing Director of Launchpad Venture Group. Launchpad is a Boston-based angel group that focuses on seed stage technology companies. He manages the group's deal flow, due diligence and investing activities. Ham is an active angel investor and advisor to early stage companies. He is a board member for Building Engines and a board observer for EveryScape.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ham's senior management experience was in the software industry, most recently as co-founder and Vice President of Marketing for Advanced Visual Systems (AVS). AVS develops software for scientists and engineers involved in applications such as Medical Imaging, Geographic Information Systems(GIS), Engineering Analysis and Oil&amp;amp;Gas Exploration. Muse Technologies acquired AVS in 2000. Prior to AVS, Ham helped launch two computational chemistry companies, MicroChem Technologies and Polygen. These two companies were pioneers in the development of software for drug discovery, and were part of an industry wide acquisition roll-up that resulted in Accelrys Inc. (NASDAQ: ACCL).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ham graduated magna cum laude with a degree in computer science from Brown University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Caruso - Angel Investor; President, Bantam Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the last 20 years Joe has served as mentor, coach, and personal advisor to numerous CEO’s and entrepreneurs...dealing with issues of strategy, leadership, team building, venture capital, deal structure, exit strategies, and matters of personal growth. In recent years, he has served as investor and active director with numerous companies…public and private. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe has served as interim CEO for companies in need of strategic change and has served as personal advisor to numerous company presidents. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe is a Director and active investor in Boston MicroMachines and i2Chem. He is currently a member of CommonAngels, eCoast Angels, and a Managing Partner of Brookwood Partners, and was previously a principal in Walnut Venture Associates, all investment groups for early stage companies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe is past-president of the National Association of Corporate Directors (New England Chapter), a member of the advisory board for the Boston University Photonics Center and Northeastern University's School of Technological Entrepreneurship. Joe has served as a Charter Member of TIE Boston (The Indus Entrepreneur), a global not-for-profit organization dedicated to the advancement of entrepreneurship. Joe is recipient of the Leadership in Private Corporate Governance award from the National Association of Corporate Directors New England Chapter. He is a graduate of Northeastern University (BSEE with honors) and the Harvard Business School (MBA).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark C. Terrell, President and CEO, SepSensor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As CEO of SepSensor, Mark has raised millions of dollars from angel investors to back his groundbreaking sensor company, which uses patented sensor technology to mitigate hazardous waste (fats/oils/greases) spills from restaurants and related food service companies.  Mark has experience in leading and advising a number of technology based organizations.  Prior to SepSensor, Mark was COO of Sionex Corporation, a VC backed company producing chemical and biological sensors using a MEMS based technology.  Mark was also a co-founder and VP of Radiometers of Inframetrics, Inc. a company producing spectral radiometer instruments and night vision systems; currently part of FLIR Systems.  Mark has designed and sold products in the electro-optical and thermal sensors market and successfully managed sensor companies for over 25 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark has an electrical engineering degree and certificate in advanced engineering study from Cornell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Organizer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fairbairn – Managing Principal: Fairbairn Ventures&lt;br /&gt;Andrew is an investor, entrepreneur and advisor who partners with driven entrepreneurs to rapidly prove out value propositions and to build solid businesses. Prior to establishing Fairbairn Ventures, Andrew was a founding partner of JVKellyGroup, Inc. (JVKG), a New York-based management consulting, performance management and software development firm recently sold to D&amp;amp;B. He has also served as Vice President of Deutsche Bank, focused on corporate venturing in financial technology companies and strategic planning roles in New York and London. Andrew began his career with UBS Securities in New York, where he worked on global networking and telecommunications industry financings, across a range of geographies and investment banking product disciplines. &lt;br /&gt;Andrew earned his B.A. in Economics and M.A. in International Development Policy from Stanford University. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Cost:&lt;br /&gt;$25 public, $10 students&lt;br /&gt;and active military; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEETING LOCATION&lt;br /&gt;Emerging Enterprise Center at &lt;br /&gt;Foley Hoag the Bay Colony Corporate Center&lt;br /&gt;1000 Winter Street, Suite 4000 (North Entrance)&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Georgia</member_name><member_id>6917121</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 7170621</member_name><member_id>7170621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264117368000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249668075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>When Angels Speak: Understanding the Angel Financing Process </name><id>11059263</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263943800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/11059263/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_4560057.jpeg</photo_url></item>