<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>395 River Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01001</zip><lat>42.056824</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413 789-1917</phone><name>Michaels Pasta In The Pan</name><city>Agawam</city><id>988061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.605049</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;Glenn Beck's Common Sense: The Case Against an Out-of-Control Government, Inspired by Thomas Paine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In any era, great Americans inspire us to reach our full potential. They know with conviction what they believe within themselves. They understand that all actions have consequences. And they find commonsense solutions to the nation's problems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One such American, Thomas Paine, was an ordinary man who changed the course of history by penning Common Sense, the concise 1776 masterpiece in which, through extraordinarily straightforward and indisputable arguments, he encouraged his fellow citizens to take control of America's future -- and, ultimately, her freedom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nearly two and a half centuries later, those very freedoms once again hang in the balance. And now, Glenn Beck revisits Paine's powerful treatise with one purpose: to galvanize Americans to see past government's easy solutions, two-part monopoly, and illogical methods and take back our great country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From a single, abbreviated life grew a seemingly immortal line of cells that made some of the most crucial innovations in modern science possible. And from that same life, and those cells, Rebecca Skloot has fashioned in The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks a fascinating and moving story of medicine and family, of how life is sustained in laboratories and in memory. Henrietta Lacks was a mother of five in Baltimore, a poor African American migrant from the tobacco farms of Virginia, who died from a cruelly aggressive cancer at the age of 30 in 1951. A sample of her cancerous tissue, taken without her knowledge or consent, as was the custom then, turned out to provide one of the holy grails of mid-century biology: human cells that could survive--even thrive--in the lab. Known as HeLa cells, their stunning potency gave scientists a building block for countless breakthroughs, beginning with the cure for polio. Meanwhile, Henrietta's family continued to live in poverty and frequently poor health, and their discovery decades later of her unknowing contribution--and her cells' strange survival--left them full of pride, anger, and suspicion. For a decade, Skloot doggedly but compassionately gathered the threads of these stories, slowly gaining the trust of the family while helping them learn the truth about Henrietta, and with their aid she tells a rich and haunting story that asks the questions, Who owns our bodies? And who carries our memories? --Tom Nissley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave</member_name><member_id>5826846</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meagan</member_name><member_id>6521348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296102508000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287357113000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January: Glenn Beck's Common Sense and The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks</name><id>15140356</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295998200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/15140356/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/e/c/global_20995516.jpeg</photo_url></item>