<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Gail Mazur and Tom Sleigh&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, January 31, at 7 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pierre Menard Gallery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10 Arrow St., Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A reception follows. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gail Mazur’s recent book, Zeppo’s First Wife: New &amp;amp; Selected Poems, (Chicago, 2005) is winner of the 2006 Massachusetts Book Award, a finalist for the 2005 Los Angeles Times Book Prize and for the 2006 Paterson Poetry Prize. She is author of 4 earlier books of poetry, Nightfire, The Pose of Happiness, The Common, and They Can’t Take That Away from Me ( University of Chicago Press ), which was a finalist for the National Book Award in 2001.  She is Writer in Residence at Emerson College and Founding Director of the Blacksmith House Poetry Series in Cambridge , a weekly poetry reading series she ran for 29 years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mazur is a fellow in poetry at the Radcliffe Institute for Advanced Study 2008-2009, and was a fellow at the Bunting Institute of Radcliffe College, and the 2005 recipient of the St. Botolph Club Foundation’s Distinguished Artist Award. An interview with Mazur about her work is online at The Atlantic.  She and her husband, the artist Michael Mazur, live in Cambridge and Provincetown , Massachusetts , where she serves on the Writing Committee, the Board of Trustees, and the Summer Prog ram Committee of the Fine Arts Work Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Sleigh's books include After One, Waking, The Chain, The Dreamhouse, Far Side of the Earth, Bula Matari/Smasher of Rocks, and a translation of Euripides' Herakles. His book of essays, Interview With a Ghost, was published in spring, 2006, by Graywolf Press. His most recent book of poems, Space Walk (Houghton Mifflin, 2008), was published by Houghton Mifflin in spring 2007. Among his many awards are the $100,000 2008 Kingsley Tufts Award, the Shelley Prize from the Poetry Society of America, an Academy of Arts and Letter Award in Literature, an Individual Writer's Award from the Lila Wallace/Reader's Digest Fund, and grants from the Guggenheim Foundation and the National Endowment for the Arts. He teaches in the MFA Prog ram at Hunter College and lives in Brooklyn .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pierremenardgallery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pierremena...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233876312000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233007891000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading by Gail Mazur and Tom Sleigh</name><id>9606607</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233446400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/9606607/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/5/global_187765.jpeg</photo_url></item>