<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hopkinton State Park is less than an hours drive from Boston.   I've gone swimming here several times but never actually walked it.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hopkinton State Park is located in the towns of Hopkinton and Ashland and includes the picturesque Hopkinton Reservoir and contains 1450 acres. The park offers a variety of year round recreational activities including 2 life guarded swimming beaches, stocked fishing, 1 reservable group picnic site (see Split Rock below), 12 tree shaded, first come first served, picnic areas (300 picnic tables and 165 charcoal cooking grills), 10 miles of marked trails, open field space and a concrete boat launching ramp for non-motorized watercraft. Outdoor Recreation of Hopkinton Inc. provides seasonal boat rentals &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/hpsp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Park Directions&lt;br /&gt;Rte. I-495 (north or south) to exit 21A, Main Street Hopkinton. Travel on Main Street until the third traffic light located at the heart of downtown Hopkinton. Turn left, traveling North on Route 85. Proceed approximately 2 miles to the Hopkinton State Park entrance on the right (do not enter the Field Office on the left).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner:  TBA&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197903664000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195871848000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hopkinton State Park</name><id>6793581</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197223200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6793581/</event_url></item>