<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>911 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348186</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 266-3399</phone><name>Foggy Goggle</name><city>Boston</city><id>210753</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084370</lon></venue><fee><label>Group expenses</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Socializing for Justice at the Foggy Goggle for the Second Putting the Social Back in Social Justice Event: &amp;quot;The 1/31.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be our biggest event yet, so if you haven't tried SoJust, now is the time.  If you've already joined us in the past, be sure to come back for the same SoJust fun!  We'll also have some psychics on hand to provide readings and let you know how your year's forecast is looking as well as gauge progress on those New Year's resolutions.  Half of the proceeds we collect will be donated to a non-profit social justice organization of your choice!&lt;br /&gt;[Sign up for psychics will be handled the night of...Be sure to get there early to get your name on the list!]  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be drink and appetizer specials - 1/2 price appetizers, $7 pitchers of beer, and $12 fishbowls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program. No speaker. Just arrive and enjoy yourself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Sorry, this event is 21+ and the bathroom is located downstairs (no elevator).&lt;br /&gt;The Foggy Goggle is across from the Hynes Convention Center.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1170533027000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>70</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163999095000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Putting the Social Back in Social Justice II: "The 1/31"</name><id>5279879</id><headcount>123</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1170288000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5279879/</event_url></item>