<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>820 West Columbus Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01105</zip><lat>42.092317</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-733-1300</phone><name>Uno's Chicago Grill</name><city>Springfield</city><id>1008805</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.583154</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/2/2/event_146620482.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gone Girl: A Novel by Gillian Flynn&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

On the day of their fifth wedding anniversary, Nick's wife Amy disappears. There are signs of struggle in the house and Nick quickly becomes the prime suspect. It doesn't help that Nick hasn't been completely honest with the police and, as Amy's case drags out for weeks, more and more vilifying evidence appears against him. Nick, however, maintains his innocence. Told from alternating points of view between Nick and Amy, Gillian Flynn creates an untrustworthy world that changes chapter-to-chapter. Calling Gone Girl a psychological thriller is an understatement. As revelation after revelation unfolds, it becomes clear that the truth does not exist in the middle of Nick and Amy's points of view; in fact, the truth is far more dark, more twisted, and more creepy than you can imagine. Gone Girl is masterfully plotted from start to finish and the suspense doesn't waver for one page. It's one of those books you will feel the need to discuss immediately after finishing because the ending doesn't just come; it punches you in the gut. --Caley Anderson &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by Sara&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Destiny of the Republic: A Tale of Madness, Medicine and the Murder of a President by Candice Millard &lt;br /&gt;

James A. Garfield was one of the most extraordinary men ever elected president. Born into abject poverty, he rose to become a wunderkind scholar, a Civil War hero, and a renowned and admired reformist congressman. Nominated for president against his will, he engaged in a fierce battle with the corrupt political establishment. But four months after his inauguration, a deranged office seeker tracked Garfield down and shot him in the back. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

But the shot didn’t kill Garfield. The drama of what happened subsequently is a powerful story of a nation in turmoil. The unhinged assassin’s half-delivered strike shattered the fragile national mood of a country so recently fractured by civil war, and left the wounded president as the object &lt;br /&gt;

of a bitter behind-the-scenes struggle for power—over his administration, over the nation’s future, and, hauntingly, over his medical care. A team of physicians administered shockingly archaic treatments, to disastrous effect. As his condition worsened, Garfield received help: Alexander Graham Bell, the inventor of the telephone, worked around the clock to invent a new device capable of finding the bullet. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Meticulously researched, epic in scope, and pulsating with an intimate human focus and high-velocity narrative drive, The Destiny of the Republic will stand alongside The Devil in the White City and The Professor and the Madman as a classic of narrative history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: Mystery Guest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sara</member_name><member_id>6494254</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348670963000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341182696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September's Discussion</name><id>71564982</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348612200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/71564982/</event_url></item>