<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Before proceding to some future Meetup topics which had been requested, it is important that members  first understand some basic parts of our multi-dimensional bio-spiritual anatomy, as well as that of the cosmos.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Meetup will therefore be devoted to introducing some new terminology to identify basic energetic structures.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;None of what we plan to study next will make any sense at all, unless members first understand our expanded 15 chakra system, and 15 dimensions of our fields and shields. It is important to also understand the multi-dimensional nature of creation, and basic correspondences between the macrocosm, microcosm, our DNA encoding, and Star Gates.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This information comes from recent translations of ancient Maharata Texts, publilshed by the Azurite Press, www.azuritepress.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Diagrams similar to those found on the following web-page will be presented and explained:  &lt;a href="http://" target="_blank"&gt;http://...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.katharateam.com/Nweb/Kathara%20Healing%20Brochure.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There should be ample time for discussion also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members are requested to bring their own refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the lady with long black hair and a BIG smile (see photo here).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269201554000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247357127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Basic Energy Body Anatomy</name><id>10855570</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249167600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/10855570/</event_url></item>