<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Skyline Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.282416</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Green Hill Park</name><city>Worcester </city><id>918893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.775371</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Food Update: We have people bringing the following items:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hamburgers, Hotdogs, Veggie Burgers &amp;amp; Condiments / Green Salad &amp;amp; Couscous Lentil Salad / Brownies / Cookies / Chicken/Potato Salad / Vegetarian Mango Black Bean Salad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we could use - Pasta Salad, Fruit Salad, PotatoChips/Tortilla Chips, some drinks, or anything else that you might want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of picnic tables so you don't need to bring chairs unless you want them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every year, the Greater Worcester Humanists get together to get some sun and have a cookout!  We have burgers, hot dogs, veggie burgers for the morally superior, and lots of side dishes and wonderful desserts from the membership's fine chefs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Then, once we are all plump and satisfied, there's more time to get some sun and play outside. We have lively sessions of volleyball, frisbee, cricket, and whatever else we an find enough people to play. or, you can just sit back, soak it all in, and chat with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

This year's outing is back at Green Hill Park in Worcester! We are holding it on Saturday, June 16th from 11AM to 3PM.  We would love for you to bring your whole family as this is also our most kid-friendly event, so bring them along!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

So, we hope to see you all there - this event is free and open to members and non-members alike. This is also a great introductory event so feel free to invite that guy in the office who always asks about Humanism, or that friend who's been talking about wanting to hit a meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Please help make the event great by volunteering.  If you can't make the meeting and want to contribute, please feel free to contact us at worcesterhumanists@yahoo.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

We hope to see you and your family there!! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://eepurl.com/hfyCE" target="_blank"&gt;Sign up for our free newsletter!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the ones grilling and chatting!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Lackey</member_name><member_id>7618967</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn Franke</member_name><member_id>10837891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339975043000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336006983000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Day Out at the Park</name><id>63181022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339858800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/63181022/</event_url></item>