<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>555 Asylum Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767876</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-978-2622</phone><name>ArtSpace</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1045061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.682486</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;Experiencing intense, daily cravings for sugar, white flour and/or chips harms our waistline and our moods. Fortunately, fine-tuning the way we eat quickly zaps those cravings, making these problematic foods a whole lot less desirable. Learn about how and why we cause our body chemistry to call out for these foods - and how to stop those cravings in their tracks. You’ll realize that will power usually has very little to do with saying “no” to the foods we’re trying to avoid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;ABOUT OUR SPEAKER: &lt;br /&gt;

Maribeth Abrams, MS is a Nutritional Consultant, Certified Holistic Health Practitioner, Certified Lifestyle Educator, Certified Plant-Based Nutritionist, and author of numerous magazine articles and two natural foods cookbooks both in international distribution. Known for her upbeat demeanor and ability to convey nutrition concepts in a clear and easily-understandable manner, she is frequently invited to present at regional and national health conferences and she hosts a cooking DVD with former Olympic athlete Carl Lewis. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Maribeth has a masters degree in counseling and she completed nutrition programs at the Global College for Natural Medicine and the T. Colin Campbell Foundation for Plant-Based Nutrition at eCornell University. She is Board Certified by the AADP and she provides nutrition counseling for weight loss and the treatment and prevention of disease from her office in Glastonbury.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;*************************************** &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;This event is organized by CT Health Foodies, a supportive, dynamic community for people interested in healthy eating. We are a diverse group. People follow all different types of diets: gluten-free, vegetarian, omnivore, raw food, Ayurvedic, Weston A. Price. We respect everyone's choices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;We organize monthly potluck dinners and talks on the second Tuesday of the month at ArtSpace in downtown Hartford.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;***************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;Schedule for the evening:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;7:15 pm: Delicious Potluck Dinner begins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;7:45 - 9:00 pm: Talk and Discussion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;9:00 pm - 9:30 on: Hanging out and clean up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;About the potluck dinner:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;-Many people have dietary restrictions. Be mindful as you prepare your dish, and list the ingredients on a note card at the event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;-This a zero-waste event. Please bring your own plate and utensils.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;***************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;FREE PARKING! In the back of the ArtSpace building. Ignore "Resident Parking Only" signs. Parking is allowed during this event. Enter through the back entrance by the murals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FFFFFF"&gt;***************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go around to the rear of the building and enter through the door by the murals.  Walk down the long corridor.  We will be meeting in the lobby outside the art gallery.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>13105264</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347456195000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341524057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Help, I’m addicted to sugar!" -- Talk, Discussion, Potluck Dinner</name><id>qvvmcdyqmbpb</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347405300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/72105262/</event_url></item>