<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A free enlightening &amp;amp; enlivening talk with sacred sexuality pioneer and author of Polyamory in the 21st Century: Deborah Anapol! Thrilled to have her on east coast for this unique opportunity to chat candidly about the challenges and benefits of LOVING WITHOUT LIMITS! I know that there is interest in this work, yet hesitation. I understand!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I first met Taj 15 years ago!!! And had the same ideas and feelings that I do today but all I could do was swirl the concepts of what I dreamed possible around in my head....only today can I actually begin to imprint them as a physical reality. This is the work we are all being called to do right now on the planet....sister goddesses &amp;amp; warrior brothers supporting one another in our own healing, the healing of each other AND the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come meet Taj and feel here energy and know that you are safe to move to deeper places. Now is the time! I promise the dialog will be intriguing and inspiring. It may enable you to think about things in a different way - hearing what is possible...it is like telling a woman that orgasmic birth is possible when before when only knew pain. This new way of thinking that is upon us is all about ABUNDANCE and LIMITLESS LOVE - not restricting, conforming, oppressive ways of loving and being in relationship - be it personal, business or global. Come hear about what is possible and join us on Saturday for a workshop experience to IMPRINT the possible. We all deserve it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deborah Taj Anapol, Ph.D. attended Barnard College, graduated Phi Beta Kappa from the University of California at Berkeley in 1975 and received her Ph.D. in Clinical Psychology from the University of Washington in 1981. Dr. Anapol is the author of Polyamory in the 21st Century (2010), Polyamory: The New Love Without Limits (1997) and The Seven Natural Laws of Love (2005) and co-founder of Loving More Magazine, and producer of the video, Pelvic Heart Integration. Dr. Anapol has worked with groups, partners, and individuals who are exploring conscious relationships and sexual healing for over three decades, leads workshops internationally, and is an inspiring and dynamic speaker. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;She is currently offering training and consultation for professionals working with polyamorous clients and is available for relationship coaching in person or by telephone, private retreats, seminars, and public speaking engagements. Dr. Anapol has two daughters and two granddaughters and currently divides her time between her permaculture style farm in Hawaii and the San Francisco Bay Area. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hear Deborah speak:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/DeborahAnapol?feature=mhee#p/u/4/vDrPX284g8c" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/user/DeborahAnapol?feature=mhee#p/u/4/vDrPX284g8c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306550694000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305430161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Limitless Love: Free Talk with Deborah Anapol</name><id>18406081</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306450800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/18406081/</event_url></item>