<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Plum Island Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.799107</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-5753</phone><name>Parker River Rufuge Headquarters</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>879211</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847862</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's take a walk on Plum Island Beach starting at the Parker River Refuge.  The tide will be going out (low tide 11:23am) so we will have plenty of beach to walk and the weather looks good so far.  Rain will cancel this event.  We will meet at the first parking lot on the left after you enter the refuge, &lt;b&gt;Parking Lot #1&lt;/b&gt;.  I plan on doing 5 miles round trip, which, with a break should be approximately  1 1/2 hours.  If you choose to do less you can turn back anytime.  I'd like to do a slightly more intense hike, a little more on the aerobic side, a pace of about 2 1/2 miles an hour, need to get the heart rate up a little.  Try to be there by 9:45am so we can start at 10.  My cell # is 603 965 5332 if your running late or need directions.  Parker River Refuge charges $5 at the gate.  There are many great restaurants in the area if anyone wants to go for lunch after the hike and the boardwalk is a great place to check out with the new Harbor Trail to Cashman Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No dogs are allowed inside the refuge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The refuge is located ~35 miles north of Boston near the City of Newburyport. From Route 95 take exit 57 and travel east on Route 113, then continue straight onto Route 1A South to the intersection with Rolfe’s Lane for a total of 3.5 miles. Turn left onto Rolfe’s Lane and travel 0.5 miles to its end. Turn right onto the Plum Island Turnpike, and our visitor center will be shortly on the right. If not stopping at our visitor center, continue to travel 2.0 miles crossing the Sgt. Donald Wilkinson Bridge to Plum Island. Take your first right onto Sunset Drive and travel 0.5 miles to the refuge entrance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The refuge is a carry in/carry out facility, this means any trash or items you bring in with you, must leave with you. The trash people leave behind can have negative impacts on the marine life and wildlife that call the refuge home. Also, collecting anything living or non-living on the refuge (shells, sand, plants, rocks, nests, etc) is prohibited. Please leave only footprints, take only memories!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lood for my green Toyota 4-Runner in parking lot #1</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290135814000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289255696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Walk on the beach at Plum Island.</name><id>15383905</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289660400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15383905/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/5/global_11261669.jpeg</photo_url></item>