<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>At Unique People we discuss all topics that have meaning and importance.  Sex definitely qualifies as a subject of great interest to most of us.  Herb Pearce is leading a workshop about this topic.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description from Herb:&lt;br /&gt;“Do you have questions about sex that you are afraid to ask? Curious about? Curious how others feel? Herb will create a safe environment to ask whatever you want about sexuality, how to ask for what you want with another person, when to take risks, how to listen to another, how to deal with differences, how to deal with sexual &amp;quot;problems&amp;quot;, optional ways to express sexuality, how sex relates to connection and bonding, male/female different perspectives on sexuality, stages of sexuality, how to have safe sex, how to deal with raging hormones, how to deal with difficulties around sexual pleasure, etc.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it. Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit has been set.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce *****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb is a therapist and relationship coach, specializing working with couples, for 30 years. He has been a sex therapist and educator in the past and still deals with sexual issues with couples and clients.&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248479387000</updated><rating><average>4.36000013351</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243483725000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meaningful, Educational and Fun Questions About Sex With Herb Pearce </name><id>10511257</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247871600000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/10511257/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/2/4/global_7019412.jpeg</photo_url></item>