<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt.77 and Charles E Jordan Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04107</zip><lat>43.576172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sprague Hall (Cape Elizabeth Grange)</name><city>Cape Elizabeth</city><id>924390</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.250481</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>suggested donation @ door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What do climate change, peak oil and economic uncertainty mean for farming, our local food systems and food security in general? Let's continue the public discourse on this critical issue at an event co-sponsored by Portland Maine Permaculture, &lt;a href="http://www.foodformainesfuture.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Food for Maine's Future&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://mofga.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;MOFGA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.maine.gov/agriculture/index.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maine Department of Agriculture&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://capeelizabethfarms.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cape Farm Alliance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  The use of Sprague Hall has been generously donated by &lt;b&gt;Cape Elizabeth Grange #242&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a community social hour (6:00 pm) followed by a timely and compelling talk by farmer and author Sharon Astyk (7:00 pm) at Sprague Hall, home of the Cape Elizabeth Grange.  &lt;i&gt;Please note that due to the need to accomodate more attendees, we will have to forego the &amp;quot;full potluck&amp;quot; and reconfigure the room for more seating!  Check this page for updates before heading to the event.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sharon is the author of &lt;i&gt;Depletion and Abundance&lt;/i&gt; as well as the upcoming &lt;i&gt;A Nation of Farmers: Defeating the Food Crisis on American Soil.&lt;/i&gt;  This is likely to be the inaugural event for &lt;i&gt;A Nation of Farmers&lt;/i&gt; and Sharon will be bringing books to sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5.00 suggested donation to help defray the cost of bringing Sharon to Maine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our Meetup Event RSVP Guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://permaculture.meetup.com/58/messages/boards/thread/5233158#20208623"&gt;http://permaculture.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a beverage or appetizer-type snack to share for our social hour.  Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)! Please consider bringing your digital camera and posting up a few photos after the event!  Potluck food safety ideas here: &lt;a href="http://fycs.ifas.ufl.edu/news/2007/potluck.htm"&gt;http://fycs.ifas.ufl....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;::::::::::::&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Nation of Farmers:  Defeating the Food Crisis on American Soil &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By Sharon Astyk and Aaron Newton  &lt;br /&gt;Once we could fill our grocery carts with cheap and plentiful food, but not anymore. Cheap food has gone the way of cheap oil. Climate change is already reducing crop yields worldwide. The cost of flying in food from far away and shipping it across the country in refrigerated trucks is rapidly becoming unviable. Cars and cows increasingly devour grain harvests, sending prices skyrocketing. More Americans than ever before require food stamps and food pantries just to get by, and a worldwide food crisis is unfolding, overseas and in our kitchens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can keep hunger from stalking our families, but doing so will require a fundamental shift in our approach to field and table. A Nation of Farmers examines the limits and dangers of the globalized food system and how returning to basics is our best hope. The book includes in-depth guidelines for: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creating resilient local food systems &lt;br /&gt;Growing, cooking and eating sustainably and naturally &lt;br /&gt;Becoming part of the solution to the food crisis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The book argues that we need to make self-provisioning, once the most ordinary of human activities, central to our lives. The results will be better food, better health, better security and freedom from corporations that don't have our interests at heart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Critical reading for anyone who eats and cares about high-quality food.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;About the Contributor(s)  &lt;br /&gt;Sharon Astyk is a former academic who farms in upstate New York with her husband and four children, raises livestock, grows vegetables and writes about food and peak oil. (Check out her blog - &lt;a href="http://sharonastyk.com/."&gt;http://sharonastyk.co...&lt;/a&gt;)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241881874000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>68</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239043813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Nation of Farmers:  An Evening with Sharon Astyk</name><id>10128199</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241301600000</time><rsvp_limit>73</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/10128199/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/a/global_8024106.jpeg</photo_url></item>