<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/6/f/a/event_56186362.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;WHAT NATURE DESTROYED, IT ALSO PRESERVED! The Innovators young professionals group at the Museum of Science are holding a preview of the exhibit "A Day in Pompeii" on Friday, September 30, 2011. Public tickets to the event are $50 but we have been offered a special HALF PRICE discount for Nerd Fun members!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ticket price includes a buffet dinner, wine/beer/soda, self guided audio tour, and entrance to the Pompeii exhibit - a day before even the MoS members can see it! The event also includes access to the regular MoS exhibit halls - which are open until 9pm on 9/30 - after you've been through the Pompeii exhibit - and complimentary parking. Business casual attire is required. Event runs 6-8pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We only have a limited number of these half price tickets so please book yours fast!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to buy tickets - first, sign up for this MeetUp. When I know you're definitely coming, I'll email you the special Nerd Fun MeetUp code that you'll need to purchase your $25 ticket on the event's website: &lt;a href="http://www.mos/innovatorsrsvp"&gt;www.mos/innovatorsrsvp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note, these tickets are NOT available on the main Museum of Science website and can't be purchased through their Box Office either. Tickets are NOT refundable, so please make sure you really can attend before entering your credit card details. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exhibit Info: Get a glimpse of daily life in Pompeii, one of Imperial Rome&amp;rsquo;s most cosmopolitan cities. Hundreds of artifacts&amp;mdash;including body casts of the volcano&amp;rsquo;s victims&amp;mdash;bring to light the vibrancy of this bustling resort town, but the darkening skies ahead and violent sounds of Vesuvius spewing ash and debris signal imminent danger. Presented in partnership with Soprintendenza Speciale per i Beni Archeologici di Napoli e Pompei.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Finally, the cloud lifted and vanished in a sort of smoke or fog&amp;hellip;the sun even reappeared, but livid, as when there is an eclipse&amp;hellip;The landscape looked changed and covered by a thick blanket of ash, as if it had snowed.&amp;rdquo; Pliny the Younger, in a letter to the historian Tacitus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Innovators are the Museum&amp;rsquo;s community of philanthropic young professionals (up to age 45) who are passionate about science and technology, enjoy networking opportunities with their peers, and share an interest in developing their nonprofit leadership skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information: 617-589-0370, &lt;a href="mailto:innovators@mos.org"&gt;innovators@mos.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Innovators: THE FUTURE OF THE MUSEUM OF SCIENCE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2011 &amp;ndash; 2012 Young Leadership Committee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greg O&amp;rsquo;Shaughnessy (Chair) - Partner, Nixon Peabody, LLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Stafford (Vice Chair)- Director of IT Operations and Service Management, Raytheon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan Allred - Senior Relationship Manager, Silicon Valley Bank&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walter Fromm - Engineering Manager, National Grid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;David Kreisler - Partner, Weil Gotshal &amp;amp; Manges, LLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alison Nolan - General Manager and Director of Business Development, Boston Harbor Cruises&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Papayannis - Science Teacher, Fenway High School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eric Solem - Principal, Landmark Real Estate Advisors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jay Spencer - Partner, Ernst &amp;amp; Young&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carrie Stalder - Boston Co-Founder, Startup Foundation; Business Manager, Garden at the Cellar&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Registration Desk in main Museum lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracey</member_name><member_id>11551904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>26</waitlist_count><updated>1317649711000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316187926000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pompeii Exhibit Preview and Dinner - Half Price Tickets</name><id>33803182</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317420000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/33803182/</event_url></item>