<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Visit another one of those mountains named after a President.  The Air Line Trail is a &lt;b&gt;very&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;strenuous&lt;/b&gt; route up to the peak with great views of King's Ravine and the surrounding presidential mountains.  We will start at the Appalachian parking lot on US 2, hike to the summit, have lunch and then return to our cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will be canceled if the weather is bad because portions of this hike are above the tree line where there is no shelter from the weather.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adequate clothing and equipment is a must for this hike.  Multiple layers of clothing that can be easily taken on and off as conditions merit must be worn. This includes a base layer, an insulating layer, and a rain/wind blocking layer.  &lt;b&gt;No cotton clothing!&lt;/b&gt;  Hats and gloves are also necessary.  Please bring a flashlight or headlamp in case we must hike out in the dark.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winds are fierce above tree line, the weather can change suddenly, the unexpected can occur!  Be prepared!  The forecast is predicting a sunny day but it is getting much cooler up north and temperatures for Saturday night are expected to be in the teens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Distance: 8.6 miles&lt;br /&gt;Time: 8 hours&lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain: 4500ft&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most difficult with &lt;b&gt;very steep climbs&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;difficult footing&lt;/b&gt;.  You &lt;b&gt;must&lt;/b&gt; have prior recent experience hiking steep and difficult trails before attempting this hike.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Equipment:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Multiple layers of clothing for various conditions, hat, gloves, rain/wind blocking layer, hiking boots, headlamp or other light source, food and several liters of water.  NO COTTON!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take North I-93.&lt;br /&gt;2. Take Exit 35, US-3 North towards Lancaster/Twin Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;3. Turn right on Rt-115 after Twin Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;4. Turn right on US-2 at the end of RT-115.&lt;br /&gt;5. Go about 7.1 miles.  The Appalachian parking lot is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lucas will be organizing this hike</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>naturegirl</member_name><member_id>3135826</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224592415000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224206092000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Adams via the Air Line Trail</name><id>8977018</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224419400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8977018/</event_url></item>