<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Branch St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.705210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Valley Office Park</name><city>Methuen</city><id>669264</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.214195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;11.23.10 UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; If you plan on buying raffle tickets to try to win one of the beautifully decorated trees. They ask that you write your name and phone # on each of the tickets that you purchase.  So as a helpful hint you can make up some smaller sized stickers with your name and phone # on it, so it will take you less time to fill out all those tickets maybe like 15-20 depending of course how many tickets you buy maybe more if you plan on buying more? then you can stick them right on the tickets, which will take you less time filling them out and more time walking around checking out the trees.  See you Saturday, Donna &amp;amp; Janet  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get into the Christmas spirit and go to the Tree Festival. There will be over 200+ decorated Christmas Trees and you can buy tickets to win on the beautiful trees.....what a concept: a tree that comes all decorated. We did this last year and it was absolutely beautiful to see all the tree's....and who knows maybe you could get lucky enough to win one of them.&lt;br /&gt;The Festival of Trees, is an annual event, it began to fund the restoration of the Tenney Gatehouse. It is a magical event held annually by the Methuen Festival of Trees, Inc., to celebrate the spirit of the holiday season. The Festival is dedicated to the richness and history of our community by developing partnerships with the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, the City of Methuen, the Methuen Historic District Commission, the Methuen Historical Society, and the people and organizations of Methuen. The proceeds from the Festival of Trees provide funding to preserve our heritage and the monuments that make Methuen so unique.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitors are invited to attend the Festival and view the 200+ trees donated by individuals, businesses, organizations, and school groups from Methuen and several Merrimack Valley communities. Their is a cafe where we can grab a snack and last year they had a mini auction from donated items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General Admission: $8 for Adults, Children under 12 FREE!&lt;br /&gt;Children age 14 or younger must be accompanied by an adult.&lt;br /&gt;Tickets for the raffling of the trees is a separate cost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;From the North: Take Route 93 S, Exit 46 - follow signs for Rt. 113 W toward Dracut. Bear right off the exit ramp. Follow the signs to the Festival of Trees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: Take Route 93 N, Exit 46 - go 3/4 of the way around the rotary. Bear right on to 113 W toward Dracut. Follow the signs to the Festival of Trees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is: 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nov/Dec:&lt;/b&gt; November 1-Dec 11 we will be collecting donations for the Lazarus House in Lawrence. If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dues:&lt;/b&gt; Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event. If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change. Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank You, we look forward to seeing you at this event.&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go through the door on the right and meet in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290953067000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286654762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Festival of Trees</name><id>15056873</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290880800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/15056873/</event_url></item>