<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Outside Park St Station</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.358429</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Commons</name><city>Boston</city><id>7865452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059776</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In December 1984, the city of Bhopal, India, witnessed the world's worst industrial disaster; resulting in over 25,000 deaths to date. The disaster was a result of negligence and greed of a chemical company Union Carbide, whose current owners Dow Chemicals refuse to clean-up the toxic site left behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other unethical practices of Dow chemicals include illegal testing of chemicals on unsuspecting prison inmates at Holmesburg Prison (Philadelphia), Dioxin poisoning in Midland (Michigan) and dispensing Agent Orange in Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Ironically, Dow chemicals is a high-profile sponsor for the International Olympics Association, mocking the spirit of Olympics which has always stood for fairness and justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us in protesting against the injustice inflicted by Dow chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What: A peaceful, candle-light vigil marking one month before the inaugural ceremony of the London Olympics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Date: 27th of June, 2012 (Wednesday)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 7-8pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Venue: Boston commons (Outside Park street station)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;facebook page: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/196122303848050/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/196122303848050/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organized by: ICJB ( International Campaign for Justice in Bhopal)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The following is a short background about our group, our cause, and the Bhopal disaster:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In December 1984, the city of Bhopal in Madhya Pradesh, India suffered the world’s worst industrial disaster. A chemical plant belonging to Union Carbide (now a subsidiary of Dow Chemical) released 40 tons of methyl isocyanate, a highly toxic chemical, immediately killing 4,000 people and affecting over 500,000 residents of the area. Till now, over 25,000 people have died as a result of the disaster, and thousands of Bhopalis are suffering from illnesses caused by exposure and water contamination due to the toxic waste left behind. On average, one person dies every day from its effects. Meanwhile, Indian authorities have failed to bring Union Carbide and Dow chemicals to account. Moreover, despite the repeated promises to clean up the toxic wastes, it remains, poisoning the water, the land, and spreading its tentacles every passing day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The International Campaign for Justice in Bhopal is a group working with members of the South Asian and human rights community to provide justice to the survivors of the Bhopal Chemical Disaster. Besides trying to engender support for the cause and work towards providing justice, our group is trying to build a movement that ensures or tries to ensure that there are No More Bhopals as a result of gross negligence and lack of corporate responsibility anywhere in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 www.boston4bhopal.org - www.bhopal.net - www.bhopal.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please consider signing a petition to oust Dow out of the Olympics: &lt;a href="http://www.change.org/petitions/drop-dow-chemical-as-partners-for-the-london-2012-olympic-games-bhopal"&gt;http://www.change.org/petitions/drop-dow-chemical-as-partners-for-the-london-2012-olympic-games-bhopal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Dow's crimes and world-wide movement calling for its severance with the Olympics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dow in Midland Michigan: &lt;a href="http://www.commondreams.org/views05/0418-31.htm"&gt;http://www.commondreams.org/views05/0418-31.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dow in Holmesberg prison: &lt;a href="http://www.demotix.com/news/963194/occupy-philadelphia-protests-dow-chemical-philadelphia#.T-XHxr87j_4"&gt;http://www.demotix.com/news/963194/occupy-philadelphia-protests-dow-chemical-philadelphia#.T-XHxr87j_4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agent Orange: &lt;a href="http://twocircles.net/2011dec24/london_olympics_now_victims_agent_orange_demand_eviction_dow_chemical.html"&gt;http://twocircles.net/2011dec24/london_olympics_now_victims_agent_orange_demand_eviction_dow_chemical.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter help with Amnesty:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tweet for Good! Tell the London Olympic Committee to Stop Defending Dow Chemical and Apologize to the Survivors of the Bhopal gas disaster!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perhaps the largest black cloud hanging over this summer’s London Olympics is Dow Chemical’s high-profile sponsorship of what organizers have dubbed “the greenest games to date.” With its 2001 purchase of Union Carbide (another chemical company), Dow has inherited the legacy of the 1984 Bhopal gas disaster.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This might sound like ancient history. But after the deaths of over 20,000 Indians, the site of the Union Carbide pesticide plant that leaked tons of toxic gases remains contaminated. Over 100,000 survivors suffer today from inadequately treated medical conditions. Survivors have failed to receive adequate compensation, and Union Carbide has not cooperated with Indian courts. This is now Dow’s problem, despite its assertions to the contrary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Despite wide-spread and vocal outrage, the London Organizing Committee of the Olympic Games (LOCOG) has been unapologetic about supporting Dow, and has argued that Dow has no responsibility for cleaning up the contaminated site, no responsibility for compensating survivors, no responsibility for ensuring health care for those who need it, and no responsibility to cooperate with Indian courts. Such a misguided position &lt;/span&gt;disregards both the facts and the ongoing suffering of the people of Bhopal. &lt;strong&gt;LOCOG’s support of Dow adds insult to injury for the Bhopal survivors, many of whom have fought for more than quarter of a century for justice.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amnesty International USA is asking that activists flood the Twitter accounts of LOCOG Chairman Lord Coe and London 2012 on June 27 beginning at 8 pm Eastern Daylight Time/5 pm Western Daylight Time. Let’s show that the world stands with the people of Bhopal, and make #DisqualifyDow trend before the games begin! Please share far and wide!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sample messages:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #1155cc"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;.@London2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;@sebcoe Stop defending @DowChemical- don't pollute London2012 with a toxic legacy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; #DisqualifyDow  Please RT! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #1155cc"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;.@London2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;@sebcoe, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; stop defending @DowChemical’s failures on Bhopal #DisqualifyDow Please RT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #1155cc"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;.@London2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;@sebcoe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;LOCOG must apologize now! @DowChemical is not clean from the Bhopal legacy&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;#DisqualifyDow Please RT!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #1155cc"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;.@London2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;@sebcoe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Don’t forget Bhopal! LOCOG defended @DowChemical and must apologize&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;#DisqualifyDow Please RT!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #1155cc"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;.@London2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;@sebcoe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;LOCOG must retract its statements about @DowChemical!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;#DisqualifyDow Please RT!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #1155cc"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;.@London2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;@sebcoe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;How could LOCOG forget Bhopal?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;#DisqualifyDow Please RT!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340843182000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340463107000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Candle-light vigil to protest Dow's partnership with the Olympics</name><id>70400332</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>3600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340838000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/70400332/</event_url></item>