<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Discover two outdoor gems with North Quabbin Trails Assoc. president Bobby Curley and ABNC guide Allen Young, author of North of Quabbin Revisited.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The group will meet at the Center and proceed by shuttle bus to Skyfields Arboretum, the headquarters of Mount Grace Land Conservation Trust, for a walkabout of the arboretum and information about Mount Grace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Then the group will head on to S. Royalston and the brand new P+P loop trail, a short, easy walk(1/2 mile according to Bob Curley) along the just-developed eight-mile Millers/Baquaq River trail, before returning to the Center.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This event is cosponsored by ABNC, NQTA, MGLCT, Americorps and the Athol Council on Aging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #003366 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Email from Bob Curley regarding this event and line up: NQTA is proudly, in co-sponsership with Athol Bird and Nature Club, leading a Autumn Naturalist Walk at two of N.Quabbin Region Areas true botanist and nature spots.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366 ; font-size : medium"&gt;In partnership with Mnt Grace Land Trust / Americorp , Council for Aging , AARP , Garden Club and invaluable assistance from CTS. We will start our adventure. @ MREC (millers river environmental center ) @ 9 o'clock . We will then proceed by shuttle bus to Mnt Grace headquarters / Skyfield Arboretum where we will be led on a Walkabout of the amazing Arboretum by Tom , Mount Grace biologist with valuable input from Athol Bird Club personnel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Then a short bio by Leigh Youngblood on the history and projects that make Mnt Grace Conservation Land Trust such an important fabric of our region. Lite refreshments will be served.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Then back to the buses and of to the brand new P+P loop trail a short naturalist walk along the just developed 8 mile Millers / Baquag River Trail. This loop trail is being developed as a limited mobility access trail and offers a wonderous blue heron fishing pool , a walk along the river and thru a beautiful old growth hemlock stand and large vernal pool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366 ; font-size : medium"&gt;For you that know me we will be doing something different and be going at a very moderate pace to take advantage of the vast knowledge of our surroundings by our nature club friends. ( promise ) This is shaping up to be a great event to celebrate the coming of Autumn and the joining of our outdoor organizations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366 ; font-size : medium"&gt;We need a head count for shuttle service so your response would be appreciated. The timing of event is 9 o'clock MREC , Leaving Mnt Grace 10:30, Leaving P+P loop trail (s.royalston) 12:30 Back at MREC 1:00 This event is open and free of charge so all outdoor peeps come join us for a day of fun and education. Happy Trails Bobby Curley Pres. NQTA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking is in the rear of the building. There is also roadside parking available on Main Street.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350443241000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347398551000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Autumn Naturalist Walk(Not a Regular Hike)</name><id>81941792</id><headcount>3</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350392400000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/81941792/</event_url></item>