<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/d/7/c/event_162983932.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Seven Strategies to Grow Your Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Speaker:&lt;/strong&gt; Ja-Nae Duane &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; Members- $20 in advance (with $5 cash back at check-in), $20 at the door. Non-members- $20. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Whether you are just starting out in business or have been at it for a while now, finding ways to grow your business is a challenge that everyone faces. Within this presentation, Ja-Nae Duane will walk through seven strategies that can help you succeed in building your business, no matter what stage you are in. &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are just a few examples of what you will learn:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;• How to Develop a Growth Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;• How to Spread the Word&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;• Obtaining Expert Status&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Growth strategies are never pursued in a vacuum. Join us as we connect the dots between the willingness to change course in response from the to implementing a strategy that works for you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Ja-Nae Duane:&lt;/strong&gt; One-woman revolution Ja-Naé Duane stormed into the limelight at age 13 as an award-winning public speaker. Since then, the intrepid speaker, strategist, social scientist, artist, creative economist, and author of How to Start Your Business with $100 has captured the media’s attention, appearing in The Associated Press, NPR, Classical Singer Magazine, The Boston Globe, and Business Week. Her impressive skill set and unwavering commitment to improving the quality of life for the global community garnered Ja-Naé a nomination as one of New England’s Most Innovative Leaders of 2007. Ja-Naé spearheads a plethora of ventures as the Managing Partner and VP of Digital Strategy at the Revolution Factory, Founder of Wild Women Entrepreneurs, Co-Founder of the Massachusetts Artist Leaders Coalition, and Founder of The Leaders. Additionally, Ja-Naé is a professional opera singer and a faculty member at Northeastern University and Clark University. Her recent book, "How to Create a Revolution: A Step-by-Step Guide to History's Social Influencers" focuses on social influence and how we can motivate people to make positive change in the world.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350595878000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348586551000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Breakfast Meeting: Seven Strategies to Grow Your Business</name><id>84007922</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>6300000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350560700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/84007922/</event_url></item>