<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.794332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 278-2670</phone><name>Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>716384</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.664378</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Phoenix Art After Hours&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Phoenix Art After Hours provides a stimulating setting for mingling with friends after work. Sip a cocktail, enjoy music and other live performances, attend a gallery talk, and even see a classic movie or art film. The Wadsworth Atheneum is open until 8 pm the first Thursday of every month, with movie following at 8:00.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;$5.00 ADMISSION will include the movie if you wish, just hold onto your ticket stub. Also make sure you collect any belongings from the coat room before you go in to see the film as you will not be able to enter the museum area afterward.&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;ARTIST SMALL TALKS 5:30 and 6:30 PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Take a psychedelic trip to Werewolf Karaoke, a four-room installation, with MATRIX 159 artist Justin Lowe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;    Justin Lowe, an artist known for transforming white-cube interiors into cluttered labyrinths, plans to recreate the graffiti-covered restroom of the defunct CBGB punk rock club within the stately galleries of Hartford’s Wadsworth Atheneum.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;    Lowe’s installation, up June 3 through Sept. 5, will take over four of the museum’s galleries and feature walls papered in Day-Glo collages involving movie stars, vintage book covers and illustrations of insects. The work aims to evoke the Bowery Street venue where punk bands like the Ramones and the Misfits found fame in the 1970s. The club itself closed in 2006.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;    The project seems familiar territory for Lowe, who has spent the past few years meticulously constructing rooms that evoke the gooey grit of the urban underground. Last July, he and a collaborating artist Jonah Freeman built a fake methamphetamine lab in the New York gallery Deitch Projects — complete with gurgling beakers, tubes and a melting toilet. The installation, “Black Acid Co-op,” brimmed with items that collectors could buy individually, from $500 T-shirts to $35,000 for an entire room. An earlier piece, “Helter Swelter,” involved building several city hangouts like a convenience store &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;b&gt;PSYCHIC ILLS 7 PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Revel in the sounds of the experimental band that the Village Voice named &amp;quot;Best Psych Rock Band&amp;quot; in their 2006 Best of NYC issue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TAP THE KEG&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Free while supplies last from Olde Burnside Brewing Co.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DAMAGE ON THE DANCE FLOOR&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DJ Breakadawn spins dance, trance and hip-hop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;b&gt;GRITTY GRAFFITI&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hands-on graffiti art making project&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;BADASS MOVIE NIGHT 8 PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Herb and Dorothy(2008) collaboration with AIGA Connecticut&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;HERB &amp;amp; DOROTHY tells the extraordinary story of Herbert Vogel, a postal clerk, and Dorothy Vogel, a librarian, who managed to build one of the most important contemporary art collections in history with very modest means. In the early 1960s, when very little attention was paid to Minimalist and Conceptual Art, Herb and Dorothy Vogel quietly began purchasing the works of unknown artists. Devoting all of Herb's salary to purchase art they liked, and living on Dorothy's paycheck alone, they continued collecting artworks guided by two rules: the piece had to be affordable, and it had to be small enough to fit in their one-bedroom Manhattan apartment. Within these limitations, they proved themselves curatorial visionaries; most of those they supported and befriended went on to become world-renowned artists including Sol LeWitt, Christo and Jeanne-Claude, Richard Tuttle, Chuck Close, Robert Mangold, Sylvia Plimack Mangold, Lynda Benglis, Pat Steir, Robert Barry, Lucio Pozzi, and Lawrence Weiner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;   After thirty years of meticulous collecting and buying, the Vogels managed to accumulate over 2,000 pieces, filling every corner of their tiny one bedroom apartment. &amp;quot;Not even a toothpick could be squeezed into the apartment,&amp;quot; recalls Dorothy. In 1992, the Vogels decided to move their entire collection to the National Gallery of Art in Washington, DC. The vast majority of their collection was given as a gift to the institution. Many of the works they acquired appreciated so significantly over the years that their collection today is worth millions of dollars. Still, the Vogels never sold a single piece. Today Herb and Dorothy still live in the same apartment in New York with 19 turtles, lots of fish, and one cat. They've refilled it with piles of new art they've acquired.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;    HERB &amp;amp; DOROTHY is directed by first time filmmaker Megumi Sasaki. The film received the Golden Starfish Award for the Best Documentary Film and Audience Award from the 2008 Hamptons International Film Festival. It has also received Audience Awards from the 2008 SILVERDOCS Film Festival and the 2009 Philadelphia Cinefest. Palm Springs International Film Festival named HERB &amp;amp; DOROTHY one of their &amp;quot;Best of Fest&amp;quot; films in 2009.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Convenient parking available at the Front Street Garage, off Prospect Street, behind the museum.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the front lobby, will wear my bw scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275693161000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273506745000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Phoenix Art After Hours</name><id>13437499</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275600600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13437499/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/f/global_15130623.jpeg</photo_url></item>