<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This hike is a step up in difficulty from the Pemi Loop (which Bacpacker magazine calls America's second hardest day hike and the hardest in the east).   It is intended for people who have already tackled some of New England's toughest day hikes (or their equivalent elsewhere).  Substantial hikes in preparation for this hike are essential.  (For example Alex plans on completing three Pemi loops and at least on Presi traverse this summer in preparation, David plans on completing two Pemi loops and one Presi traverse in the weeks between this posting and the trip itself).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the challenging nature of the hike, we will be carefully screening hikers. Everyone who plans on going will be asked to start on the waiting list and answer some RSVP questions. It will be important to do some major hikes in the month leading up to this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be cautious in committing to this trip, while we are trying to prevent some problems with our screening - your self-screening is more important.  Please do your own research on the trip to determine what the risks are for you and if the risks are worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Loop covers the Carters, Wildcats and the Northern Presidentials with 34.5 miles and 14.5K feet of cumulative elevation gain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start and finish at the Dolly Copp campground and will summit 9 official 4K peaks (and several others including Clay, Hight and Wildcats B, C, and E):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.  Madison (5367 ft.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.  Adams   (5774)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.  Jefferson  (5712)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.  Washington (6288)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.  Wildcat (4422)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.  Wildcat D (4070)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.  Carter Dome (4832)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8.  South Carter  (4430)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9.   Middle Carter (4610)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A description of a very similar route is available at: &lt;a href="http://dailey7779.blogspot.com/2011/07/mmd-2011.html"&gt;http://dailey7779.blogspot.com/2011/07/mmd-2011.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Book Time is 24 Hours 30 mins but we'd like to complete it in substantially less time.  We do expect to start and finish in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some of the things to consider before joining us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.   This trip is long, rugged and strenuous.  We will start in the dark and may finish in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.   &lt;span&gt;We very much want to under book time for this hike.  Book time is about 25 hours not counting breaks.  We would like to average 2 miles an hour while moving.   Allowing for breaks this would have us finishing around 8PM (assuming a 1AM start).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Since we're planning to start hiking around 1AM we suggest camping at Dolly Copp and trying to get in a few hours sleep before hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.  If the numbers are right, we may want to car spot in case some or all of us need to cut the hike short.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.  We will be hiking as a group.  Anyone who gets ahead will be expected to wait at any trail junctions and at any place where there could be confusion about the route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.  We'll be watching the weather carefully and may re-schedule or cancel accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;David (PedXing) notes:  As meetup organizers, our primary function is social.  We are getting people together for this trip.  We are not functioning as guides or protectors.  The risk of injury due to accident or overuse will be significant.  While we attempt to head off many problems that we can see and anticipate - hiking for extended hours and hiking in the dark at average speeds better than 2 mph will definitely pose significant risks.   Any attempts on our parts to increase the comfort and safety of the group should not lead you to believe that we are taking responsibility for your safety or that there will not be substantial risk involved. Our underlying assumption is that if you come on this trip, you are a responsible adult who will use good judgement and that you have the skills and ability complete this hike as safely as possible, and that we are all equally responsible for its success, but individually responsible for our own safety and knowing our own limits.  This hike has inherent risks due to the nature of the trail and the speed with which we will hike it.   Ultimately your safety and your assessment of whether the risks are worth it is up to you.  If you have any uncertainty about the advisability of completing this trip from a medical standpoint - please consult a physician.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==========================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ad364c"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the eager hikers.  I'll be driving a gray Elantra with a Longhorns logo and a VFTT sticker by the rear plates (sometimes its a black HHR with a VFTT sticker).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David (Ped Xing)</member_name><member_id>4566112</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1343462635000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340074831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dolly Copp (President Carter?) Loop - extremely challenging</name><id>69769372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343451600000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/69769372/</event_url></item>