<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1 Mile West of the Hairpin Turn</address_2><address_1>Rt. 112</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.052784</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greeley Ponds  Trailhead</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>823375</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.580761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability policy as outlined on this web site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers must have foot traction and winter hiking gear.  All attendees must be able to maintain a two mile an hour pace for a minimum of four hours without breaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;starting at Greeley Ponds Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.30 mi/42 min/+337 ft on the Greeley Ponds Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail begins at the Kancamagus Highway, leaving the parking lot on an even path with moderate grades. It crosses two branches of the South Fork of Hancock Branch and continues up at easy grades but with rough footing. &lt;br /&gt; to Mad River Notch &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.50 mi/45 min/+1851 ft on the Mount Osceola Trail &lt;br /&gt; From the Greeley Ponds Trail, the Mount Osceola Trail ascends moderately under the impressive cliffs of Osceola’s north spur. It turns sharp right, with an abandoned route of the trail on the left. It ascends very steeply past a sloping rock face then goes diagonally across a small, rocky slide with good views. It ascends the steep, loose gully; at the top of a gully, there is an outlook 25 yd. to the right on a side path. The trail then reaches a shoulder and ascends steeply to cross a lower knob. &lt;br /&gt; to East Osceola &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.00 mi/40 min/+150 ft on the Mount Osceola Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail reaches the summit of East Osceola (marked by a small cairn). It descends moderately with steep pitches past a fine outlook on the right. The trail continues to descend then ascends a steep chimney, which can be avoided by a detour to the right (north). The trail then reaches the main pass between Osceola and East Osceola. The trail then turns and ascends to the summit, alternating flat stretches with steep, rocky ascents. &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Osceola &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 3.80 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 2 hr 7 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2785 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -447 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +2338 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.00 mi/40 min/-150 ft on the Mount Osceola Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail then turns left and descends from the summit, alternating flat stretches with steep, rocky descents. Just before reaching the main pass between Osceola and East Osceola, it descends a steep chimney, which can be avoided by a detour to the left (north). The trail crosses the pass and climbs moderately with steep pitches past a fine outlook on the left, reaching the summit of East Osceola (marked by a small cairn). &lt;br /&gt; to East Osceola &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.50 mi/45 min/-1851 ft on the Mount Osceola Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail then crosses a lower knob and descends steeply, then moderately, to a shoulder. At the top of a gully, there is an outlook 25 yd. to the left on a side path. The main trail turns right and descends the steep, loose gully, then goes diagonally across a small, rocky slide with good views. It continues to descend very steeply past a sloping rock face, where it turns left. It turns sharp left, with an abandoned route of the trail straight ahead, and descends moderately under the impressive cliffs of Osceola’s north spur to the Greeley Ponds Trail. &lt;br /&gt; to Mad River Notch &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.30 mi/42 min/-337 ft on the Greeley Ponds Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail descends easily on an old logging road, bears right off it, and continues down at easy grades but with rough footing. It crosses two branches of the South Fork of Hancock Branch and ends at the Kancamagus Highway. &lt;br /&gt; to Greeley Ponds Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 7.60 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 4 hr 14 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3232 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -3232 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change 0 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in a beat up blue Legacy Subaru</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272894377000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272458109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Osceola Peaks (Both)</name><id>13316691</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272720600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13316691/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/2/global_14305586.jpeg</photo_url></item>