<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pitch Perfect&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beca is that girl who'd rather listen to what's coming out of her headphones than what's coming out of you. Arriving at her new college, she finds herself not right for any clique but somehow is muscled into one that she never would have picked on her own: alongside mean girls, sweet girls and weird girls whose only thing in common is how good they sound when they sing together. When Beca takes this acoustic singing group out of their world of traditional arrangements and perfect harmonies into all-new mash-ups, they fight to climb their way to the top of the cutthroat world of college a cappella. This could wind up either the coolest thing they'll ever do or the most insane, and it will probably be a little of both.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cast: Anna Kendrick, Brittany Snow, Anna Camp, Rebel Wilson, Alexis Knapp &lt;br /&gt;

Director: Jason Moore&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Website:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.pitchperfectmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pitchperfectmovie.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Facebook:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pitchperfectmovie" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/pitchperfectmovie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of our members, Katie, pointed out that Rave Motion Pictures  in both Manchester and Berlin show &lt;strong&gt;5 dollar movies&lt;/strong&gt; every Tuesday night (3D for 8 dollars) no matter what time and suggested we post a weekly Cheap Movie night.  Let's give it a try, starting Tuesday, October 2nd with the movie Pitch Perfect at the Manchester location.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there's good interest, we can continue this as a weekly event. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Movie starts at 7:00 but please meet in the lobby no later than 6:45.  This meetup doesn't have a host.Please look for each other in the lobby near the entrance to the restaurant. &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby near the entrance to the restaurant</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349229844000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348199851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pitch Perfect - $5 Movie night</name><id>83404062</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349217900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/83404062/</event_url></item>