<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;*FOR NEW MEMBERS ONLY*&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't let the random weather keep you from attending one of our popular new member meetups!  There are a lot of you who are new to the group (or have joined but never made an event), and this is a great way for you to find out about our nightlife events and to meet other new members.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;**If the RSVP is full, please put yourself on the wait list, as I will be opening up more spots as the event date approaches**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bar Lola has great atmosphere and they serve a wonderful selection of tapas, along with wine and sangria, of course!  This will be a very laid back, no agenda meetup - just good drinks (and food!) with good people.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get the most out of the nightlife group, I *STRONGLY* recommend new members to attend!  Also, feel free to bring a friend or two, and we will see you SUNDAY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: Meeting time is 5pm at Bar Lola, and the event will last until 8pm.  If you come after 7pm, be sure to give me a call.  We will meet in the bar area at Bar Lola, which is on the right hand side of the restaurant when you first walk in.  If you have any problems finding the group, give me a call.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVENT FEE:  Feel free to buy your hard working organizers a drink!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bar Lola is a Spanish Tapas Restaurant/Lounge located at 160 Comm Ave, on the corner of Dartmouth St.  It is located 5 minutes from the Copley Square T station on the Green Line.  You will need to walk downstairs to enter the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan to have drinks and food, be sure to bring extra cash to for easier bill paying. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*FOR NEW MEMBERS ONLY*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The Organizer reserves the right to adjust RSVPs in order to balance out group turnout.*&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site, call my cell if you need help finding the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1248571861000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247079483000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Member Meetup - Loungin with Wine and Tapas on Sunday</name><id>10831756</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247432400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/10831756/</event_url></item>