<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Avenue A &amp; 7th St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01376</zip><lat>42.605553</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Downtown Turners Falls, MA</name><city>Turners Falls</city><id>728402</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.559560</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/9/b/event_5092123.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;What: Turners Falls Block Party, Parade and Fashion Show When: Saturday, August 11, 2012 Saturday 2:00 pm to 8:00 pm    Our very own Kristi and her canine companion, the lovely Martha, along with and many many more, including you and your dog(s)  will be marching in the Dog section of the Parade, which travels from 2nd Street along Avenue A (the main drag in Turners) to Peskeomuskut Park, (only about 1/3 mile). To join in the dog parade, show up near the Discovery Center at 1:30 to 1:45 pm, we will line up and march off at 2:00 pm.  Costumes for dogs and people are encouraged but not required. There will also be food, music, and other entertainments. Come one, come all, bring your friends and family (well behaved, leashed dogs are OK, too.) It's basically free unless you choose to purchase food, drink, etc.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the Parade, Kristi (and Martha, a black lab with a black leash) will be milling around Main Street at the front of Peskeomuskut Park near the intersection of Avenue A and Seventh Street. Best parking is probably near Unity Park on 1st or 2nd street, (near start of parade), or in the Food City/Rite Aid Plaza just south of the Park at the corner of Avenue A and Seventh Street.(end of parade)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Link: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The 2nd Saturday in August, Turners Falls celebrates living in our little brick city! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/TurnersFallsBlockParty" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.facebook.com/&lt;/span&gt;TurnersFallsBlockParty&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; More info, maps &amp;amp; directions: Rt 91 to Routes 5&amp;amp;10 North out of Deerfield, past Old Deerfield (HIstoric Deerfield?) over Green River Bridge bear sharp right, under railroad underpass -- this road becomes Avenue A in Turners &amp;amp; takes you into the center of downtown. For more information, contact:Krist at 413-695-9848&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet to form the parade near the Discovery Center at the Corner of Avenue A and Second Street.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristi</member_name><member_id>7010444</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345998268000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342972351000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turners Falls Block Party, Parade &amp; Fashion Show</name><id>74408892</id><headcount>9</headcount><duration>23400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344706200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/74408892/</event_url></item>