<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Empire Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821526</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>95 Empire Black Box</name><city>Providence</city><id>10328112</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415779</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Pearl Harbor Day…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Very Special Live Bait Christmas...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christmas is coming early this year, thanks to the folks at “Live Bait: True Stories from Real People.” Since there has never been a Christmas-themed Live Bait before, it was decided that December 7th, Pearl Harbor Day, would be the perfect occasion. And while Live Bait has always recognized and appreciated the solemnity of Pearl Harbor Day, and the sacrifices made, it was the closest date to Christmas without going past. And in the spirit of Yuletide, no matter what day it may occur, Live Bait’s grand gift to the loyal and semi-loyal story-sharers of Rhode Island will be a choice of themes (a Live Bait first!). The themes will be &lt;strong&gt;“Naughty or Nice”&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;“Ho.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone has a story that in any way, shape or form fits December’s themes, they should come to “Live Bait: True Stories from Real People” at the &lt;strong&gt;95 Empire Black Box&lt;/strong&gt; in Providence, put their name in the fishbowl and, when their name is called, come up and tell their story. There is a six minute time limit. They may also choose to just sit back and listen. Live Bait is hosted by Phil “The Host” Goldman with musical accompaniment and offhand comments by Jerry “The Professor” Gregoire. Santa, elf and reindeer costumes are highly encouraged, as are random presents and various nogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside most likely wearing a purple scarf. I will e-mail people the day of with my cell number!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stacee </member_name><member_id>12831814</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355438213000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352934384000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Bait: A Very Special Live Bait Christmas!</name><id>91428822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354935600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/91428822/</event_url></item>