<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Faint of the heart, need not come!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween is creeping closer.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What better way to enjoy the season by visiting a haunted forest and mansion!?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hhhproductions.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hhhproduct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Henry Haunted House Production's attractions offer many things you simply won't find at other Dark Attractions.  Some of the reasons why you should go (from the website):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. YOU WILL BE TERRIFIED.   We specailize in fear, your fear, and you will know it all to well when we are done with you. (We do know when someone is too terrified and will not push the envelope).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. BE BRAVE.  We had over 200 bailouts in our last season and have added many thing to raise that number.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. IF SOMEONE SCREAMS IN THE FOREST AND NO ONE IS AROUND TO HEAR IT.......If you can make it through our Forest and think your heart can take more you can try to make it through the Mansion.  If you can't make it, we understand.  We have a nice place for the 'I didn't know it was so scary' kind of people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. WE ARE PROFESSIONALS.   We are not first timers. Our average scare technician has been with HHHP for 12  years, and we believe that quality counts and that you should get what you pay for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details regarding car pooling and where to meet will be posted when the event nears.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193097990000</updated><rating><average>3.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-27</urlname><id>610218</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Group Closing - Indian Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191609220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Are you in for the scare of your life?! - Haunted House/Forest</name><id>6495608</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192924800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-27/events/6495608/</event_url></item>