<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join Friends as we celebrate the Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR) purchase of a 5-acre wetland for the Myles Standish State Forest. The former cranbery bog, completely surrounded by MSSF, previously belonged to the Town of Carver. Now it belongs to all of us—thanks to the folks at DCR and Kurt and Helga Stottmeier, who first brought the bog to DCR’s attention. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 11, 2010&lt;br /&gt;1 to 3 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;Kurt and Helga Stottmeier’s House &lt;br /&gt;2 Priscilla Mullins Way, Carver, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to hike with us to the party?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The lovely bog is near the end of Ryan Road in the MSSF. Those who would like to have an hour-long hike from the MSSF Headquarters to the bog and then go a short distance to the party will meet at the Forest Headquarters at 12:30 p.m. &lt;b&gt;Sign up for the hike at the FMSSF Hiking and Birding Meetup Group under &amp;quot;Hike to 'Kurt's Bog' and Party&amp;quot;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kurt will lead a tour of the bog around 1:30 p.m. (or whenever the hikers arrive at the bog). Kurt and Helga will serve beer, wine and cheese and plenty of sparkling water. Children and good dogs are invited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the Stottmeier’s: From Cranberry Rd, turn onto Myles Standish Drive (a loop road with two entrances onto Cranberry Road). Go to Bradford Blvd. If you came from MSSF, turn right onto Bradford; If you came from Carver, turn left. Go to the end of Bradford and turn left into the rotary, #2 Priscilla Mullins Way is on your right. Please park in the rotary (do not block drive ways) or on the property. Call 508-866-4599 for help. View map to Kurt and Helga's house in the &amp;quot;Files&amp;quot; section under &amp;quot;More&amp;quot; in the heading at the top of the page.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the backyard. Kurt and Helga promise to be home.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharl</member_name><member_id>712534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284329886000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282249102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Kurt's Bog": A Welcome-to-MSSF Party</name><id>14477095</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284224400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/14477095/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/3/global_17308387.jpeg</photo_url></item>