<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>470 Liberty St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.205223</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pond Meadow Park</name><city>Braintree</city><id>669075</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.982680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's meet for a Saturday Morning Walk in the Park @ Pond Meadow Park!  This is one of our favorite walking locations.  We will be meeting on the Braintree side of PMP at the top of the path where the Bike Path Rules are posted immediately next to the parking lot next to the map and ranger station.  The loop is 1.6 miles, with the walk to and from the parking lot it is 1.9 miles.  It takes about 35-40 minutes to walk the loop.  If we walk the loop twice that will be 2.5 miles total and it takes us a little over an hour.  We will wait about 5 minutes for late arrivals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Please Note: There are only two entrances to PMP - in Braintree and Weymouth.  There is only one place to meet on the path and that's where the Braintree and Weymouth paths converge.  If we walk against the flow of traffic and you will be more than 10 minutes late you could potentially meet us at the merge as we will wait 5-10 minutes for late (Yes RSVP) arrivals, and within 5-10 minutes of our departure we will pass the convergence of the paths.  However, if we walk the right away we won't pass that point until almost 1/2 hour into our walk.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this time is too early/late for you and you would like to walk PMP please note it in your RSVP so we may note your feedback for scheduling future walks and events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Morning Walk&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 27th @ 10:15am&lt;br /&gt;Pond Meadow Park&lt;br /&gt;470 Liberty Street, Braintree&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: The flagpole in front of the ranger station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer(s): Angela &amp;amp; ?  (If someone wants to co-o with me please email me by Tuesday.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: None.  However, there is a donation can for PMP near the top of the path if anyone wants to throw in a dollar towards the preservation and upkeep of the park.  (We used to donate a portion of the event fees.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: At  least 6 Yes RSVPs by 6pm on Thursday, March 25th.  (If we don't have the minimum by then this event may be cancelled shortly thereafter.  A cancellation email would be sent out.)  Attendance is unlimited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome!  2 per member.  Adults only please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Please finalize your RSVP by 6pm on Friday, March 26th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: Heavy rains will cancel.  We will walk if it is overcast or there is a slight drizzle.  Please plan to bring a lightweight jacket with a hood just in case.  I will walk only if the temps are in the 40's or warmer.  (If the weather is looking questionable I will email my cell number to the Yes RSVP's shortly at or after the RSVP Deadline to call after 8:30am on Saturday.)  *Please check back here Thursday night after 8pm for an update.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Best directions should be taken from mapquest.com or maps.google.com. Located on Liberty Street, 500 feet from the intersection of Liberty and Middle Street near the Route 3 overpass directly across from Zana Park Drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note there is a rotary now instead of a regular intersection just before PMP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 17/Union St., Braintree.  Exit on the side of the (Sunoco) Gas Station and Police Station.  Follow Union Street to the first set of lights.  Take a Right at the lights onto Middle Street.  Follow about 1 mile to a Rotary.  Go 3/4 of the way around the Rotary and exit onto Liberty Street.  (This used to be a regular intersection where you took a left.)  PMP is 500 feet up on the Right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet by the flagpole near the ranger station and map.  My picture is posted.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269872905000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268787721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Morning Walk</name><id>12896498</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269699300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/12896498/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/8/global_3818056.jpeg</photo_url></item>