<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Mount Carmel Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06518</zip><lat>41.420751</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 789-7498</phone><name>Sleeping Giant State Park</name><city>Hamden</city><id>683125</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.898515</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi folks! Hope you can join us in exploring the outdoors and getting some exercise in the company of friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING WATER, there is a pump to fill up at the start of the hike but not along the route, I'd recommend 2 liters or more for the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: This Meetup will take place at Sleeping Giant, which is a Connecticut State Park located in Hamden.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN AND WHERE: Meet at the big trail map at the Park entrance, which is located on Mt. Carmel Avenue, between 9:55 and 10:00, and the hike will begin at 10:05.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WEAR: Hiking or other sturdy shoes with treads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: &lt;b&gt;Suggested donation&lt;/b&gt; of one dollar, towards the monthly fee that is charged by the Meetup Website. Please bring any contributions with you on the day of the hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Please see &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/Dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2716&amp;amp;Q=325264" target="_blank"&gt;Sleeping Giant State Park Website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PARKING NOTE: It is usually free to park inside the gate before Memorial Day. Please note that at random times the DEP charges a fee to park in the lot. In such cases, please take advantage of the street parking on Mt. Carmel Avenue, adjacent to park, ACROSS FROM (not inside) Quinnipiac University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail maps are usually available at the park entrance, if you are interested.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Robin at the big trail map, near the main parking area</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280663692000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hiking-575</urlname><id>1282762</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Walks in the Woods</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280537847000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Haven Hikers' Saturday Morning Sleeping Giant Walk</name><id>14268767</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280584800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hiking-575/events/14268767/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/0/global_7947184.jpeg</photo_url></item>