<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>147 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.355130</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-426-3115</phone><name>Boston Commons</name><city>Boston</city><id>449886</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063370</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;With more than 750,000 people across the state struggling to make ends meet, this year’s Walk for Hunger is more important than ever. Since 1969, the Walk for Hunger has relied on support from religious organizations like ours. Over the years, that support has grown from one to more than 1,000 religious and community organizations that step out on the first Sunday in May to help end hunger in our state. Join us for Project Bread’s 45th Annual Walk for Hunger on Sunday, May 5th. The 20-mile Walk, weaving through Boston, Brookline, Newton, Watertown, and Cambridge, will include entertainment and free snacks, as well as help raise more than $3.5 million to fight hunger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your pledges will fund hunger relief programs throughout Massachusetts that provide food through community-based meal programs, early childhood and school nutrition initiatives, and improved access to farm-to-table and local food resources. Project Bread believes that the opposite of hungry is not simply full, but healthy. Celebrate the spirit of giving along with 40,000 other concerned citizens by participating in this fun and safe family event. For more information, visit &lt;a href="http://www.projectbread.org/walk" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.projectbread.org/walk&lt;/a&gt; or call 617-723-5000. Online registration is now open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

If you have any questions you can contact Nicolette at nicolette_greene@projectbread.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367766876000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362087522000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk for Hunger 2013</name><id>106936012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367755200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/106936012/</event_url></item>