<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Into the Wild ~ Jon Krakauer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Publishers Weekly&lt;br /&gt;After graduating from Emory University in Atlanta in 1992, top student and athlete Christopher McCandless abandoned his possessions, gave his entire $24,000 savings account to charity and hitchhiked to Alaska, where he went to live in the wilderness. Four months later, he turned up dead. His diary, letters and two notes found at a remote campsite tell of his desperate effort to survive, apparently stranded by an injury and slowly starving. They also reflect the posturing of a confused young man, raised in affluent Annandale, Va., who self-consciously adopted a Tolstoyan renunciation of wealth and return to nature. Krakauer, a contributing editor to Outside and Men's Journal, retraces McCandless's ill-fated antagonism toward his father, Walt, an eminent aerospace engineer. Krakauer also draws parallels to his own reckless youthful exploit in 1977 when he climbed Devils Thumb, a mountain on the Alaska-British Columbia border, partly as a symbolic act of rebellion against his autocratic father. In a moving narrative, Krakauer probes the mystery of McCandless's death, which he attributes to logistical blunders and to accidental poisoning from eating toxic seed pods. Maps. 35,000 first printing; author tour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time ~ Mark Haddon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Publishers Weekly&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Boone, the autistic 15-year-old narrator of this revelatory novel, relaxes by groaning and doing math problems in his head, eats red-but not yellow or brown-foods and screams when he is touched. Strange as he may seem, other people are far more of a conundrum to him, for he lacks the intuitive &amp;quot;theory of mind&amp;quot; by which most of us sense what's going on in other people's heads. When his neighbor's poodle is killed and Christopher is falsely accused of the crime, he decides that he will take a page from Sherlock Holmes (one of his favorite characters) and track down the killer. As the mystery leads him to the secrets of his parents' broken marriage and then into an odyssey to find his place in the world, he must fall back on deductive logic to navigate the emotional complexities of a social world that remains a closed book to him. In the hands of first-time novelist Haddon, Christopher is a fascinating case study and, above all, a sympathetic boy: not closed off, as the stereotype would have it, but too open-overwhelmed by sensations, bereft of the filters through which normal people screen their surroundings. Christopher can only make sense of the chaos of stimuli by imposing arbitrary patterns (&amp;quot;4 yellow cars in a row made it a Black Day, which is a day when I don't speak to anyone and sit on my own reading books and don't eat my lunch and Take No Risks&amp;quot;). His literal-minded observations make for a kind of poetic sensibility and a poignant evocation of character. Though Christopher insists, &amp;quot;This will not be a funny book. I cannot tell jokes because I do not understand them,&amp;quot; the novel brims with touching, ironic humor. The result is an eye-opening work in a unique and compelling literary voice. &lt;br /&gt;Paperback: 226 pages&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263396447000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258992124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December's Book -  Into the Wild &amp; The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-</name><id>11938754</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262214000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/11938754/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/b/global_12029675.jpeg</photo_url></item>