<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Skyline Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.282416</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Green Hill Park</name><city>Worcester </city><id>918893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.775371</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Every year, the Greater Worcester Humanists get together, welcoming members from all the other local secular groups to get some  sun and have a cookout!&amp;nbsp; They have burgers, hot dogs, veggie burgers for  the morally superior, and lots of side dishes and wonderful desserts  from the membership's fine chefs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, once we're all plump and satisfied, there's more time to  get some sun and play outside. We have lively sessions of volleyball,  frisbee, cricket, and whatever else we an find enough people to play.  or, you can just sit back, soak it all in, and chat with friends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year's outing will be a special Father's Day event at a new  location - Green Hill Park in Worcester, on Sunday,  June 19th from noon to four.&amp;nbsp; The organizers would love for you to bring your whole  family, whether you are a dad, you bring along your dad, or a special  dad in your life. This is also kid-friendly event, so bring  them along!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is free and open to  members and non-members alike. This is also a great introductory event  so feel free to invite that guy in the office who always asks about  Humanism/Atheism, or that friend who's been talking about wanting to hit a  meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/18120351/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/18120351/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the folks grilling and chatting!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Lackey</member_name><member_id>7618967</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308504536000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305742619000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Father's Day / Summer Day Out at the Park (with Worcester Humanists)</name><id>18858631</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308499200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/18858631/</event_url></item>