<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main STreet</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.813828</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Coastal Trails</name><city>Newburyport </city><id>1241555</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.930793</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Update:  We will meet at the Parker Street MBTA Station and walk the trail.  There is free parking in Lot C.  If you get lost, running late or can't find us please call the Meetup cell phone at 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newburyport has been improving their hiking trails and is having a grand opening celebration this year.  Lets go out have some fun and do some low key hiking.   The below is what I can get from their site and I will update the site as I get the information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Celebrate the grand opening of new rail-trails in Newburyport and Salisbury. Free family-oriented activities include ribbon cutting ceremonies, art, music, community group exhibit booths, and refreshments – all along the trail. The two trails will be linked by a water shuttle ferrying pedestrians and cyclists across the Merrimack River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come experience how overgrown rail corridors have been transformed into safe, attractive and popular community assets providing easy walking and bike access to the MBTA commuter rail station, Merrimack River and the Great Marsh.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep in mind foul weather will cancel this event.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on the trails&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Newburyport MBTA Station on Parker Street, Lot C</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275238414000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270858092000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coastal Trails Grand Opening Hike</name><id>13139209</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274630400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/13139209/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/7/global_14239943.jpeg</photo_url></item>