<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>With James Coburn, Kris Kristofferson, Bob Dylan &lt;br /&gt;US 1973, 35mm, color, 122 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peckinpah's revisionist Western follows closely in the footsteps of McCabe and Mrs. Miller, combining comedy and satire to read Billy the Kid's death at the hands of a professional assassin as an expression of the corporatization of the West, a potent symbol of the frontier's transformation from a zone of anarchic freedom, where pre-modern values both good and bad can flourish, to a place of soulless commerce. Beneath Peckinpah's habitual themes of male friendship and its betrayal lies a rich subtext suggested by the presence of Kris Kristofferson as Billy and Bob Dylan as a mysterious trickster figure—suggesting that rock and roll may offer a new kind of Wild West, the rock star a new breed of desperado. MGM outraged Peckinpah by cutting fifteen minutes from the film, crucial footage that has been carefully restored in this new version, which approximates Peckinpah’s original. &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid is probably the most legendarily “troubled” of all Peckinpah’s troubled film testaments. The rambling film was embroiled in financial entanglements and editing dispures. Still, it stars the pop icons of Kris Kristofferson and Bob Dylan and a whole host of other Peckinpah Western regulars. Some Peckinpah devotees consider the film among his finest work, others regard it as, well, troubled. Fascinating, nonetheless. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Marjorie Baumgarten [1999-11-24] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should be a great discussion, afterwards, hopefully at Z-Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for me holding the Meetup Sign both before and after the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the guy with the 6-shooter and meetup sign in his hand</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220917471000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220020299000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid, Directed by Sam Peckinpah</name><id>8646822</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220742000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8646822/</event_url></item>