<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>274 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.317829</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Academy of Music</name><city>Northampton</city><id>9426332</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Part of Pioneer Valley Jewish Film Festival. Tickets are $9 and the &lt;strong&gt;ticket window opens at 6:30pm...we suggest arriving by then because there is a chance this will be packed. Meet group in lobby at 6:45pm.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Filmmaker Doron Eran and his partner, screenwriter, Bili Ben Moshe, were inspired to make this film upon hearing reports of parents who refused to visit their injured children in the hospital after a deadly attack at the Tel Aviv LGBT Youth Center. The first Israeli film to address the issues of transgendered people and their families, Melting Away follows a family drawn into crisis when the parents learn that their son is a secret cross-dresser. Years later, as the father is dying, his wife tracks down their estranged son, only to find a lovely woman. How will everyone cope? (Mature subject matter, recommended for ages High School and above). Co-sponsors: PVJFF, Noho Pride, SAGE Western Massachusetts. Drama. Israel. 2011. 86 mins. Hebrew w/subtitles. Post-film guest speakers: JM Sorrell, Sage Western Mass., Jayne Guberman, Keshet Parent &amp;amp; Family Connection Program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366198168000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>filmgroup</urlname><id>1279822</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Western MA Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365790233000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>See "Melting Away" at the Academy of Music, and enjoy post film guest speakers</name><id>114037762</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366151400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/filmgroup/events/114037762/</event_url></item>