<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>email for details</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.208138</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UNH School of Law</name><city>Concord</city><id>10285212</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.537575</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;REGISTER HERE:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.constitutionallyspeakingnh.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.constitutionallyspeakingnh.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for the second component of Constitutionally Speaking: a daylong Symposium scheduled for Saturday, November 17, at the UNH School of Law in Concord.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is FREE and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Titled “The Conversation Continues: How Does the Constitution Keep Up with the Times?” the symposium aims to elaborate on the themes explored by Justice David Souter and PBS Newswoman Margaret Warner at the launch of Constitutionally Speaking in September.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this forum, nine constitutional scholars and authors will share their perspectives in &lt;br /&gt;

15-minute talks tailored for non-lawyers. Our presenters include Dartmouth Professor Sonu Bedi; Vermont Law School Professor Michele Martinez Campbell; retired NH Supreme Court Justice James Duggan; Georgetown Law Visiting Professor Judith Richards Hope; New York Times columnist Adam Liptak; UNH Law Professor Calvin Massey; Swarthmore Professor Carol Nackenoff; and Suffolk Law Professors Patrick Shin and Jessica Silbey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Audience members will have an opportunity to pose questions to our presenters and participate in small group discussions of the concepts introduced throughout the day. &lt;br /&gt;

To register, please click here to email Sharon Callahan at the UNH School of Law. &lt;br /&gt;

 The aim of Constitutionally Speaking is two-fold: to engage NH citizens of all ages in civil yet spirited dialogue about important constitutional issues of our time; and to galvanize support for the reintroduction of meaningful civics education in our schools. It is made possible in part by generous support from the Hoffman Family Foundation, the Treat Foundation, and the New Hampshire Charitable Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Beginning in February 2013, the NH Humanities Council will organize public dialogues on constitutional topics in geographically distinct areas around the state, assist community groups interested in initiating topically related discussion series, and help facilitate the development of model curricula by public school teachers who participate in the fall symposium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our pilot year will conclude May 17, 2013, with the NH Supreme Court Society’s John W. King Lecture, featuring renowned constitutional litigators Ted Olson and David Boies, who argued opposing sides in Bush v. Gore in 2000. More recently, the pair joined forces to challenge California’s Proposition 8 ban on gay marriage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to all who helped make the September 14 event with Justice Souter and Margaret Warner a resounding success&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353170587000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352743704000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How Does the Constitution Keep Up with the Times? Symposium</name><id>91075042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353159000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/91075042/</event_url></item>