<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>984 Lowell Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01741</zip><lat>42.556460</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Great Brook Farm State Park</name><city>Carlisle</city><id>13422952</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.348434</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the Park&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The farm and buildings at Great Brook Farm comprise a classic eastern Massachusetts agricultural landscape. The arrangement of open fields, sturdy walls, diversified woodlands and historic structures are significant images of our agricultural past. An active dairy farm operates year-round and guided barn tours are available from May to October. Amidst the beautiful scenery lie 20 miles of trails for hiking, bicycling and horseback riding. Notable Native American sites can be seen from these paths. During the winter months, trail-grooming allows skiing enthusiasts to take part in cross-country skiing. One of the farm buildings has been converted to a ski rental concession. Meadow Pond has a canoe launch and is ideal for fishing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Park Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Great Brook Farm State Park is located in north-eastern Massachusetts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;From Rt. 128:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Take exit 31B. Follow Route 225 West for 8 miles to the Carlisle center rotary, then turn right on Lowell St. (following the sign to Chelmsford.) Fern's Market is on the corner. The Park entrance is 2 miles ahead on the right. The Park Office (984 Lowell St) is just beyond the entrance also on the right. Make right hand turn onto North Road. Parking area is 1/2 mile down on left. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;From the West (Route 2):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Follow to Rt. 495 North. Use directions below. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;From the North:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Take 495 South to Exit 34. Follow Route 110 West for .6 miles to Chelmsford Center, continue through light onto Route 4 South for 1 mile, then take right fork onto Concord Road towards Carlisle. The Park office is 2 miles ahead on the left. The Park is just beyond the office , go left on North Rd, parking lot is 1/2 mile down on the left.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;From the South:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Take Rt. 495 North to exit 32 (Westford &amp;amp; To Route 225). At the bottom of the ramp go right. At the lights go straight through. At the T intersection go left (onto Rt. 225). Follow Rt. 225 till you reach the center of Carlisle (small rotary with monument in the middle). Go 3/4 of the way around the the rotary onto Lowell Street towards Chelmsford. The Entrance to the park is two miles down the road on the right. The Park Office (984 Lowell St) is just beyond the entrance also on the right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/3/7/event_8616663.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/greatbrook-summer.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/greatbrook-summer.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My vehicle: red ford pickup truck.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Madeleine Kando</member_name><member_id>19674751</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369781417000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Subnats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>science-88</urlname><id>1005141</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Suburban Naturalists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368546929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Brook Farm State Park</name><id>119337612</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368975600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/science-88/events/119337612/</event_url></item>