<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I am very excited to tell all you that I shall be having a meeting on Monday evening at 7 pm, August 23 at &amp;quot;Music Together&amp;quot; in Yarmouth.  It is located on Route 1 and traveling on 295 coming from the south (Portland), take exit 15, go thru the light, then it will be in the offfice park on the left.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also be having a meeting on Tuesday evening at 7 pm, August 24 at an undetermined location.  If I am unable to find another place, we shall meet at Borders at the Maine Mall.  I'll let everyone know later on.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to mention right here that in the past, people were unable to agree upon the locations of the meetings - some wouldn't go to Falmouth, some wouldn't go to Gorham, too far for this one, too far for that one.  Here's what I have to say about it:  If there was a Genie that you could go visit that would give you anything that you wished for in order to change your life - I mean really truly, a real Genie that was real and would change your life drastically into what YOU want it to be, would you drive to Gorham or Falmouth or  Yarmouth or Biddeford ?  MY answer:  I would WALK to all of those places!!  Wouldn't you???  Well, the Law of Attraction is just like having a Genie that will give you all your wishes.  Can you really not drive 1/2 an hour or 15 minutes in order to change your life?  And if not, do you really believe what the Law of Attraction teaches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In our meeting I thought I would have everyone tell how they learned about the LOA, what books or movies they've seen and any organizations that they've belonged to.  I also thought it would be fun if you could tell the group about any experience you've had that proved the LOA.  It's a way to get to know each other and support each other.  By the way, I teach the Science of the Law of Attraction at Portland Adult Education and privately, as well as running a support group for my students privately. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the things that I think that most of you are not aware of is that the Organizer for the group has to pay to be the Organizer (probably one of the reasons people don't step up to do it).  Historically leaders have asked for a dollar or two fee to pay for this cost of organizing and I thought we would institute that fee again in order to pay for the organizing costs.  If we receive more than the fee, we'll put it towards the next month's fee.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Honestly I'm very excited to meet a whole bunch of like minded people.  We need each other to support and remind each other of the truth - your thoughts create the life that you live right now.  Change your thoughts and you'll change your life!!  sure hope I can see a whole bunch of you on Monday and Tuesday!!  Till then, I send my best thoughts to all of you,  Cheryl Squiers&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282731655000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>MegaMagnets</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PLOAConnection</urlname><id>1426391</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Laws of Attraction Connection</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282062920000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Law of Attraction Connection</name><id>14450513</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282604400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PLOAConnection/events/14450513/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/5/global_14523685.jpeg</photo_url></item>