<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 JFK St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-0930</phone><name>Wagamama Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802033</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120892</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meeting #3 of the Theoretical Computer Science Problem-Solving group is scheduled for Fri. 9/25/09 at 7PM at Wagamama 57 JFK in Harvard Square, Cambridge.  We will begin by ordering supper or appetizers.  Then there will be a talk on the results of Kurt Godel in 1931 and Alan Turing in 1937.  This will be followed by a general discussion.  Some specific points:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. What did Godel and Turing prove?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. How did they prove it?  Are there other proofs?  What is the simplest possible proof?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. What were the later contribution of others e.g. Rosser in 1936 and Smullyan for the past 50 years?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. What does it mean to Logic?  Mathematics? Science?  Computer Science?  Theoretical Computer Science? Artificial Intelligence?  Philosophy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Does it place limitations on doing real Mathematics?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Does it say something about the inherent abilities of man vs. machine?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. How do the results of Godel and Turing actually relate to each other?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8. In what ways are Logic/Axiomatic Systems equivalent to computer programs?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9. Can we translate Godel’s theorem into a statement about computer programming?  Can we translate Turing’s theorem into a statement about systems of Logic?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10. How do Godel and Turing’s theorems relate to simple but extremely difficult mathematics problems like proving Fermat’s Last Theorem or Goldbach’s Conjecture?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be followed by an open forum for anyone who would like to discuss some question or problem of interest.  We will discuss them and perhaps devote a future meeting to the topic.  Always feel free to send in your own suggestions for topics or attend the meeting to voice your interests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wagamama has long simple tables that allow lots of people to converge and have a lively discussion – like all of the meetings we have had so far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see everyone there, with their ideas and profound discoveries in Theoretical Computer Science!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the right end with a notice on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie</member_name><member_id>2078145</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256244637000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Theoreticians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving</urlname><id>1340773</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Theoretical Computer Science Problem-Solving</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253064956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Theoretical Computer Science Meeting #3. Godel &amp; Turing: Theorems &amp; Implications</name><id>11383572</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253919600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving/events/11383572/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_9894127.jpeg</photo_url></item>