<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 William St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02740</zip><lat>41.635693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Bedford National Whaling Historical Park</name><city>New Bedford</city><id>757258</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.924065</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The second Thursday of every month New Bedford has an evening of entertainment sponsored by AHA! (art, history, and architecture).  I have gone many times and it's always fun.  The theme for this evening, Feb 12, is Lincoln 200.  As of Jan 14 the schedule isn't up online but given the theme, expect events to celebrate Lincoln's 200th birthday in addition to the usual suspects of gallery events, live music, and fun.  If none of the Lincoln events look good we can always go to the whaling museum, free for AHA night. We can check out what's going on for awhile and then get some dinner (probably around 7:30).  I like No Problemo, a taqueria, or Spicy Lime, yummy Thai food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the AHA! website for this month's event: &lt;a href="http://www.ahanewbedford.org/calendar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ahanewbedf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can park for free on the street after 6, or if you decide to come earlier just bring a couple quarters for the meters.  I will meet people at 6pm at the National Park office, but I might get down there earlier, so if you want to come earlier just e-mail me and we'll meet up earlier.  I'll send out my cell number the day before to Yes responders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come out for a night of free entertainment!  Hope to see you there.  This is a joint event with The South Shore 30+ Singles Meetup, so if you are a member of both clubs, just RSVP on one site.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby.  Check out my picture! I'm tall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Trina</member_name><member_id>2292253</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234658938000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231971448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AHA! night in New Bedford</name><id>9524582</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234479600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/9524582/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/7/global_6044183.jpeg</photo_url></item>