<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>My Personal Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>787702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Friends:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This party is postponed until April 9th. We need a minimum of 12 guests to have the party. Please check this website the Sat. morning of the party by 10:00am to determine if the quota is reached. This is a catch 22. Some people get disapponted if I cancel, and others complain if we do not have enough singles to meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please register and others will follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome BestMatchClub members. Not a member, please preview our private club: &lt;a href="http://www.BestMatchClub.com"&gt;www.BestMatchClub.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please invite a gentleman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entry fee for this party is $25.00 and includes professionally catered food and one glass of wine. This is more than a 50% discount as opposed to comparative services. If you want more wine then be proactive like several people did at the last party. They contributed a bottle of wine. I thought that was class and quality combined.( some wine was valued at $15.00 plus) These are the altruistic members I want to attract for you and me to meet. We will find them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notice the quality of people who attended the last party. I'm very happy. You will notice another higher level of quality will be achieved at this party.&amp;nbsp; Surprise! You will observe, Continuous improvement is a process. More improvements to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This party is for single individuals.(30-65)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mission is to have fun and meet other high integrity single people with common interests. Develop friendships and possibly find a lifetime partner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Values: Be positive, nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and respectful to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please invite other eligible single people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***The entry fee is $25.00  &lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location is in a warm, loving, supportive and relaxing environment of my home.  &lt;br /&gt;"Dress code - " professional casual" Comfortable.  &lt;br /&gt;First impressions are most meaningful.  &lt;br /&gt;7:00PM - 10:00pm  &lt;br /&gt;Sat. March 12th, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maximum attendees 60&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location and Directions  &lt;br /&gt;My Home  &lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road  &lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA  &lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;128-Exit 16B/Route 109 toward Westwood  &lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles left on Pond Street- just past the middle school on left-if you go by Dunkin Donuts on right you missed it.  &lt;br /&gt;Go I mile left on Oak St. (google search says go right-this is wrong)  &lt;br /&gt;Go 1.5 miles to end-right on Brook St.  &lt;br /&gt;100 feet take a right on Woodridge Road  &lt;br /&gt;My home is the 3rd house on the left-cream colored- number 36 Woodridge, Westwood, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you on Saturday, Feb. 19th at 7:00pm----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7-8 eat and communicate with everyone  &lt;br /&gt;8:01-8:10 Welcome speech by myself- sharing our mission/values and objectives  &lt;br /&gt;8:11-- Everyone gives a 30 second presentation of who you are and who is your BestMatch.  &lt;br /&gt;9:00- approximate communicate with anyone-Discussion questions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website is published www.BestMatchClub.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best is right now!  &lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS: Speed dating it coming soon- offering privacy and a touch of class!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299978773000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Curious Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dinner-parties</urlname><id>1245686</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Singles Dinner Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296685229000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Home Party</name><id>16418496</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299974400000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dinner-parties/events/16418496/</event_url></item>