<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"The ET Agenda: Why don't they land on the White House lawn?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The preponderance of evidence tells us that Earthlings have not only been visited by one or more technologically advanced extraterrestrial civilizations, but that some humans have been temporarily kidnapped and returned to their natural environment by beings that they describe as non-human.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is Earth being visited by interstellar predatory species intent upon conquering and colonizing us, or are they benevolent overseers adhering to a policy of non-interference? How have they evaluated Earthings based upon our behavior? Why don’t they make overt contact?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abductees from around the world have contributed their personal information on the ET agenda to a research project designed to identify commonalities among abductees’s experiences and E.T. technology observed on the craft. It is apparent that E.T. groups may have different agendas—some more positive than others. Their compelling information is an eye opener for everyone interested in alien abduction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Kathleen: &lt;br /&gt;

Scientific Ufologist Kathleen Marden earned her B.A. in Social Work at the University of New Hampshire in 1971. Thereafter, she entered into graduate studies in Education at the University of Cincinnati, and later, at U.N.H.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She began her professional career as a social worker and eventually entered the field of education as a teacher. Later, she was promoted to a supervisory position, coordinating education programs and supervising education staff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She left her job in 1990, and decided to pursue a career as a UFO investigator, researcher and writer. She taught adult education classes on UFO and abduction history, and for 10 years volunteered as the Mutual UFO Network's Director of Field Investigator Training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2003, MUFON publicly recognized Kathy for her most outstanding contribution of advancing the scientific study of the UFO phenomenon by dedicating the annual MUFON International UFO Proceedings to her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is currently a UFO &amp;amp; abduction writer and lecturer investigating some of the very substantial cases in the annals of UFO and abduction history. She was recently appointed as MUFON's Director of Abduction Studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the niece of Betty and Barney Hill, Kathy had the opportunity to observe and learn from many of the great late abduction researchers in action. As such, she has been able to present substantial evidence that the Betty and Barney Hill UFO abduction was quite possibly a veridical experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She also takes to task the pseudo-skeptics who fail to do their research, but disseminate false and misleading information with regard to several of the high profile, substantial evidence abduction cases, and the hoaxers and attention seekers who blur the lines between fantasy and reality and bring impropriety to legitimate UFO research and investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kathy is currently a full time researcher, writer and lecturer. Several of her articles have been published in UFO magazines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, she has written papers on the use and misuse of hypnosis in abduction investigations, the ethical use of hypnosis in abduction investigations, the comparative analysis of Betty and Barney Hills' statements made under hypnotic regression versus Betty's dream account of abduction, a critical analysis of the Harvard false memory study of self reported UFO experiencers, and “The Conundrum of Alien Abduction” (available from MUFON).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her 2007 book Captured! The Betty and Barney Hill UFO Experience, with coauthor Stanton T. Friedman is a case study of her aunt and uncle, Betty and Barney Hills' 1961 UFO close encounter and abduction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Autographed copies of her 2010 book Science Was Wrong (with Stan Friedman) are now available at her website. You can also find them in the "Science" section at bookstores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2011 brought a new book, UFOs and Aliens, with a chapter on alien abduction by Kathy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kathy has appeared on dozens of television and radio programs in the US, Canada and Europe, including the History and Discovery channels, NH Chronicle, FOX News and Coast to Coast AM. Additionally, she has lectured at major conferences and colleges throughout the United States. She is available for employment as a researcher, lecturer, and expert witness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit her website for more information... &lt;a href="http://www.kathleen-marden.com/"&gt;www.kathleen-marden.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost is by donation: Suggested Donation is 10$ per person.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike </member_name><member_id>6862973</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348855572000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345483428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kathleen Marden Lecture:</name><id>78554982</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348786800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/78554982/</event_url></item>