<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>42.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is not a scheduled event. It is for those who are requring transfer to and from JFK only. Please do not reply unless you are going to Ireland!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The time is tentative...so don't worry about that. I would like those who are going to need transfer to RSVP here. Also, please post where you are going to get the bus in the comment field so I have somewhat of a feel for that. If you can get dropped off and picked up...that would be ideal. I will keep you updated on pickup locations...but I will say this...there will be a pickup in Hartford, another in Waterbury/ Southington and. last but not least. in Danbury. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am posting this here as a meetup because as we discussed I will need payment for this ASAP and in order for me to collect monies on the site...I need to schedule as an event! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, don't fail me kitties...please RSVP as soon as possible on this one!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU ARE NOT A MEMBER OF HAVE FUN WILL TRAVEL...YOU WILL HAVE TO JOIN TO PAY ONLINE. IF YOU WISH TO SEND A CHECK ...SND TO TERRI BRUNO, 319 TODD ROAD, WOLCOTT, CT 06716. Check will need to be received by Tuesday, Oct 27th.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the HAPPY TRAVELERS practicing their Irish stepdancing in the parking lot...lol!!!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258233004000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256063065000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ireland Bus Transfer to and from JFK!!!</name><id>11670745</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258059600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/11670745/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/3/global_11330611.jpeg</photo_url></item>