<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1374 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02368</zip><lat>42.201332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Randolph Holiday Inn</name><city>Randolph</city><id>338611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062770</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>EASTERN MASS REIA &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Thursday December 13th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randolph Holiday Inn   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1357 Main st, Randolph, MA   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting time is 6:30PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Annual Members  do not need to pre-register. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For all others it is recommended you follow the link below  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to pre-register for only $15. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Door fee is $25. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Thursday December 13th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 5 Things You Must Know Before Spending Another Dime or Minute on Advertising, Cold Calls, Postcards, Networking or Letters of Introduction in your &lt;br /&gt;Real Estate Investment Business... &lt;br /&gt;and What To Do About It?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He?s back, Jay Wallus of Street Smart, who had us all laughing and pumped up back in August, will expose the secrets of the marketing and advertising industry?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He?ll also show all of us exactly what we can do to differentiate ourselves and get in touch with virtually any decision maker? and actually have fun doing it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop banging your head against the wall and join us next month?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jay?s been featured in Entrepreneur Magazine, Speaking of Success with Brian Tracy and Steven Covey and was recently a guest on the BNN Network News?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Save a few bucks and pre-register online at: &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/30/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foreclosur...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure to register today as space is limited and we will be closing registration when the room is full.  &lt;br /&gt;See you on Thursday! &lt;br /&gt;All the best,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Derek Ebrecht &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;p.s. This is Our monthly networking, education, and deal making event, here at Eastern Mass REIA,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.p.s. Have a deal and need a buyer, partner or financing? Make up a one page flier and bring plenty of copies with you! Eastern Mass REIA is also a great place to make deals!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eastern Massachusetts Real Estate Investors Association (Formally AREI-south) &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Massachusetts REIA does not claim to give expert advice in investing, nor do we endorse what featured speakers say. We do not give professional, legal, financial or tax advice. We suggest that you get competent licensed counsel before putting into effect anything you hear in our club, whether in private conversation or something said publicly. The ideas presented are only meant to stimulate your thoughts in the field of real estate investing and are not to be taken as professional advice. All investing comes with risk; therefore, as adults, it is your responsibility to exercise due diligence before making any purchase, great or small. We encourage you to be careful when ordering coffee at a McDonalds drive through window...coffee is usually hot.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pay only $15 by preregistering. &lt;br /&gt;SAVE MONEY OFF THE DOOR FEE BY REGISTERING EARLY AND guarantee SEATING AS IT IS LIMITED.  The door fee is now $25. You can save $10 by preregistering.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To register follow the link to a great company we are affiliated with Foreclosuresmass.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/30/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foreclosur...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pay only $15 dollars by preregistering now. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have trouble following the link copy and paste it to your browser.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing many new faces this month.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there,   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Derek Ebrecht   &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Massachusetts Real Estate Investors Association  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Derek Ebrecht</member_name><member_id>4695117</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542563000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-730</urlname><id>598232</id><group_lat>42.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>EMREIA-Eastern Mass Real Estate Investors Assoc.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194568710000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eastern Massachusetts Real Estate Investment Association December Meetup</name><id>6705463</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197588600000</time><rsvp_limit>99</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-730/events/6705463/</event_url></item>