<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Edgewater drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03106</zip><lat>43.105765</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edgewater Canoe &amp; Kayak</name><city>Hooksett</city><id>991054</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.467022</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Beginner Kayaking, Picnic and Wimp Volleyball&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday May 8th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kayaking from 11 am. to two  or any time til around 2 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IF IT RAINS, SNOWS OR IS JUST TOO COLD? THIS EVENT IS CANCELED!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A reservation was placed for a warm sunny day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not Kayaking?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just want to do the Picnic at 1 pm. or play Volleyball at 2, or anytime til around 4 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;PICNIC: BYOD &amp;amp; FOOD 4 YOURSELF &amp;amp; A LITTLE TO SHARE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your own chairs and what ever?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A DOG AND KID FRIENDLY EVENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RENTAL KAYAKS $5 HR. for a one or a two seat boats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have your own boat? No problem, but there is a $5. parking fee for those not renting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edgewater Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;35 Edgewater drive hooksett , NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please reserve your boat. Call Rob at 603-540-6520 or 603-485-9251 He will return your call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve O.  603-491-1962 ob@tds.net   Steve Obermiller.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteers needed before and after, please!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Info. on carpooling from your area or Nashua and Manchester, or to help, call Steve O.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/b/5/event_23035477.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  Bring the friends, kids and dogs, and please join Steve O. and   friends, and lets go kayaking! This is great setting for new people to   the sport, or the old timers. It is a low cost easy setting for parking,   easy in, easy out. So, people can learn or improve their skills, and   enjoy themselves at the same time. We'll paddle up the Merrimack river   to a park along the river. Where we all feel comfortable and take a   break for our picnic. Then head up river again. Then heading back down   once we feel we are done. The river is wide and easy to move along. This   is a good opportunity to see if you like the sport.  Please, call  ahead  and reserve your boat. Sunday looks to be nice and sunny.   We  will  paddle by the park in Pembroke.  We will stop and eat on the way.    Everyone bring their own food and drink.   We can also go back from   there, or go longer. There at the park we can sit and have our picnic   lunch. Edgewater has many different types of rentals at only $5/ hour,   or $25 for the day. The same price for either a one seat or a two seat   boat. Plus, you can take the rental anywhere at anytime.  So lets have   some fun on the water. bring your sunscreen, cameras ,water, food,   snacks, bug spray and smiles.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or tex Steve O. 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304871161000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304266318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginning Kayaking, Picnic &amp; Wimp Volleyball.</name><id>17499106</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304866800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/17499106/</event_url></item>