<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>166 Capitol Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.762536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-987-6000</phone><name>Bushnell Theater</name><city>Hartford</city><id>890377</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>Group Rate Discount</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Club Swing featuring Five by Design with the  Hartford Symphony Orchestra and The CT Theatre Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;featuring Five by Design&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, October 24, 2009, 8pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mortensen Hall, the Bushnell Center for the Performing Arts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edward Cumming, conductor&lt;br /&gt;Five by Design, guest artists&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Five by Design makes classy cool again – one song at a time! From the up-tempo opening of Benny Goodman’s Bugle Call Rag to the blockbuster finale of Louis Prima’s Sing, Sing, Sing, celebrate the songs, events and personalities that defined America during the Swing era. Whether performing the madcap parody of Spike Jones’ Cocktails for Two, or the lush romance of Nat King Cole’s Mona Lisa, Five By Design enchants audiences by deftly blending music and theatrics. So check your coat and grab a seat for a night of unparalleled delight at the fabulous Club Swing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $32.50&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUY ONLINE AND GET OUR GROUP DISCOUNT&lt;br /&gt;Only $25 While Tickets Remain &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE will leave your ticket(s) for you under your name at the Will Call window.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions or problems, call the CT Theatre Group at (860) 987-7888 ( we will have this number forwarded to a cell phone so you can contact us before or after the show )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE HAVE A VERY LIMITED NUMBER OF TICKETS IN THE CT THEATRE GROUP SECTION&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT WILL SELL OUT - GET YOUR TICKET NOW&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info, visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or call us at (860) 987-7888&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ENJOY THE SHOW WITH CT THEATRE GROUP&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256684640000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252608611000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Club Swing featuring Five by Design with the Hartford Symphony Orchestra</name><id>11339834</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256428800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/11339834/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/f/global_10634223.jpeg</photo_url></item>