<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>EVENT DATE: January 31st at  5:30pm The Enormous Room. “It’s  Relative” is our theme. Can you relate? Are you related? Perhaps you have a theory about the theory of relativity? If so, you have a story, and you can tell it.  massmouth hosts Cambridge’s first Story Slam January 31st  at  The Enormous Room,  567 Mass Ave Cambridge, MA.   www.enormousroom.com  Tel 617.491.5550  Andrea Lovett @  norah@massmouth.com or call Norah 617.460.3544&lt;br /&gt;massmouth’s story slams have arrived in Cambridge at the Enormous Room. After a four slam series in Boston, with standing room only crowds, massmouth returns to Cambridge for the first slam in a series of 3.  The Enormous Room opens at 6:00 and stories start at 6:30pm.   Two more slams at Jazz Club on the 14thof February and on the 21st of March will have an earlier star time of 3:30PM.The Enormous Room  is a 2 minute walk from Red Line Central Square  stop. If you have a five-minute story on the theme “It’s Relative”, bring it and drop your name in the box. Ten lucky tellers will be drawn at random to tell and be judged. Other audience members can join in on judging teams or just listen and enjoy a night of stories. Like poetry slams and the well-known Moth story slams in NYC, there will be 3 teams of 3 judges and massmouth awards the top two stories. Listeners will be engaged in story Improv games between each 5 minute feature. Local Storyteller, Doria Hughes and Will Luera director of Improv Boston will  co-host. massmouth  and The Enormous Room  offer a $50 gift certificate and a t-shirt for the winner of each monthly slam. In April 2010 all the winners will gather for a BIGMOUTHOFF story slam at Rabb Hall  at Copley Square Library.  massmouth  will award  the lucky winner of this contest a one-week stay in a townhouse in Tuscany, along with other prizes. If lived it and a have a mouth, you have a story.  Bring it. There is a cover charge of $7 discounts for students and seniors with ID.&lt;br /&gt;The Cambridge slams have been made possible with a grant from the &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge Cultural Council +in-kind support from The Enormous Room, Ryles Jazz Club, Toscanini’s, Cambridge Library, and CCTV &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265151864000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264423777000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>story slam JAN 31st - "it's relative"</name><id>12415661</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264978800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/12415661/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_10410532.jpeg</photo_url></item>