<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join me for a hike in this little gem in MetroWest, Ashland State Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a three mile walk of mostly flat, easy terrain around the Ashland Reservoir. We’ll go at a slow/moderate pace to enjoy the woods and fall colors. Light hiking boots or sneakers with good ankle support are recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Apres hike lunch at La Cantina, Rte 135, Framingham.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.golacantina.com/homepage.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.golacantin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO ASHLAND STATE PARK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM BOSTON AND POINTS NORTH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mass Pike West to Exit 13, Natick. After the tollbooth, stay left for Route 30 East &amp;amp; Speen Street Natick. Follow the ramp to Rte 30 east and at the first set of lights, turn right onto Speen Street. You will pass the Natick Collection (a/k/a Natick Mall).  Continue straight on Speen Street for 1.8 miles. Just over the railroad bridge, at the lights turn right onto Rte 135 West. Travel 5.0 miles through Framingham into Ashland. Turn left onto Main Street (insurance agency on your left).  At the top of the hill, you will come to a double set of lights. At the second set, turn right onto Chestnut Street. Follow Chestnut Street 1.2 miles and turn right onto South Street. Follow to the end and turn right onto Spring St. and go down the hill to the boat ramp parking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE SOUTH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128/95 North to Route 9 West and take exit for Rte 27 south. Follow to Natick Center and turn right onto Route 135.  Follow 135 through Natick and Framingham into Ashland. Turn left onto Main Street (insurance agency on your left).  At the top of the hill, you will come to a double set of lights. At the second set, turn right onto Chestnut Street. Follow Chestnut Street 1.2 miles and turn right onto South Street. Follow to the end and turn right onto Spring and go down the hill to the boat ramp parking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE WEST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 9 east to 495 South. Travel for 3 miles and take exit 21A to Ashland. This will bring you to West Main Street.  Follow West Main and stay straight as it becomes Rte 135 east. Follow 135 through Hopkinton (starting line for the Boston Marathon) into Ashland. Turn right onto Main Street from 135 – this turn is 5.1 miles from 495.  &lt;br /&gt;At the top of the hill, you will come to a double set of lights. At the second set, turn right onto Chestnut Street. Follow Chestnut Street 1.2 miles and turn right onto South Street. Follow to the end and turn right onto Spring and go down the hill to the boat ramp parking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will email my cell number to participants the night before the walk.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224715646000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220744527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LOCAL FALL FOLIGAGE WALK</name><id>8704624</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224340200000</time><rsvp_limit>33</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/8704624/</event_url></item>