<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>215 Great Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01464</zip><lat>42.578570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-425-4311</phone><name>The Bull Run</name><city>Shirley</city><id>380565</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.642235</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Details&lt;br /&gt;COST: $12.00 advance cash &lt;br /&gt;$16.00 day of the show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: The show begins @ 8pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rory Raven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MASTER MENTALIST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rory Raven is neither a psychic nor a magician. He is a master mentalist who has been astonishing audiences for over a decade at colleges, companies and private events. A life-long interest in things psychic and paranormal have led him to pursue a career as mentalist and mindbender, to produce live on stage the kinds of effects parapsychologists have been researching for years. His knowledge of theater and the inner workings of the mind, both real and imagined, contribute to his apparent ability to read the thoughts of total strangers, make predictions which come true before your very eyes, and generally bend the minds of the audience. His performances have been described as &amp;quot;spooky&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;creepy&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;elegant&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;sardonically humorous&amp;quot;. His work has brought him to a number of wonderful places over the years: from Salem's Hawthorne Hotel, to Newport's Belcourt Castle, to Manhattan's Metropolitan Club. He has appeared before students and faculty at Bristol Community College in Fall River, (where he apparently contacted the spirit of Lizzie Borden), as well as Emerson College and MIT. He has performed for bar patrons, educational groups, nightclub crowds, New Year's Eve revelers, champion bridge players, and even a coven of witches! You don't even have to believe in ESP or paranormal psychology to find his shows highly entertaining. Remember, you're in the Theater of the Mind, and not just Rory?s mind... but yours as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: When you purchase your ticket ask to be seated at the Meetup table(s). This event is a joint one..other meetup groups are invited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;_Jo&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be there (along with my guest) for dinner at 7pm. If you want to join me? for dinner? appetizers? or drinks? Just ask to be directed to  the meetup table.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210633621000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>The Bull Run has some excellent entertainment! This show has had some great reviews.</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206740665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RORY  RAVEN - Master Mentalist @ The Bull Run</name><id>7623443</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210460400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7623443/</event_url></item>