<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Welles St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06033</zip><lat>41.713967</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.652.9800</phone><name>Whole Foods Market</name><city>Glastonbury</city><id>738679</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.606285</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;SPEED Match Dating - 21-40 Instant Mini-Dates In One Exciting Evening - Meet Someone Special and Party with SinglesCT.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating is inexpensive and fun way for busy people looking to meet other local singles. It gives you 15- 30 instant mini dates to help you find that special someone that you will enjoy spending time with and share common interests. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instead of boring and frustrating dates with people you have little in common with, find someone who matches up with you, your interests and lifestyle, and then build a great relationship!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;THURSDAY SEPT 30 -7pm *AGES 21-40&lt;br /&gt;at Whole Foods Market &lt;br /&gt;340 N. Main St. &lt;br /&gt;West Hartford, CT 06117 &lt;br /&gt;at BISHOPS CORNER&lt;br /&gt;Event held in the Restaurant Area&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SinglesCT....&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 236-3343 for more info&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check us out in the Hartford Courant - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.courant.com/features/hc-speed-dating-whole-foods-0601-20100601,0,6776556.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.courant.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why is SPEED Match Dating so popular? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating is designed for busy people who want to meet other single people in their age group and local area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may have seen Speed Dating in the movies or on TV. Speed Dating gives you the unique opportunity to not only meet, but also have a conversation with people that you have not met before. During this process, you are able to interview them, asking questions to see if you are compatible and have similar interests, goals, lifestyles, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This gives you the opportunity to pre-screen potential dates and avoids bad dates by pre-approving someone before you waste your valuable time and money on a boring dead-end date that goes nowhere. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating works on nature’s laws of chemistry and attraction – when you meet someone new &lt;br /&gt;– you know instantly whether there is a romantic potential&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have a 5-minute conversation with each SPEED Match Dater, and them YOU decide who is a great match for you. If both SPEED Match Daters pick each other as a potential match, we will send you the email address of your matches so you can contact each other to make arrangements for dinner, drinks, movie, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speed Match Dating is a SAFE and Easy way to meet new people - all your info is confidential and is kept private. Only your email address is exchanged with your matches to ensure your privacy and safety &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPACE IS LIMITED - RESERVE YOUR SEAT TODAY &lt;br /&gt;ADVANCE TICKETS ONLY $30 * TICKETS AT THE EVENT ARE $40 if any space remains&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy Your Ticket in advance to reserve your seat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Includes Appetizers &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SinglesCT....&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 236-3343 for more info &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be the first to know about our NEW EVENTS – Visit &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com/JoinUs.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SinglesCT....&lt;/a&gt; and sign up for our Email Newsletter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Event will be held in the Restaurant section</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Singles CT .com  -Join The Party</member_name><member_id>5188478</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285892009000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280987888000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THU SEP 30 * 7:00pm * SPEED Match Dating *AGES 21-40 * Whole Foods Glastonbury</name><id>14326312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285887600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/14326312/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/a/a/global_12418266.jpeg</photo_url></item>