<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Washington St., Suite 6B</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.518270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-639-1236</phone><name>A Higher Balance Healing Center</name><city>Salem</city><id>1342529</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For anyone who has received RYSE Levels 1 &amp;amp; 2, this workshop addresses subpersonalities and cycles of transformation. Subpersonalities of your basic energy system are cleared so your energy may be used to manifest with clarity and ease. We will explore subpersonalities and how you can address them yourself, clearing them to their highest asepct so they can support you. Subpersonalities such as your inner critic, procrastinator, loner or impatient one may be holding you back from your joy and they are easy to address energetically.  &lt;br /&gt;

     RYSE 3 also includes a clearing of your cycles of transformation...the energy imprints of your conception, your birth, your inner infant, toddler, child, adolescent, teenager, young adult, adult, senior and elder...and all the way through your transition to heaven. Past experiences and future beliefs may get in the way of your joy. RYSE 3 addresses all of these, bringing you freedom and empowerment to fully express and manifest your highest potential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have receive RYSE Levels 1 &amp;amp; 2 privately or in a workshop, you are invited to this session; or you may repeat this class if you've already receive RYSE 3. Repeating any RYSE will bring you to your next level of alignment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for this fun class...and meant for your conscious evolution!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RYSE 4 will be held shortly following RYSE 3.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy Copp</member_name><member_id>8642061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354932923000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Evolving Beings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Evolving-Beings</urlname><id>1429576</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>Evolving Beings</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353291999000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RYSE Level 3 Workshop</name><id>91967962</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354921200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Evolving-Beings/events/91967962/</event_url></item>