<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>369 Huntington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.339890</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Atrium at Northeastern University</name><city>Boston</city><id>635519</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090310</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is part of a series of Spanish films being shown at the MFA, in conjunction with the the Museum's  two Spanish exhibitions:  El Greco to Velázquez: Art during the Reign of Philip III (April 20 through July 27), and Antonio López García (April 13 through July 27). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the film starts at 8:15, I thought meeting first would be best.  If there are other suggestions for where to eat let me know....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tix can be bought in advance at the MFA's website; at the very least I recommend getting them before we gather at 6:45 -- the line and crowd can be big for these screenings.  We can discuss our favorite Spanish films and filmmakers (Almodovar!) and some of the other films included in this series.  (See mfa.org for full schedule, and maybe some more these will be added as future Meetup events...?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Contestant (Concursante) by Rodrigo Cortes (Spain, 2007, 109 min.). The Contestant recounts the rollercoaster ride of Martín Circo Martín, the fortunate winner of the most lucrative game show in the history of television to the tune of three million euros. In this biting satire of consumer society, Martin?s stroke of good luck will see his life turned upside down, proving that a stroke of good luck can truly ruin your life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Since we'll meet before the movie, I'll be with a Meetup sign in the atrium at Northeastern University, near the Au Bon Pain.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214226785000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212786312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Contestant (shown at the MFA)</name><id>8094369</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214001900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8094369/</event_url></item>