<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Temple Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.295784</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 875-0060</phone><name>Blockbuster</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1122165</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.447727</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Blockbuster is holding a CrAzY fun pah-tay to celebrate the release of the DVD version of Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince. They have very kindly invited lil' ol' us. Come with me to partake of this wickedly fun evening!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fun starts at 9:00 and is totally free for us to attend. Games, prizes, and mayhem will ensue. Look forward to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- an &lt;b&gt;illusionist/magician&lt;/b&gt; who actually levitates a broom and plays with a white rabbit!&lt;br /&gt;-- &lt;b&gt;giveaways&lt;/b&gt;, including a &lt;b&gt;Blockbuster card&lt;/b&gt; that 1 lucky person from our group will take home. (Card is good for one rental per week for 26 weeks and is worth $130!)&lt;br /&gt;-- &lt;b&gt;door prizes&lt;/b&gt; for everyone who comes!&lt;br /&gt;-- more prizes as awards for &lt;b&gt;trivia contests&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a seriously fun night! Blockbuster will be pulling out all the stops. They'll be serving ice cream and soda, too. Towards the end of the evening, we can even watch the movie (in case you missed it when we went as a group this past summer or in case you want to see it again!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd love to have this be a nice big party for our members -- something truly creative and different and fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to dress up if you can. There may be a radio station and a newspaper reporter/photographer there, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Giveaways, ice cream, a magician, a drawing for a huge Bbuster gift card -- what more could you want?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP as soon as you can and keep your RSVPs as up-to-date as you can, please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm good for direx if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. ;-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260411123000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258430340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Party!!! Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince -- take deux </name><id>11892204</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260237600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/11892204/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>