<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If like me you were too late to sign up for the first &amp;quot;Waltz&amp;quot; meetup, here's your second chance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't have to sell this one too hard:  it's already won several awards, is on most everyone's top 10 list, and is likely the one to beat for Best Foreign Film at the Oscars.   Here's the synopsis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One night at a bar, an old friend tells director Ari Folman about a recurring nightmare in which he is chased by 26 vicious dogs. Every night, the same number of beasts. The two men conclude that there's a connection to their Israeli Army mission in the first Lebanon War of the early eighties. Ari is surprised that he can't remember a thing anymore about that period of his life. Intrigued by this riddle, he decides to meet and interview old friends and comrades around the world. He needs to discover the truth about that time and about himself. As Ari delves deeper and deeper into the mystery, his memory begins to creep up in surreal images… Folman's animated documentary has been acclaimed worldwide and is winner of 6 Israeli Film Academy Awards, including Best Film, Director, Screenplay and Art Direction. (Fully subtitled)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It'll be the 1pm-ish show; since the Kendall doesn't list times this far in advance I'll update this as the day approaches.  And of course we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you then!&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. For the first time I'm using a Waiting List option, so I apologize in advance for any technical difficulties that may occur.  How it works is if it fills up, you'll be added to a wait list, and automatically added to the Yeses if a spot opens up.  So remember to help us out and change your RSVP if you can't attend.  Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the movie I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232227251000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waltz With Bashir -- redux</name><id>9545443</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233426600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9545443/</event_url></item>