<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1660 Soldiers Field Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.358898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>California Closets </name><city>Brighton</city><id>1677021</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.153595</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ladies- come and join Smiling Stiletto Shoe Club for a fabulous and free evening at California Closets gorgeous Brighton showroom. Guests will enjoy a complimentary wine tasting, cocktails, appetizers, Pretzel Crisps and Hint Water. Darren Young, a strolling magician, will be entertaining the crowd! There will also be a DJ and the famous pink carpet walk-off for the Best-in-Shoe competition- so break out your sexy spring shoes for a chance to win some great prizes! Smiling Stiletto is a free social organization for women who love shoes and fashion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Along with some great spring and summer fashions on display, there will be special shopping opportunities from:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bittersweet Jewels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fetysh Shoes and Accessories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mary Kay Cosmetics by Kim Sviontek&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thirty-One Gifts by Kelly Fennell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to enter a raffle for a $2,500 California Closets gift certificate among other prizes! The raffle will benefit Project Smile, the non profit helping children in traumatic events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is plenty of free parking available.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside the venue. I am hosting the event!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336787436000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335894561000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ladies Night at California Closets: Comp Cocktails, Apps, Prizes and More!</name><id>62940752</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336689000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/62940752/</event_url></item>