<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Very long, 21 miles, with frequent steep hills...but on dirt roads, no climbing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Endurance walkers/hikers" join us for a fun and beautiful day!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hooh, boy! I have another Sunday off! And the weather is looking good so far; cloudy, HIGHS ABOUT 72! The first time we did this hike, it still got dark early, so we had to really push the pace. Now we can just do "brisk," and cross to the little island at the end of the dam. Last time up here, we saw a herd of moose!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/e/c/event_86864012.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/d/8/event_86863992.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploratory Hike Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can no longer drive over the dams. Goodnough Dike loop is on the right about a mile into the park via the East Entrance. Park in the triangle intersection, or in the dirt parking lot immediately before the loop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll warm up by walking the paved road over Goodnough Dike. It has the most spectacular views you can get of the southern end at ground level (including a peek at Mount Monadnock)! Mts. Lizzie and Pomeroy (lovely islands) are visible from here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end, Gate 50 leads to a dirt fire road. It goes uphill a while, meets an old logging road, then back down, where it's near the shore for a several miles. We'll have a picturesque view of Little Quabbin Hill (see photo). On the way, we'll also pass a picturesque island called Mt. Lizzie. After a half-mile, the road detours around a steep hill and into the woods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we'll hit Greenwich Road (paved), which is 2/5 of the way up Quabbin Reservoir, and turn left. Where South Baffle Dam meets the shore, we are surrounded by islands seperating the Middle from the East Branch (which you can normally see only from lookouts and high points, or from Dana Common hikes). This is where we'll eat lunch. We'll venture onto the connected island, and hopefully can see Baffle Dam from there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bring lunch, snacks, plenty to drink, flashlight or headlamp (in case of emergency), rain gear, "deep woods" repellant, toiletries (TP/napkins, sanitizer) and ziplock bag (there are NO OUTHOUSES on this route).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There's one outhouse where we park, so I highly advise you use it while you have the chance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Camera highly recommended!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry-in, carry-out. (Take your trash with you, in an extra pocket or plastic bag.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No removing items from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. (From the North, use I-290 to get to Route 9.) Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware and two steep hills with climbing lanes, there's not much except scattered houses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the bottom of the 2nd one, look for a dirt pulloff with wood barrier. After a curve, turn right at the East Entrance and continue roughly one mile. Park in the small dirt lot on the right, or in the loop road intersection. (A small, white sign says, "Goodnough Dike.")&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you pass marsh on both sides of Route 9, you've gone too far. That's okay, just take the next entrance (the Middle Entrance) on the right. After almost 2 miles, go straight through the rotary. (Don't go uphill to the tower.) The Goodnough Dike loop will be almost 3 miles on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live closer to Route 31 or 122 than to I-290, just take the appropriate route South to Route 9, then follow directions "from Worcester" as above. Or, as an alternative, take 122 North (it heads kind of West), and take Route 32A South to Route 9. See the directions from Worcester...pick it up from downtown Ware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points North and West:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the North, take Route 202 South. (From east or west, use Route 2 to get there.) Turn left and go East on Route 9. After 2 miles are 3 entrances on the left, in about a 5-minutes span. Do not take the West Entrance (blue "State Police" sign) as you can't drive the park from there. Take the Middle Entrance to squeeze in a little scenic drive, or the East Entrance (after you pass marsh on both sides of the road). See above re: "Goodnough Dike."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334205830000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331595612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Super-Hike: Gate 50 (from Goodnough Dike) to S. Baffle Dam, and back!</name><id>56095542</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332079200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/56095542/</event_url></item>