<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1/4 mile South of the Pheasent Lane Mall  in Nashua., NH.</address_2><address_1>355 Middlsex rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01879</zip><lat>42.669186</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Roller Kingdom</name><city>Tyngsboro</city><id>345153</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.418060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Indoor Roller Skating / Roller Blading 4 Adults &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunday March 18th. 7:30-10:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 Skate 3 Roller Kingdom &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.waymarking.com/waymarks/WM4WKG_Skate_3_Roller_Kingdom_Tyngsboro_MA" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waymarking...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 355 Middlesex Road. &lt;br /&gt;

 Tyngsboro Mass. (978) 649-3440 &lt;br /&gt;

 Cost: $7. admission $3., skate rental. &lt;br /&gt;

 Skate rental are available roller or inline skates. &lt;br /&gt;

 Rentals: It is suggested: That you bring two pairs of socks when renting any type of skates or boots. &lt;br /&gt;

 Also: If you have wrist guards? Bring and wear them. &lt;br /&gt;

 Because this is a controlled setting. No other safety equipment is needed. &lt;br /&gt;

 Host: Steve Obermiller 603-491-1962 ob@tds.net &lt;br /&gt;

 Please join Steve O. and friends for an evening of exercising, socializing and music. The rinks opens at 7 pm.. But Steve O. will not be there until 7:30. Don't want to skate? They may still charge you to get in. But, then you can meet some old and new friends, hang out, &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/0/c/event_18489740.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;sit, and talk and watch. This is an indoor adult setting, no kids. Because there are no little kids. This is also a great place to learn to skate, roller or inline skates. It is a great way to improve your skiing and skating skills,and to also just get out and about. Steve O. is an Free dance Inline Skating &amp;amp; a PSIA Skiing instructor. He teaches a skate to ski program. He can teach skiing at the same time he is teaching you to skating. This is because, skies are just long skates. So, if you ask Steve? He will be happy to offer you some free help to get you started skating. Come and see skating in an all new way, and do it at your level. There will be music, and people of all ages. There is a snack bar, skate shop, and a places to dance or just sit in a warm rink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Release&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and he, his, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All&amp;nbsp; meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call us at anytime.  603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332175918000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331733780000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indoor Skating Tyngsboro 4 adults</name><id>56312852</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332113400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/56312852/</event_url></item>