<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello All,&lt;br /&gt;  Thank you to all those who attended the January meetup. I hope everyone had a fabulous time at the party as well as the meetup in Brookline. A very special thanks to Rob Galeski and the staff at Doggie Day for once again providing us with a great atmosphere and those extra special accouterments!  So, how many of us thought that cake was for humans!!!!:) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February is almost here and our meetup is back to our regularly scheduled times. Please don?t forget to update the location you will be attending. I would like to increase the number of individuals allowed to rsvp, but that can not be done without your help. So, please make sure to annotate a location. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, keep in mind since February is le mois d'amour. Doggie Day will also be hosting the 2nd Annual Puppy Love Shack. The Puppy Love Shack will be held on Valentine?s Day, February 14, from 7 p.m. 10 p.m.  As, previously stated, Dog?s are encouraged to attend, but you do not need to have a dog to attend this event. The Puppy Love Shack party will include light hors d?hoeuvres, refreshments, give-aways and the chance to find romance among other animal lovers. Gourmet goodies will also be provided for the pups. Tickets are $25 (pooches get in free!) and proceeds benefit the event for anyone interested in attending. Please refer to the message boards for more information?.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On another note, many you may have noticed that Sheri has stepped down as organizer. I just wanted to extend  a special thank you for the work she has done in the past. Sheri will remain a member of the group and has been instrumental in overseeing the Brookline location meetups. Thank you again Sheri?.&lt;br /&gt;I hope everyone is happy with the group, and thank you to all our ?in house ? photographers, the pics are great!...&lt;br /&gt;See you all next month. &lt;br /&gt;-Susana &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Locations:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Doggie Day -- 400 Tremont Street in Boston    &lt;br /&gt;2. Paws for a Cause - 10:30am -- 1386 Beacon Street in Brookline (Coolidge Corner)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1171382565000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1168794228000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua February Meetup</name><id>5392924</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171209600000</time><rsvp_limit>49</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/5392924/</event_url></item>