<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Three (3) Reasons to be Cheerful:&lt;br /&gt;1) Half priced appetizers at the Cactus Club bar from 4 PM until 7 PM&lt;br /&gt;2) 3 Course Dinner -  Appetizer, Entree and Dessert all for $13.95&lt;br /&gt;3) Purchase Sauza Tequila from Cactus Club bar...get a free five (5) minute massage between 6 PM and 8 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cactus Club has been voted to have the best margaritas in Boston....join me to be the judge of that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the Cactus Club menu here &lt;a href="http://bestmargaritas.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bestmargaritas...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared to be flattered.....you may be carded as you enter, so have your identification ready.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first new member who finds me at the bar, gets a free drink. Don't be shy...Say hi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get there when you can. I'll arrive at 5 and hang out at the Cactus Club bar until 7. Then I'm heading across the hall to hear the Boston University Medical Campus Band perform at Cafe 939 at Berkelee (NOT the Mass Ave bldg). This is a diverse ensemble composed of medical students, faculty and staff whose mission is to foster interpersonal relations through the enjoyment of music from every tradition...in other words having fun musically. Concert tickets are $10 and can be purchased at the door or ticketmaster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This link has concert details &lt;a href="http://www.berklee.edu/events/detail/5884/boston-university-medical-campus-band-carley-tan" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.berklee.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out this link for details about the Cafe 939 &lt;a href="http://www.cafe939.com/about/index.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cafe939.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This link has the Cafe 939 menu &lt;a href="http://www.berklee.edu/pdf/news/Cafe939menu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.berklee.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt;  or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Hynes subway station on Green line is closest, a walk of less than five (5) minutes or Copley subway station on Green line is nearly a ten (10) minute walk. #1 Mass Avenue bus is a walk of less than five (5) minutes (get off at bus stop on Mass Avenue and Boylston Street)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the Cactus Club bar from 5 until 7 then heading across the hall to Cafe 939 at 7 for concert</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266491263000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266153120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy 'Margaritas, Massages y Musica' Hour  Wednesday February 17th </name><id>12601102</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266444000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/12601102/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/5/b/global_13093115.jpeg</photo_url></item>