<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Superhuman Happiness Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.192070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dan's Place</name><city>Millbury</city><id>10803932</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.761520</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ok so this is kind of nerdy but since I love me a good bonus feature and anything documentary-ish, what the hell.  This will please the history buffs and anyone interested in delving deeper into the events that took place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically what happens is you watch the movie start to finish, but the volume is lowered while a smaller screen/box pops up and plays in the corner showing interviews (with tha actual hostages! And Jimmy Carter) and other footage.  I find that when done well it can really enhance your appreciation of a certain movie and what went into it - especially for historical events like this.  It's recommended that you only watch these types of things if you've already seen the movie.  You certainly don't &lt;em&gt;have to&lt;/em&gt; do it that way, but it might kind of ruin the actual film experience for you if you haven't seen the movie proper first :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a more informal night where the lights will be semi-dimmed and we can feel free to discuss in between interview segments. My feelings won't be hurt if no one signs up for this, I was gonna watch this feature regardless but thought some may find it a cool idea.  It's likely that most rental versions of the disc will have all bonus features deactivated because they want you to purchase it, but I'm purchasing it anyway :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what a couple websites say about this particular bonus feature:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;Picture in Picture: Eyewitness Account&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;(HD, 120 minutes): Headlining&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Argo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;'s supplemental package is an excellent Picture in Picture experience that features interviews with the survivors of the Iran hostage crisis and other notable participants, among them President Jimmy Carter, Tony Mendez, Mark Lijek, Bob Anders, Cora Lijek, Kathy Stafford, Lee Schatz and USMC hostage Al Golacinski. Listening to firsthand accounts of the events depicted in&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Argo&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;serves as a testament both to the bravery of those involved and the authenticity of the film, and stands as the first of many first-rate extras to provide insight into the events surrounding November 4, 1979 and all that followed."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&lt;a href="http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Argo-Blu-ray/57932/#Review"&gt;Blu-ray.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eyewitness Account&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;(HD) — An excellent and highly-informative Picture-in-Picture commentary track that features interviews with all those involved in the hostage crisis, including the survivors and President Carter. Listening to their comments while watching the film at the same time makes for an even better re-watch, adding an emotional and courageous element to the story's depiction."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;-&lt;a href="http://bluray.highdefdigest.com/8241/argo_combo.html"&gt;HighDefDigest.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I live in Millbury - just off routes 146, 90, and 20 - and will disclose the address and my contact info in a private email to the members who sign up.  Please plan on arriving about 7:00 to get settled and chat a bit, and the movie starts at 7:30 sharp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to bring munchies and/or beverages for yourself and/or others, but please do not feel obligated to do so.  The assumption should be that people will have eaten a proper meal before they come over, and if that's not the case then by all means bring whatever.  I will make it a point to always make fresh popcorn for these movie nights, but really I expect nothing in return besides a good time had by all.  I'll have unlimited Brita-filtered water, yay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And as a reminder I do have a cat.  He will be locked away in the bedroom but just wanted to give you fair warning in case you're allergic.  I also have a private patio which smokers can feel free to use for a smoke break if they wish.  Just don't expect me to pause the movie while you do that ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If all 6 slots are taken up, I recommend jumping on the waiting list and marking your calendars, since we all know plans change for people and folks may back out last minute.  Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I live in Millbury - just off routes 146, 90, and 20 - and will disclose the address and my contact info in a private email to the members who sign up.  Please plan on arriving about 7:00 to get settled and chat a bit, and the movie starts at 7:30 sharp.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to bring munchies and/or beverages for yourself and/or others, but please do not feel obligated to do so.  The assumption should be that people will have eaten a proper meal before they come over, and if that's not the case then by all means bring whatever.  I will make it a point to always make fresh popcorn for these movie nights, but really I expect nothing in return besides a good time had by all.  I'll have unlimited Brita-filtered water, yay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And as a reminder I do have a cat.  He will be locked away in the bedroom but just wanted to give you fair warning in case you're allergic.  I also have a private patio which smokers can feel free to use for a smoke break if they wish.  Just don't expect me to pause the movie while you do that ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If all 6 slots are taken up, I recommend jumping on the waiting list and marking your calendars, since we all know plans change for people and folks may back out last minute.  Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan</member_name><member_id>41397892</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361536038000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-579</urlname><id>797632</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8099975586</group_lon><name>The Worcester Movie Fans Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360940082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Argo revisited: Picture-in-picture track with the actual hostages!</name><id>104734142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361491200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-579/events/104734142/</event_url></item>