<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Many of you have probably seen at least one film directed by Gus Van Sant (Good Will Hunting, Drugstore Cowboy, My Own Private Idaho, To Die For etc.), now here's your chance to see the first film he ever directed: 1985's Mala Noche. Never fully distributed in the U.S. and available only in bootleg VHS copies, this reissue features a fully restored and newly struck film print and represents one of the first opportunities for Bostonians to see this film in the way it was meant to be seen. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gus Van Sant?s first feature film, MALA NOCHE is an adaptation of the cult autobiographical 1970s novel by Walt Curtis. Walt is a young, out, gay man in Portland, Oregon where he runs a convenience store in an area populated mainly by bums and homeless immigrants. Despite himself, Walt falls into an ?amour fou? with Johnny, an illegal Mexican who doesn?t speak a word of English and is barely 18. Walt is fully aware of his folly but pursues his romantic quarry nonetheless, while trysting on the side with Johnny?s more-willing friend, Pepper. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shot in black and white 16mm, MALA NOCHE is a little like a Pacific Northwest echo of Jim Jarmusch?s Stranger Than Paradise but is also a piece all of its own. Van Sant skirts the grim side of life with subtle humor and a lyrical visual style reflected in the rest of his films. He is helped considerably by the low-key and charming performance of Tim Streeter as Walt ? ?one of the most realistic, likable gay characters seen in years,? according to PlanetOut.com. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?Written and directed by Mr. Van Sant with sardonic humor ? Tim Streeter, who looks a bit like Richard Gere, gives an exceptionally intelligent performance as Walt, a man who is tough as nails up to a point and, beyond that, conniving, selfdestructive and forlornly romantic.? ? Vincent Canby, The New York Times (1986) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film will be hosted by Nicole, who will be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater during the credits to lead everyone off to a local Thai restaurant for dinner and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182180373000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181086631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gus Van Sant's First Film - Mala Noche</name><id>5857809</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181950200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5857809/</event_url></item>