<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This coming Wednesday is another session of the new series of the class Introduction to Meditation and Mysticism. if you miss some sessions, you can still join and catch up later for the missed sessions. We are already a group of 7 people and more can join.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is what the series is about&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever ask yourself why you are on this earth? What is life about? And is there more? &lt;br /&gt;If yes, this course is for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a powerful 5-week introductory course designed for modern mystics. Classes will include teachings on: the Inner Spiritual Path, Meditation, Soul, Light, Prayer and Blessing. Time will be spent teaching the principles of meditation that will allow you to move deeper than the body, beyond thinking and emotions, and into the reality of God's peace and presence within. In each class we explore three areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Understanding the cosmos, the Laws and Beings that govern it, and our roles as living, conscious humans in that cosmos&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Spiritual exercises designed to help you develop skills needed for inner work&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Hands-on experiences, through which you can learn to see, hear, and feel the spiritual world&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This course is free of charge, as are all of our classes. This class will be taught by Rev. Christine in her home in Cambridge. Contact me if any questions. &lt;br /&gt;Classes in that format are held in Framingham too on Thursdays at 7:30 pm.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>just ring the bell of the front door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276165172000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275530922000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>class on meditation and mysticm</name><id>ffhsnynjbmb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276123500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/13679759/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/7/global_5061495.jpeg</photo_url></item>