<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Soldiers Field Rd &amp; Everett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.364819</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Artesani Park along Charles River</name><city>Brighton</city><id>723026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.135521</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Enjoy the river upstream in the afternoon.....then take a dinner break and enjoy the Boston area of the Charles with the backlight of the city. This is a night time paddle down the Charles River from Artesani Park to the Galleria Mall (Museum of Science) and back to enjoy the city lights of Boston from the river at night.  This is a very enjoyable trip of about 9-10 miles (slow pace) and a great photo opportunity.  The route will take us from Artesani Park, down along the right bank of the river to the Esplanade.  We'll travel the inner route pass the Hatch shell down to the bridge and then across the river to the Galleria Mall.  Then back along the same route.  We'll avoid the right bank on the return trip to stay out of reflecting waves off the stone wall of Memorial Drive.  The trip should be 3.5 to 4 hours. I have done the trip numerous times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is NOT a Common Adventure Model trip.  For safety reasons, this trip is limited to 20 paddlers and they must have the required equipment and follow the guidelines set forth by the leaders, as safety is the #1 priority on this trip.&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will paddle in two groups (if there are 20 paddlers)  Each paddler will have a partner that they must stay within sight of. The groups will absolutely stay together....NO stragglers or Olympic speed paddlers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Required equipment:&lt;br /&gt;Kayak with bulkheads or float bags&lt;br /&gt;paddle&lt;br /&gt;PFD (lifejacket) that must be worn&lt;br /&gt;paddle float&lt;br /&gt;pump&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.boat-ed.com/ma/handbook/lights.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boat-ed.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Massachusetts law requires:&lt;br /&gt;If less than 23.0 feet long, these vessels should:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If practical, exhibit the same lights as required for unpowered vessels less than 65.6 feet in length. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If not practical, have on hand at least one lantern or flashlight shining a white light as in Figure 3.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So in addition to the above equipment you must have:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a waterproof headlamp or flashlight&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;two (2) chemlight sticks of any color  (one of these will tie to the bow of your boat, the other to the shoulder of your pfd. that way, in the event of a capsize, we can see the boat and the person on the water)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested:&lt;br /&gt;Bugspray&lt;br /&gt;VHF Radio&lt;br /&gt;camera!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will not be using deck lights unless they are a &lt;u&gt;diffused&lt;/u&gt; LED type.  Other types are too bright and hurt the night vision capability of other paddlers and make photography difficult because the camera focuses to the bright light near it...that is why we will all use chemlights.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lots of cars with Kayaks on them</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy Foley</member_name><member_id>7753713</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Eldredge</member_name><member_id>7765158</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248820358000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247081370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charles River (Night) Paddle</name><id>10832036</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248559200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/10832036/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/a/global_8720682.jpeg</photo_url></item>