<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>8th Floor</address_2><address_1>100 Milk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.357075</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-905-5560</phone><name>Exemplar Law Partners, LLC</name><city>Boston</city><id>207203</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a Special Business Plan Hot Seat featuring VINTAGE BLUE Apparel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE COMPANY&lt;br /&gt;Vintage Blue is a hot and new vintage-inspired apparel company with tremendous market potential.  Headed by its passionate founder, Liza Goncalves, Vintage Blue designs are tailored for the trend-setting woman whose main interests and passions are sports, music, and fashion. Vintage Blue has acquired licenses from professional sports organizations that inspire their design team to complete a line of fashionable sportswear for women.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THIS HOT SEAT:&lt;br /&gt;The business plan hot seat is an opportunity for entrepreneurs to present their business plan to fellow entrepreneurs, service professionals, and investors for the purpose of receiving critical feedback, analysis, and support.  CEOs present their plan and get constructive criticism so that they can prepare to raise capital to finance their businesses.   Attendees are encouraged to participate in the critique.  In this special hot-seat, Exemplar CEO Christopher Marston will lead the critique to provide maximum value to the company.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE FROM THE CHIEF EXECUTIVE OFFICER: VINTAGE BLUE&lt;br /&gt;Hello Entrepreneurs and Investors,&lt;br /&gt;Vintage Blue is the best of then and now- the fusion&lt;br /&gt;of old and new. It hasn't been my side job or my&lt;br /&gt;full-time job for the past five years- it's been my life.&lt;br /&gt;I am Vintage Blue.&lt;br /&gt;After years in the entertainment industry, hosting&lt;br /&gt;my own show, and deconstructing men?s jerseys for&lt;br /&gt;celebrity clientele, I?m launching my line ?Vintage&lt;br /&gt;Blue.? I acquired the license to the All-American&lt;br /&gt;Girls Professional Baseball League featured in the&lt;br /&gt;movie ?A League of Their Own.? The line is vintage&lt;br /&gt;inspired with an innovative twist to women?s sports&lt;br /&gt;apparel.&lt;br /&gt;To believe in yourself, and that you can do&lt;br /&gt;something- anything, is the number one quality I&lt;br /&gt;believe is necessary to start your own business.&lt;br /&gt;However, believing in yourself is not the only thing&lt;br /&gt;you need to be successful in your business. You have&lt;br /&gt;to have drive, ambition, skills- and most importantly,&lt;br /&gt;a love and vision for your company.&lt;br /&gt;We have made major inroads at Macy?s and&lt;br /&gt;ADIDAS, and a deal is close to being on the&lt;br /&gt;table. We almost have every piece in place to make&lt;br /&gt;this work on a grand scale, and because of all the&lt;br /&gt;developments over the past few months, I?ve never&lt;br /&gt;been more enthusiastic, encouraged, and&lt;br /&gt;optimistic. It?s been a struggle; I acknowledge the&lt;br /&gt;stepping-stones along the way, and know that it&lt;br /&gt;has made us poised for success.&lt;br /&gt;I invite you to come to learn more about this&lt;br /&gt;opportunity to become a part of a company&lt;br /&gt;formed by creative, motivated, and driven&lt;br /&gt;individuals. We are seeking financial investment&lt;br /&gt;to further design, develop, manufacture,&lt;br /&gt;distribute, and market our brand and collections.&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting you.&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;Liza Goncavles&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Marston</member_name><member_id>2731493</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190239333000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188185183000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Business Plan Hot Seat: Vintage Blue Apparel</name><id>6248748</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190066400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/6248748/</event_url></item>