<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Mass. Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.359097</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass. Institute of Technology</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>594779</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093636</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>All, ....................Please consider attending this event @ MIT Friday May 16th @ 7pm. Richard Gage, AIA, Architect, a San Francisco area architect, is in town for the AIA National Convention and will make his very compelling, subject presentation . When he addresses architects and engineers his conversion rate is nearly 100% to seekers of 911truth. .............Best, Rich&lt;br /&gt;ARCHITECTS &amp;amp; ENGINEERS FOR 9/11 TRUTH&lt;br /&gt;  Richard Gage, AIA, Architect&lt;br /&gt;        www.ae911truth.org&lt;br /&gt;      rgage@ae911truth.org &lt;br /&gt;                                                                                                               May 12, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Dear Honored Citizen: &lt;br /&gt;You are invited to attend a forum at MIT concerning the Collapse of the 3 World Trade Center high-rises on 9/11.&lt;br /&gt;I am the founder of the organization Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth which is a fast-growing collaboration of more than 350 architectural and engineering professionals. The last few years have witnessed the emergence of mounting scientific evidence that the collapses of the Twin Towers and WTC Building 7 were not adequately explained by the official theories outlined in the 2002 FEMA and 2005 NIST reports. The Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth call for a new, fully funded unimpeachable Congressional investigation with subpoena power.&lt;br /&gt;We are dedicated to presenting the evidence that supports our call in this comprehensive presentation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Evening Forum (Open to the Public)&lt;br /&gt;9/11: Blueprint for Truth / The Architecture of Destruction&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Friday May 16, 7:00 pm No RSVP for this.&lt;br /&gt;MIT, Room 54-100 Map at &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?mapterms=54-100&amp;amp;mapsearch=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What the Evidence Shows&lt;br /&gt;Sounds of explosions coming from each of the WTC Twin Towers were heard well before the collapses began. These were reported by over 118 first responders in the FDNY recorded &amp;quot;oral histories&amp;quot; (the release of which was resisted by the City of NY until forced by a New York Times FOIA filing). Numerous accounts of &amp;quot;flashes of light&amp;quot; which commonly accompany the detonation of demolition charges were also reported. Video footage reveals the striking symmetry, explosiveness and rapidity of the Towers' destruction. This destruction differed from the more classic controlled demolition of WTC 7 in its extreme explosiveness.&lt;br /&gt;Each rubble site contained tons of molten metal &amp;quot;flowing like lava&amp;quot; in the basements - as observed by Leslie Robertson, WTC structural engineer, and numerous other first responders. The temperatures of these flows were far in excess of anything possible from a jet fuel fire or from the burning contents of the buildings. Scientists have determined conclusively that thermate - a high-tech incendiary - was used. Chemical traces of thermate were found in the steel and dust. Each &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot; exhibited thick billowing pyroclastic dust clouds that rapidly expanded to over ten times the volume of the buildings. Each also showed squibs (explosive ejections of pulverized building materials) easily observed in many of the videos. The twin towers were explained to have &amp;quot;pancaked&amp;quot; down, however there was no stack of floors found at the bottom - nearly everything was blown outside the footprint of the towers in a symmetrical pattern extending 1,200 feet in diameter around each building - and 90,000 tons of concrete , metal decking and floor trusses were completely missing from the debris field. &lt;br /&gt;Most damaging to the official story, WTC building 7 was a 47-story high-rise not hit by an airplane and yet became the 3rd modern steel-framed skyscraper to collapse symmetrically at near free-fall speed on 9/11 - in the exact manner of a controlled demolition with explosives. It collapsed into a neat, compact pile, exhibiting ALL the classic features of controlled demolition:&lt;br /&gt;Rapid onset of &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Sounds of explosions at ground floor - a full second prior to collapse &lt;br /&gt;Symmetrical &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot; - through the path of greatest resistance - at near free-fall speed (i.e. the [core] columns offered no resistance) &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Collapses&amp;quot; into its own footprint - with the steel skeleton broken up for shipment &lt;br /&gt;Massive volume of expanding pyroclastic dust clouds &lt;br /&gt;Tons of molten metal found in basement by demolition workers &lt;br /&gt;Chemical signature of thermate (a high-tech incendiary) found in slag and dust samples &lt;br /&gt;Rapid oxidation and intergranular melting found (by FEMA) in the structural steel samples &lt;br /&gt;Expert corroboration from controlled demolition professionals &lt;br /&gt;Foreknowledge of &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot; by First Responders, media, NYPD, FDNY, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can review all of this evidence and much more online at www.AE911Truth.org. &lt;br /&gt;Thank you - we look forward to meeting each of you at the forum!&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Gage, AIA, Architect&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>please also find out how you can pass out fliers at the convention here in boston THIS WEEK!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211151801000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210711419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ARCHITECTS &amp; ENGINEERS FOR 9/11 TRUTH @ MIT Friday May 16th @ 7pm </name><id>7931061</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210978800000</time><rsvp_limit>985</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7931061/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>