<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In the kick off of the new Boston Integral commons incarnation, we will tackle the idea of Integral communities.  There are already many integral salons in place throughout the world where like-minded individuals can come together and talk about integral ideas.  In addition, the online medium has made it possible for integrally-minded people to find each other to share ideas and opinions on various topics.  &lt;b&gt;But when we talk about sustainable integral communities, we are really bringing out the need for a physical space where people can co-create something in the presence of collective being.  What would these integral communities look like?  What would be their purpose?&lt;/b&gt;  Some integral advocates have said that you may need to emphasize that this is sort of new religion with its own creeds, practices, position papers, texts, philosophies, and so forth in order to build something beyond a once-a-month coffee house gathering.  Some mention that there would need to be a flexible model to cater to the “spiritual buffet” of offerings in accord to one’s own spiritual path.  Others have stressed that such communities should mimic the quadrants and developmental levels, in that buddha, dharma, and sangha can come together respecting the spiral at hand.  &lt;b&gt;In any case, there appears to be agreement that for a community to evolve, there must be a vision and purpose, commitment by its members, and the structure and space that can hold it in place.&lt;/b&gt;  In this meetup, we will take this topic directly on in a no holds barred way.  Your ideas and opinions will help shape where we go as an integral community in the greater Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Much love, &lt;br /&gt;Ted &amp;amp; Nicole&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole Trudel Churchill</member_name><member_id>3348175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238717905000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234979807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Integral Communities: The Why and The What</name><id>9768688</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236298500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/9768688/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/f/global_7098607.jpeg</photo_url></item>