<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;read the entire event listing&lt;/span&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;answer all of the questions&lt;/span&gt; that are part of the RSVP process. If you RSVP from a mobile device you may not see them - visit the site using a computer so you can answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your safety and the safety of the group is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of the trip; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you may put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared to respond to an emergency situation or being able to send a night in the woods if you have to. Bring your own stuff and know how to use it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We are going to visit the summits of two of the NH 48 - North Kinsman (#28 @ 4,293') and South Kinsman (#22 @ 4,358'). These two summits are the highest peaks along Kinsman-Cannon Ridge. The ledges below North and the mostly open summit of South offer great views of the Franconia Ridge across the Notch. We will be taking the less-used western approach - the Mount Kinsman Trail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expect winter conditions&lt;/strong&gt; (see updated list of stuff to bring below) and remember that it will be getting darker earlier now so we may finish in the dark.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted.&lt;/strong&gt; All participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are permitted&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on this hike provided they are well-behaved, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, you clean up after them, and you have a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;one-way trip we will use Mount Kinsman Trail and Kinsman Ridge Trail. Along the way we will summit both North and South Kinsman. You will need to be prepared for &lt;strong&gt;wet&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;muddy&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;snow-covered&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;icy&lt;/strong&gt; conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about 9.8 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,900 feet&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- for perspective the top floor of the Empire State Building is about 1,250 feet. It should take an average hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;about 9 hours 30 minutes to complete&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;this trip - this estimate is adjusted to allow for slower travel during winter (carrying heavier packs) and includes time for changing clothing (to regulate your temperature) and gear (putting on/taking off snow shoes or crampons) along the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip is considered&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/photos/2030971/"&gt;Click here for information about&amp;nbsp;our trip ratings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did all of my research for this trip using the Appalachian Mountain Club's&amp;nbsp;"White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards&amp;nbsp;since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click below&amp;nbsp;for more information about each peak:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6898"&gt;North Kinsman (peakbagger.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6899"&gt;South Kinsman (peakbagger.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/?ll=44.129,-71.735&amp;amp;z=13&amp;amp;type=Terrain&amp;amp;label=South-Kinsman-North-Kinsman"&gt;Current trail conditions&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/?ll=44.129,-71.735&amp;amp;z=13&amp;amp;type=Terrain&amp;amp;label=South-Kinsman-North-Kinsman"&gt;(TrailsNH.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as described here (e.g. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. The higher we climb the colder, windier, and wetter it will be - we will need to be prepared. Remember, on average it gets 3-4 degrees (Fahrenheit) colder for every 1,000 feet of elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&amp;nbsp;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or out on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the snow out of your boots. While we may not need snow shoes on the hike you need to bring them to the trailhead - know how to attach them to your pack in case we do need to bring them along. Traction - while 10-12 point mountaineering crampons aren't necessary, microspikes (or something similar) are. If you bring crampons make sure they are the correct type for your boot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and conducts heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket (e.g. fleece). Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants (e.g. gore-tex). Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners. Windproof/waterproof&amp;nbsp;over-mittens&amp;nbsp;(e.g. gore-tex).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - it's time to switch from a hydration pack (e.g. camalbak) because the hose tends to freeze. Use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead (e.g. nalgene).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;You should always be prepared to&amp;nbsp;spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket (which packs small and weighs just ounces).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in colder temperatures). Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trail climbs to the Kinsman Ridge Trail from a recently relocated trailhead on the east side of NH 116. The new trailhead, with a short road leading into a large parking area, is 4.7 mi. south of NH 18 in Franconia village, just beyond the Tamarack Tennis Camp, and 1.7 mi. north of the Easton town hall.&amp;nbsp;According to Google Maps this spot is about 151 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 35 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.164961,-71.765851(Mount+Kinsman+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.164961,-71.765851&amp;amp;sspn=0.009282,0.019376&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFWHnoQIdpfC4-w&amp;amp;vpsrc=0&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;here&amp;nbsp;for the driving directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Once you open Google Maps simply change the generic starting point ("Boston, MA") to your own starting point to get customized directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate&amp;nbsp;in this activity; you know and will follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in either a white or a green Toyota Highlander with MA Plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1323111293000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321622045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K North &amp; South Kinsman (INTEREMDIATE)</name><id>41613712</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323001800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/41613712/</event_url></item>