<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Aborn St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>331-8829</phone><name>Cuban Revolution</name><city>Providence</city><id>493494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415690</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event is hosted by the local chapter of AIGA–the professional organization for design, of which I'm a member. This is open to the public and should be a nice social event. If you are creative, excited about the election, enjoy rubbing shoulders with creative people, or just think Cuban Revolution as a venue is cool, this event is for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AIGA RI - “Viva Choice!”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Election Day is November 4 – less than 10 days away! Since 2000, AIGA has been encouraging people to exercise their right to vote in local and national elections by inviting designers from across the United States to create nonpartisan posters for the AIGA Get Out the Vote campaign. AIGA Rhode Island is participating through a special:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Get Out the Vote” @ Cuban Revolution, 60 Valley Street, Providence, RI - Thursday October 30th 6-8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AIGA Rhode Island invites you to join us for a viewing of some of this year’s posters at DxN. Discuss, exchange opinions and prime yourself to pull that lever on November 4th. Posters will also be available for you to post in your community – or in your workspace as a reminder and memento.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the national non-partisan campaign that is about encouraging voting visit: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aiga.org/content.cfm/get-out-the-vote" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aiga.org/c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;email me if you'd like more information or my cell phone to make sure we connect. - val&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is open to the public. I'll probably be there around 7.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225577622000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225029398000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Viva Choice – Get Out the Vote Poster Exhibit and Cocktail Party</name><id>9033543</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225404000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/9033543/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/3/global_3163235.jpeg</photo_url></item>