<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>140 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.177994</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 429 1500</phone><name>The Meadows</name><city>Holliston</city><id>959576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.442941</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I apologize for not having a meet in March due to a couple of family crises that have now passed! I know we could have allused a meet to go to during all that cold rain!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next meet is on April 18th, from 12:30-2:30 pm, and 3 pm - 5 pm.  It is again of course at Holliston Meadows, 140 Summer St, Holliston, MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Heidi  Sedovsky and her lovely little Peanut are the hostess/assistants for the 12:30 group and Barbara Stryer and personality-plus Gabi are the hostess/assistants for the 3 pm meet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please sign up for the time of meet you want,&lt;/b&gt; so that we can make sure that we have enough room for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again, each meet can hold 20 members/couples/family.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last time, we had a very manageable number of people and dogs at the 12:30-2:30 pm, but an overflow of people at the 3 pm - 5 pm because some people did not sign up for a particular time slot.  I hate to turn anyone away, but it gets too full and less peaceful if there are too many people and dogs! Plus it is more fun for our dogs if they have enough room to play!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is an outdoor space adjacent to our meetup room, where dogs can go out to potty etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP as soon as possible to reserve a space, and let me know what kind of food or beverage you'd like to bring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am so looking forward to seeing you all again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small dog best!&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;laptopmaltese@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask someone where I am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271781423000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270307537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BOSTON MALTESE &amp; TINY DOG MEETUP  SUNDAY  April 18th, 12:30-2:30 pm and 3 pm-5pm</name><id>13075938</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271608200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/13075938/</event_url></item>