<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Alewife T Station</address_2><address_1>5 Cambridge Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.394234</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-2200</phone><name>Bertucci's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>838765</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.144722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>New England Organizers Meetup for September 2010 and now its time for Review and Planning for a Fun Year Ahead. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group will only be helpful if you make an extra effort to help and to real try to attend the bi-yearly meetings as they happen. WE ARE NEVER GOING TO HAVE A PREFECT LOCATION so instead of complaining about location offer to run a meeting in your area please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will  do short introductions and we will not spend too much time crying over spilt milk its NOT a time to complain,  but a time to reflect and make improvements to this and to your groups more importantly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting will be 1 hour long so please do not be late and afterwards there will be a 30 minute free period to chat with others and for a short follow-up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is MBTA assessable via the Redline Alewife MBTA Station stop and there is FREE parking across the street from the Bertucci and its marked as such. YOU DO NOT have to pay to park here since we are eating at Bertucci.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bertucci is actual inside connected to one side of the MBTA station but is accessible from the street /side walk too.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Subjects of interest: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also ask for 5 more loyal helpful loyal Social Fun members and 5 more Social Fun Organizers to attend as well provide more feedback and make this more of a productive working meeting! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll discuss RSVPing and low turn out, how to lay out events to increase turnout, including what info to provide for members and good free location to use, and we’ll leave a extra half hour to socialize more afterward and to ask questions to each other!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That should keep us busy for 1 hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok so please let me know if you can make this its important and will help us all. You are NOT alone in your Meetup issue we all go through these!&lt;br /&gt;Thanks and ciao&lt;br /&gt;Biagio&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Biagio</member_name><member_id>3847345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296324224000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Organizers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>NEOrganizers</urlname><id>321127</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>New England Meetup Organizers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276608027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Organizers Meetup for September 2010</name><id>13806372</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284933600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NEOrganizers/events/13806372/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/a/global_13341098.jpeg</photo_url></item>