<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since Tom said this film is hysterical, I (Nicole) thought this would make a fun Friday night flick.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The action-packed new comedy from the makers of Shaun of the Dead stars co-writer Simon Pegg as Nicholas Angel, the finest cop London has to offer. He's so good, he makes everyone else look bad, so Angel's superiors send him to a place where his talents won't be quite so embarrassing -- the sleepy and seemingly crime-free village of Sandford. Once there, he is partnered with well-meaning but overeager police officer Danny Butterman (Nick Frost), a huge action movie fan looking for a chance to experience the life of gunfights and car chases he's only dreamed about. Co-starring Jim Broadbent, Paddy Considine, Steve Coogan, Timothy Dalton and Martin Freeman. Directed and co-written by Edgar Wright. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Simon Pegg, Nick Frost, Jim Broadbent, Paddy Considine, Steve Coogan, Timothy Dalton, Martin Freeman, Anne Reid, Billie Whitelaw, Stuart Wilson, Edward Woodward&lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: R&lt;br /&gt;Run Time: 2hrs 1min&lt;br /&gt;Release Year: 2007&lt;br /&gt;Country Of Origin: UK &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film will be hosted by Nicole. Look for her AFTER the film as she will be standing in the front of the theater with a meetup sign. After the film we will head off to Anise for appetizers and drinks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179097276000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178642125000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Still Hot! -- Hot Fuzz</name><id>5755618</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178924400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5755618/</event_url></item>