<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Salem, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.523510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>812-240-3236</phone><name>Salem Common</name><city>Salem</city><id>365193</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895233</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/2/4/event_108974372.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Before the competition starts, our fictional countries from around the world will be joining hands to engage in a cooperative, team building ceremony. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assuming good weather today, we will be hosting the Minilympic Opening Ceremony out on the gazebo on the Salem Common (if not, we will retreat indoors to some place in downtown Salem).  Teams will be asked to participate in the most important ritual of the games: the construction of the Minilympic Torch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...And of course, it wouldn't be a proper ceremony if the torch construction wasn't a game in it of itself. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Minilympic Torch will be made out of Jenga blocks.  The goal will be to increase the height of torch as much as possible.  Each team that participates will receive bonus points before the official games begin based on how many levels you can make the tower.  This is not competitive and there is no penalty for knocking the tower down.  You all will have to work together in the spirit of universal harmony to maximize the amount of points you all can receive.  :-D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, any team that doesn't help with the construction will not be eligible for bonus points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you aren't participating in the Minilympics you are more than welcome to come spectate. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336417183000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334007262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Minilympics: Opening Ceremony</name><id>59884952</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336330800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/59884952/</event_url></item>