<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>152 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02568</zip><lat>41.457836</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(800) 264-8941</phone><name>Raw B &amp; B</name><city>Vineyard Haven</city><id>1261668</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.603661</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Raw Vegan Bed &amp;amp; Breakfast&lt;br /&gt;raw food certification vacation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We wanted to put together a special package that would rawk your socks off at a great value. And I think we’ve done exactly that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOUR PACKAGE INCLUDES ALL OF THE FOLLOWING (AT NO EXTRA CHARGE!):&lt;br /&gt;*all meals – breakfast, (picnic) lunch, dinner, ample snacks and goodies&lt;br /&gt;*beachfront yoga in the mornings&lt;br /&gt;*a bike tour of Edgartown, the pristine waterfront town on the other side of the island&lt;br /&gt;*a bike tour of Vineyard Haven, the lovely year-round port&lt;br /&gt;*a bike tour of Oak Bluffs, the charming and colorful town with all the gingerbread cottages&lt;br /&gt;*a walking tour of the Vineyard Haven area&lt;br /&gt;*your stay at the historic bed and breakfast half a block from the beach&lt;br /&gt;*Level 1 Chef Certification – go home certified as a raw food chef&lt;br /&gt;*Level 2 Instructor Certification – go home certified to teach others to become raw food chefs, armed with the knowledge of how to get a business started&lt;br /&gt;*Mini classes on the following: pizza, calzones, breads, crackers, ice cream, desserts, nut milks, smoothies, sprouting, juices, and more!&lt;br /&gt;*Connect with other raw foodies and enjoy the company of like-minded individuals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***********************************&lt;br /&gt;May 14, 2010 to May 17, 2010&lt;br /&gt;***********************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just picture it… you’re on Martha’s Vineyard… at one of the most beautiful vacation destinations on the planet… in a historic bed and breakfast… less than a block from the beach… with people who “get it”… exploring… having fun… learning with others… sharing with others… making life-long connections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**********************&lt;br /&gt;THE BASIC DETAILS&lt;br /&gt;**********************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHO&lt;br /&gt;Anyone interested in raw food + vacation on the gorgeous island of Martha’s Vineyard. We will spend a full afternoon talking about the business side of teaching classes to others, so this is geared towards entrepreneurs and those who want to share raw food with others. HOWEVER, if you are interested in the vacation and learning but want to explore the island during that afternoon, that would be perfectly fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT&lt;br /&gt;4 days/3 nights of biking, hiking, exploring, un-cooking and a nice mix of relaxation and adventure&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN&lt;br /&gt;Check-in is Friday, May 14 at 3:30pm (although early and late arrivals are OK)&lt;br /&gt;Check-out is Monday, May 17 at 11am (although you may leave early or keep your bags here to stay longer and explore)&lt;br /&gt;[Note: You have the option to stay up to 4 additional nights at a discounted rate, if desired (ask for details - less than $80/night/person!).]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE&lt;br /&gt;Main Street, Vineyard Haven, Martha’s Vineyard, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHY&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a mix of learning, relaxation, exploration with other like-minded travelers. And have an amazing vacation at the same time. :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawbnb.com/certification-vacation" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawbnb.com/certification-vacation" target="_blank"&gt;http://rawbnb.com/cer...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/members/8405637/"&gt;Eva Rawposa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW MUCH&lt;br /&gt;Total cost (ALL INCLUSIVE - including the B&amp;amp;B stay, Living on&lt;br /&gt;Live Food Chef &amp;amp; Instructor certifications, meals, tours, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;is $966 BEFORE a 10% discount for locals. There is a discount&lt;br /&gt;code - boston - that zaps 10% off.&lt;br /&gt;(option to stay up to 4 additional nights with breakfast only at $79.55/pp/pn/dbl)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawbnb.com/certification-vacation"&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawbnb.com/certification-vacation" target="_blank"&gt;http://rawbnb.com/cer...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://rawbnb.com/wp-content/themes/thesis_17/custom/images/header-rawbnb.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://rawbnb.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/04/MV-collage1.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(posted by &lt;a href="http://www.essenic.org"&gt;www.essenic.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eva Rawposa</member_name><member_id>8405637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273880406000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272840987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raw Chef Certification Vacation</name><id>13360462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273865400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/13360462/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/5/global_14778709.jpeg</photo_url></item>