<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; News, Announcements&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Semantic Web Awareness Initiative – Marketing -- by Dean Whitney&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; The SIRA Technology: Ontology + NLP + ? = Natural Language Understanding -- by Chuck Rehberg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Semantic Web Awareness Initiative – Marketing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are numerous applications for semantic web technologies in the marketing and advertising space. Brand managers, ad agencies and strategists need to understand the value if they are going to start leveraging it. If there was an initiative to explain the potential, collect and organize case studies/examples, manage ideas and promote the value of semantic web technology it could result in more mainstream applications. This presentation will highlight some of the high level ideas and open a discussion to get more insight from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dean Whitney is a interactive strategist, user experience expert and president of Garfield Group Interactive – an integrated digital agency.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The SIRA Technology: Ontology + NLP + ? = Natural Language Understanding”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Semantic Insights™ (a Division of Trigent Software) has been developing a system that applies [and grows] Ontologies to the process of Natural Language Understanding of written prose. We have numerous patents applied and some granted. Among other things, this allows us to: apply domain knowledge to machine-based Natural Language Understanding, grow Ontologies, map a given text to a given Ontology, and to compare two Ontologies. To accomplish this we have made specific extension to current Semantic Web notions of Ontology. Although not appropriate for this forum, the full breadth of our work anticipates machine augmented human cognition. This presentation will introduce the essential concepts of our approach and demo an application of these concepts. I will be sharing a work-in-progress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chuck Rehberg, CTO, Trigent Software, CSO, Semantic Insights™, www.semanticinsights.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Star Conference Room. 4th Floor, Stata Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>William S Hayes</member_name><member_id>8504830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260316962000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Semantic Web Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1336198</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge Semantic Web</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255475453000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Semantic Web November Meetup</name><id>xmbklympbnb</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257894000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group/events/11620429/</event_url></item>