<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Pine St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371396</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-893-2500</phone><name>Embassy Cinema</name><city>Waltham</city><id>751478</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.235373</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Short notice.  Watchmen at Embassy Theater on Thursday!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watchmen was a twelve-issue comic book limited series created by writer Alan Moore, artist Dave Gibbons, and colorist John Higgins. The series was first published by DC Comics during 1986 and 1987, and featured original characters so as to avoid problems with future story lines.  Moore used the story to reflect on contemporary anxieties and to critique the superhero concept. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watchmen takes place in a United States similar to our own.  But don't let that fool you.  In the alternate US depicted by Moore,  superheroes emerged in the 1940s and 1960s, and helped the United States to win the Vietnam War. As the country edges closer to a nuclear war with the Soviet Union, freelance costumed vigilantes are outlawed and most costumed superheroes enter retirement or take up working for the government. Moore's story focuses on the personal development and struggles of several superheroes who are pulled out of retirement following the murder of one of their own, and who must confront a nuclear plot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watchmen received critical acclaim both in the comics and mainstream press, and is regarded by critics as a seminal text of the comic book medium. After a number of attempts to adapt the series into a feature film, director Zack Snyder's Watchmen was finally released in March 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternative beverages optional, wear your winter coats&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan</member_name><member_id>2230421</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238525221000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237864579000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday night movie</name><id>10021708</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238110200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/10021708/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/f/global_6760543.jpeg</photo_url></item>