<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1001 Watertown St., Rear (shares the huge parking lot with CVS)</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.349796</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gymnasium</name><city>West Newton</city><id>11891252</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.225052</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I LOVE my gym - incredibly holistic &amp;amp; integrative approach, warm community, fun workouts. They have an awesome free event coming up, thought this would be relevant for many of you. I've copied the details below, check it out and hope to see you there. ~Taylor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Performance vs. Longevity: You Don’t Have To Choose (Free event)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: Gymnasium &lt;br /&gt;

1001 Watertown St., Rear (We share the huge parking lot with CVS) &lt;br /&gt;

West Newton, MA 02465 &lt;br /&gt;

When: March 9, 2013, 1:00-5:30pm (Doors open at 12 pm) &lt;br /&gt;

RSVP: By March 2 please, to &lt;a href="mailto:josh.conway@inspiredperspiration.com"&gt;josh.conway@inspiredperspiration.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full Details; including what to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.inspiredperspiration.com/march-9th-free-event-performance-vs-longevity-you-dont-have-to-choose/"&gt;http://www.inspiredperspiration.com/march-9th-free-event-performance-vs-longevity-you-dont-have-to-choose/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sessions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1) *Active Isolated Stretching: Stretch For Mobility, Resilience, Recovery and Performance*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LED BY &lt;br /&gt;

Peter Benjamin LMT, CPT, AIST &lt;br /&gt;

1:00-1:50pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn how this one advanced stretching technique can help you... &lt;br /&gt;

• Make an 80% recovery in 10-15 minutes &lt;br /&gt;

• Prevent and heal injuries to muscles, tendons and ligaments &lt;br /&gt;

• Build resilience and performance - at the same time &lt;br /&gt;

• Reprogram your brain and body with a much greater range of motion &lt;br /&gt;

The Active Isolated Stretching (AIS) Technique is ideal for athletes who are aging or dealing with injuries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2) *Twice The Results In Half The Time: Build Power, Strength AND Resilience With Kettlebells*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LED BY &lt;br /&gt;

Josh Conway, CPT, WKC Coach, &amp;amp; Founder, Inspired Perspiration &lt;br /&gt;

2:00-2:50pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most athletes face increased risk of injuries and grim prospects as they age as a result of demanding training regimes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kettlebell training, done properly, integrates strength, power and flexibility with your body’s natural movements. Learn how to increase performance AND resilience simultaneously, and be better, faster, and stronger - for longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3) *Chiropractic And Sports Medicine: Are Your Fitness And Health Aligned?*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LED BY &lt;br /&gt;

Dr. Karson Mui, DC &lt;br /&gt;

3:00-3:50pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Active lifestyles rely on a strong, healthy core and spine. Learn how chiropractic and sports medicine techniques improve your performance, range of motion and posture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Mui covers techniques including Graston, FAKTR, vibration plate therapy, flexion distraction and kinesio taping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4) *How Your Fitness Is Hurting You And What To Do About It*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LED BY &lt;br /&gt;

Josh Conway, CPT, WKC Coach, &amp;amp; Founder, Inspired Perspiration &lt;br /&gt;

4:00-5:15pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s no surprise that many programs produce as much injury as they do fitness and health. Even holistic approaches such as yoga can result in overuse and hyperextension injuries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The solution is simple: We need to exercise in ways that mimic and enhance the body’s natural movements and functions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re a fitness instructor, regular gym-goer or casual walker, these 10 essential movements and strength patterns will get you to peak health and keep you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Josh Conway</member_name><member_id>11945200</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Taylor Jacobson</member_name><member_id>25978182</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362873188000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361815579000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Performance vs. Longevity: You Don’t Have To Choose (Free event)</name><id>106331002</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>19800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362848400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/106331002/</event_url></item>