<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>5 minutes from Park Street T</address_2><address_1>42 Province Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-426-3333</phone><name>Kennedy's Midtown</name><city>Boston </city><id>1088491</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060079</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What is a story slam ? Based on a poetry slam format and similar to American Idol, a story slam is a contest of wit, words and in this case, story by known and undiscovered talent. massmouth posts a theme on it's blogspot and story slammers sign up on the night to tell a 5-minute short story on the evening's theme . Ten lucky tellers will be picked at random, or participants can opt to listen, or join a judging team. There will be 3 teams of 3 judges and the 2 sets of 5 stories will begin with a short-short feature by one of the judges. Listeners will be engaged in story improv games and other entertainment between the 5 minute features. And the audience will have full service for the pub menu and bar at &lt;a href="http://www.kennedysmidtown.com/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kennedysmi...&lt;/a&gt;. Their menu is varied and the food is good! Stories start at 7PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month's theme is &amp;quot;scared to death &amp;quot;. We are looking for real stories of fear, terror and dread, which may be supernatural or plain as mud. Each of the ten 5 minute stories is judged on how well it is told, how well it is constructed and how well it honors the time limit and relates to the theme. The 3 highest-scoring tellers are awarded prizes and an opportunity to perform at the &amp;quot;the big mouthoff&amp;quot; venue and date TBA. Prizes will be awarded at each slam. There is a $5.00 cover and a one drink minimum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;October 26, 2009 from 6pm stories start at 7PM to 9:30PM&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kennedy's Midtown&lt;br /&gt;Street: 42 Province Street&lt;br /&gt;City/Town: Boston - 5 minutes from Park Street T&lt;br /&gt;Website or Map: &lt;a href="http://www.kennedysmidtown..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kennedysmi...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 617-426-3333&lt;br /&gt;Event Type: storyslam, competitive, openmic&lt;br /&gt;Organized By: Doria Hughes Norah Dooley Andrea Lovett Stu Mendleson&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256780829000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255037901000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Story Slam!</name><id>11583577</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256594400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/11583577/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/1/4/global_11121860.jpeg</photo_url></item>