<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West Broadway St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01440</zip><lat>42.564140</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 730 8094</phone><name>The Haunted Victorian</name><city>Gardner</city><id>1386224</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.002910</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you ever driven by the beautiful Victorian mansion on Rte 2A in South Gardner and wondered whether it was haunted? Well, it is.&lt;br /&gt;It was even featured on an episode of &amp;quot;Ghost Hunters&amp;quot; and in the book haunted New England.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  The mansion has new owners now, and they are opening up their home for serious investigations by paranormal groups. We have scheduled a joint meetup with the Footsteps Paranormal meetup to conduct an all-night investigaiton of the mansion. &lt;br /&gt;I can personally attest to the presence of spirits in this house, as I knew the past owner,&lt;br /&gt;Mark Voux, and have spoken extensively with the new owner, Edwin, and it sounds like the ghostly activity has increased with the new owners, with slamming doors, footsteps, the doorbell ringing with no one there and spector being seen as well as showing up on photos.&lt;br /&gt;If you've ever wanted an opportunity to investigate a haunted house, then here's your chance!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out their website at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hauntedvictorian.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://hauntedvictori...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a paid event: $50 per person, payable in advance. For an all-night investigation, this is a very reasonable price. The are only (7) spots available, and this time it IS strictly adhered to-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When::&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 20, 8pm - ?  I don't know what the cutoff time is, but I imagine it will last until the early hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:&lt;br /&gt;The house is on the corner of Union Street and Rte 2A in Gardner. It's a beautiful 3-story yellow Victorian with a turret.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost:&lt;br /&gt;$50 per person, payable in advance. If you sign up, please send Sandy MacLeod a check no later than October 16th for the full amount. We will be paying the owners in advance for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sandy MacLeod&lt;br /&gt;7 Old Princeton Road Cutoff&lt;br /&gt;Hubbardston, MA 01452&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who want to, we will be meeting before the event for supper at 7:00pm at the Southside Grill (Mexican/American Restaurant), on Rte 2A in Gardner. Please let  Sandy  know in advance when you send your check if you are planning on going so that I can make reservations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equipment:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a flashlight and any investigation equipment you have (camera, digital voice recorder, etc.) We will have a video setup on location to take video of the most active rooms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is somthing written by the new owner:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello &amp;amp; good evening, I'm currently the new home owner of the victorian mansion. since we purchased the home late last year we have been having odd things going on. such as objects moving in front of us (cups &amp;amp; a metal plant holder). The first week we bought the home we had placed an xmas ornament on the mantle left to go back to our apt. and found the ornament on the middle of floor (glass ornament didn't break) so we decided to just place it in the corner of the room with other xmas stuff we left &amp;amp; when we came back to the house we found it was back in the middle of the floor again// our neighbors have ? if we a have any young children staying at the house they notice at night a young boy running back &amp;amp; forth (problem is we don't have children) The piano did play one Sunday morning twice, our TV shuts off &amp;amp; turns on, Our dogs will not go towards the staircase at all even if we throw a toy/treat, they bark&amp;amp; growl up the staircase for no reason .//we have a door that slams going up the 3rd floor/in the basement shadows &amp;amp; footsteps are seen &amp;amp; heard. We also smell odd orders through out the house one order is in the master bedroom where it smells like a camp fire there was a man who back in 1963 who died there (spontaneous combustion) I recently did some research on the home and found out a woman was murdered there back when the house was a brothel. //Orbs in many of our pictures/ While working in my office late afternoon I saw a face that appeared in front of me which almost knocked me off my chair. (I actually got mad) I was later told a man had passed away in front of the pizza shop around the same time./ there is more but its late &amp;amp; I'm tired. //Eventually we will have tours again just as the previous owners did maybe around Halloween. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1290437760000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285521548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Haunted Victorian Mansion Investigation</name><id>14900642</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290301200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/14900642/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/f/global_3694063.jpeg</photo_url></item>