<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>970 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.761542</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-521-8495</phone><name>COSI</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>867623</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.743376</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The New Moon Book Club serves to connect a community of like-minded souls to discuss topics related to understanding, enhancing and sustaining the health of the human and planetary energy field. Topics such as spirituality, holistic health, disease prevention, living green, nourishment, feng shui and more will be discussed. It is also a forum for those interested in holistic health to ask questions and share information about healing practices. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: sandybrown"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Discussion for the February meetup will include Part IV:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perceptual Tools of the Healer  (all chapters)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New Moon Book Club discusses the &lt;i&gt;Hands of Light&lt;/i&gt; by Barbara Ann Brennan, a classic on the topic of energy healing. Published in 1987, &lt;i&gt;Hands of Light&lt;/i&gt; is a scientist's look at the field of bioenergetic healing. Trained as a physicist and psychotherapist, Brennan spent 15 years studying the human energy field and working as a healer. &lt;i&gt;Hands of Light&lt;/i&gt; goes beyond conventional, objective knowledge while retaining scientific clarity. It details a study of the human energy field and how it is intimately connected to a person's health and well being. This book is a must-read for for anyone involved in healing and conscious health care, including people seeking to heal themselves. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the New Moon is a special time during the moon cycle, each month around this time, we will meet to focus on creation and inspiration. This is the best time to begin new projects, birth ideas and tap into your innate creative powers to fulfill your life's purpose. Please join us if you are currently reading or have read &lt;i&gt;Hands of Light&lt;/i&gt; and would like to participate in the discussion. The New Moon Book Club meets on the third Sunday of the month which is usually a few days away from the time of the new moon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: yellow"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note: this event has spots available for just 8 people due to space limitations. So please kindly RSVP only if you are absolutely positive you will attend the meetup. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the cafe.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269376596000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268355841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Moon Meetup &amp; Book Club Discussion</name><id>12854035</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269203400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/12854035/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/6/global_11765222.jpeg</photo_url></item>