<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Cummings Center, Suite 435-K</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.558906</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 864-7076</phone><name>Eternal Balance</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1226709</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887042</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please come to our two hour Art of Natural Breathing class, where you will have a wonderful and deep experience of yourself through breathing in this connected way. During seasonal changes, in the Fall and other times of transition the breath is of utmost importance to allow us a safe and easy passage into the next cycle of being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breathing is the foundation for all life processes. On all levels the breath is a prerequisite for growth and transformation, whether we are looking at a single cell, entire tissue structures or the organ system. Human beings, animals, plants and the whole planet depend on the flow of life-force. Our reversed inner tree of life, the bronchial tree resides within our chest allowing us, through the medium of the breath, to make this connection between our outer and inner worlds. With every inhale and exhale we take part in this infinite exchange of giving and taking. Our breath connects us in every moment with the alternating current of life at the same time it can free us from the claims of our material existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dunja Carlson-Moeller Ph.D. has done extensive research and clinical training in medical anthropology. She wrote &amp;ldquo;Gentle Medicine&amp;rdquo;, a book on anthroposophical medicine. She has worked at the Center for Psychology and Social Change at Harvard Medical School, where she chaired an academic and interdisciplinary forum addressing healing and social change. Her expertise lies in an integral approach, bridging the world of western medicine and alternative health. She is both a Body Memories and The Art of Natural Breathing Master Practitioner and teacher, is certified in Postural Integration (deep tissue structural bodywork), and graduated from the Lynn Andrews Center for Sacred Arts and Training. Her private practice is located in Billerica, Massachusetts. Breathing fully and sharing it with the world has become a way of life for Dunja.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday, March 29 at 7 to 9pm &lt;br /&gt;

Cost: $40 (scholarships available)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olga </member_name><member_id>10158912</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333127154000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>members with unlimited potential</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club</urlname><id>1467921</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Holistic Lifestyle  Women's Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330995896000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art of Natural Breathing</name><id>55135332</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333062000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club/events/55135332/</event_url></item>