<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Here's the first of what we hope will be a series of extracurricular ATC+ activities: A hands-on Goddess Doll Workshop taught by our very own Dori. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WORKSHOP DESCRIPTION:&lt;/b&gt; An afternoon of appeasing your goddess within? What could be better? You'll create a 3-D piece of art in the form of a goddess of your choice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can work from Greek, Roman, Norse, Celtic, Hindu or Native American myths,just to name a few. Or you can design your own personal goddess!  How about a chocolate goddess ?  A pregnancy or menopause goddess? A domestic goddess?  You are only limited by your own imagination! No previous art experience required. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S INCLUDED:&lt;/b&gt; Hands-on instruction, a goddess torso shaped like the universal Earth goddess, and a polymer clay face, as well as access to ArtStudio 360 (see details under &amp;quot;Cost.&amp;quot;). The firm cardboard torso is gessoed so that it's ready to receive your artwork and embellishments, and you may choose between an open-eyed and a closed-eyed face (if you enroll, you'll be asked to e-mail Dori with your choice).  &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;For sample goddess dolls, see the Photos section. They're GORGEOUS, and you'll be able to make something along the same lines, but of your very own design. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING: &lt;/b&gt; Bring paints, collage paper, fabrics, rubber stamps and pads, brads, buttons, charms, old jewelry, lace and anything else you have in your artistic toolbox! Note: The host venue, ArtStudio 360, can supply scissors, basic glue sticks, some basic acrylic paints  and a few embellishment odds and ends, but we encourage you to bring your own favorite tools and materials.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Also:&lt;/i&gt; Please bring an informal story (verbal, not written) about your goddess to share with your fellow artists. Tell us why you chose this particular goddess to honor, or why you made up your own. And please feel free to release your own inner goddess: Wear your own goddess crowns, jewels or attire, if you desire. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $30, which includes instruction, materials and access to ArtStudio 360 during and following the workshop. ArtStudio has ample free parking, work tables and chairs, a restroom, a kitchen with fridge/microwave/sink, spring water, Wi-Fi, and access to a rich range of shared tools and supplies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt; You &lt;i&gt;must&lt;/i&gt; RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function so we know who's coming and how many to expect. Please don't e-mail anyone or post a message here to RSVP; use the RSVP function, which will instantly reserve your slot. Sorry, no &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; RSVPs for this one--we need a firm headcount.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/b&gt; If &lt;u&gt;we&lt;/u&gt; need to cancel due to weather, we'll post a message here AND e-mail or call anyone who's RSVP'd as far in advance as possible, probably by the night before. &lt;b&gt;SNOW DATE:&lt;/b&gt; To be announced, if needed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we need to cancel due to low enrollment, we'll make that call by Thursday, 2/19. So if you're interested, &lt;u&gt;don't wait until the last minute&lt;/u&gt;: Sign up NOW. You can always change your RSVP later. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;If you need to cancel, you may do so without penalty until 10 a.m. the day of the event. If you cancel after 10 a.m. on the day of the event (when it's too late for us to cancel or reschedule), or if you RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and then don't show, we will ask you to pay the full workshop fee anyway&lt;/u&gt;. (This is because Dori will have prepared all the materials in advance and driven an hour each way to teach the workshop.) You will receive all the materials for the workshop at a future date, so you'll still be able to get goddess-like on your own. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONTACT INFORMATION: &lt;/b&gt; We'll e-mail the address in Holliston, and your hosts' cell-phone numbers, before the workshop date. The address is also posted in the Message Board on the Web site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; NEED INSPIRATION? &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lowchensaustralia.com/names/gods.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowchensau...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.katyberry.com/Goddesses/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.katyberry....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt; &lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going to have a LOT of fun during and following this workshop. Join us!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Anne</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235847764000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232330257000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEW! Goddess Doll Workshop, taught by Dori</name><id>9552582</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235239200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/9552582/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/2/3/global_6986851.jpeg</photo_url></item>