<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>383 Dot Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02127</zip><lat>42.335083</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>GrandTen Distilling</name><city>Boston</city><id>9649172</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057205</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello liberty drinkers!!! Liberty Drinks is back with an awesome line up for 2013 and we are officially kicking it off on Saturday, March 23rd @ 1PM with the GrandTen Distilling Tour!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Owned and operated by two cousins(and the only employees) since early 2012, join us as we explore this hidden gem whose products are produced entirely by hand and distilled in copper. Since first acquiring government permission to open their doors, they are already a big hit and generously share their time and knowledge wi...th those interested in seeing how they distill their award winning products firsthand. The tour is expected to last for about an hour and we will also be able to sample all their products as well as the ones about to hit the market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT INFO: For those driving, there is plenty of free street parking and a lot behind the distillery. If you are coming via public transit, take the red line to either Broadway or Andrew Square since both are of equal distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GrandTen Distilling &lt;br /&gt;

383 Dorchester Avenue &lt;br /&gt;

Boston, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope everyone can make it out this fun event, and keep in mind this is also an opportunity to support a local business and help get their name out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for details on getting together at a local venue after our tour for more drinking and socializing.......&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364069425000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Libertarians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>libertarian-349</urlname><id>593245</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Libertarian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363297099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Liberty Drinks Does GrandTen Distilling Tour!</name><id>109298392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364058000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/libertarian-349/events/109298392/</event_url></item>