<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;PUB RUN IS STILL ON EVEN WITH THE SNOW!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HERE ARE THE DETAILS!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So pub run is in 2 days and I wanted to give a quick update. There has been a slight change of plans and we will be starting and ending at Whiskey's (which is less than a block from Lir!). The event starts at 2:00 pm and goes until we're done!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have my phone on me, so please send me a text if you can't make it the first bar and I can give you our location and ETA at the next bar my cell is 603.560.3897. With that said, here is the list of bars in order:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whiskey’s&lt;br /&gt;885 Boylston St, Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;(617) 262-5551&amp;#8206;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crossroads Irish Pub&lt;br /&gt;495 Beacon St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02215&lt;br /&gt;(617) 262-7371&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cask n Flagon&lt;br /&gt;62 Brookline Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;617 536-4840&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;O'Leary's&lt;br /&gt;1010 Beacon St&lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA 02446&lt;br /&gt;Phone: (617) 734-0049&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An Tua Nua&lt;br /&gt;835 Beacon St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02215-3303&lt;br /&gt;Phone: (617) 262-2121&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cornwall’s&lt;br /&gt;654 Beacon Street&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;(617) 262-3749&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FAQ:&lt;br /&gt;How long is Pub Run?&lt;br /&gt;It varies but we spend about 30 minutes at each bar and about 15 minutes to get everyone from one bar to the next!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How far is it between bars?&lt;br /&gt;About .5 miles, the longest is about .75 miles between bars. I mapped the distance and it looks like it ends up being a little less than 3 miles total.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What should I bring?&lt;br /&gt;Your ID, $$, T-pass, maybe a camera. I would recommend a small backpack or one of those cinch backpacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What should I wear?&lt;br /&gt;Running gear, including running shoes. Dressing in layers is highly recommended. If you have them, bring reflective materials/ blinking lights as it will be dark for the last few runs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What will happen if it rains?&lt;br /&gt;We'll get wet when running (yes pub run is rain or shine!) Right now the weather looks ok, with maybe a couple snow showers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where should I park?&lt;br /&gt;I wouldn't recommend driving at all, because I wouldn't recommend driving afterwards for safety reasons. There is also limited parking near Whiskey's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What should I do to get ready for Pub Run?&lt;br /&gt;Make sure to eat and hydrate well in the morning!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will it be fun?&lt;br /&gt;Well gosh, of course!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is there food?&lt;br /&gt;Well, as you know this is a free event, and there are no dues to be a member of the group, so there will not be free food. However, Whiskey's has 15 cent wings and last time we were there everyone pitched in and we got a couple plates full. If you need to stop along the way for food there are plenty of places in this little corridor of Boston!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy running and see you on Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jen&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in running gear with a beer in my hand</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230998801000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227301702000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pub Run</name><id>9208780</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229799600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/9208780/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/4/global_2413972.jpeg</photo_url></item>