<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.794332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 278-2670</phone><name>Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>716384</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.664378</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It time for the monthly First Thursday at the Wadsworth Atheneum.  Going to the Party, gets the movie for free.  Movie is at 8:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Phoenix Art After Hours provides a stimulating setting for mingling with friends after work. Sip a cocktail, enjoy music and other live performances, attend a gallery talk, and even see a classic movie or art film. The Wadsworth Atheneum is open until 8 pm the first Thursday of every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;High Water Marks&lt;br /&gt;See how the arts continue to be an agent of reconstruction in New Orleans in the exhibition opening of High Water Marks: Art &amp;amp; Renewal After Katrina presented by the Amistad Center for Art &amp;amp; Culture&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music&lt;br /&gt;Experience an eclectic mix of deep New Orleans rhythm and sound with the Congo Square Ramblers featuring Richard McGhee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hurricane Punch&lt;br /&gt;(Free while supplies last from Hartford Distributors, Inc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creole Cuisine&lt;br /&gt;Food provided by Rajun' Cajun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Constructing Art&lt;br /&gt;Gallery talk and community art project with exhibition artist Donald Boudreaux&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film 8 PM&lt;br /&gt;The Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call - New Orleans (2009)&lt;br /&gt;A drug- and gambling-addled detective in post-Katrina New Orleans investigates the murders of five Sengalese immigrants.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be floating around during the party and in the lobby downstairs prior to the movie.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273457830000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272715960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Thursday and Movie The Bad Lieutenant (with Nicholas Cage)</name><id>13347957</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273179600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/13347957/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>