<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1232 Whitney Ave,</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.346050</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 287-2401</phone><name>The Playwright Irish Pub and Restaurant in Hamden</name><city>Hamden</city><id>1073504</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.912486</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Well, we're almost there, My fellow travelers!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're getting together to celebrate and plan our strategy. We'll meet and choose our sightseeing options, listen to some traditional Irish music, share a great Irish meal and meet all our fellow travelers. If you need a roommate ...we'll be doing that as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have a pint (or two) in the pub between 3 and 5 pm, while listening to some great music and discuss our travel options. At 5 pm we'll move into the restaurant to break bread...Irish style! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come join us at our pre-Ireland get together and join in the fun! I want to welcome each and every one of you and we will all get together to introduce ourselves to one another. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, I have great news...I have been in touch with a Meetup group in Ireland and we are planning a meetup together. This is a meetup group based in Dublin with over 1200 members. Wow...we are gonna have a blast! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So try to make it on this special day so we can reunite with old friends, or make new ones. NEXT STOP...DUBLIN!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign on the table/ ask for Terri Bruno's table!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256173616000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253681128000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Irish Dinner, Music and Plannng Strategy for My Irish Travelers!</name><id>11444322</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255892400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/11444322/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/2/global_10861234.jpeg</photo_url></item>