<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us in our continuing exploration of Advanced Energy Healing.  A new DVD of advanced energy healing opportunities will be shown.  This includes topic of recharging the Krystos Seed Atom and Moda Adhura Centers for Manifestation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The resetting of the Cosmic Clock in this Time Matrix will also be expained as it relates to our Planetary Templar Complex.  The relationship between the cosmic clock and the Zodiac as well as Merkaba Mechanics will be explained also. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These teachings are part of Keylontic Science modality called Ka-Tha-Ra which is the ancient Anuhazi translation for &amp;quot;light-sound-one&amp;quot;.  The detailed technicals are FASCINATING!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is CORE level healing, from the inside out.  All miasms can be progressively cleared by drawing frequency from the 12th dimension, where our original DNA template for perpetual health has been preserved.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since members generally remain well beyond the posted 8:00 PM ending time.  Usually some members stay till 11:00 PM, so bring your own refreshments.  Although pristine pure well water will be provided, you might want to bring a sandwich or something to munch on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please do NOT park in the driveway with the &amp;quot;ULCS Clinic&amp;quot; sign. Instead go up the first driveway which has the Meetup Sign at the end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a good idea to check the website for a last minute cancellation notice before leaving!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349856570000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259716121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recharging Krystos Seed Atom Monad and Moda Adhura Manifestation Centers</name><id>11994932</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272751200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/11994932/</event_url></item>