<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Delwende&lt;/b&gt; by S. Pierre Yameogo (Burkina Fasco/France/Switzerland, 2005, 90 min.) is being screened as part of this year's African Film Festival at the MFA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Delwande&lt;/b&gt; tells a rousing story of a woman’s courage in the face of patriarchal injustice... is a landmark femininest-themed African film and is a worthy companion to Moolaadé and Faces of Women. MFA Description. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the review from The NY Times: &lt;br /&gt;S. Pierre Yameogo tackles social injustice in present-day Burkina Faso with grace, economy and exquisitely controlled anger. &lt;br /&gt;The instrument of his fury is Pougbila (Claire Ilboudo), a 16-year-old village beauty who elicits jealousy from the local girls and appreciative glances from their boyfriends. But the village elders are preoccupied with the decreasing rainfall and rising number of child deaths; led by Pougbila’s father (Célestin Zongo), they accuse her mother (Blandine Yameogo, the filmmaker’s cousin) of witchcraft and banish her to fend for herself. &lt;br /&gt;From here “Delwende” gathers momentum and emotional force as Pougbila, incensed, sets off to find her mother and expose her father’s shameful secrets. Cutting between the women’s journeys — one fearful and hopeless, the other purposeful and noble — Mr. Yameogo contrasts the shackles of tradition with the stirrings of rebellion, never allowing the heat of indignation to cloud his eye for a striking landscape or an expressive face. &lt;br /&gt;Using mostly nonprofessionals (Ms. Ilboudo is a dancer, and it shows), he demonstrates how superstition supports patriarchy and how easily both can slide into misogyny. In a country where women can be forced to drink a vile “truth potion” or become outcasts, Pougbila’s resolute march is more than just an act of defiance: it’s the promise of progress.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Strictly Film School: &lt;br /&gt;S. Pierre Yameogo returns from last year's NYAFF mid-career retrospective with perhaps his most mature, immediately relevant, and socially confrontational film to date, a provocative moral tale on the barbaric (and largely misogynistic) tribal custom of scapegoating through witch denunciation and exile - often of the most weak, disempowered, and vulnerable members of the village ....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Delwende&lt;/b&gt; favorably evokes the films of Ousmane Sembene and Idrissa Ouedraogo in its incisive social expositions of outmoded customs that contribute to the cultural stagnation of post-colonial Africa. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233367922000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Delwende at the MFA</name><id>9638059</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234724400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9638059/</event_url></item>