<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The movie starts at 7:30.  Let's meet in the lobby not later that 7:15.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hurt Locker: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hurt Locker is a riveting, suspenseful portrait of the courage under fire of the military's unrecognized heroes: the technicians of a bomb squad who volunteer to challenge the odds and save lives doing one of the world's most dangerous jobs. Three members of the Army's elite Explosive Ordnance Disposal (EOD) squad battle insurgents and one another as they search for and disarm a wave of roadside bombs on the streets of Baghdad—in order to try and make the city a safer place for Iraqis and Americans alike. Their mission is clear—protect and save—but it's anything but easy, as the margin of error when defusing a war-zone bomb is zero. This thrilling and heart-pounding look at the psychology of bomb technicians and the effects of risk and danger on the human psyche is a fictional tale inspired by real events by journalist and screenwriter Mark Boal, who was embedded with a special bomb unit in Iraq.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thehurtlocker-movie.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.thehurtlocker-movie.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Critics: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In Kathryn Bigelow's hands, the tale of an Army bomb squad unit deployed in Baghdad becomes a classic study of men in combat and the toll it takes.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- LA Times, Kenneth Turan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...captures the complexities of the war in Iraq with visceral suspense as well as explosive battle sequences and powerful performances.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- USA Today, Claudia Puig&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Kathryn Bigelow's The Hurt Locker, centered on an elite U.S. bomb squad in Baghdad, doesn't bring anything new to the table of grunts-in-the-firing-line movies &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- Variety, Derek Elley&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249428264000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248801524000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hurt Locker</name><id>10977480</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249254900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/10977480/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/global_9918257.jpeg</photo_url></item>