<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Beacon Hill</address_2><address_1>77 Charles St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.358330</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-523-9074 </phone><name>The Sevens</name><city>Boston</city><id>684711</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070396</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Everyone... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come and join me at The Sevens to help celebrate Nick's birthday!! Let's be sure to show him a good time! Keep in mind, though, this will be on a Tuesday night so clear your schedule ahead of time :]  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sevens, Beacon Hill’s best neighborhood pub. As you stroll down one of Boston’s most beautiful cobble stoned areas, you feel like you’ve stepped back in time. This is a really wonderful... and friendly... neighborhood Beacon Hill pub.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John, one of the barmen there says this place is very special. The place must be surrounded by good luck and karma. Over the years he's known over 60 couples who've met there and who eventually got married. Even last year a man walked in off the street and simply asked a woman the score of the baseball game and they're now engaged. The Sevens first opened its doors in 1933 and has been passing along good luck and karma ever since! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This also happens to be where Nick and I hold our weekly Writers Anonymous group meeting! It is the quintessential place for having pints of beer and discussing great literature, and great writers and poets. And, if you're lucky, you'll get to meet members of The Sevens writers crew! Although, I am not sure that you'll be able to handle such sheer profoundness :]    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there... It's going to be fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244817060000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244049304000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come celebrate Nick's Birthday!!!</name><id>10566691</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244592000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/10566691/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/2/global_8960834.jpeg</photo_url></item>