<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Springfield Uprising Men's Group is holding an Open Men's Group from 6:30 until 9:00 pm at 380 Union Street, West Springfield, MA. (Across Union Street from the Crepes Tea House)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Special Exploration of Male Purpose. This night could be the beginning of a powerful journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;You’ve probably felt the call…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know you could be waking up on fire every day. You could be accomplishing truly meaningful things. Have a powerful impact on the world. Do something you were born to do. You could be surrounded by alive, engaging people — people you admire and respect and who admire and respect you. You could be living a bold and passionate life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s true — your life could be like this. You’ve probably felt it. Maybe you’ve even done something about it, yet still know you can improve your game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;You’ve probably had some kind of wake-up call in your life …&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Like waking up from the matrix, you’re no longer buying into the illusions surrounding you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re no longer convinced that a bigger paycheck, a nicer house, a cooler car, more “toys,” or a sexier partner are going to bring more meaning into your life. You’re beyond those clichés, beyond pursuing someone else’s dreams. You know there’s more to life than what you’ve seen and done so far.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because you’ve had this ‘A-HA,’ you get that &lt;strong&gt;those old desires are a dead-end road.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know there’s something bigger for you … yet merely knowing isn’t enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;So what’s the missing piece?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life may feel like it’s stuck in a rut. You keep doing the same things — or maybe even different things — but none of them truly resonate as that missing piece. The thing that really sets the clear direction for your life and &lt;strong&gt;brings you alive … from the inside out&lt;/strong&gt;. And as long as it’s missing, your life will keep feeling empty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, maybe you don’t feel that way. Maybe your life is going exactly the way you want it to. You wake up inspired. You jump out of bed knowing exactly what to do. Your power and impact are growing. You’re totally alive and achieving huge things …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If that sounds like you, you’ve probably discovered &lt;strong&gt;that one core thing ALL men need&lt;/strong&gt; to live a rich, fulfilling and meaningful life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your purpose.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like every hero who ever lived…or was imagined, a man needs purpose. It’s what gives him energy. Direction. Focus. A sense of power by bestowing his unique gifts and talents upon the world that needs his passion, creativity and care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;Join us for an introduction to PURPOSE.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We know we won't change the world in a night - but there is a powerful opportunity to GET SOMETHING STARTED.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This night's content is based on the "Power of Purpose" - a program developed by the  ManKind Project USA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us! Support yourself!&lt;/strong&gt; The ManKind Project is a world-wide community of men. We are not for profit and non-religious. Learn more about men's work, &lt;a href="http://mankindproject.org"&gt;the ManKind Project&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://nwta.mkp.org"&gt;New Warrior Training Adventure&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park between Charlie's Diner and A to Z Movers. This is across the street from "Crepes Tea House" (261 Union St) . --Look for AtoZ Moving Trucks and Sign. Entrance is on the ground floor, front (NE) corner of the building.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boysen </member_name><member_id>7527796</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert</member_name><member_id>9199047</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368702986000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Men</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>openmen</urlname><id>1200732</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5500030518</group_lon><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307624724000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Men's Group - W.Springfield - The Power of Purpose</name><id>pzvctyrhbtb</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368657000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/events/118641472/</event_url></item>