<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Another last minute hike! ;-) This moderate hike on the southern portion of the Mattatuck Trail will be a total of about 3.5 miles in a thru-hike style. Well start off with hiking by the Mad River with some low falls and deep pools and then make our way over Boy Scout built bridges and through a narrow gorge flanked with steep walls of Becar Hill. Well pass a foundation for an old milldam and continue on. Being out in the forest again well eventuall pass 2 caves that we'll explore: Charlie Krug Cave and Indian Jack Cave. The caves are anticipated to be hollows or rockfall caves but you never know until you see them. ;-) Indian Jack Cave perportedly had an indian family living in it so there has to be something. We'll take a short .1 mile blue/yellow blaze loop trail to reach a rock ledge with an overlook for views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet up at Peterson Memorial Park in the parking area off of Mad River Rd. in Wolcott at 8 AM. The trailhead is behind the skateboard area. The hike should take 2.5 to 3 hrs depending how much time we spend at the caves. We'll shuttle back to the parking. Optionally, some of us may make a run up to check out Leatherman's Cave further up the trail near Black Rock State Park after this hike (we'd drive up to the park and hike south to the cave). Another optin is to continue on north 1.3 miles to Buttermilk Falls (this would add 2.6 miles with an out and back).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may want to bring a headlamp or flashlight to check out the caves. Remember some water and good shoes to hike in. It'll likely be cold so dress warmly in layers so you can shed some as you warm up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to parking:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;latitude=&amp;amp;longitude=&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;phone=&amp;amp;level=&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;cat=&amp;amp;address=109+mad+river+rd&amp;amp;city=wolcott&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan won't be at the start as it will be at the endpoint.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leader on this one is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is available from Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan from the Hartford area. Please arrange with Kevin S as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192594560000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192282720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on Mattatuck Trail near Wolcott CT</name><id>6542208</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192363200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6542208/</event_url></item>