<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Garden St &amp; Waterhouse St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.377331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>7813011791 (Chris' Cell)</phone><name>Cambridge Common</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>442822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We have a very special guest playing frisbee with us today: Amelia Earhart!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Audience claps as Amelia walks onto the field. She takes the podium and speaks.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello, hello all! (She's all smiles. The audience is in awe; mouths gape.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, it's true ladies and gentlemen! I am alive and couldn't feel better. On this day 76 years ago, I took off from Harbour Grace, Newfoundland, riding my trusty ol' Bessie, the fire horse. She and I spent 15 hours together, crossing the Atlantic and landing in kind Ireland where I observed some field hands throwing a pie tin to and fro.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I watched, awe-struck, as they smiled and laughed and ran about without a care in the world. They hardly noticed when I walked up to them, asking them what game they were playing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Frisbee, ma'am&amp;quot;, one replied, and I smiled as they handed me the tin. I gave it a toss to a young, dirt-covered lad and I was immediately hooked. The throwing and the catching and the freedom of it all-- so much better than flying little planes across the Atlantic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I took the pie tin back to America, psyched to tell all my friends about this rad-tacular new game. They loved it and we played in secret at night under candlelight. This was &amp;quot;our thing&amp;quot;; we didn't want other commoners catching on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sadly, the press kept pestering me to fly, and I couldn't exactly tell them what I was filling my time with. Instead, I planned this glamorous circumnavigation of the globe along the equator, looking to go out with a bang. I &amp;quot;disappeared&amp;quot; on July 2nd, 1937.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, indeed, what happened to me? My frisbee playing friends and I all planned to meet on nearby Hawaii, where we would play under the red sun and palm trees. I faked my death, getting the press off my back, and spent my days throwing around that tin and eating coconuts and having Luau's. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now that frisbee is a worldwide, multi-billion dollar venture, I'm happy to return to the world and play some disc at night with you folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all! Let's play some ultimate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Audience claps; the roar can be heard for miles.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the generic information from the (boo-ring) organizers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Same deal as always: We'll meet around 8, throw around for a bit while we learn each other's names, then split up into teams and play ultimate. After the game, we'll go out and socialize at Uno's, Herrell's, or some other place around Harvard. Before attending our events, please review our About Us page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd recommend you bring a light-colored shirt for visibility's sake and a change of clothes. We supply all of the equipment necessary so there's really nothing else you need to bring besides your smiling face.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Organizers pay out of pocket for the frisbees, lanyards, glowsticks, field cones and first aid kits. Please consider bringing a couple bucks or visiting our Amazon Wishlist to support our equipment costs. Our group is free and will always be that way but your optional donations are certainly appreciated!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;Chris &amp;amp; Amy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be near the bench beside the baseball/softball field.  We'll be the two tall people chatting and goofing around with whoever shows up.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>4875881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211573682000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>#5: The weather is nice.
#4: Frisbee people are super-fun
#3: Your friends and family will be impressed (and confused) that you play frisbee in the dark 
#2: You can eat dessert afterward guilt-free
#1: Chris McClelland will be there</why><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210966148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Tuesday of Frisbee Fun</name><id>7952739</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211328000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/7952739/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/c/global_3460060.jpeg</photo_url></item>