<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jane has been kind enough to offer her home as the venue for an interesting impromptu discussion on Transcendentalism.&amp;nbsp; She has also expressed interest in William James and, as it happens, there are fairly close links between nineteenth century American Transcendentalism and American Pragmatism. Both, I think, are well embodied in the figures of James and&amp;nbsp; most especially in Ralph Waldo Emerson.&amp;nbsp; Here is Jane's preface to the meeting:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I've long been intrigued by the Transcendentalists, especially with their roots being so deep here in our Boston back yard.&amp;nbsp; In the past, our Impromptu Philosophizer meetups have been.. well, impromptu;&amp;nbsp; for this one I'd like to offer a theme: Transcendentalism.&amp;nbsp; Too broad a topic, you say?&amp;nbsp; Of course it is, which is where the impromptu comes in.&amp;nbsp; Whether you know a lot or a little or nothing at all, bring your appetite for a hearty discussion and let's see where the spirit of Emerson leads us.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;I'll be providing a light meal &amp;amp; beverages for the evening.&amp;nbsp; All you have to do is show up."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Jane&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The regular Impromptu Philosophizer introduction follows&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An Impromptu Philosophizer is a casual meeting at a cafe or pub that may or may not have a specific topic, and may even be scheduled &amp;ldquo;on the spur of the moment!" It's great to know that there is now a way for philosophically minded people to meet but with no particular agenda other than that of satisfying the need to talk about what's on your mind. Whether the interest or concern involves current events or politics, cultural or intellectual issues, personal stuff, pure philosophy or whatever else is on your mind we can all benefit from sharing philosophical perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Therapy for the sane," a term used by Gerd Achenbach (founder of the modern 
&lt;a href="http://www.integralhypnosis.com/philosophical_counseling.htm" target="_blank"&gt;philosophical counseling&lt;/a&gt; movement), may partially suggest the Impromptu Philosophizer concept but it is more multifaceted than, say, an occasional "therapy" session after a trying day. IPs are designed to be fun, engaging and unique opportunities for creating a near spontaneous venue to meet other group members for the purpose of sharing thoughts, ideas and concerns from a philosophical perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Impromptu Philosophizers are spontaneous, existentially driven meetings and discussions. Of course, continue to check back often for the scheduling of the somewhat more structured, topical meetings that are regularly scheduled by Boston Area Philosophy Discussions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;SPECIAL NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; By its very nature, an Impromptu Philosophizer may often have a small turnout. Accordingly, in order to prevent situations in which the event host arrives and there is no one else who shows up, in some cases those who 'Yes" RSVP may be asked to email a further confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;-- Arthur 
  &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be provided.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jane</member_name><member_id>4027830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1315013743000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313004856000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Impromptu Philosophizer:  Transcendental Ramblings</name><id>29013141</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314658800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/29013141/</event_url></item>