<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Get ready for that big Xmas dinner by taking a hike on Xmas Eve Day &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Crawford has a bare summit but offers protected hiking trails most of the way. The final section may be icey and exposed to high winds. There are a few look outs along the way. On a clear day this 3K peak offers views that rival many 4K peaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will follow the Davis Path from the parking area on Rte 302 to the Mt Crawford Spur trail, then to the summit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check your maps and AMC White Mountain Guide for a description of the trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dogs are Welcome!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance - @ 5.0 miles, &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain - @2,100 feet &lt;br /&gt;Book Time  @ 4:30 excluding stops &lt;br /&gt;Goal time 4:30 including stops&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive in enough time so that you are ready to hit the trail at 10 AM sharp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike at or slightly faster than booktime with limited short stops in order to stay warm. Plan on food/snacks that you can eat while moving.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared for full Winter conditions - snowshoes, crampons, microspikes, goggles, extra gloves/clothes may all be needed - plan your hike accordingly based on your experiences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions on equipement or the hike please ask before showing up for the hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the trailhead: The trail starts on Route 302 at a parking area on the West side of the Saco River near the Notchland Inn, @ 5.6 miles south of the Wiley House in Crawford Notch. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in a green Suburban with NH plates and ROT &amp; VFTT decals.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob &amp; Geri</member_name><member_id>4842806</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261840215000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261497841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Crawford via Davis Path</name><id>12131664</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261666800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12131664/</event_url></item>