<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Medford, Massachusetts</address_1><state>Ma</state><lat>42.427498</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Middlesex Fells Reservation</name><city>Medford</city><id>7528482</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109200</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ok, this will be a weekly event to get those trail legs in better shape for long weekend death marches..... This meetup repeats every Tuesday evening through the summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's the plan?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll do the entire Skyline loop in the Middlesex Fells.  The goal is to cover the 7 miles in 2 hours but bring your headlamp in case we run late for unforseen circumstances.  There are a few steep ascents to rocky outcrops and we'll get in a bit of elevation gain/loss.  You will need to have a good level of aerobic fitness as we will be going at a fast walk pace (if not jog on downhills) for the whole hike and will not be taking any break other than quick stops to drink a splash of water.  So you know what to expect - we're out to get exercise, not take a leisurely, relaxed stroll in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where will we meet?n &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're meeting &lt;span&gt;at the northwest corner of the North reservoir on Hillcrest Parkway near the intersection with Appalatian Rd in Winchester - not in one of the parking lots.&lt;/span&gt; Please be on time - We &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;will start the hike promptly at 5:30 and go in a clockwise direction.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should I bring?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water, good hiking shoes/trail runners, bug spray, headlamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Info:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain will cancel - I'll cancel the even by noontime the day of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs are not allowed for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more information about the Fells here: &lt;a href="http://www.fells.org/visit/"&gt;http://www.fells.org/visit/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And you can print out free maps here: &lt;a href="http://www.fellsbiker.com/maps"&gt;http://www.fellsbiker.com/maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Northwest corner of the North Reservoir - park on Hillcrest Parkway in Winchester near intersetction with Appalatian  Rd</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris L</member_name><member_id>6602385</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340153294000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339628086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fast Paced after work Skyline Trail circuit in the Fells</name><id>dlrxxcyqjbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340141400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/69061172/</event_url></item>