<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 willow st</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03038</zip><lat>42.854582</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-472-6516</phone><name>Jason Moore Photo Studio</name><city>Derry</city><id>359606</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.303662</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Adrien has been photographing since he was about 16, after discovered his father’s darkroom equipment in storage. He let me set it up in the basement and after a few lessons he was hooked on the process of creating a black and white image and seeing it come to life in the tray of chemicals. He photographed his surroundings, which was often nature and small still-life compositions. Eventually, Adrien was shooting for the local newspapers and taking family portraits...which, at the time, were portraits of the family. After studying music and performing around Boston, he entered the corporate world, where he stayed for more years than he want to admit. The early days of software development were, oddly enough, a creative outlet for Adrien. But eventually, he knew that he needed to come back to his first passion. Since then, he has been pursuing my goal with a vengeance. Every day, looking forward to the next opportunity to work with someone new, painting them with light, drawing them out, and capturing forever what makes them unique and special.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us to chat about his business and his photographs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.adrienbisson.com/storage/28-nov-09-COOL-098.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1259615809830" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266948711000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263660981000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pro Photographer Guest Speaker Adrien Bisson</name><id>12336261</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266775200000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/12336261/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/a/global_12638842.jpeg</photo_url></item>