<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Here's a wonderful FREE LOA-related event invite from Clarissa Rodriguez &amp;amp; Bob Reinhart, BostonLOA Meetup members and Christopher Marston ( the organizer of the Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Meetup).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**If you're an employee, even more important for you to participate!**&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's in Burlington with lots of free parking. ;o)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Details are below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Look forward to seeing you at the event! Appreciate your sharing the invite with other folks.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;===============================================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE EVENT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:30 – 9:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Light Appetizers &amp;amp; Refreshments served&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AGENDA:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us to mastermind with 3 successful Boston-based business entrepreneurs who have exploded their businesses (and for their clients) using the LAW OF ATTRACTION despite naysayers, credit crunch and extremely economic challenging times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Folks they know are intrigued by how they've done it using the &amp;quot;Secret&amp;quot;. Because of the many requests from folks asking: &amp;quot;How did you do it? Can it happen for me too?&amp;quot;, Clarissa, Christopher and Bob are inviting their friends, colleagues and folks interested in Law Of Attraction to meet up, learn, share and chat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;An Evening Of &amp;quot;Masterminding&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's your opportunity to ask your questions and mastermind with Clarissa, Christopher and Bob. They will share their &amp;quot;real life experience&amp;quot; insights to help you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their intention is to make sure you get&lt;br /&gt;- your most pressing questions answered,&lt;br /&gt;- practical action steps and&lt;br /&gt;- real world proven techniques &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;you need to put into practice everyday to have happier, successful , fulfilling personal and professional lives, &lt;i&gt;in spite of this tough economy.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Law Of Attraction is powerful and it works! &lt;br /&gt;(They've done it, so can you!)&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Not An Entrepreneur?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guess what! As an employee, you don't want your professional and financial well-being in the hands of your boss, so you need to think and act like an entrepreneur. You'll be able to leave with powerful tips and ideas that you can apply right away that puts you in the driver's seat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Go here to read WHO THE HOSTS are:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/messages/boards/thread/6341953"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;(not enough room on calendar page to provide info)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236126310000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>51</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235245084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPECIAL EVENT:   LOA-MASTERMIND with 3 Successful Entrepreneurs</name><id>9791042</id><headcount>51</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235691000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/9791042/</event_url></item>