<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>To be given </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06408</zip><lat>41.549847</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ralph's Place</name><city>Cheshire</city><id>1461553</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.923950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope this will be top all past wine tasting parties.&amp;nbsp; It is being held by request as a memorial to Rena DeMarzo.&amp;nbsp; She was titillated with each wine tasting and looked forward to meeting everyone she could.&amp;nbsp; We need to show our support for her wonderful heart making everyone feel welcome.&amp;nbsp; She always made the most scrumptious dishes and brought the most expensive bottles of wine she could find.&amp;nbsp; Those that knew her well are devastated by her early passing.&amp;nbsp; She will be there in spirit I&amp;rsquo;m sure!&amp;nbsp; Tom may even sing his new song he wrote for Rena when he heard the news.&amp;nbsp; This is not a morbid night but one of partying as Rena would have wanted it. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;For wine night, everyone will bring a bottle of wine (no boxed wine or 1.75MLs please) AND a pot luck dish, finger food, hors d'oeuvres or desert. Please indicate what food item you want to bring when you sign up. If you are coming by yourself or don't want to go in with someone just bring a bottle of wine that is $15 or more ( 750 ml) with your dish. Couples or groups can go in together on a bottle that is $30 or more depending on the quantity of people in the group, to ensure we have a good assortment of wines to taste. Get some different types of wine so we have a varied taste testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reds - Malbec, Blends, cab, merlot, shiraz pinot noir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whites - sav blanc, chards, reisling, pinot grigio, etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please ensure you show up if you RSVP yes, since we may have a waiting list and you are taking up a person's spot if you do not show up. If you must cancel, the earlier the better if there is a waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Please note* The address will be sent a few days prior to the event if you don't have it already to all the "yes" RSVPs, due to this being a private residence. It should go without saying to Drink Responsibly. I will have water and coffee too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is for 4 meetup groups with 20 invites&amp;nbsp;to blow this out with a great party. Only sign up on one site if you belong to more than one for an accurate count.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the night in fun, style and class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**As always this is a multi group meetup and a BYOWG...bring your own wine glass!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This event if from 6pm - 10pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304389879000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>These were one of Rena's favorite meetup's.  She had already been talking about the next wine meetup before she past.</why><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302218778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine tasting at Ralph's house in memory of Rena DeMarzo</name><id>17225758</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304200800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/17225758/</event_url></item>