<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You've Heard it All Before - a workshop with Father Peter Bowes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, September 11.  7:30pm.  $25 (includes refreshments) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a vast difference between theory and evidence, knowledge and wisdom, concept and experience.  If you have ready many books about the ocean, for example, that certainly does not mean that you have been to the ocean and that you know what the ocean is like.  You cannot really know the ocean until you have been there and experienced it for yourself.  The same holds for God.  Books, concepts and theories about God can only bring you so far.  They are helpful in that they can pave the way for an actual experience.  But why stop there?  Why stop at the temporary inspiration gleaned from other people's experiences?  Why stop at the shallow well of belief and theory?  Why not learn how to dive deeply into an actual experience of God's peace and presence?  This is certainly possible for everyone.  This seminar will introduce you to the powerful ways in which you can move steadily and smoothly into the reality of God's love, joy and acceptance that awaits you within.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Center of Light is on the Orange Line - Stonybrook T-stop.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221348874000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213636872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Father Peter Workshop:  You've Heard It All Before</name><id>8152802</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221175800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/8152802/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/8/global_1017208.jpeg</photo_url></item>