<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>281 Summer St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.349976</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Space With A Soul</name><city>Boston</city><id>2453561</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.049881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Any Sitecore project being started today is likely planning for mobile, but what does that really mean?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The April New England Sitecore User Group will feature a panel presentation and discussion from ISITE Design’s battle-tested User Experience and Sitecore Development teams that explore the many considerations that go into planning, designing and developing responsive and mobile-friendly Sitecore experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The teams will look at real-world projects with example deliverables, code and approaches for a variety of scenarios. We’ll look at trade-offs in the development processes, approaches to adaptive vs. responsive and the experience-based planning and content strategy necessary for success. Rock-star Sitecore developers are only part of the equation when it comes to making responsive design work with Sitecore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The discussion will be geared toward both experienced developers and end users and organizations approaching mobile and responsive design for the first time. There's something for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Come join our expert panel and bring your own experiences with mobile and responsive design to add to the discussion:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Deanna Glaze: User Experience Architect, ISITE Design&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Petra Gregorova: Front End Developer, ISITE Design&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Wendy Derstine: Solution Architect, ISITE Design&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Ozell McBride: Sitecore Developer, ISITE Design&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moderated by John Eckman: Managing Director, ISITE Design&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Cram</member_name><member_id>2226539</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368733033000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Sitecore-User-Group-New-England</urlname><id>1535858</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Sitecore User Group - New England</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>51</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363674587000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Responsive Design &amp; Sitecore</name><id>109961732</id><headcount>30</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366840800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Sitecore-User-Group-New-England/events/109961732/</event_url></item>