<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Packard Avenue </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.407650</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Barnum Hall 008</name><city>Medford</city><id>12201852</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120605</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hello Fellow Meet Up'ers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As you may or may not know I have a vested interest in education, outreach, and advocacy for survivors of sexual assault and rape.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;As the Staff Assistant to the LGBT and Latino Center, I have a variety of op&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;portunities to be a part of social justice initiatives on and off campus. Because of my back ground in the military and the programs that I work with, I am compelled to share my vested interest in education and outreach of sexual assault and rape with the students, faculty&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; and staff at Tufts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As &lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; survivor of military sexual trauma&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; I have been looking for some form &lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;of&lt;/span&gt; justice or advocacy from the government and military for the past 10 years. Last summer&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; an incredible documentary called&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://invisiblewarmovie.com/index.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Invisible War&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; was playing in Boston and it changed my life forever. The film is an investigative documentary about one of the military’s best kept secrets&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; rape. &lt;em&gt;The Invisible War&lt;/em&gt; shows how the trauma of rape has affected their lives, their family and their career. It discusses the challenges that survivors of military rape endure while also trying to work with their state representatives to solve issues of under-reporting, the investigation process&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; and the overall masking of rape as an &lt;em&gt;invisible&lt;/em&gt; issue &lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;in&lt;/span&gt; the military. &lt;em&gt;The Invisible War&lt;/em&gt; has been making waves federally and it even earned a 2013 Oscar Nomination for Best Documentary this year!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;I will be hosting a screening of &lt;em&gt;The Invisible War&lt;/em&gt; and a talk-back discussion with &lt;a href="http://tsongas.house.gov/"&gt;Congresswoman Niki Tsongas&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;strong&gt;March 27th from 7pm-9pm in Barnum Hall 008&lt;/strong&gt; (163 Packard Avenue). The panel will include military survivors, representatives from Tufts Health Services and Counseling Services and a representative from the Boston Area Rape Crisis Center.  It is open to the public so please tell your friends. Barnum hall has 224 seats. There aren’t tickets for this event so seats are first-come, first-serve!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;This is a Tufts event and I thought it suitable to send this to you because it might be of interest to you and possibly your students. If you could spread the word and extend this invite to your students that would be wonderful!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;I’m including the event flyer on this email and early next week you might see some of these flyers posted around campus. I look forward to seeing you at the event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Best,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Emily&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;All non-Tufts visitors can park in the lots marked with the red arrows. The event in in Barnum hall (follow the star!) Tufts TUPD will not be ticketing these lots the during this event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/5/f/c/event_216262012.jpeg" width="456" height="395" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/8/0/event_213193952.jpeg" width="424" height="657" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>first-come, first-serve</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emily </member_name><member_id>13614628</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364432578000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363024701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film Screening: The Invisible War</name><id>108731122</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364425200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/108731122/</event_url></item>