<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Main St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06051</zip><lat>41.665730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860) 229-3049 </phone><name>The Hole in the Wall Theater</name><city>New Britain</city><id>914030</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.782113</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What did people do for entertainment when America was last going through a financial meltdown? what did they listen to during World War II? Why, live radio shows, of course! Remember Hope and Crosby? Burns and Allen? Baby Snooks? Hole in the Wall Theater of New Britain is proud to present &amp;quot;Live Old Time Radio,&amp;quot; which opens Friday, March 20, and runs for five weekends.&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Hole in the Wall co-founder Ted Guhl and with a lively cast of 16, the theater presents old favorites such as Sam Spade, Burns and Allen, Doris Day, Bob Hope, Baby Snooks, Flash Gordon, Popeye, and a host of other talk shows, as well as live music for your entertainment. Come on down, be a member of our live studio audience, and enjoy some popular and well known vignettes and music. Leave the cares and woes of our present crisis at the door and revel in Hole in the Wall’s &amp;quot;Live Old Time Radio&amp;quot; – comedy, mystery, songs, memories and more.&lt;br /&gt;Cast members include Hole in the Wall regulars Dennis Hull, with his wonderful baritone, Doug Seeley, Denise Clapsaddle, Johnny Peifer, Fritz Messerschmidt, Dianne Provenzano, Wendy Wolowicz, Ted Guhl, Mary Ann Kelly and silver voiced Jody Bechard, with John Carroll manning the piano. Newcomers Nathaniel Oaks, John Basinger, Deb Thaler, John Kawecki, Emily Ravita and Dan Czlapinski round out our studio gang.&lt;br /&gt;Performances are Friday and Saturday nights, March 20 through April 18, at 8:00 p.m., with two matinees on Sunday, March 29 and April 5, at 2:00 p.m. Admission is by a suggested donation of $20.00, and Hole in the Wall's concession stand always has delicious home baked goods for sale, just like an old fashioned taste of home. So come on down, leave your cares behind, and enjoy an entertaining evening that will transport you back to a gentler time.&lt;br /&gt;Reservations are recommended. Call 860.229.3049 for ticket information or to make a reservation. Go to theatercalendar.org for more information and a short radio broadcast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Show Dates:&lt;br /&gt;March 20, 21, 27, 28&lt;br /&gt;April 3, 4, 10, 11, 17, 18&lt;br /&gt;Fridays &amp;amp; Saturdays 8:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donation: $20&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Hole In The Wall Theater 116 Main St. New Britain, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For reservations call: (860) 229-3049&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;Free Parking Available in Garage on Chestnut St.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will Meet and Buy tickets together</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238976609000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238068466000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Old Time Radio Show</name><id>10040056</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238803200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/10040056/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_2930168.jpeg</photo_url></item>