<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a continuation of the meetup group previously hosted by James Ryan-Henry, and will meet in the same place at the same time (room 1128 at CCRI, on Tuesdays at noon). For all new players, we are in an original campaign world called &amp;quot;The World of Vale.&amp;quot; The party is curently at 8th lvl. If you would like to join, please create an 8th lvl character. You may use anything from any of the d20 system books, as long as your power level is equal to that of the other characters, and you do not use anything that would not be found in the time period that the game is set in , which is the Middle Ages (so no guns, lasers, bombs, cars, etc). If you use a nonstandard book, please convert it to Dnd v3.5 rules, which will save everyone a big hassle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last week, we split into two groups, because the group was becoming too big. In the campaign I am DMing, we traveled to the town of Grendel, where we learned that an ancient item of great power called the &amp;quot;rod of dark fate&amp;quot;, which could decide the fate of the world, was hidden in the ruins of a drow city nearby. We traveled to the city, where we found and defeated 2 Colossal Spider Skeletons, and met up with and befriended a pair of drow wizards who were also searching for the rod. We left off with the party just bedding down for the night.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2295622</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540486000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1156804521000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CCRI Roleplayer's Guild DnD meetup (new)</name><id>5101801</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1156867200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/5101801/</event_url></item>