<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>53 Ashburton St.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02895</zip><lat>41.837766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.351.POOL</phone><name>Snookers Pool Lounge</name><city>Providence</city><id>1094702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415001</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Providence Collective Monday Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Snookers Pool Lounge (in the new location - near Rt 146, the big Post Office and the downtown Marriott)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this week we're returning by request to Snookers! If you're a pool player this place is for you, and if you're not, there are still a lot of distractions to take part in if you're so inclined. Always fun and always a good time, Snookers is a RI institution and was located over in the Jewelery District overlooking 195 for years. Known as a pool hall in which the tables stretched on for miles, they left their old location and moved on to bigger digs (and more importantly, LOTS more parking) a few years ago over near 146 and the turnkey post office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's on a one way street, but you'll see the building on the left first and then the parking lot. If you get to the gas station, just go around it and swing through again going under 95, keeping the post office on your right and take the left-hand split. If you get to 146 you've gone too far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new location is huge inside, still has a lot of pool tables and "sports" (no pun intended) a ridiculous amount of large screen TV's. If you're a sports fan, you'll want to know about this place!So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there! Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever. Except Hurricane Sandy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the scarf or hat int the picture, but we're not hard to find!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355945581000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355351471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Snookers !</name><id>95129582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355785200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/95129582/</event_url></item>