<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP early! We need to determine whether to request a larger room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Get In The Game: Developing a sound investing routine using Daily Graphs Online® (DGO) by Matthew Inouye, Data Research Analyst and Cornelio Ash, Data Research Supervisor, both from Daily Graphs Online&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt and Cornelio will review how Daily Graphs Online can support your daily investing routine, demonstrating advanced applications and uses of the premium data research tool.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Introduction/Agenda:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;15-20 minute introduction covering the basics of DGO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overview of historical stock market leaders:   Understanding the significance of key characteristics of past leaders&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Custom Screen Wizard:  Review: Technical Screens, Relative Strength, Accumulation/Distribution, Suggested Screens, Price Performance, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Premium Stock Graphs:   Discuss the importance of adjusted earnings per share, importing/exporting data, spreadsheet manipulation, annotations and many more…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Industry Groups:   Brief overview of the importance of Industry Groups and how to find leading Industry Groups&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fund Center:   Seek outperforming mutual funds, identify which stocks leading fund managers are putting their money into&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Q&amp;amp;A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio on Matthew Inouye and Cornelio Ash&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Matthew Inouye is a Data Research Analyst with William O'Neil + Co. Incorporated and a Product Coach for Daily Graphs Online, the premium investment data research tool created for the individual investor. A devoted practitioner of the CAN SLIM® investment strategy for over 12 years, Mr. Inouye offers his experience to share ways to simplify investing routines, uncover potential new stock ideas, and illustrate the full potential of Daily Graphs Online. Mr. Inouye has spoken at numerous workshops and seminars for investors who follow the investment strategies pioneered by William J. O’Neil, founder of Investor’s Business Daily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Cornelio Ash is a Data Research Supervisor with William O’Neil + Company, where he has led various teams in analyzing numerous SEC filings to gather the fundamental information that appears in Investors Business Daily and Daily Graphs Online.  As a Product Coach for Daily Graphs Online, Mr. Ash has presented at numerous investing workshops and seminars, articulating key benefits of using Daily Graphs Online for stock analysis and investing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Daily Graphs Online® is coming to town!  Preceding the IBD Level II workshop, Daily Graphs Online Product Coaches will be in Boston to help our members maximize the benefits of Daily Graphs Online premium data research tool.  The Daily Graphs Online team will demonstrate basic as well as advanced applications this tool has to offer; so come spend an evening and learn how to simplify your investing routine, while discovering key features of Daily Graphs Online. Discussion items include Industry Groups, Fund Center, spreadsheet manipulation, annotating charts, and many more tips.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246405312000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>74</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216087333000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Get In The Game: Developing a sound investing routine using Daily Graphs Online®</name><id>8342439</id><headcount>76</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218841200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/8342439/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>