<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Cambridge Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363735</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>588384</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Keeping your Brain Plastic &lt;br /&gt;Steve Haggarty, Ph.D.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your brain is a highly &amp;quot;plastic&amp;quot; organ capable of remarkable feats of adaptation. Intricate processes that allow the brain to adapt are essential for maintaining our mental health. Steve Haggarty will discuss how advances in areas of genetics, chemistry, and neuroscience are providing insights into the molecular nature of brain plasticity, and how this information could be used to develop new ways to treat memory and mood disorders. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wed, August 4th, 6-7pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen J. Haggarty, Ph.D., is an Assistant Professor of Neurology at Harvard Medical School, an Assistant in Neuroscience at Massachusetts General Hospital’s Center for Human Genetic Research, an Affiliate Faculty member of the Harvard Stem Cell Institute, and the Director of Chemical Neurobiology for the Stanley Center for Psychiatric Research at the Broad Institute, a research collaboration of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Harvard University and its affiliated hospitals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Haggarty graduated from The University of British Columbia, Vancouver in 1997 with a degree in genetics and received his Ph.D. from Harvard University in 2003 for his work developing methods for high-throughput chemical screening and the identification of small-molecule probes of the cell cycle and chromatin remodeling. Dr. Haggarty then joined the Broad Institute as a research Fellow in the Chemical Biology Program and became a founding member of the Psychiatric Disease Program and the Stanley Center for Psychiatric Research. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lectures are free and open to the public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;For more information on Midsummer Nights’ Science at Broad, click &lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/outreach/midsummer/schedule.html" target="_blank"&gt;HERE&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Megan Rokop &lt;br /&gt;Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard &lt;br /&gt;7 Cambridge Center &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA 02142&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P: 617-714-7992 &lt;br /&gt;E: rokop@broadinstitute.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Eli and Edythe L. Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard was founded in 2003 to bring the power of genomics to biomedicine. It pursues this mission by empowering creative scientists to construct new and robust tools for genomic medicine, to make them accessible to the global scientific community, and to apply them to the understanding and treatment of disease. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281035975000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276594280000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Keeping your Brain Plastic </name><id>13805504</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280959200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/13805504/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/4/global_14000500.jpeg</photo_url></item>