<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>adv registration</description><amount>144.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us for an extraordinary day-long event&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miracle Manifesting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;with&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spiritual Teacher, Healer and Transformational Speaker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maureen Whitehouse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/9/4/event_196701652.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As miraculous beings, every single aspect of our lives is meant to be divine. Is there anything keeping you from experiencing that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover how to unchain yourself from your limiting beliefs about prosperity Experience Spiritual Success and Conscious Creating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allow for Abundance to flow in a new direction - towards you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I never associated consciousness with personal prosperity. Now my world is a reflection of the acceptance of the treasure I’ve found within. I’ve given up the guilt associated with success.” ~ Mary Reuter, executive assistant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the past 20+ years Maureen has helped people radically shift their perspective to awaken to the miraculous in their lives. While studying a Course in Miracles, Maureen experienced what the course calls the “Atonement” or At-One-ment, Absolute Self Realization. This intense and empowering encounter created a total shift in her perception. Since this profound awakening, she has lived her life help- ing others unmask their Divinity so they can live purposeful, peaceful and powerful lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today she works with highly motivated individuals in all walks of life, helping them to restore their trust in the process of life. She can help you shift your perception of every personal hell into a miraculous view of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a speaker, her provocative, life changing message is complimented by her unique ability to draw you with her into the awakened state of presence. Her experience as an international model, actress, talk show host and world traveler adds to her provocative message. Maureen has been called the embodiment of shining conviction and her work has been consistently described as not only life changing, but life jolting!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Her vision is enthralling, and her enthusiasm, contagious!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a personal note, in year that I’ve been workings with Maureen my life has completely changed. My life is more peaceful as a result of experiencing direct connection to God on a moment-to- moment basis. All things I was hoping for or wishing for, have manifested within me and are reflected out- wardly in my deepening relationships with my children, alignment with my spiritual purpose here on earth, abundance in my personal and professional life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am honored to host Maureen and have you experience the awe, and absolutely transformational light she offers just being in her presence. She has been my True Tantra teacher. This will be a very special day... I’m grateful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DATE/TIME: Saturday, May 4th, 10am - 4pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost $144  -- pre-registration only&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Limited Space - Reserve Now: Robyn@SacredTantricFire.com or call (508) 380-9254&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is RARE OPPORTUNITY to be with Maureen for a full-day!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;** Please note RSVPing on Meetup does not reserve your space.  Full payment required. **&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367777892000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366551796000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Miracle Manifesting with Spiritual Teacher, Maureen Whitehouse</name><id>115407932</id><headcount>15</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367676000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/115407932/</event_url></item>