<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Values continued:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We value diversity in religions, nationalities, and ethnic backgrounds. We cooperate as a team to be successful by inviting other professional people we know. &lt;br /&gt;4. We demonstrate this respectful/ nonjudgmental mindset in two ways: &lt;br /&gt;A. By saying Yes to someone who asks us to dance. (once) &lt;br /&gt;B. By offering positive solutions or alternatives if you disagree with someone. (Please utilize basic human relationship skills by not criticizing, condemning or complaining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Men and women bring healthy food selections  &lt;br /&gt;Make it a festive occasion/celebration for the Holidays&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have an Open bar/wine/beer/soda/water/Dessert- $10.00 fee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host- Richard Tosti   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. &amp;quot;Time of party: 6:00PM -10:00pm&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;2. &amp;quot; Dress code- &amp;quot;business casual&amp;quot; -  No shoes, jeans, or sneakers- stockings good, slippper great! &lt;br /&gt;3. &amp;quot;You can enjoy the people, music and dance if you like&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purpose is to Socialize with similar people of your age who are searching for a lifetime partner.   30-50 age group   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I began these parties in my home in July 2006-twice a month   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Circulate, talk to everyone.   &lt;br /&gt;If someone is alone go up to them and say hi!   &lt;br /&gt;Nonsmokers- inside my home   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite other friends, Particularly men.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually have an equal number of men and women.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group was formed on the principle of synergy. Working together to invite quality people. We must take responsibility for inviting people. My personal goal is to always have an equal ratio of men and women, hope you will help.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maximum - 40 guests only.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's have fun!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions -You will see open house signs-simple   &lt;br /&gt;My Home&lt;br /&gt;44 Pickman Drive&lt;br /&gt;Bedford, MA&lt;br /&gt;128- Exit route 4/225 toward Bedford, 3.9 miles (stay right at two forks in road-&lt;br /&gt;-left on Dudley (Huckins Farm sign lite up) and left on Pickman &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;larger dance party- 100-150 guests- www.dance.meetup.com/393/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345157309000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Curious Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dinner-parties</urlname><id>1245686</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Singles Dinner Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232981705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Home Dance Party</name><id>9603208</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235170800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dinner-parties/events/9603208/</event_url></item>