<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>567 Crawford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.557892</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 345-9580</phone><name>Fitchburg Municipal Airport</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>360080</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.754395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here we go again. We have a metar date of the next day, a Sunday. This is one of the best events we've had and even though we were weathered out last year, there are a lot of great memories from 2008. At that time, Fred let some of the pilots put their planes in hangars the night before :-).  If the weather is good, the skies, controllers and airport will be busy, so pay attention to assigned altitudes and runways.   An early start is a good idea and getting off the ground by 8:30 is even better.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.navmonster.com/apt/ACK" target="_blank"&gt;Nantucket Airport&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's more about the Nantucket Stroll weekend:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nantucketchamber.org/visitor/events.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nantucketc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NANTUCKET, MA - Nantucket Island is particularly enchanting during the holiday season, when New England’s finest traditions come alive for the Annual Christmas Stroll Weekend, December 3 - 5, 2010 and Nantucket Noel, Nov. 26 – Dec. 31, 2009, a month-long celebration organized by the Nantucket Island Chamber of Commerce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festivities begin on the Friday evening after Thanksgiving, with the lighting of over 150 Christmas trees in Nantucket’s historic downtown. Residents and visitors alike gather to watch while the cobblestone byways become illuminated with color and light. Community caroling follows, filling the air with the familiar sounds of an old-fashioned Christmas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Annual Christmas Stroll Weekend is a community holiday celebration attracting visitors from around the world. Santa and Mrs. Claus arrive to the island via a Coast Guard vessel and ride up Main Street in a horse-drawn carriage accompanied by the Town Crier. Carolers in Victorian costumes, bell ringers and and other musicians stroll through town performing, while visitors enjoy Nantucket’s unique shops and restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For visitors unable to attend during Stroll weekend, Nantucket Noel festivities continue through New Year’s Eve. Highlights include theatrical and choral performances, concerts, holiday exhibitions, and craft shows. Lodging should be secured in advance, and be sure to ask about midweek specials during Nantucket’s quiet season.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Louise Anderson</member_name><member_id>6714056</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Bortle</member_name><member_id>6715847</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary Archer</member_name><member_id>6716312</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291506777000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287697360000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nantucket Christmas Stroll at KACK</name><id>15187117</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291471200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/15187117/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/4/9/global_6232681.jpeg</photo_url></item>