<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the Brettl-Hupfers as we attend the showing of the 2011 Teton Gravity Research film&amp;nbsp;located at&amp;nbsp;the IMAX Theatre - Boston Aquarium. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Online Tickets are Now Onsale: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.tgrtix.com/Tickets/OFTR/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tgrtix.com/Tickets/OFTR/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One For The Road Film Information: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.tetongravity.com/one-for-the-road/"&gt;http://www.tetongravity.com/one-for-the-road/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One for the Road&lt;/em&gt; is an HD ski film that follows some of the world's most progressive snow sports athletes as it documents their lives on the road and captures some of the most stunning riding to date. Road trips are an integral part of every adventurer's life and a conduit to define one's being. Journeys to new lands shed light on each skier's personal mission. Whether shredding with long time ski partners, or meeting a seasoned character in some far off country, wisdom is gained through these new experiences. The road trip is a metaphor for every skier's existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shot on location, prepare for a visually stunning voyage generated with Phantom, Red, Canon DSLR and GoPro HD footage. Join the athletes as they rock a record breaking season in Jackson Hole, immerse themselves into the culture of Japan's powder mecca Hokkaido, discover Iceland's urban side, explore the Balkan wonders of Macedonia and Montenegro, shred deep pillow lines at Baldface Lodge, uncover first descents in Pemberton, BC, and hit full throttle lines in the perfect snow and weather of Juneau, AK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>dan</member_name><member_id>8253363</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan Spurr</member_name><member_id>13677144</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321067205000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320112243000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Teton Gravity Research "One For The Road" - IMAX at Boston Aquarium</name><id>39439392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321063200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/39439392/</event_url></item>