<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>470 College St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.310580</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Sprague Hall, Yale University</name><city>New Haven</city><id>399657</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.926310</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Yale school of music presents&lt;br /&gt;Help Can't wait - A concert to benefit relief efforts in China, Myanmar, and the Amerian South. Details below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most importantly, of prime interest is that the NHC's own lovely and talented Ms. Elizabeth Fleming, who recently performed at the illustrious Carnegie Hall, will treat us to her Strauss Serenade (with solos!), and the Mozart Clarinet Concerto. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Sprague Hally at 6:30, we'll take seats at 6:40 for the 7pm showtime. These concerts fill up quickly, so come soon for a good seat!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission to the concert is free, however there is a &lt;br /&gt;suggested donation of $20 for disaster relief.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you make a contribution online, please print a &lt;br /&gt;copy of your receipt as it will serve as your ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are also available by phone and at the Sprague Hall &lt;br /&gt;Box Office 9am-5pm on Monday and Tuesday &lt;br /&gt;and 9am-7:30pm the night of the concert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benefit Program &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chinese Solo flute piece &lt;br /&gt;Mingzhu Wang (?07)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meguru - Traditional by Ovambo&lt;br /&gt;Bawo Thixo Somandla - Matyila, arr. Mzilikazi Khumalo&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members of the Yale Glee Club&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?Ich habe genung? (from Cantata BWV 82) by J. S. Bach&lt;br /&gt;Joshua Copeland, baritone &amp;amp; Douglas Dickson, piano&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meditation from Thais by Massenet&lt;br /&gt;Jaewon Choi, Violin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Serenade in Eb, Op. 7 (1881) by Richard Strauss&lt;br /&gt;Thomas C. Duffy, conductor&lt;br /&gt;Members of the Philharmonia Orchestra of Yale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Unanswered Question by Charles Ives ?98&lt;br /&gt;Toshiyuki Shimada, conductor&lt;br /&gt;Yale Symphony Orchestra&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Irish Tune from County Derry by Percy Aldridge Grainger&lt;br /&gt;Thomas C. Duffy, conductor&lt;br /&gt;Yale Concert Band&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clarinet Concerto in A major, K. 622 by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart&lt;br /&gt;II. Adagio&lt;br /&gt;David Shifrin, Clarinet&lt;br /&gt;Members of the Philharmonia Orchestra of Yale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How You'll Make a Difference &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All proceeds will be given to major charities &lt;br /&gt;providing services to the victims of the earthquakes in China, &lt;br /&gt;the typhoon in Myanmar and the recent tornadoes in the United States. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To ensure that these three disaster areas will be served, &lt;br /&gt;benefits will be shared by the American Red Cross, &lt;br /&gt;Save the Children and AmeriCares. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the third ?Help Can't Wait? concert organized &lt;br /&gt;by musical organizations at Yale. The first was in response to the &lt;br /&gt;Tsunami and earthquakes in Southeast Asia and the Pacific in 2004 &lt;br /&gt;and the second to benefit victims of Hurricane Katrina in 2005.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211581949000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211321560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Help Can't Wait - a Yale concert fundraiser with NHC member Elizabeth</name><id>7977807</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211409000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7977807/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>