<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>6.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Can't get away for the holidays? No problem! Our last meetup of the year will give you a taste of dishes from around the world but you won't have to leave Massachusetts. You will, however, need to venture a little north/west of Boston! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linda and Mitch Poirier of Methuen have graciously agreed to host a cooperative brunch on the Sunday after Christmas and we're going to use an international theme. This means that 1) everyone needs to bring something and 2) that something should NOT be traditional American brunch fare. Think blintzes, huevos rancheros, muesli, Belgian waffles, etc.  or go a little further off the beaten path by visiting this link for recipe ideas: &lt;a href="http://www.whats4eats.com/breakfast" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.whats4eats...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linda is the Event Host for this meetup and will be overseeing the food contributions to prevent duplications. Please have some idea of what you plan to bring when you RSVP, as you will get a question about this when you do. (Sorry, I can't disable the questions if you RSVP &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; so just ignore them if that's the case.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your event fee will cover the cost of juice, coffee, tea, and if you want, an alcoholic drink. We will have Mimosas and Bloody Mary's available. If you are not planning to consume alcohol, please let us know that when you RSVP and we will give you a $3 refund at the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wishing everyone a wonderful Christmas/Hanukkah/Kwanza/Solstice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Linda &amp;amp; Mitch:  Please be aware that we have a long-haired white cat - if you are allergic, you will have a problem!  We will send you directions to our place along with a parking map - we live in a condo complex, and there are specific &amp;quot;visitors' parking spots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are planning to provide the appetizers and a Greek pastitsio dish.  Let us know what you would like to bring - we need some sort of salad, 2-3 more main dishes, and desserts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be sent after you RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262106456000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260637294000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cooperative Brunch Chez Poirier</name><id>12071025</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261933200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/12071025/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/9/global_12192793.jpeg</photo_url></item>