<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>44 Hope St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01301</zip><lat>42.586300</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-774-3150</phone><name>Hope &amp; Olive</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>1109344</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.599200</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Greetings, all! By popular demand and a great conversation with Jim at Hope &amp;amp; Olive, I am excited to announce that our next meeting will be on Sunday, November 15th at 5:30pm at &lt;a href="http://hopeandolive.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Hope &amp;amp; Olive&lt;/a&gt; in Greenfield. Guess what? it's really easy to find, it's on the corner of...Hope AND Olive streets!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the last year, since I moved to the area, I have heard only great things about this little gem of a spot, tucked away off the main drag in Greenfield. Their stated mission: &lt;i&gt;We serve homegrown, farm-inspired food &amp;amp; drink, presented simply, using the best ingredients from our neighborhood&lt;/i&gt; is in perfect alignment with our criteria, so let's go chow down and have fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions or special requests, please let me know as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who have not registered for an event before, please let me remind you that there is a $5.00 per person registration fee, which covers our admin costs and also provides us with a delicious &amp;quot;tasting plate&amp;quot; at the restaurant! Once we are there, we are each responsible for our $25.00 per person 3 course meal, (not including tax + gratuity) and any beverages we may have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know I speak for Chris and myself when I say I am so much looking forward to this upcoming event, please RSVP whether or not you plan to attend so we can get an accurate count for the venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take care and see you in a couple of weeks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;warmly,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jessica&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260918752000</updated><rating><average>4.55999994278</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257191367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November EatUp! at Hope &amp; Olive in Greenfield!</name><id>11773037</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258324200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/11773037/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/c/global_11609868.jpeg</photo_url></item>