<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>555 Asylum Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767876</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-978-2622</phone><name>ArtSpace</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1045061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.682486</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Many Americans have poor eating habits.&amp;nbsp; Trying to eat healthier isn't easy -- you may feel like you're swimming against the tide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's the answer?&amp;nbsp; Get support!&amp;nbsp; Spend time with folks committed to making healthier choices!&amp;nbsp; Find out how they achieved their health goals. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us!&amp;nbsp; Learn, laugh, and make new friends!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15 pm: Potluck Dinner begins.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30 - 8:00 pm: Talk on "The Tao of Diet: Restorative Nutrition"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:00 - 8:30:&amp;nbsp; Discussion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 -&amp;nbsp;on:&amp;nbsp; Clean Up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisl Meredith Huebner (Herbalisl) will explain how to introduce nutritive herbs into your meals so that your health will flourish in all seasons. Potently nourishing herbs and the correct nutritional choices will dramatically improve stamina, digestion, immune function and overall well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisl Meredith Huebner is a nationally board certified Chinese herbalist. In addition, she is a certified practitioner and teacher of Auriculotherapy, Medicinal Aromatherapy and an advanced Reiki practitioner.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This event is part of a series organized by CT Health Foodies which will usually be on the second Tuesday of the month at ArtSpace in downtown Hartford. CT Health Foodies is a supportive community for people interested in learning more about healthy eating. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; ***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the potluck dinner:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Bella Gusta, an olive oil and vinegar shop in West Hartford Center, has donated a Tuscan Herb olive oil for people to sample.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Many people have dietary restrictions. Bring a note card that lists the ingredients in the food you bring or fill out a note card at the potluck.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-This a zero-waste event.&amp;nbsp; Please bring your own plate and utensils.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free parking in the back of the ArtSpace building.&amp;nbsp; Ignore "Resident Parking Only" signs.&amp;nbsp; Parking is allowed during this event.&amp;nbsp; Enter through the back entrance by the murals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donations accepted to cover publicity costs.&amp;nbsp; No one turned away due to a lack of funds.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you on Tuesday, March 13!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>13105264</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331950763000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329157607000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healthy Potluck Dinner and Nutrition Talk Given by Chinese Herbalist</name><id>52184242</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331680500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/52184242/</event_url></item>