<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>695 Hillside St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.213120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Hills - Houghton Pond</name><city>Milton</city><id>5099502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094185</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am doing 2 hikes on Saturday. Starting with an easy hike up the Skyline Trail to the Elliot Tower at 10:30 then meandering down the yellow triangle trail or back down the South side. I hope to do this in 2 or 2.5 hours. Second hike is at 1:30 to possibly 3:30 for a brisk hike with strenuous elevation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LOCATION: Houghton's Pond, Milton, Ma parking area (I will be parked here). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ADDITIONAL INFORMATION: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/b"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/b&lt;/a&gt;... RECOMMENDED GEAR: Water, snacks, food, gloves, proper shoes for hiking, proper clothing for weather conditions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Debra's Cell # - 508-237-4454 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;

 GPS Coordinates - 42.2141 N, 71.1200W &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Address - 695 Hillside St, Milton, MA 02186 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Take Route 93 to Exit 3, Houghton's Pond. Turn right at the stop sign onto Hillside Street. Houghton's &lt;br /&gt;

 Pond is located approximately 1/4 miles on the right; continue onto the Houghton Pond entrance on the &lt;br /&gt;

 right. Or you can take Exit 5 MA 28 Randolph Milton, keep on Randolph St. until you get to set of lights, &lt;br /&gt;

 take left at lights onto Chickatawabut Rd, then left onto Hillside St near the State Police, continue onto &lt;br /&gt;

 the Houghton Pond entrance on the left. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Peaks: Great Blue Hill (635 feet). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Difficulty Level: Moderately Strenuous. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Distance: Will have to find this out. If anyone has a pedometer, bring it along. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Elevation Gain: 2,500 feet - will have to verify this. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Time: We have averaged about 3 hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Weather Forecast: &lt;a&gt;http://www.weather.com/weather/today/Milton...&lt;/a&gt; CANCELLATION POLICY: Inclement weather (mainly Rain) may cancel the hike. If cancelled, it will be &lt;br /&gt;

 rescheduled a few weeks later. I will not have the time to call everyone, so you'll need access to your &lt;br /&gt;

 email to see if the hike is canceled. I will try to post it 4 hours before the hike. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 CODE OF CONDUCT AND DISCLAIMER: In order to participate in this activity, you acknowledge and agree that this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You assume all risk associated with this activity. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at hikesafe.com. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group on the hike and others in the group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * Weather can change quickly. Weather conditions which normally do not appear problematic can be when the body is stressed by hard exercise. You can develop hypothermia or hyperthermia very easily at any outside temperature. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You agree to hike as a group, with the slowest member of the group. If you are late to the meetup, you &lt;br /&gt;

 may try to catch up with the group. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to &lt;br /&gt;

 the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; &lt;br /&gt;

 you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to &lt;br /&gt;

 safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;br /&gt;

 www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and &lt;br /&gt;

 indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Debra's Silver Volvo at the Houghton Pond parking area near the playground.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debra </member_name><member_id>12483780</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326671375000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326205965000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Hike Blue Hills</name><id>47489252</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326555000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/47489252/</event_url></item>