<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Happy Spring to all! Below is a long overdue update for upcoming events for our future meetups. Please take a moment to read the ENTIRE update, as we are adding new meetup dates/locations?.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginning in May, we will now be hosting TWO meetups! For those of you who have been unable attend due to time conflicts, we will continue to hold our regular Meetups on &lt;b&gt;Sunday&lt;/b&gt; as well as on the 4th &lt;b&gt;Saturday&lt;/b&gt; of every month, 1-3pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;  Starting in June we will begin our outdoor season as well!!! As we have done so in the past, we host both indoor/outdoor meetups on SUNDAYS!! I can not stress enough that it is imperative that you RSVP for the event and write in which location you will be attending! Doggie Day will continue to accommodate our usual numbers but since indoor/outdoor events are held on the same day, you don't want to get to the park and have no one there (outdoor meetups do not have number caps for obvious reasons!!!) &lt;br /&gt;Therefore, please list where you will be!  More information about the outdoor meetup location will be posted later in May. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, in JUNE we will be hosting a special event &lt;i&gt;Dharma Dog: a pawsitive experience..... A fun afternoon filled with information and discussion on how to provide the healthiest environment for your pet.&lt;/i&gt; This will be a special meetup to be held at Doggie Day, I am hoping to acquire a guest speaker. Again more info to be posted in a few weeks. Most likely to be held June 28th (1-3pm), so save the date! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Therefore our tentative schedule is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;Sunday May 11th (Happy Mother?s Day) Doggie Day: 1-3pm&lt;br /&gt;Saturday May 31st let?s attempt to meet at Carlton Park in the South End; I will leave a description of the park location on the CALENDARS section of the Meetup site! please rsvp&lt;br /&gt;Sunday June 8th both indoor/outdoor meetups begin! Indoor to be held at Doggie day (1-3pm) Outdoor location: TBA &lt;br /&gt;Saturday June 28th Dharma Dog event/meetup, Doggie Day (1-3pm)...future Saturday meetups will also be held at Doggie Day (with the exception of May 31st) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should anyone have any questions, feel free to contact me.&lt;br /&gt;Susana&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210729613000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208110167000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua May Meeting</name><id>7731641</id><headcount>34</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210525200000</time><rsvp_limit>42</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/7731641/</event_url></item>