<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Canucks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you may know Australia has been through quite the summer (our winter) already. There has been a rash of floods through their country and now a very strong cyclone is approaching the coast line. A fundraiser to help with relief efforts has been organized through the British Consulate.&amp;nbsp; It would be great if we can come and support our Commonwealth cousins. Here are the details:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Aussies request your help raising funds for the victims of the Australian floods. Please join us for a wine reception and silent auction complete with live performances by Australian musicians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All proceeds will benefit The Premier&amp;rsquo;s Flood Disaster Relief Appeal in Queensland and be directed to the Queensland Relief Appeal. The Australian Red Cross will manage the distribution of the donated funds on behalf of the Queensland Government.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All attendees will need to register and pay prior to the event. Please follow the link the American Australian Association website for full registration and payment details: &lt;a href="http://www.americanaustralian.org/en/cev/reg/703/"&gt;http://www.americanaustralian.org/en/cev/reg/703/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once you have registered with the Australian Consulate please RSVP here on this site as well. We will meet before hand at the Au Bon Pain in Kendall Square at 1:30 PM (On Main Street right outside the T stop)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew</member_name><member_id>2881088</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce Turnbull</member_name><member_id>4018534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298127028000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296574552000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Australian Flood Relief Fundraiser at the BRITISH CONSULATE!</name><id>16397378</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297537200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/16397378/</event_url></item>