<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>269 Newbury St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349556</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>"Itadaki" Japanese Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>3418362</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083595</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Japan Society of Boston is holding its annual "Sake Tasting Event" this Friday, May 17th from 5:30---7:30pm. The venue is the Itadaki Restaurant and Bar in Back Bay on 269 Newbury Street. The Sake Expert John Gauntner and 7 Master Sake Brewers from Japan, will be on hand to pour over 30 varieties of Sake from more than 12 of Japan's finest breweries. Admission includes Sake Tasting and food provided by Itadaki Japanese restaurant. This is an amazing opportunity to try 30 varieties of Sake and have it be presented by Sake Masters direct from Japan! This event is good for beginners new to Sake and also those who are advanced! Admission is $35 for Japan Society Members/ $50 for Non-Members. (Note: if you join the Japan Society the cost is only $20 AND you enter a drawing for a FREE Business Class ticket to Japan by JAL)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Event sells out every year. You MUST register DIRECTLY through the Japan Society of Boston. &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.JapanSocietyBoston.org"&gt;http://www.JapanSocietyBoston.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To check out Itadaki's Japanese menu see: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://ItadakiBoston.com"&gt;http://ItadakiBoston.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please Note: If the event is sold out or you wish not to do the Sake Tasting ---please join us for a delicious Japanese meal or Sushi at Itadaki beginning from 7:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP and let me know if you will be attending the Sake Tasting? Or if you will join us for Dinner AFTER the Sake Tasting? I will save us good seats. Let's enjoy a nice Friday nite dinner at a Japanese restaurant in Back Bay! Best, Kim&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: Itadaki Restaurant is located on Newbury Street between Fairfield Street and Gloucester Street in Back Bay. The closest subway is the Green Line at Copley or Hynes Convention Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Questions please see: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging/events/119223472"&gt;http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging/events/119223472&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim</member_name><member_id>88605612</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368850330000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368501413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enjoy Japan Society's 'Sake Tasting Event'  AND/OR Japanese Dinner in Boston!</name><id>119276532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368825300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/119276532/</event_url></item>