<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>89 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351844</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-439-3142 </phone><name>The NonProfit Center </name><city>Boston</city><id>1058586</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057489</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$20.00 (pay at the door)</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you often get stuck in conversations? Not know how to approach people at networking events?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;Join Socializing for Justice for a&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;fast-paced,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;fun &amp;amp; interactive&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Skillshare on the Art of the Schmooze on September 7, 6:00 - 8:30 PM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SoJust hosts events that draw progressives of all stripes that share common values but may work on different issues. We host monthly socials that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections and run a monthly Skillshare Series, hosted by The NonProfit Center*, which increases our individual capacity for movement building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing -&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;bring your own dinner&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;6:30-8:30 Training and Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;SoJust's Co-Founder, Robbie Samuels, who is well known for his schmoozing skills, is this month's facilitator.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Art of the Schmooze&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;Forming and cultivating relationships is at the heart of any successful fundraising campaign, volunteer drive, committee effort or community building activity. This training will give you the confidence to pursue your personal goals - from the importance of shaking hands and making eye contact, to tips on the best opening line and how to exit a conversation gracefully. An amazing side benefit is that you'll learn how to create a welcoming community space by keeping an eye out for outliers, considering yourself a host instead of a guest and knowing how to compliment someone without "othering" them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT OUR PRESENTER&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Robbie Samuels&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;has extensive community organizing, events logistics and fundraising experience. In 2006 he co-founded Socializing for Justice to build a cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston based on the philosophy of abundance. He is the Special Events Manager at Gay &amp;amp; Lesbian Advocates &amp;amp; Defenders (GLAD), an adjunct professor at Lesley College teaching &amp;ldquo;Activism and Change in Communities&amp;rdquo;, and a 2011 Fellow at the New Leaders Council Institute. On the side he offers trainings and consultation to non-profit boards, venture capitalists and grassroots organizers. Learn more about his networking and fundraising trainings at&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.robbiesamuels.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.robbiesamuels.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;*&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.nonprofitcenterboston.org/site/c.ddKGIQNuEmG/b.1363373/k.5381/About_Us__Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;- The NonProfit Center&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;is located one block from South Station at 89 South Street. The Center is physically accessible through the main lobby.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this "Movement Moment". Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With almost 1800 members and 5 years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston (100+ events!), Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Check out our&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315567616000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308357436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Art of the Schmooze</name><id>22614921</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315432800000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/22614921/</event_url></item>