<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Chestnut Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01364</zip><lat>42.558395</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Forster's Farm </name><city>Orange</city><id>3661692</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.320880</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;(UPDATED 9/28)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;There's good news, and there's not so good news... The good news is that the Weather Channel is calling for the showers to end around 9am Saturday with just a 20% chance after that. The bad news is that we are parking in corn fields. Plan on slippery, muddy conditions there as well as the venue site (held in a field).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;More good news!  There are &lt;strong&gt;TWO&lt;/strong&gt; parking areas now!  As you approach from the South (from New Salem) on Holtshire Road, the main parking area is on your right (can't miss it thanks to a couple dozen signs!!!) AND...  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is now a "hikers only" parking area on the LEFT side of the road about 100' past Fairman Road!!!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;This, my fellow hikers, is where we will meet.  I drive a silver Toyota Corolla and will be parked in the hikers lot. I will then stand patiently beside the road, wearing a backpack waiting for you garlic loving hikers (and even those of you who don't love garlic).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;So...  Plan on it being cloudy and chilly. Think about bringing a rain coat. Dress warm. Consider having wet feet so perhaps dry socks/shoes in your car for when you return. Also, this is a very "green" event, so if you bring a bottle of water, find a recycling bin to throw it away in, or bring it home with you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;(end of update)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;Please note that this venue charges a small admission fee (I think it is around $5) So be prepared. Also, there is A LOT for sale as there are numerous vendors. Also a number of food selections as well. So...   BRING MONEY!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AND NOTE THAT WE ARE &lt;em&gt;NOT&lt;/em&gt; MEETING AT THE ACTUALLY GARLIC FESTIVAL. WE ARE MEETING AT THE SATELLITE PARKING LOT AT THE INTERSECTION OF HOLTSHIRE ROAD AND FAIRMAN ROAD IN ORANGE. (FOLLOW THE SIGNS)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This festival runs from 10:00am to 5:00pm rain or shine on September 29th and 30th. I normally take the shuttle bus provided (It's free!), but thought it might be fun to organize a bunch of "hikers" to hike in. There is a nearby trail that is supposed to lead directly to the venue site. A casual search for it turned up empty this weekend, but I will continue to seek out the trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;The trail has been found!!! &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I spent a few hours this morning in the hot and humid air hiking from the venue spot back to near the parking area. "Most" of the trail is well marked. I will attempt to find those in charge of trail maintenance and mark the Bullard Farm portion of the trail a little better. I literally bush whacked 1/4 mile through ferns and picker bushes to get out to the road!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;From the parking area at the intersection of Fairman Road and Holtshire road (in Orange), we will be hiking east for less than half a mile before entering the woods on the Bullard Farm Loop Trail (white blazes on trees). This trail is pretty much all uphill for a half mile until it connects with the North Pond Ridge Trail (yellow blazes on trees). From there is is a pretty level trail heading west for 1.45 miles until it ends at the Garlic and Arts Festival site.  Should you choose to return by these trails, keep a good eye out for the blazes on the trees. And pay NO ATTENTION to the red blazes or blue blazes as those are property line markers.  Total one way hike should be approximately 2.5 miles and take roughly one hour. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For information, check out &lt;a href="http://garlicandarts.org/"&gt;http://garlicandarts.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 2 Eastbound:&lt;/em&gt; Take Exit 16, at the end of the ramp turn left onto Route 202 South, drive 2 miles (there will be signs!) to Elm St. Turn right, then follow signs 1.8 miles to the shuttle lot at the intersection of Holtshire and Fairman Rd. (Elm St will change name to Holtshire Rd at the Orange town line)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 2 Westbound:&lt;/em&gt; Take Exit 16, at the end of the ramp turn right onto Rt 202 South, drive 2 miles (there will be signs!) and turn right on to Elm St , then follow signs 1.8miles to shuttle lot at the intersection of Holtshire and Fariman Rd. (Elm St will change name to Holtshire Rd at the Orange town line)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 202 Northbound:&lt;/em&gt; Follow 202 to Elm St, Turn Left and follow signs 1.8 miles to shuttle lot at intersection of Holtshire and Fairman Rds.  (Elm St will change name to Holtshire Rd at the Orange town line)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 122 Northbound:&lt;/em&gt; Follow 122 until you reach the blinking light at the intersection of Rt 202 in New Salem. Turn left onto Rt 202 South, and drive approximately 1/2 mile (there will be signs!) and turn right on to Elm St, then follow signs 1.8 miles to shuttle lot at intersection of Holtshire and Fairman Rd. (Elm St will change name to Holtshire Rd at the Orange town line)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry Rooney</member_name><member_id>43555442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349014313000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340662936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>This hike STINKS!  Hike to the North Quabbin Garlic &amp; Arts Festival</name><id>70712522</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348927200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/70712522/</event_url></item>