<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Emerson Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.615200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Open Door</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1528276</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.675987</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do you like to paint? Do you like to help out a great cause?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Let’s go paint a bowl for the Empty Bowl.  I will be scheduling the actual event in May be watching for that coming up soon......&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;I have been asked a few times what this event is and if you "have" to need to know how to paint??&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;So what this is, is a &lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt;, great (and creative way) to help a food pantry raise money to help out the homeless in their community. What we will do, when we get there we will get a bowl and a pallet of 8 different colors of paint. From there we will sit and create our own masterpieces. If you think that you can't paint anything freehand then bring some stencils or stamps, they do have some items that you can use to paint your bowl.  It's a fun morning out, helping a community, getting creative and having fun with friends.  Some samples of previous bowls are solid back ground with pock-a-dots, flowers all over the bowl, or even all different stripes inside and out of the bowl.  All cute in their own ways!  So come on out and help a great cause and spend a Saturday morning with some fun people! Hope to see you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do you have painting skills? No matter what your answer is come on down to this event and paint a bowl anyways, maybe they will even let us paint 2 bowl’s... each? How gratifying would it be to see your bowl on the table amongst all the bowls that people are picking from, to take home on the day of the Empty bowl event in May (see below).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I will be making a reservation for us so PLEASE only serious RSVP’s. If your plans change please come back and change your RSVP as soon as possible, so I can tell them that the # of people is different. Be prepared I am NOT sure we will all be able to sit together, if this is a problem then this event may not be for you. Children are welcome to this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Pl&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;ease note that the painting time is only from 10:00-noon. If you can't come at 10, but still want to paint, then come when you can, but let me know in your RSVP so I am not looking for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information about the Empty Bowl Event (which will be scheduled in May):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The mission of The Open Door is to alleviate the impact of hunger in their community. They use practical strategies to connect people to good food, to advocate on behalf of those in need, and to engage others in the work of building food security, at this event you pay to get in what that gets you is a bowl (maybe your own, if you can find it or another one), soup, bread, beverage and a cookie. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;an&lt;/span&gt; be a little tight, please make sure you are not blocking anyone’s driveway, if needed you can always park across the street at the school (no one will bother you there).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is: 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues? Please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer” You can give your dues to either Donna at any event. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside, not matter which door you come in look around for us, we will likely be in the middle room on one of the sides.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363564415000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361659953000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paint a bowl (for the empty bowl to be posted soon in May)</name><id>106064952</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363442400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/106064952/</event_url></item>