<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>S Bremen St &amp; Marginal St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02128</zip><lat>42.367220</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>East Boston Greenway cabbose</name><city>East Boston</city><id>823441</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.040211</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Boston Natural Areas Network's signature event - Winter Lights Along the Greenway&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Enjoy the East Boston Greenway lit up with festive luminarias and a holiday sing-along with local performers and carolers. Hot chocolate and cookies will keep you warm.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will take a short walk along the Greenway to enjoy the lights and perfomers, then head to DParma for an Italian dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the caboose near South Bremen and Marginal Streets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The East Boston Greenway is a linear park planned along the old railroad right-of-way, connecting neglected portions of East Boston’s historic waterfront to the Piers Park, the Boston Parks stadium and two Urban Wilds - Wood Island Bay Marsh and Belle Isle Marsh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The East Boston Greenway provides a buffer along the Logan Airport edge to the City and when complete, will add over 12 acres of new park land and a 3.3 mile pedestrian/bike trail through the center of East Boston. The Greenway’s development is closely tied with the &amp;quot;Big Dig&amp;quot; project which is building the 15 acre Bremen St Park and a 7 acre expansion of Memorial Stadium along the greenway alignment. The City of Boston who purchased the abandoned Conrail railroad line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DParma Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;186 Sumner St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02128&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(617) 567-9670&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228772284000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227936052000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Lights Along the Greenway</name><id>9245364</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228599000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9245364/</event_url></item>