<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Plymouth</address_2><address_1>114 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.960255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 830-0001</phone><name>Isaac's Restaurant</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>360116</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.665980</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It's finally happening! Save the date!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday, September 8 at noon, Mike will be leading his long-discussed lunch in Plymouth Center, followed by a walk around the square and/or along the waterfront for those who have the time and would like to see a bit of Plymouth after the tourist season. Historic attractions in this area include Plymouth Rock and the Mayflower II (celebrating its 50th anniversary this year). Other attractions include the Antique Mall, various gift and specialty shops, the Chocolate Bar and a Kiskadee Coffee Company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of the recommendations of several members as well as many other good reports that Mike has heard over the years, we have chosen to dine at Isaac's Restaurant on the waterfront. After lunch, we will form one or more informal groups depending on which areas people would like to see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us at Isaac's, and then in the open air of &amp;quot;America's Hometown&amp;quot; as we put the &amp;quot;out&amp;quot; in dining out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3 South (coming from Braintree) take Exit 6A (Route 44 East). From Route 3 North (coming from Cape Cod) take Exit 6 (Route 44) and head East toward Plymouth Center. Once you get onto Route 44, you will quickly pass under Route 3, then immediately come to a traffic light (go straight through) and pass a large Hess gas station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next stoplight is at the end of Route 44 where it intersects with Route 3A. Go straight across Route 3A, then follow the short stretch of road as it turns right, then left, heading down towards the water. After about a minute, you will come to the intersection with Water St., where you have to either turn right or go around a rotary to turn left. Turn right onto Water St. This is the Plymouth Waterfront.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Isaac's is in the block of buildings between Chilton and Howland Streets (the second and third streets on your right.) Metered parking is available on both sides of Water St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Isaac's is located on the second floor of its building (the first floor houses a couple shops). There is an elevator available for those who do not wish to take the stairs. Look for Mike and other members around the foot of the stairway, but if you somehow miss the main group, both Mikes name and the name &amp;quot;South Shore Meetup Group&amp;quot; should be noted with our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312746714000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188048151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk Around the Rock!</name><id>6240355</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189267200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/6240355/</event_url></item>