<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>65 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.398327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 591-2100</phone><name>Orleans Bar &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669349</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123787</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for our usual casual brunch affair, where the conversation ranges widely in a superstition-free atmosphere. Whet your appetite with a peek at the menu: &lt;a href="http://www.orleansrestaurant.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.orleansrestaurant.com/&lt;/a&gt;. As we often do with our brunches, we've selected a charity to support with voluntary giving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time, we're supporting a fundraising effort undertaken by the brother of one Olivia van N., of our members. His organization, &lt;a href="http://www.upenyu.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.upenyu.org...&lt;/a&gt;, provides treatment for children afflicted with parasitic diseases. If their project at &lt;a href="http://www.globalgiving.org/projects/treatment-for-worm-diseases-ir-zimbabwean-children/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.globalgivi...&lt;/a&gt; raises $5,000 from 40 donors by February 29, 11:59 PM, they'll earn a permanent spot on the website GlobalGiving, making their future development work a lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SINCE the fundraising deadline is BEFORE the brunch date, please note in the comments section below whether you plan to donate -- I'll send a check in on the group's behalf, and recoup anything I pay out of pocket when I see you. With no additional charge for the service, ahem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if you don't plan to attend the brunch, you're welcome to chip in to the donation via PayPal (or other arrangements... contact me to make a cash or check contribution). 85% of donations to this cause go directly to Upenyu; the remaining 15% is retained by GlobalGiving to maintain their infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Olivia writes: "I thought I would try to reach out to any of you who want to help my brother's secular effort in a region of Zimbabwe that is dominated by religious influences. His team treats schistosomiasis, which mainly affects little kids-- they urinate blood and fail at school because of these horrible parasites that are actually incredibly easy to treat."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are aware of a local cause that you'd like to see supported by an upcoming Blasphemy Brunch, let us know!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330949281000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329495040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Blasphemy Brunch</name><id>52720742</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330876800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/52720742/</event_url></item>