<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Directed and photographed by Ron Fricke. Screenplay by Ron Fricke and Mark Magidson. Cinestudio is pleased to present Ron Fricke and Mark Magdison’s long-anticipated follow-up to Baraka, one of our audience’s most loved films! Samsara - a Sanskrit word meaning the ever turning wheel of life - is a nonverbal movie that was made, according to director Ron Fricke, to “delve deeper into my favorite theme: humanity’s relationship to the eternal.” Shot over four years in 100 locations in 25 countries, the images of our planet are simply stunning. Equally powerful is the focus on individuals - dancing in a Filipino prison yard, using weapons, creating sand mandalas, working in mines, and worshipping at Mecca - who make up the diversity of life on Earth. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The mesmerizing images of unprecedented clarity were created by shooting in 70mm, then transferring the film through the highest resolution scanning process available to the new 4K digital projection format - now in place at Cinestudio! “Visually breathtaking! Unlike anything you will ever see.” - IndieWire. "Samsara is pure cinema." American Cinematographer 99 min &lt;a href="http://barakasamsara.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://barakasamsara.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Stay for post-film discussion &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Questions? Susanlaranoff@yahoo.com or 860.798.6854 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For directions to Cinestudio- map quest 300 Summit Street, Hartford, CT or visit the Cinestudio web site www.cinestudio.org or call 860.297 CINE (2463) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Stay for post-film discussion - see in details below</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349404573000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-469</urlname><id>836707</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>12 Step Buddhist &amp; Recovery Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348613854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie Night - Samsara @ Cinestudio, Hartford, Ct</name><id>84078042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349392500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-469/events/84078042/</event_url></item>