<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>341 Milford Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06013</zip><lat>41.733662</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sessions Woods Wildlife Management</name><city>Burlington</city><id>8738552</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.954659</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Connecticut Forest &amp;amp; Park Association (CFPA) is the non-profit organization responsible for the blue trail system in CT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://runandwalkforthewoods.dojiggy.com" target="_blank"&gt;Run (&amp;amp; Walk) for the Woods&lt;/a&gt; on Sunday, September 16th to support CFPA's efforts to protect forests, create walking trails, and educate children and adults about the amazing natural resources of Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join the Connecticut Forest &amp;amp; Park Association (CFPA), Fleet Feet, REI, Connecticut Department of Energy and Environmental Protection (DEEP), and The Connecticut Woodcarvers Association for a fun-filled event at&lt;/span&gt; Sessions Woods Wildlife Management Area in Burlington. There will be a 5K Trail Race, 5K Walk, and lots of family friendly activities. Fleet Feet and REI will organize the race and walk and host clinics about running, walking, and hiking. The Connecticut Woodcarvers Association will hold a "Carve a Walking Stick" session. Letterboxes are in the woods and DEEP's &lt;span&gt;Sessions Woods Conservation Education Center&lt;/span&gt; will be open for you to enjoy and learn more about Connecticut wildlife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Registration begins at 8:30 a.m., the 5K Trail Race begins at 9:30 a.m., and the 5K Walk starts at 10:00 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 5K Trail Race fee is only $25. The race fee will be waived for those who raise contributions of $50 or more. Walkers will be asked to raise funds to support CFPA's programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For all event details, registration, and pledge instructions, visit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://runandwalkforthewoods.dojiggy.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://runandwalkforthewoods.dojiggy.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You probably walk or run every weekend, so please set this day aside to walk for CFPA, the association of conservationists working all year long to keep the forest and trails alive for you to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347916730000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345078660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CFPA's Run (&amp; Walk) for the Woods</name><id>77939412</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347798600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/77939412/</event_url></item>