<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372593</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>4961552</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116318</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Harvard Book Store is thrilled to welcome Booker Prize–Winning novelist Peter Carey for our annual Chuck Pacheco Memorial Lecture. Mr. Carey will be reading from his new novel, &lt;em&gt;The Chemistry of Tears.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An automaton, a man and a woman who can never meet, two stories of love—all are brought to incandescent life in this hauntingly moving novel from one of the finest writers of our time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;London 2010: Catherine Gehrig, conservator at the Swinburne museum, learns of the sudden death of her colleague and lover of thirteen years. As the mistress of a married man, she must struggle to keep the depth of her anguish to herself. The one other person who knows Catherine’s secret—her boss—arranges for her to be given a special project away from prying eyes in the museum’s Annexe. Usually controlled and rational, but now mad with grief, Catherine reluctantly unpacks an extraordinary, eerie automaton that she has been charged with bringing back to life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she begins to piece together the clockwork puzzle, she also uncovers a series of notebooks written by the mechanical creature’s original owner: a nineteenth-century Englishman, Henry Brandling, who traveled to Germany to commission it as a magical amusement for his consumptive son. But it is Catherine, nearly two hundred years later, who will find comfort and wonder in Henry’s story. And it is the automaton, in its beautiful, uncanny imitation of life, that will link two strangers confronted with the mysteries of creation, the miracle and catastrophe of human invention, and the body’s astonishing chemistry of love and feeling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Chuck Pacheco Memorial Lecture is held each year in honor of a beloved Harvard Book Store staff member who died of cancer in 2006. Proceeds from this event will be donated to the Dana Farber Cancer Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/event/peter_carey/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.harvard.com/event/peter_carey/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338473666000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Larrikins</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aussie-145</urlname><id>222356</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Aussie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337632699000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peter Carey at Harvard Book Store</name><id>65743392</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338418800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aussie-145/events/65743392/</event_url></item>