<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Me mandaran el idea que puedimos tener un noche de charlas sobre viajes por ejemplo alguin puede hablar sobre su viaje a Machu Pichu.  Yo voy a ser el primero voluntario de hablar sobre mi viaje a Machu Pichu y otras sitios turistico en Peru.  Por favor espero que alguin mas quiere hacer un charla sobre sus viajes a lugares turistico.  Mandame una nota con tu nombre y la tema de que deseas hablar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I received an email giving me an idea for the next meet up and it was well received by other member.  For our meeting in June we are looking for volunteers to speak about interesting touristic places they have been to.  I will be the first volunteer to speak about my trip to Machu Pichu and other touristic sites in Peru.  I am asking for others to come forward and speak about their experiences on trips to touristic places.  Please sent me a note with your name and what you wish to speak about.  We need at least 5 more volunteers.  It will give you a great opportunity to practice your Spanish. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West (Hartford)                                                                                                                        # Take ramp left for I-84 East / US-6 East / US-44 East / Bulkeley Bridge9.1 miles&lt;br /&gt;# 7At exit 63, take ramp right for SR-30 / SR-83 toward South Windsor0.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;# 8Turn right onto SR-30 / Tolland Tpke0.7 miles&lt;br /&gt;# 9Arrive at 230 Deming St, Manchester, CT 06042-1778 on the left0.0 milesThe last intersection is Hale Rd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East&lt;br /&gt;# Take ramp left and follow signs for I-84 West9.5 miles&lt;br /&gt;# 4At exit 63, take ramp right for SR-30 toward Manchester / South Windsor0.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;# 5Turn left onto SR-30 / Deming St0.3 miles&lt;br /&gt;# 6Arrive at 230 Deming St, Manchester, CT 06042-1778 on the left0.0 milesThe last intersection is Hale RdIf you reach Shares Ln, you've gone too far&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Dworski</member_name><member_id>2589505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Weingartner</member_name><member_id>8679708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276701617000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274807122000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Un Noche de Presentaciones</name><id>13590785</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276556400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/13590785/</event_url></item>