<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 6:55, so&lt;b&gt; let's meet at 6:25&lt;/b&gt; right inside the theater lobby. Then I'll get us tickets, we can all buy snacks and head into the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unos after to chat!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case you missed it, Christine Tello posted on our &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/messages/boards/"&gt;Message Board&lt;/a&gt; this article about Shutter Island:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hollywoodeastconnection.com/?p=4832"&gt;Scorsese’s Shutter Island Set off the Coast of Boston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By: Ian Ross&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’ve seen the trailer for the soon-to-be-released Shutter Island, directed by Martin Scorsese. But did you know it was shot almost entirely in the Boston area?  Excluding a documentary on The Rolling Stones, Scorsese has most recently brought us the academy award winning film, The Departed, which was also famously filmed in Boston.  Based on the novel by Dennis Lehane, who is himself a Boston native, Shutter Island has an all-star cast and is sure to keep viewers on the edge of their seats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Someone is missing.”  That is the publicized tagline for the dramatic thriller set in 1954 at a secluded island off the coast of Boston. Shot mostly in or around the Boston Harbor (including Peddocks Island), the creepy Medfield State Hospital campus, and the scenic Acadia Nat’l Park in Maine, Shutter Island marks the fourth collaboration between Scorsese and Leonardo DiCaprio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DiCaprio plays Teddy Daniels, a U.S. Marshal investigating the recent disappearance of a woman incarcerated for murder at a hospital for the criminally insane, which is located on Shutter Island.  She vanished from her room overnight and is supposedly hiding somewhere on the premises. Daniels’s search for the woman uncovers terrible mysteries that the doctors and staff would rather keep quiet.  Is that another fake Boston accent we hear Leo attempting?  When asked about what it was like working with Scorsese, DiCaprio said in this interview, “he expects you to do all the research” and “it’s a really empowering process when someone gives you full ownership over the character.” In addition to DiCaprio, the cast includes Ben Kingsley, Mark Ruffalo, Emily Mortimer, and Patricia Clarkson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With such classics as Taxi Driver and Cape Fear under his belt, Scorsese is not inexperienced with the darker side of cinematic storytelling.  However, he’s taking a slightly different turn with his new plot-based and genre-oriented film.  “I tried to pull back a few times and not get so emotionally and psychologically involved,” says Scorsese of the filming, as quoted in the Los Angeles Times.  “But this story, these characters — it was a very unsettling experience.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scorsese wasn’t the only person affected by the project, as DiCaprio also fell victim to the intensity of the production. “It was draining,” says DiCaprio.  “It got to the point where it became more and more realistic the deeper it got – swerving away from anything stylistic and becoming more about human nature.” In fact, a psychologist was deemed necessary to be on the set during filming due to the emotional demands on the actors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having come a long way from the blockbuster Titanic in 1997 – which launched him into the public eye – Leonardo DiCaprio has established himself as one of Hollywood’s most sought after leading men.  He has appeared in over 20 films throughout his career, taking on challenging roles that have only added to his popularity. DiCaprio’s partnership with Scorsese has lead to three critically acclaimed films, and their newest will likely join those ranks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shutter Island overcame a postponement from its original planned release in October 2009, moving it to February 2010.  Though this removes it as a contender for the 2010 Oscars, the film is open to nomination for the following year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether it will truly become a classic and grabs some Oscars like so many others of Scorsese’s films still remains to be seen.  And yet DiCaprio seems confident, saying, “There were moments on set where I definitely felt like we were going into uncharted territory.”  Only time will tell if the unique experience the actors had making the film translates to the screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shutter Island opens nationwide February 19th, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, I know what you're thinking... Dana doesn't DO horror films. To which I tell you, &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809998389/details"&gt;Shutter Island&lt;/a&gt; seems to me to be more of a thriller/action movie than a horror flick. If I'm wrong, I'll be prepared: I'm bringing Paul to protect me. Unless Leonardo DiCaprio protects me... ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW, this is another pick that was filmed in MA, Medfield to be precise. With a little Seoul, Korea thrown in the mix for flavor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two U.S. marshals, Teddy Daniels and Chuck Aule, are summoned to a remote and barren island off the coast of Massachusetts to investigate the mysterious disappearance of a murderess from the island's fortress-like hospital for the criminally insane.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Shutter Island!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268696846000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267126193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shutter Island</name><id>12707752</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268177400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12707752/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>