<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research and Development Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1534447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ampagency.com/"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/6/c/event_109359532.jpeg" width="200" height="200" style="max-height : 200px ; max-width : 200px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pizza is sponsored by &lt;a href="http://www.ampagency.com/"&gt;AMP Agency&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;AMP Agency is an integrated communications agency that employs an&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;“Insights Inspired, Results Driven” approach to conceive, develop and&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;implement innovative marketing solutions across a range of channels.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;All recommendations AMP makes are inspired by consumer insights and a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;deep understanding of all media channels and powered by an agency-wide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;spirit of integration and creativity. Our client roster is comprised&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;of industry leaders including Maybelline New York, Hasbro, Samsonite,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Intel, Princess Cruises, NFL PLAYERS and Ansell Healthcare.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, if you would like to donate to the Boston WordPress meetup, please visit our &lt;a href="http://bostonwp.org"&gt;bostonwp.org&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30-7:00PM: Pizza and Networking&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00-7:10PM: Opening remarks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15-8:00PM:  Talk 1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:10-8:55PM: Talk 2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 1 (for Developers):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prototyping Web Apps with WordPress &lt;br /&gt;

 by &lt;span&gt;Blaise Freeman and&lt;/span&gt; Ned Lomigora (@&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/zeeenmedia"&gt;zeeenmedia&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this presentation we'll share how our startup—Zeeen—is using WordPress to quickly prototype and test novel web applications for promoting books. We wrote a plugin to simplify and accelerate creation of promotional platform for authors, which may have a wider application. We'll walk you through tradeoffs we made while building this plugin. We will make this plugin available the WordPress community at large and welcome any feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blaise Freeman and Ned Lomigora are local entrepreneurs and co-founders of zeeen.com, a book promotion startup based in Boston, MA. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 2 (for Beginners/Intermediate):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WordPress and Ecommerce &lt;br /&gt;

 by &lt;span&gt;Brian Piccolo&lt;/span&gt; (@&lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/amp_agency"&gt;amp_agency&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn how to sell your stuff through WordPress as we walk you through some of today’s most popular Ecommerce solutions within WordPress. We’ll take a look at some of the more popular WordPress plugins to help get the job done and take an in depth look at the new WooCommerce plugin from WooThemes. We’ll show you the easiest ways to sell physical goods, affiliate products and downloadables. This session will cater to beginner/intermediate users however we’ll be prepared to answer all of your WordPress Ecommerce questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brian Piccolo has been managing and designing the technical requirements of Web development projects for over ten years. As the VP of Interactive at AMP Agency, he oversees the technology aspect of all client projects. In this role, Brian is responsible for the design and development of dozens of complex online systems, serving as an IT strategist, systems architect and lead developer. He has helped clients from both Fortune 500  companies as well as small to mid-sized organizations use the Internet for competitive advantage. He is well-versed in an array of enabling technologies and draws upon this expertise and experience to deliver customized technology solutions to AMP’s clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prior to joining AMP Agency, Brian was a Principal and the Senior Technologist at Pixel Bridge. Brian also held positions as Actuarial Analyst and Senior Business Analyst at Liberty Mutual Group. Brian was a senior member of the project team that designed and implemented the first homeowners data warehouse for the Personal Lines business, a multi-terabyte system.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brian is a graduate of Bryant College with a Bachelor of Science in Business Administration and a concentration in Applied Actuarial Mathematics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>James Coletti</member_name><member_id>7809368</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Eng</member_name><member_id>9694496</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Bishop</member_name><member_id>13435843</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337045325000</updated><rating><average>4.84000015259</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>158</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330449586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Apr2012: Prototyping Web Apps with WordPress (DEV) &amp; WP and Ecommerce (Beginner)</name><id>54185662</id><headcount>110</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335825000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/54185662/</event_url></item>