<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Arrow Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.370087</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-910-0822</phone><name>Club Oberon</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1058452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113556</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/8/6/event_152215942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;I am hosting this event with two other groups (MetroWest Single Parents &amp;amp; Central Mass Singles 25-45) and I thought I would open it up to this group too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Tickets are $10 on Goldstar.com!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;Bye Bye Liver: The Boston Drinking Play&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Friday, August 31st (Labor Day Weekend)  at 8:00pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drunken friends, over-served basket cases, pushy bouncers and all of the other hallmarks of bar culture collide in the hilarious, booze-fueled sketch comedy of Bye Bye Liver: The Boston Drinking Play. A 75-minute romp through the best, worst and all-too-familiar aspects of social imbibing, Liver goes way beyond the standard sketch show. In a lively theater-turned-bar atmosphere, audience members interact with the actors, competing in social games and an often-called for "social drink." Thanks to Liver, now bar-goers don't have to choose between grabbing a drink and catching a show. &lt;br /&gt;

Bye Bye Liver is a fun, fast-paced comedic romp that takes a satirical look at the pratfalls and pitfalls of the drinking culture. Whether it's the girl we all know that should never, ever drink liquor or a terrifying (yet enlightening) look into the Ladies Room at the club, every drinking danger is captured in hilarious detail. And it's all interspersed with interactive social games with the audience, such as Never Have I Ever and Would You Rather! You'll not find a better time with your clothes on OR off but, you know....please wear clothes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note in your RSVP if you are interested in meeting for dinner before the show. Tickets are general admission so we will meetup at 7:00 and go in for the pre show. More details to come!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346512030000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345922858000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Interactive play -- Bye Bye Liver!</name><id>79335992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346454000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/79335992/</event_url></item>