<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Greene Street</address_2><address_1>One Regency Plaza</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821662</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Regency Plaza</name><city>Providence</city><id>1118378</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.418759</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's the last one for the year so let's not miss our chance.  We can meet at the main parking lot where the bus will take us around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experience Gallery Night Providence&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gallery Night Providence is a free, fun-filled introduction to Providence’s exciting art scene! On the third Thursday of the month, from March through November, twenty-one of the city’s hot “art spots” open their doors inviting you to a visual arts party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Information Center For 2009, Gallery Night Providence offers a new location for our central Art Bus depot and information booth. As of March 19, we are located at Regency Plaza in downtown Providence best described, in true Rhode Island fashion, as directly behind where the old Providence Police Station used to be. Kitty corner from the rear of the Providence Public Library on Greene Street, a hop skip and a jump from the Dunkin Donuts Center, Regency Plaza offers us our first time ever indoor information booth for those rare less-than-perfect evenings in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Free at any one of the seven parking lots situated conveniently throughout the city and walk to your favorite gallery. Stroll from gallery to gallery, enjoying the Providence skyline and the historic city streets. Use the brochure maps to discover the galleries, museums, art spots, and parking lots just a short walk from one another.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ride the Art Bus through Providence. Park your car at our new central location at Regency Plaza located on the corner of Greene and Fountain Streets, conveniently located near both the Dunkin Donuts center and the Providence Public Library. Board the Art Bus, or pick up the bus from any one of your favorite galleries. Art Busses circulate the city from 5 to 9 p.m. The final run for each Art Bus is at 8:40 p.m. Be sure to catch the last bus to return you to your car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gallery Night Guides are stationed at Regency Place and ride the Art Busses. They offer information about different art exhibitions and point out the city’s historic and architectural treasures.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrity Guided Tours Providence celebrities take time to share their thoughts about artworks on display. Walking tours start from Regency Plaza at 6pm and 6:30 pm and last about an hour. As always, we end the season in November with our one-of-a-kind art shopping tour. Call us at 401 490-2042 for up-to-date information. more&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions &lt;br /&gt;From the South&lt;br /&gt;* Take I-95 northbound to Exit 21 (Broadway)&lt;br /&gt;* Take right at end of ramp onto Broadway&lt;br /&gt;* Bear right onto Empire Street&lt;br /&gt;* Take second right at light onto Washington Street&lt;br /&gt;* Take a right on to Greene Street&lt;br /&gt;• Take a left into the second parking lot. There will be a concierge to direct you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North&lt;br /&gt;* Take I-95 southbound to Exit 21 (Atwells Avenue)&lt;br /&gt;* At third light, turn left onto Washington Street&lt;br /&gt;* Take a left on to Greene Street&lt;br /&gt;* Take a left into the second parking lot on your left. There will be a concierge to direct you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park your car in the designated lot for Gallery Night at Regency Place, the second parking lot on the left. Art Busses pick up and depart from in front of the lobby, under the red awning that reads One Regency Place. The Gallery Night information table will be set up inside the lobby and Gallery Night guides will be there to assist you with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Inside the Regency Plaza by the info Booth -  i'll be wearing a black leather jacket &amp; i'm short.  my hair is still the same as in my photo</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258845148000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258032476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gallery Night - Last one of 2009</name><id>11858030</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258671600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/11858030/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>