<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Greenleaf Woods Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.053665</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-6664</phone><name>Seacoast Sports Club - Greenleaf</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1077608</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.770721</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/5/8/4/event_23154660.jpeg" width="251" height="260" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wallyball is volleyball played indoors on a racquetball court.  It's a fun and fast-paced game where the left and right side &lt;strong&gt;walls&lt;/strong&gt; are part of the field of play.  Only the ceiling and back walls are out of bounds.  Wallyball is competitive but &lt;strong&gt;FUN!&lt;/strong&gt; (Poor sportsmanship will be severely punished by Sheila.)  It's also a great workout that will improve cardio-vascular fitness and muscle tone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can play volleyball, you can play wallyball.  It's indoors so weather is never a problem, and you don't have to chase the ball down the beach every time someone hits it too hard!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Games are &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;every Thursday evening&lt;/span&gt; at Seacoast Sports Club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive 6:15 pm. Play generally will last until 9pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wallyball is free for Seacoast Sports Club members,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;$7 for non-members&lt;/span&gt;, payable at the desk.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The $7 fee entitles you to full use of the locker rooms, saunas, steam rooms, etc. for the evening, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP EARLY in the week!!&lt;/strong&gt; Courts have to be reserved and games will be cancelled if a minimum # of players has not signed up.  (No-shows will also be severely punished by Sheila!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALWAYS CHECK THE MEETUP SITE&lt;/strong&gt; for cancelled games before showing up.  Lots of people cancel at the last minute so a game could be cancelled if there won't be enough players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer, host, and their heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup, including risks inherent in travel to and from the activity. Wallyball and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheila </member_name><member_id>8905072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369963122000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344784923000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wallyball 5/30/13</name><id>qqdmgdyrhbnc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369952100000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/107675342/</event_url></item>