<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>315 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.362343</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 868-6739</phone><name>Middlesex Lounge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>254023</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098560</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;nerdnite: be there and be square&amp;quot;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet up in the Middlesex Lounge by &lt;b&gt;7:00 pm&lt;/b&gt; and see if we can grab tables next to each other for dinner before the lectures start. I've never been to a Nerdnite, or the Middlesex Lounge, so I'm not sure how they are. Anyone want to explore it with me? The talks start at 8:00 pm and costs five dollars.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it's merely bitterly cold, T.J. Maher will be outside the place casually holding a red MEETUP sign starting at 6:45 pm and trying not to look like a chauffeur or a docent. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brwn hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and another red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. He'll hand out little red MEETUP stickers to people so we can identify the &amp;quot;Nerd Fun&amp;quot; nerds with all the other nerds that might be there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Nerdnite site&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://nerdnite.com/category/boston/" target="_blank"&gt;http://nerdnite.com/c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hello nerds and friends of nerds, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The next &lt;b&gt;Nerdnite&lt;/b&gt; hits Monday January 25, 8pm at the Middlesex Lounge (address below).  We’ll have two speakers, and of course  nerd-appropriate tunes by DJ Claude Money, which can be heard before, between, and after the talks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Talk 1 by Aaron Foster&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'Nerds &amp;amp; Whey: Or, how the controlled spoilage of milk begets the world’s tastiest cheeses.' &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Aaron Foster knows a lot about cheese, and has the paunch to prove it. At St. John’s College in Annapolis, MD, Aaron studied philosophy and literature, all the while working as a cheesemonger at the local shop. Shortly after graduating in 2003, he moved to Piedmont in Italy to study gastronomy at Slow Food’s Università di Scienze Gastronomiche. Back in the US, he has been a cheese buyer at NYC’s Artisanal Premium Cheese, he has helped develop a cheese cave and beer room for Whole Foods’ lower east side store, and now has turned his attention to chocolate at Somerville’s Taza Chocolate. During his off hours, he can be found making lacto-fermented pickles, brewing beer, curing meat, and pondering cheese. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;u&gt;Talk 2 by Iolanthe Chronis&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'Everything You Can Do I Can Have Measured: Studying Face to Face Social Networks Using Cellphones' &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Lanthe just finished her Masters at the MIT Media Lab, where she worked to understand influence patterns in face-to-face social networks.  Before that, she was an MIT undergraduate in EECS and Physics, enjoying activities ranging from museum curation to square dancing.  Now, she’s about to voyage to Silicon Valley to lead Startup House, an intern entertainment and job-hunting startup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Be there and be square&lt;/b&gt;! &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Monday January 25 &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Middlesex Lounge &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;315 Mass Ave, Cambridge &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;8pm, $5&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Nerd Nite&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://nerdnite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://nerdnite.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Nerd Nite is an informal gathering at which nerds get together for nerdery of all sorts (well, mostly presentations and drinking). Nerds and non-nerds alike gather to meet, drink and learn something new. Born in Boston and fostered in New York, Nerd Nite recently spread to Austin, TX and Munich, Germany, and is now in Washington DC too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Watch the Nerd Nite Documentary on Japan’s NHK!:  This documentary about Nerd Nite aired nationally across Japan on Sunday May 17, 2009. Watch it now here! &lt;a href="http://dailynewsonline.magnify.net/video/New-York-Wave-Nerd-Nite" target="_blank"&gt;http://dailynewsonlin...&lt;/a&gt; (23 minutes).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Nerd Nite. It’s like the Discovery Channel… with beer!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I have only seen events all the way in the Midway Cafe. This is the first event I have seen in Cambridge, MA with this group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Middlesex Lounge&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.middlesexlounge.us/about.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.middlesexl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Winner of the 2005 Honor Award for Design Excellence, Middlesex Lounge, a minimalist and chic urban lounge, is the height of all that is unpretentiously vogue. Middlesex's dual identity caters to the lunch and after-dinner crowd with an award-winning burger and a robust selection of beers and hand-crafted cocktails; and baits the after-nine PM crowds with its acclaimed lineup of local, national and international DJs. Widely hailed by the city as a trendsetter in the nightlife scene, Middlesex is just plain cool without being trendy.&lt;br /&gt;Middlesex does not accept reservations&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... from reviews on Yelp mention how the place is smallish. Another reviewer on Yelp mentions the low benches and the tables on wheels made it like you were eating stooped over your coffee table. Normally, it sounds like a meat market / dance club. But tonight it'll be full of Nerds. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions&lt;/u&gt;:  &lt;a href="http://www.middlesexlounge.us/location.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.middlesexl...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It looks like this place is smack dab in the middle of the Central Square and Kendal / MIT T stations. You can get off the subway at Central Square, and walk six blocks down Mass Ave. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.middlesexlounge.us/menu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.middlesexl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264695655000</updated><rating><average>3.79999995232</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264177268000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nerdnite topics: Milk, cheese, chocolate, and spying @ Middlesex Lounge</name><id>12392681</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264464000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12392681/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>