<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Pawtucket Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.643787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Heritage Farm</name><city>Lowell</city><id>2172761</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340263</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday nights Heritage Farm Ice Cream puts on FREE concerts across the street at The Sampas pavilion. They also sponsor a classic car show (begins at 6pm) -cars from days gone by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a chair or blanket ( and bug repellent) for the concert while the sun sets over the Merrimack River. Heritage It's a great night out! FREE Outdoor Concert On The River: The band “MERRIMACK”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*We will meetup at Heritage Farm - at the porch. I will have a meetup.com pin (or sign). Then, we can walk across to the Sampas Pavilion for the concert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can purchase something from the Heritage Farm menu, ice cream, hot dogs, burgers, or beverage.... or you can bring your own snack. www.heritageicecream.com This is a shared event with other meetup groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHERE THIS IS AN ALL-OUTDOOR EVENT, RAIN CANCELS. I will update as close to 6pm in the event the weather is questionable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“MERRIMACK”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The band “Merrimack” was formed in the Fall of 2010 when Ash, Sean, Brian and Tim, who had been playing together in a cover band, decided to take their original music to the next level. The band quickly decided on a name that represents their hometowns as well as the community that gave them their start. As graduates of UMass Lowell, the band became a staple on the local music scene with their blend of classic pop music mixed with bluesy vocal style and impeccable harmonies. In February 2012, the band released their first single, "You're No Good For Me," and continues to write, record and play live.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345723150000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345023538000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Outdoor Concert On The River: "MERRIMACK"</name><id>77826282</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345502700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/77826282/</event_url></item>