<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Steamed buns! Sticky rice! Egg custards and jasmine tea and stuff you can't pronounce unless you speak Mandarin or Cantonese! CHICKEN FEET!!! Join us for our now-monthly, all-social dimsum events, which will take place at either China Pearl or Hei La Moon in Boston's Chinatown. We can talk geek, or just eat ourselves silly. Alas, this is probably not for the vegetarian'd, or the strictly kosher or halal, or the diet-conscious. The bill will be split evenly among all who attend, so the more the merrier/cheaper! (Average cost seems to be about $15 per person.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The number of people who can do dimsum on Saturday outweighs the number who can do it on Sunday, so it looks like we'll have to stick to Saturday for now.  However, we will alternate locations -- China Pearl one month, Hei La Moon the next.  Since March's dimsum was at HLM, this one will be at CP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Easiest way to get there is Red Line to Boston's South Station, then walk from there.  Driving is not recommended!  (Parking is difficult to find and expensive downtown.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get there from South Station, go up to the food court area within the station.  Exit through the gates which lead to the trains, but immediately turn right and leave the station instead.  And then:&lt;br /&gt;Walk a short distance E on Kneeland St.&lt;br /&gt;Turn left on Tyler St.&lt;br /&gt;Walk a short distance N on Tyler St.&lt;br /&gt;Total walking is 0.17 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://chinapearlrestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://chinapearlrestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://chinapearlrest...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam Phillips</member_name><member_id>1902847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540146000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SF Writers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-SFandF-Writers</urlname><id>137807</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Science Fiction &amp; Fantasy Writers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1142728720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dimsum Saturday (no joke)!</name><id>4879709</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1143907200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-SFandF-Writers/events/4879709/</event_url></item>