<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The holiday market was inspired by the traditional French Christmas markets, where you can &amp;quot;stroll through our holiday gifts fair and find a gift for everyone on your list, while enjoying a warm glass of cider or mulled wine.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Discover or rediscover the wonders of the French touch. Luxury items, candles, culinary treats, interior decorations, linens, stationary, organic skincare products, children’s and adults’ fashion and more, will be available from the shops and restaurants dedicated to bringing the essence of France to Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Find the perfect gift from: Chic Nautic, Haiti Projects Inc., French Merchants, Fresh Cut Glass, GALVIN-ized Headwear, Ginger Designs, Helen’s Handbags, La Ligue Francophone, Liza Hennessy Fine Leather Goods, Lowery Art, Péché Mignon, Sherr Designs, Thousand Hills Coffee Company, and more…&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The entrance fee for FAB members is $2 and for non-members is $5. If you have a FAB membership card (which you can sign up for on-line), you can get discounts from some vendors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The library website is: &lt;a href="http://www.frenchlib.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.frenchlib....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING is available at the The Boston Common Garage, located on Charles St., below the Boston Common for $6. Park first then buy your discounted parking ticket at our reception desk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also get to the Library on the Green Line or Orange Line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that most vendors will not accept Credit Card payments. An ATM is available a few blocks away, at the corner of Boylston and Stuart St. (Bank of America) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is presented in English and French.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230422806000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227485038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Le Marché de Noël: Holiday Market</name><id>9219106</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228586400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/9219106/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/3/global_1218899.jpeg</photo_url></item>