<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a planning meeting to organize a graphic design presentation meetup (date of presentation to be determined at the planning meeting). Requesting folks who have knowledge in these areas to attend and offer their expertise, thoughts and ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The objective is to 1. gather input from people about what areas of graphic design they have questions about or would like to see covered. 2. to share our joint knowledge on these topics and establish a format where we can teach each other. One possible format would be to have two or three presentations as well as a question and answer period at the end from which future presentation topics could be derived. We could field questions about Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, possibly Flash, Typography, and general visual design principles such as composition, color, weight, line, proportion, contrast, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Obviously this is a big topic, and so the idea is potentially to have ongoing graphic design presentations, and field a few specific topics each time. We would like to hear member feedback about what topics they would like covered, and hopefully gather an idea of who has knowledge in these areas in our group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Hoag</member_name><member_id>7353473</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237224093000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235862795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>graphic design presentation planning meeting</name><id>9847306</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236812400000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/9847306/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/7/global_1616503.jpeg</photo_url></item>