<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I WANT TO MAKE A CHANGE TO THIS EVENT.  I WANT TO LEAD THOSE OF YOU WHO WANT A CHALLENGE COUNTER CLOCKWISE AROUND THE POND TO JOHN MUIR TRAIL UP WALNUT MT. THEN CONTINUE SOUTH TO SUNNY BROOK AND WALK BACK THE WAY WE CAME TO FINISH THE POND LOOP.  THIS DISTANCE WILL BE ABOUT 8 MILES. &lt;br /&gt;THOSE NOT READY FOR THE DISTANCE CAN STILL DO THE DESCRIPTION LISTED BELOW.  &lt;br /&gt;PLEASE UPDATE YOUR RESPONSE WITH &amp;quot;SHORT&amp;quot; OR &amp;quot;LONG&amp;quot; DISTANCE. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't been out hiking in a while, you will want to stick the shorter distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going out to the western part of the state to try a new venue (for me).  Burr Pond State Park is a beautiful area of trails in Torrington.  We are going around the pond on the Wolcott Trail until we hit the John Muir Trail.  From there we are headed out to Walnut Mt. at 1325 ft.  Those who have told me of this peak have never summited.  Those who have have never returned.  I am kidding.  After the summit we will head back to the pond and finish the loop. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The distance should be about 5 miles with a considerable climb up Walnut Mt.  These hikes generally last no more than 4 hours.  Dress in layers with no cotton.  As we head toward spring you will need waterproof hiking boots for the possible wet conditions.  Bring water and snacks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will park at parking area off Burr Mountain Rd., near the north end of the pond.  &lt;br /&gt;Please no dogs or children. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mapquest link to the parking area: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Torrington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=500+Burr+Mountain+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06790-2203&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.872916&amp;amp;longitude=-73.091334&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Burr Pond Park Map&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/burrpondgis.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269711543000</updated><rating><average>4.78999996185</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267489669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Burr Pond State Park/Walnut Mt., Torrington, CT </name><id>12749973</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269093600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/12749973/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>