<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Uxbridge Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01590</zip><lat>42.149452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-865-8752</phone><name>Sutton Library</name><city>Sutton</city><id>885675</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.763303</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I have arranged to have an Astronomical Presentation at the Sutton Library on Wednesday, September 30th starting at 6:45 PM for the Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group.   The full name of the library is the Sutton Free Public Library located at 4 Uxbridge Rd Sutton, MA 01590.  The topic will be Backyard Astronomy : Sucessful Starhopping under Sutton Starry Skies! I will present a 45 minute overview of successful backyard astronomy techniques for beginners using binoculars or a small telescope through a series of PowerPoint slides. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be open to the public but will have plenty of room for all Oxford Astronomy Group Members who would like to attend! I will also bring some great handouts from NASA and the Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. for all who attend. There will be plenty of time for questions and discussions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the meeting, I will set up a telescope behind the library and will invite members to bring their own binoculars or telescopes for a shared outdoor viewing experience if the weather permits. We will also be able to discuss future meetup events for this group throughout the area. I can also talk about Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. upcoming events which members might also be interested in attending.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just enter the library and ask the librarians,. I believe we will be meeting in the same room as last time when we met in a large room in one of the upper floors.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256247618000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252860654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group </name><id>11360557</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254350700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/11360557/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/4/global_7975572.jpeg</photo_url></item>