<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Why are SHORT SALES so hard???&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I mean, isn&amp;rsquo;t there an easier way to do these deals??&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;

 These are comments and questions that many people are asking these days. &amp;nbsp;And the answer is, YES, THERE IS!!! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 With short sales on the rise in MA, there are opportunities for both Realtors and Investors to make great money in this market!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Come hear local short sale expert Russ Bradchulis speak about the ins and outs of doing short sales the easy way and how to not lose your shirt -- or your listing! -- when encountering short sales! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the restaurant industry no longer provided him enough satisfaction and income, Russ decided to found Foresight Home Solutions, LLC and launched into real estate. &amp;nbsp;This was in 2008 when the market started turning, so naturally Russ was flung into the short sale world. &amp;nbsp;Now Russ is very active in short sale real estate, negotiating with banks, brokering deals, and negotiating deals for other investors and realtors. &amp;nbsp;He is also an avid probate marketer and is recognized as a local expert in probate real estate, and all of his probate deals have used none of his own money. &amp;nbsp;Russ is also a licensed real estate broker in MA and is getting his broker&amp;rsquo;s license in FL as well. &amp;nbsp;In his spare time you can find him cutting a rug on the country dance floor, creating some masterpiece in the kitchen, or sipping some craft beer at the local pub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 To learn more about our speaker, Please visit his website at www.foresighthomesolutions.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ruben B. Austria</member_name><member_id>11990827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332466285000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>At this meeting you will learn

?How to get your offer to the top of the bank?s list
?Three simple ways to speed up your short sales
?How to structure offers that banks will take seriously
?Two ways to do more short sale deals with less work</why><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>realestateinvestor</urlname><id>596743</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>InvestorsBeat.com - Massachusetts Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329673438000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Why are SHORT SALES so hard???</name><id>gdplqyqgbhb</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332370800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestateinvestor/events/52931762/</event_url></item>