<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate (est. 6-mile loop, with hills)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt; E Main St, New Salem, is off Route 202 (Daniel Shays Highway), on the Northbound side of the road. E Main St is a "live" neighborhood. Park where you can, and we'll gather on foot at the dead-end near Gate 27.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Four towns were disincorporated, and others lost or gained land, in preparation to flood the Swift River Valley. While buildings were torn down, cellarholes (and a few abandoned items) remain behind. This time, I will remember to bring "Historic Quabbin Hikes" by J. R. Greene so we can put the ruins into perspective!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trails are old roads (dirt or crumbling pavement). Expect hills, especially approaching the reservoir. This loop parallels the shore for more than a mile, so there will be lovely views!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I brake for bald eagles!&lt;/strong&gt; I estimate hike and lunch to take 3+ hours depending on the slowest in the group...but if we are lucky enough to see bald eagles, and they hang around a while (rare), it could take longer! (This happened to me in spring!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information:&lt;/strong&gt; Bring lunch, water, bug repellant, sneakers or similar, and maybe a camera.&amp;nbsp;This is a public water supply...no pets are allowed. Trash is "carry in, carry out"...there are no receptacles. There may or may not be any outhouses on the shore for fishers. On Route 202, across from E Main St., the "New Salem General Store" has an outhouse, food, books, maps, and other conveniences. You may want to stop there before the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am always up for joining anyone for ice cream or pizza after the hike...in fact, the General Store is also a pizza place, and they have picnic tables.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>E Main St, New Salem, off Route 202 (Daniel Shays Highway)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317614791000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316647015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Hike: Quabbin Reservoir Gate 27</name><id>34486272</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317391200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/34486272/</event_url></item>