<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>83 Pembroke Street</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.341846</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>K9 Strolls Shop and Play</name><city>Boston</city><id>11121142</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076111</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for our February Meetup at &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;K9 Strolls Shop and Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! Come and play Sunday, February 17 from 11 AM – 1 PM in our new, fun location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;K9 Strolls Shop and Play is a favorite of many past and present members of The Downtown Maltese Meetup! They specialize in small breeds and offer top quality day care, play groups and dog walking programs. K9 Strolls Shop and Play is also now proudly offering grooming and retail services, selling only products made in the USA and local to New England. K9 Strolls Shop and Play has generously offered a FREE private indoor space for all of our little furbabies to run around and play!! Daniel and Jim are super nice and fan favorites of many little pups in the South End. K9 Strolls Shop and Play has recently moved to 83 Pembroke Street (at Tremont Street), only 0.75 miles away from Peter’s Park Dog Park. Check out K9 Strolls Shop and Play at &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.k9strollsboston.com/"&gt;http://www.k9strollsboston.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We even get 10% off grooming appointments booked on the Meetup Sunday. We also get 10% off all products during that time!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;From K9 Strolls Shop and Play:&lt;/strong&gt; For the safety of all guests, K9 Strolls Shop and Play requires that all dogs have up-to-date vaccinations. A K9 Strolls Shop and Play Waiver Form must be filled out prior to each dog participating in the Meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mandatory Dues:&lt;/strong&gt; None!! Many thanks to K9 Strolls Shop and Play who has generously donated their play space free of charge!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; K9 Strolls Shop and Play is located at 83 Pembroke Street (between Tremont St - Columbus Ave) in the South End, just a shop or two in from Tremont Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; There is metered parking (free on Sundays) on Tremont Street. Pembroke Street has a few non-metered visitor parking (free) at the top of the street at Columbus Ave. Most other side streets also have a few spaces available for visitors, but check the signs for South End resident only parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a couple of parking garages nearby. The LAZ Dartmouth Street Garage is located at 126 Dartmouth Street, between Columbus Ave - Stuart St (0.35 miles away). The Stanhope Garage is small parking lot located at 265 and 277 Northampton Street, between Tremont St - Columbus Ave (0.48 miles away) on the other side of Mass Ave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Transportation:&lt;/strong&gt; Many bus lines (1, 10 and others) are nearby. Or the Orange Line Back Bay Station is 0.32 miles away; walk down Dartmouth Street towards Columbus Ave. Turn right on Columbus Ave, and then right onto Pembroke Street. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Thanks so much! See you there! &lt;br /&gt;

 Janine and Coco &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janine</member_name><member_id>9399538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361124368000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Maltese Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-115</urlname><id>215542</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Downtown Boston Maltese Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359220427000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The February Downtown Maltese Meetup</name><id>101491042</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361116800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-115/events/101491042/</event_url></item>