<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 6</address_2><address_1>163 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02053</zip><lat>42.147101</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 533-0669</phone><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name><city>Medway</city><id>911296</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.427202</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;RADICAL Forgiveness Ceremony&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Wednesday October 10th&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;6:30pm  - 8:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Cost: Your investment in you is $40&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presented by:  Melissa J. White&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Melissa is a writer, speaker, teacher and life coach who empowers people nationwide to live more authentic lives. Co-author of Restoring Your Beautiful Life, she is passionate about living her truth and assisting others in accessing their inner wisdom She inspires individuals and groups to move forward in their lives, provides support for day-to-day issues and decision-making, assists with life transitions, and facilitates the creation of happiness from the inside out. Where there are blocks to living life to its fullest, she uses Radical Forgiveness and other emotional clearing techniques to help clients let go of their pasts and create new futures. To cultivate inner peace and balance, Melissa teaches yoga and meditation. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Melissa earned her undergraduate degree in counseling from Marshall University, her graduate degree in higher education from Ball State University, and her law degree from The American University, Washington College of Law. She is a certified Radical Forgiveness Coach and Workshop Facilitator and a Registered Yoga Teacher. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This largely non-verbal process has proven itself to be extremely powerful and effective in allowing people to forgive themselves and others, and to find peace and happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a brief introduction to Radical Forgiveness, the facilitator will state, one at a time, common events that often present an opportunity for forgiveness of oneself or others. We voluntarily walk the circle once to honor and witness our "story" of what happened. As we see others walk too, we realize we are not alone, and we honor our shared pain. After hearing a special Radical Forgiveness story, we walk the circle again and ask inwardly to come to a new place of forgiveness and peace. And it works! People leave with tears of joy and smiling faces. It is entirely non-threatening and yet is likely to change your life forever!&lt;/p&gt;
For more information, on Radical Forgiveness, go to &lt;a href="http://www.colintipping.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.colintipping.com/&lt;/a&gt;. For more information on Melissa, go to &lt;a href="http://www.mylifeopportunities.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.mylifeopportunities.com&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Solstice Healing</member_name><member_id>9244342</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349919767000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center</urlname><id>1422661</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343498644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RADICAL Forgiveness Ceremony</name><id>75297512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349908200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center/events/75297512/</event_url></item>