<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I loved watching Julia Child on tv as a kid - and half of this movie is based on Child's best selling memoir of her days in French cooking school. The other half is from Julie Powell's memoir of cooking one of Child's recipes a day for a year, sometimes struggling, sometimes succeeding, and every cooking enthusiast can relate to that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join me for a fun weekday matinee of this free screening, and we'll head out for a coffee and chat after the show. Starbucks is one block from AMC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet early so we can all be sure to get seats.  I will arrive @ 1:15pm.  MOVIE STARTS TIME: 2:00pm. Please see link for printing free pass below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Synopsis:&lt;br /&gt;Julia Child (Meryl Streep) and Julie Powell (Amy Adams) are featured in writer-director Nora Ephron's adaptation of two bestselling memoirs: Powell's Julie &amp;amp; Julia and My Life in France, by Julia Child with Alex Prud'homme. Based on two true stories, Julie &amp;amp; Julia intertwines the lives of two women who, though separated by time and space, are both at loose ends...until they discover that with the right combination of passion, fearlessness and butter, anything is possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE PASS LINK:&lt;/b&gt; Thanks Ramon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/225256/Julie%20%26%20Julia%20%20movie%20pass.PDF"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Plieae find Susan wearing not at all dorky ;  ) bright red and white Meetup hat, in the hall just oustide of the screening cinema, both before and after the show.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan B</member_name><member_id>461418</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256892862000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246634463000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Julia and Julia" Free Screening Matinee: 1:30pm 7/7/09 Boston AMC</name><id>10796219</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246986900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/10796219/</event_url></item>