<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Navigating Through Housing Court&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get a view from the Bench.  Come listen and find out the best way to be successful in Housing Court.  Hear about landlord-litigant process from the Judge's point of view.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker Judge David D. Kerman &lt;br /&gt;Judge Kerman is the Presiding Justice of the Northeast Housing Court where he has served since his appointment as an Associate Justice of the Trial Court in 1990.  Prior to his judicial appointment he served as the Executive Director of the Neighborhood Legal Services, Inc., legal aid organization in Lynn. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Judge Kerman has served as a faculty member and assistant team leader of the National Institute for Trial Advocacy since 1984, and he teaches trial practice to lawyers and law students several times a year through NITA programs and as an adjunct member of the faculty of the Hofstra University School of Law in Hempstead, New York. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Judge Kerman’s trial court opinions are available to the public through the Social Law Library’s online and CD subscription services.  He is the author of a bench memorandum and a set of jury instructions for residential landlord tenant cases, which are published by the Massachusetts Continuing Legal Education, Inc. and the Flaschner Judicial Institute.  Judge Kerman is a frequent lecturer and participant at MCLE housing law seminars and conferences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM, Thursday, June 17, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Best Western, 380 Winter Street, Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;Free for members; $25 for nonmembers&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Downstairs in the hotel.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276814779000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>95</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274321704000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association Monthly Meetup</name><id>zhhdnynjbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276810200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/13538745/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/global_6774288.jpeg</photo_url></item>