<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>244 Park Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06119</zip><lat>41.757393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 987 7888</phone><name>Playhouse on Park </name><city>West Hartford </city><id>1272274</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.725212</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE IRA’S SINGLES EVENTS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRESENTS AN&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A FUN FILLED EVENING OF CULTURE AND DINING (How Fun) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday May 29. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE EXCITING DEATAILS ARE BELOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date:  May 29. Saturday Evening. 8:00 P.M.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:   Playhouse on Park (I love this name. “Playhouse”) &lt;br /&gt;244 Park Road&lt;br /&gt;West Hartford, CT 06119&lt;br /&gt;860-523-5900&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.playhouseonpark.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.playhouseo...&lt;/a&gt;  I have been to this theater many times, and I so much enjoy its warm and friendly atmosphere. It is very small and intimate theatre with seating on 3 sides of the stage. The farthest seat away is only 15 or 20 feet from the stage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Performance:  This is Our Youth.  (Write Up is below) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Important Ticket Information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Price is 22.50. Discounted to 20.00. A savings of  10%.  20 Tickets Only. ( This will go quickly for sure) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;R.S.V.P. On or before, May 24. Full Payment is required to hold your seat. (After this date, if tickets are available, cost will be 22.50 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email ASAP, Subject Line, PlayHouse, and I will send you my PayPal Account for Payment to hold your seat.  Email:  mistrchrming@aol.com.   860-604-5792&lt;br /&gt;For more events and the chance to receive a Limo Ride/Bottle of Wine, please see:  www.theirassinglesevents.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dining Ideas:  I think it would be great to meet for dinner/cocktails prior to show. Depending on how many like this idea, I will send out more information of where to meet.  Suggestions welcomed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An unblinking portrait of young urban life in the 1980s, Kenneth Lonergan's lacerating look at affluent young Manhattanites depicts two days in the lives of three very lost souls in the big city at the dawn of the Regan Era. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kenneth Lonergan brilliantly captures the essential period of time when we think we've got the world figured out, only to realize that we know nothing.  Graduating from our teenage years to adulthood and the pressure of identity is an intense struggle. In Dennis, Warren, and Jessica the struggle is intensified by their dependency on parents. But that dependency is both a blessing and a burden, because it provides a safety net, but the net undercuts the very freedom they enjoy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With an ear attuned to the coarse, ironic language of city kids too cosmopolitan for their own good, Lonergan spins a wildly funny, bittersweet and ultimately quite moving story.  This is Our Youth has extremely strong language, adult situations, and drug use.  It is recommended for ages 17 and up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Playhouse on Park is managed under the direction of Playhouse Theatre Group, Inc.  Located in the vibrant Park Road section of West Hartford, Connecticut, the theatre is surrounded by diverse shopping, markets and restaurants and a vast residential neighborhood all within walking distance. The Playhouse on Park theatre space has 163 seats surrounding a 3/4 thrust stage offering audiences of all ages an intimate theatre experience. A year-round performance schedule is produced and/or presented by Playhouse Theatre Group, Inc. and includes: professional and community theatre; theatre for young audiences; new works and play readings; comedy and improvisation; cabarets and concerts; dance; educational opportunities led by resident and visiting artists; corporate events, special events and more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lobby Area. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275182397000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273844837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira. Culture and Dining. Playhouse on Park.  A evening of a Play and Dining </name><id>13482509</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275177600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/13482509/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_2930168.jpeg</photo_url></item>