<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ocrtober 17, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HI! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace and blessings on you and your loved ones!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I trust this note of mine finds you all well with peace and joy in your hearts. Yesterday we saw the first snow flakes... today the sun is shinining... This is New England and we rejoice in the beauty of nature. Sorry if it took me this long to get this reminder out... but here at Fatima Shrine, life has been rather hectic for the past month or so... I still continue to count on your patience... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see all of you at our NEXT INTERFAITH BOOK CLUB MEETING... Mark your calendar:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;TIME: October 25, 2009 at 4:00PM&lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY - Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We continue our reading and reflection on MATTHEW FOX's book: &amp;quot;ONE RIVER, MANY WELLS&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For our October 25th gathering we pick up from where we left... namely, we will share on CHAPTER THREE: &amp;quot;JOY, SUFFERING, BEAUTY, SACRED SEXUALITY, SYING, RESURRECTION, REINCARNATION (pages 254-372).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I have mentioned in my previous e-mail, I hope that your summer and early fall brought you in touch with other authors and other books. So if you came across any other book you find inspirational for our group, don't forget to bring it along... It can become our next reading. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I continue to be blessed and enriched by your presence and your sharing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blessings on you and your loved ones...SEE YOU on October 25th at 4:00pm at Peace Abbey in Sherborn. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PEACE&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144&lt;br /&gt;pino.ma@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256674450000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255789927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEXT INTERFAITH BOOK CLUB MEETING</name><id>11647502</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256500800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/11647502/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/a/global_4353546.jpeg</photo_url></item>