<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join me for my first hosting of a meetup as we enjoy a blast from the past&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ridley Scott's legendary adaptation of Phillip K. Dick's Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? gave us a startling vision of a noir-ishly dystopic future, in which the line between human and non-human has worn perilously thin. Scott's masterpiece not only anticipated our future but designed it: Much of our world today appears, well, just so Blade Runner. To commemorate its 25th anniversary, Scott has gone back, corrected a few details and fashioned a version that he feels is closest to what he had originally intended. One of the greatest American films of the Eighties has just gotten even better. - from the New York Film Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Final Cut is noteworthy for its changes (significant material is actually cut) that moves the film into greatness as a glossy visual treat and meaningful social commentary film on the Reagan-era materialist generation of the 1980s.  A young Harrison Ford, music by Vangelis, the great special effects are by Douglas Trumbull, Richard Yuricich and David Dryer. Laurence G. Paull's production designs are also noteworthy. It's Ridley Scott's crowning achievement, something he never came close to duplicating. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read the complete review at &lt;a href="http://www.sover.net/~ozus/bladerunner.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sover.net/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, John will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there.  This is a great opportunity for anyone who has never seen this classic film, or for those who saw it years ago when our hair was longer and a little less grey . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195500981000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194437758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blade Runner:  The Final Cut</name><id>6694176</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195327800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6694176/</event_url></item>