<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>189 Reservoir Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.852501</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Vernon Commuter Lot</name><city>Vernon </city><id>4997832</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.428955</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We have two groups of caravans heading to NH. One departs on Friday afternoon Jan. 6th at 11:30am SHARP!!! from the commuter lot off of Exit 67 on I-84 in Vernon. The plan is to arrive early to decorate vehicles, take a few pictures and roll. The other is leaving Saturday morning Jan. 7th at around 8 am from Dave A's place in Manchester. As per Dave: "The first stop will be at the commuter parking lot at exit 67 on I-84 in Vernon. The second stop will be at the 1st rest area after the Sturbridge toll heading East to hookup with meet-ups from Western Mass." (Exact time pending, likely somewhere between 9 and 10 am). Members can join the caravan at Exit 67 or message Dave A for his address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For early arrivals, there is a Rally in Nashua at 2:00PM, then Friday night at 7:00PM there is a Town Hall in Durham, see below for details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Saturday destination once in New Hampshire is Jillian's Billiards!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jillian&amp;rsquo;s Billiards Club of Manchester 50 Phillippe Cote Street Manchester, New Hampshire 03101 (603) 626-7636&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting at 8 am Saturday Jillian's is the HQ for the Ron Paul NH Revolution, this is a weekend to take the message to the masses and it all starts there. By day we'll walk, knock and wave for Paul and then return to Jillian's that night to watch the debate and unwind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details about Jillian's / HQ via Janet:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday at 8am --Jillian's will be opening for $10 all you can eat breakfast for our "soldiers". Chris Lawless and Leah Wolesko of the Free State Project will then be handing out the marching orders to everyone who will disperse for the day in as many directions as possible --putting door hangers on doors, phone banking, putting up signs ---whatever it takes --most will have cars who traveled by car and those who can fit more in their cars will share etc. Everyone will meet back at Jillians at 7pm for the debate party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;The plan was to try and attend the debate in Manchester on Saturday but to my knowledge no meetup members were selected to receive tickets. While we still may have a presence at the debate of some sort, many will be attending the debate watching party (there is a meetup scheduled here: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ct4paul/events/46108142/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ct4paul/events/461081...&lt;/a&gt;) at &lt;span&gt;Jillian's Billiard Club. It w&lt;/span&gt;ill feature food, performances by the band Golden State and Jordan Page - and feature speakers Tom Woods and Adam Kokesh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday at 9:00AM there is also another televised debate in Concord, full details are below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there are any folks heading up on short notice or you simply need to contact the Northern CT Ron Paul Meetup &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;for up to the minute event information - please call&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;(860)730-3RON&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; This number will be live in New Hampshire all weekend please do not hesitate to call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schedule of events:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday, Jan 6th 2:00PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ron Paul Rally in Nashua&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2:00PM - 3:00PM Hangar Rally, Jet Aviation &lt;br /&gt;

 83 Perimeter Road Nashua, NH 03063&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday, Jan 6th 7:00PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Town Hall Meeting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00PM - 8:00PM &lt;br /&gt;

 UNH Memorial Union Building/Granite State Room &lt;br /&gt;

 83 Main Street Durham, NH 03824&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, Jan 7th 8:00AM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boots on the Ground in NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jillian&amp;rsquo;s Billiards Club of Manchester&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;50 Phillippe Cote Street Manchester, New Hampshire 0310&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(603) 626-7636&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is ground central - folks will be arriving here throughout the morning and afternoon then disperse to spread the word about Ron Paul. Around 7:00PM people will start returning and the fun will start (food, music, speakers) plus the debate televised at 9 for those not attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, Jan 7th 9:00PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABC/WMUR New Hampshire Debate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ABC/WMUR New Hampshire Debate will be held at the Dana Center at Saint Anselm College in Manchester, 100 Saint Anselms Drive, Manchester, New Hampshire on Saturday, January 7th at 9:00 p.m. Eastern&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday, Jan 8th 9:00AM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NBC News Facebook and Union Leader Debate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congressman Ron Paul will attend the NBC News Facebook and Union Leader Debate being held at Chubb Theatre at the Capitol Center for the Arts, 44 South Main Street, Concord, NH on Sunday, January 8th at 9:00 a.m. Eastern. This debate will air on the NBC network as a special edition of &amp;ldquo;Meet the Press&amp;rdquo; and will stream live on Facebook. This debate will also air on MSNBC and NECN.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325870901000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323066734000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ron Paul New Hampshire Debate Caravan</name><id>43412032</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325865600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/43412032/</event_url></item>