<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01247</zip><lat>53.959106</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Your home or work</name><city>Your city</city><id>1192498</id><country>us</country><lon>-1.079194</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for series of 7</description><amount>125.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>When you can open yourself to the flow of the divine, grace can move effortlessly through your life. Moments of struggle and isolation melt into ease and oneness. By surrendering your ego and trusting the Universe/the Divine/God/Spirit, magic unfolds. You come face to face with your intrinsic nature. An abiding sense of safety, support, belonging, peace, calm, wholeness, direction and purpose forms the backdrop to your daily life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prerecorded and available for download: &lt;br /&gt;Safety and Abundance, Integrated Sexuality, Will and Action, Opening the Heart, Speaking Your Truth, The Power of Intuition&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live Call:&lt;br /&gt;June 25 Divine Union&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Download this 7 week teleclass series to release self-sabotaging patterns and access your inherent power.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Times: Join the live call - or download it any time that is convenient to you!&lt;br /&gt;Location: Comfort and privacy of your own home&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounted Tuition: $125*&lt;br /&gt;*Includes seven classes; free downloads of philosophical and psychological background, guided meditation and Q&amp;amp;A of each class; and online support via message board and email.&lt;br /&gt;*You do not have to be present on the calls to participate fully in the course. *You may join at any point in the series. Download and listen to prior classes at your convenience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or register for individual classes at $20/class. (Email me for this option.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each Chakra (Vital Energy Center) stores the collection of our core beliefs, emotions and experiences in correlation to seven fundamental themes in our life: survival, creativity, power, love, self-expression, wisdom, and divine connection. Each Chakra correlates to physiological nerve ganglia, organs and glands in the body, as well as psychological aspects relating to human development and spiritual evolution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will focus on one chakra a week in order to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Gain understanding of its physiological and psychological importance.&lt;br /&gt;    * Clear negative accumulations and blockages - on both the physical and psychological levels.&lt;br /&gt;    * Activate the positive attributes and potentialities of each vital energy center - to foster vibrant health and well being.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through the guided meditations and exercises you will learn to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Feel Safe in the World&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Release Pain, Shame, Guilt, Anger and Fear&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Expand your Ability to Experience Pleasure&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Access your Core Power&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Take Effective Action in the World&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Open your Heart to Love&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Express your Truth&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Trust your Inner Guidance and Wisdom&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Tap into Abundance Consciousness&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Experience Oneness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Downloading each class will be particularly useful to have the guided meditations for your home practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional support between calls, you are encouraged to make use of the community board to ask questions that arise, and share your experience with others on the path. This will help build a sense of community as well as offer inspiration and motivation to keep going.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to email me directly (organizer) or call me at 415-244-1652 if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Blessings of Integrated Wholeness and Vibrant Well-Being,&lt;br /&gt;Brynn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Bodyworker, Tantra Educator and Intimacy Coach with over twenty years experience in the fields of Somatics and Consciousness. Brynn bridges the realms of ancient Eastern Philosophy and Energy Practices, and cutting edge Western Somatic Psychology with her unique methodologies in Conscious Relating and Sacred Sexuality.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The conference call number will be emailed to confirmed registrants</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277483884000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274887960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantric Empowerment Teleclass Series: Divine Union</name><id>13601634</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277474400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/13601634/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/6/3/global_10606195.jpeg</photo_url></item>