<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LIVING FOODS POTLUCK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive promptly at 1:00PM&amp;nbsp; for Food Demo - learn to make eggless egg  salad sandwiches&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Randy Jacobs,  owner of Lifeforce Growers, will lead us in a centering and sharing  introductory activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Movie  Possibility&lt;strong&gt; - &lt;/strong&gt;If attendees are interested, this will be  followed by a health related educational movie of your choice from our  lending library.&amp;nbsp; These include: "Delicate Balance", "Living Matrix",  "Simply Raw" or others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a raw food dish large enough to serve 6-8 people. Some ideas include a salad, appetizer, soup or dessert... just keep it raw vegan. :) There are tons of recipes on the internet. We'll be having a great time of sharing ideas, trying new foods, and spreading the word about healthy living! Decide to feel great, get energy, share your health tips and experiences, and a great raw and living foods meal with friends! See you then!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;___________________________________________&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/pages/Potlucks/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/pages/Potlucks/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/pages/Potlucks/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would like to invite you to attend our potlucks to share food and friendship and to have some fun. We have a great time sharing ideas, trying new foods and spreading the word about healthful living! Decide to feel great, get energy, share your health tips and experiences and a great raw and living foods meal with friends! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Potluck: All attending are requested to bring a 100% raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal based (vegan with no honey) ready-to-serve dish for 6 - 8 people. You do not have to be a gourmet chef to attend; just bring a dish that you like. Please bring a typed or neatly printed recipe to display next to your dish ideally with copies for people to take with them if they so choose. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Ideas for Raw Vegan Dish (without honey): &lt;br /&gt;1. organic green salad, &lt;br /&gt;2. raw recipe from online, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com/phpbb2/"&gt;http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com/phpbb2/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.living-foods.com/recipes"&gt;http://www.living-foods.com/recipes&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.goneraw.com/recipes"&gt;http://www.goneraw.com/recipes&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawsacramento.net/recipes.htm"&gt;http://www.rawsacramento.net/recipes.htm&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawfoodlife.com/Raw_Resources/Raw_Food_Recipes/raw_food_recipes.html"&gt;http://www.rawfoodlife.com/Raw_Resources/Raw_Food_Recipes/raw_food_recipes.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shazzie.com/raw/recipes"&gt;http://www.shazzie.com/raw/recipes&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawganique.com/recipes.htm"&gt;http://www.rawganique.com/recipes.htm&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;3. raw recipe from a raw food book, or &lt;br /&gt;4. organic fruit salad.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Best Regards, &lt;br /&gt;Daryl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Preparing 100% Raw Vegan Foods &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Introduction: &lt;br /&gt;To assist our Raw Food Meetup Group members in creating amazing raw vegan dishes that are in fact, 100% raw vegan, we have come up with this easy to use document.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Purposes of this document:  &lt;br /&gt;1. To help clarify what food is and what food isn't raw vegan;  &lt;br /&gt;2. Our members may of course eat whatever they like when not attending our events but when bringing a dish to our events, it is imperative that the dish be 100% raw vegan so all members attending will be able to eat the dish as some of our members are 100% raw vegan; and &lt;br /&gt;3. To help our members get the most nutritional and enzyme benefits from food.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Definitions: &lt;br /&gt;Raw means that the food was not cooked, baked, roasted, pasteurized or heated over 118 degrees. &lt;br /&gt;Vegan means that there are no animal products or honey included. These are animal products:&amp;nbsp; animal meat, fowl, fish, fish eggs, chicken or other eggs and cow or goat dairy products. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fresh is Best:  &lt;br /&gt;When adopting a raw food diet and creating delicious raw food recipes, the main goal is to include as much fresh food into your daily diet. Raw living fresh fruits, vegetables, seeds and nuts can be combined to make delicious and unique flavors. Adding anything that is NOT fresh will generally reduce the nutritional benefit of the food. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Many things that are labeled "raw" or "fresh" have actually been flash-cooked (or flash- pasteurized). This kills "bad" bacteria, but also harms good bacteria, enzymes and vitamins. For example, "raw" almonds from California are required to be pasteurized, while "raw" almonds from Spain or Utah are not. We recommend looking for the word "unpasteurized" on miso, juices, tahini, nuts and nut milks. Most unpasteurized liquids come in glass bottles not cartons or plastic.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Action Guide: &lt;br /&gt;1. If you are using something that has multiple ingredients, please read the label and ingredients list carefully and compare any questionable ingredients to this document.  &lt;br /&gt;2. If you are uncertain if an ingredient is 100% raw vegan, please exclude it from your dish.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Environmental Impact: &lt;br /&gt;According to John Mackey, the founder of Whole Foods Market, a full third of the energy used in the production and consumption of food is at the final stage of cooking. Raw foodists do not cook food so that energy is saved. Please consider reducing the use of dehydrators, juicers, blenders and food processors to keep the energy use down when preparing delicious raw vegan meals. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the Creative Process: &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the creative process and challenge yourself to come up with wonderful meals using the freshest ingredients without using too many ingredients or dried products. Creating food &amp;ldquo;to live for&amp;rdquo; starts with &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo; foods.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Below are suggestions and ideas to assist you in creating amazing fresh dishes.  &lt;br /&gt;We appreciate you and want to support you in your raw living foods experience. &lt;br /&gt;Raw Vegan Food Information &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Always Raw Vegan Foods (use these foods primarily): &lt;br /&gt;Live fruits; &lt;br /&gt;Live vegetables; and &lt;br /&gt;Live nuts and seeds labeled as "raw." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Vegan Foods that are processed: &lt;br /&gt;Kombucha; and &lt;br /&gt;Miso. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Not Raw Vegan Foods: &lt;br /&gt;Bee pollen; &lt;br /&gt;Capers; &lt;br /&gt;Dairy products (lactose, casein, yogurt, cheese, milk products;  &lt;br /&gt;Flour (sprouted live grains are raw vegan); &lt;br /&gt;Honey (agave nectar can be substituted only if it says on the label that it is "raw"); and &lt;br /&gt;Maple syrup is always boiled down. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Not Really Raw Vegan Foods (used by some raw foodists but not others--under dispute): &lt;br /&gt;Braggs Liquid Amino Acids;  &lt;br /&gt;Nama Shoyu (yes it is fermented and live but it started from cooked soy and wheat); &lt;br /&gt;Nutritional Yeast is produced by culturing the yeast with a mixture of sugarcane and beet molasses. This again starts from a cooked product (sugarcane and molasses) and then in many cases MSG is used to preserve it. Since the yeast is a live enzyme, many raw foodists use nutritional yeast. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Not Necessarily Raw Vegan Foods: &lt;br /&gt;Agave nectar is raw only if it says on the label that it is "raw"; &lt;br /&gt;Dried fruits or dried veggies are raw only if heated to 118 degrees maximum when dried: &lt;br /&gt;Nori sheets are only raw when they are labeled as "raw"; &lt;br /&gt;Nuts and Seeds are raw only if they are labeled as "raw." They are best when soaked &amp;amp; sprouted; &lt;br /&gt;Vegetable Oil is raw only if the label states that it is "cold pressed";  &lt;br /&gt;Olives are raw only if they are specifically labeled as "raw" olives;  &lt;br /&gt;Sea salt other than Celtic and Real Salt are processed; and  &lt;br /&gt;Vinegar is raw only if it is labeled as "raw." Some makers of apple cider vinegar are secretive about how they make it. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It is best to Buy Organic because: &lt;br /&gt;1. Organic foods have more nutrients by and large; &lt;br /&gt;2. Organic foods have fewer pesticides and chemicals; and &lt;br /&gt;3. Organic foods are sustainable and come from chemical-free land. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Vegan Food by Flavors &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Vegan Sweeteners: &lt;br /&gt;1. Agave Nectar only when it says "Raw" on the label; &lt;br /&gt;2. Bananas, ripe and preferably spotted; &lt;br /&gt;3. Dates pitted, most dates that have been pitted usually have been steamed. Trader Joe&amp;rsquo;s and Whole Foods carry dates with pits for raw food dishes; &lt;br /&gt;4. Palm Sugar look for it at Whole Foods; &lt;br /&gt;5. Raisins, look for organic varieties as they usually have no additives; and &lt;br /&gt;6. Stevia powder or better yet Stevia leaf may be used as long as it is just the Stevia without additives.  &lt;br /&gt;7. Any sweet fruit. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Vegan Sour Flavors: &lt;br /&gt;1. Lemon; &lt;br /&gt;2. Lime; &lt;br /&gt;3. Raw Apple Cider Vinegar only when it says "Raw" on the label although preferably use Lime or Lemon juice.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Salty Flavors: &lt;br /&gt;1. Celery; &lt;br /&gt;2. Celtic or Real Sea Salt; &lt;br /&gt;3. Dill; &lt;br /&gt;4. Kelp or Dulse;  &lt;br /&gt;5. Nama Shoyu (could use sea salt and dates or raw agave to replace the Nama Shoyu flavor); &lt;br /&gt;6. Nori sheets only when it says "Raw" on the label; and &lt;br /&gt;7. Miso. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Spicy Flavors: &lt;br /&gt;1. Cayenne Pepper (confirm that it's raw); &lt;br /&gt;2. Live Jalapeno pepper; &lt;br /&gt;3. Dried chili pepper (confirm that it's raw); &lt;br /&gt;4. Freshly ground pepper &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Raw Bitter Flavor: &lt;br /&gt;Fresh or dried herbs such as dill, parsley, basil, cilantro, etc; and &lt;br /&gt;Seasoning blends Spice Hunter or Spicely or Whole Foods brands are good. &lt;br /&gt;Use herbs that you know have been dried properly, dry them yourself if possible or buy from companies such as &amp;ldquo;Spice Hunter,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Spicely,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Whole Foods.&amp;rdquo; Herbs do not take much heat to dry them; 90 to 95 degrees works well.&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Created by Darlene Navarre contact@fruitygreenfamily.com and Daryl Elliott elliott7@comcast.net with an assist by Jason Firth. &lt;br /&gt;Version 6, January 6, 201&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Bragg</member_name><member_id>5026531</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296481600000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294416276000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck (Waltham)</name><id>15958142</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296410400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/15958142/</event_url></item>