<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Cuttersfield Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.830650</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BSA Camp Squanto</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>4277122</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.650177</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm very excited to bring you this hike. &amp;nbsp;Camp Squanto, one of the two Boy Scout camps abutting Myles Standish, has a beautiful nature trail cut through its land, which is privately owned by the Scouts and is not part of Myles Standish State Forest. They have agreed to allow us access to this trail for our hike. (They will allow access in general when it does not interfere with their scouting programs. Surprisingly, many more scouts pass through the camp in the off-season months than in the summer. The Camp can be quite busy in the middle of the winter.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their trail passes cranberry bogs, pine barrens, frost pockets, ponds and offers a number of very scenic viewpoints. As one might expect, the trail is in pristine condition. &amp;nbsp;The trail totals 5 miles in length. It may be split into two parts-- a southern section of about 3 miles and a northern section of about 2 miles. &amp;nbsp;Between the two sections, the trail passes through the Scout camp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I walked it the other day and I think it was the nicest trail I've been on all year. &amp;nbsp;I'm not sure why I felt that way-- Maybe it was the long stretches of trail with many deer tracks and no human or dog tracks that made it feel special. Hunters will not be an issue because no hunting is allowed on the camp property and because no hunting is allowed in Massachusetts on Sundays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet in the Camp parking lot and sign in with the Camp manager. &amp;nbsp;As is usual, bring enough water and snacks for a two hour hike. &amp;nbsp;Heavy rain cancels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The road into Camp Squanto, Cutter Field or Cuttersfield, is in the southeast part of the park, past the entrances to Charge Pond and Fearing Pond.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Bescherer</member_name><member_id>650729</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323178777000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320352632000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camp Squanto Nature Trail</name><id>39855942</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323010800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/39855942/</event_url></item>