<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Last month my groups visited WAS. But, we didn't have enough time to see everything! Those who did go were awestruck!!!!! WAS is HUGE! &lt;br /&gt;Yes, it's not in Worcester Counrty,... And, it's tough to find if you're not from the area... But, once you're there, trust me,  it's  definitely worth what you went through to find it!!!!&lt;br /&gt;**HINT: Don't go by the photo of the bldg like I did  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/confused.gif' border='0' alt='confused' /&gt; it may be a photo of WAS, but not from the side of the buildings we drove up to. Well.....I do need to stop here.... I don't want to spoil it! I want you see this yourself! Spring is here! Hopefully the weather will not be an issue! &lt;br /&gt;So, come out and JOIN US! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;website: www.westernavenuestudios.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: FREE&lt;br /&gt;*Today's added event at WAS: &lt;br /&gt;10th Annual International Edible Book Festival and 1st Annual Friends Of WAS Book Sale &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Saturdays : Open studios the 1st Saturday of every month 12 - 5pm. WAS opens it's doors to the public. Come in and browse the latest works by the artist and crafters. &lt;br /&gt;More than 160 Working Artists!!! &lt;br /&gt;where you will find 2 buildings and four floors of artists working in all disciplines, media and styles. The studios are located in a brick mill building at 122 Western Avenue in Lowell, Massachusetts, near the heart of downtown. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;b&gt;***NOTE: &lt;/b&gt;This event is shared with 4 other meetup groups, so there will hopefully be a large group attending! At  this type of venue members usually split up into smaller groups. If anyone is uncomfortable with this? it may not be the right event  to attend.  there is nothing planned for later athough members may opt to go for coffee at one of the many coffee houses, or do an early dinner.  PARKING is FREE at WAS. .&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meetup at the front entrance. I will have a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239667397000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234749043000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>International Edible Book Festival - Plus : Lots &amp; Lots Of Art</name><id>9749192</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238864400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/9749192/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/global_7332138.jpeg</photo_url></item>