<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Christopher Dilts Founder of Ask An Angel is here for a special Holiday Angel Weekend  in December!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We at the Larches are excited that our friend the extraordinary Angel Intuitive and Spiritual Counselor Christopher Dilts will be able to join us on his next trip from California! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;SAVE these Dates DEC. 10,11 12&lt;/b&gt; and be here for an exceptional opportunity to have a healing experience with your angels guided and supported by Christopher Dilts, one of the most trusted and experienced Angel Intuitives we know of in the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Friday night DEC 10 th  7pm – 9:00&lt;/b&gt; our first Angel Gathering with Christopher.  Come enjoy an inspiring informal talk about his fascinating experiences with Angels over the past 20 years.  Enjoy a process with Christopher that will open up your intuition and enhance your receptivity to your angels- and set the groundwork for your experiences on Saturday...  Have some delicious social time with like minded people over juices, fruits and treats and meet Christopher! Fun Fun Fun!  &lt;b&gt;Donation requested  just $20.00&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday Dec 11th  1:00pm-5:00pm&lt;/b&gt;  The workshop is-    “Angelic Holiday Harmony and Healing! Guidance, Attunement and Healing with your Christmas Angels.” Your Christmas Angels will help you create your most loving and harmonious holiday season ever. Heal the past, have family peace and harmony, find your own inner joy renewed.    .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;1:00 - 2:30pm Saturday&lt;/b&gt; – First you will learn about what Angels really are, what they do, how to attune for daily guidance, how to know if the guidance is from your angels, learn to receive their direct help and more.. a  guided meditation will help you have your own experience meeting your Angels. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;3:00 - 5:00pm Saturday&lt;/b&gt; - You will experience your Holiday Angels more deeply. This part of the day will be deeply experiential, will enhance your intuition and Angelic awareness. We will look at souls contracts and souls agreements so you can experience the upcoming holidays with new awareness, compassion, higher perspectives, peace and more love.   We will invoke your Guardian Angels, learn their names, receive their messages and blessings, learn why they are specifically with you in this life.  This is an uplifting, light filled, empowering experience you will carry with you in to your future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Donation requested $75.00&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;* Please bring your desired snacks for the short break-  in this way we are able to keep the cost of this down  for you. We will be providing drinks and fruits at he break.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday – December 12th Special All Day- you can book a private session with Christopher at The Larches.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>rain phillips</member_name><member_id>7240421</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292204928000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287012660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Angel Gathering with Christopher</name><id>15102147</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292022000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/15102147/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/7/global_10366711.jpeg</photo_url></item>