<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Asheesh Laroia&lt;/b&gt; is speaking at Pycon in Atlanta this year, and will present a draft of his 30-min talk, &amp;quot;Get new contributors (and diversity) through outreach&amp;quot;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;This talk is targeted at anyone involved in an open source project who wants to find more contributors.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Programs like Google Summer of Code often provide excited students who disappear after a summer's work. Meanwhile, request for help emails on development lists are typically met with silence. Hackathons create a flurry of commits, but then we never hear from the participants again. Expanding your team is possible, and it requires care in terms of outreach, expectation management, and mentorship.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;We will discuss three major forms of outreach:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * One-on-one check-ins with participants,&lt;br /&gt;    * Periodic drives to bring in new contributors, and&lt;br /&gt;    * In-person teaching events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each one has &amp;quot;do&amp;quot;s and &amp;quot;don't&amp;quot;s associated with it. This talk digests the experience of effective outreach into practical strategies that you can re-use within your project.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we'll turn our attention to more mundane matters: this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/ideas/583191/"&gt;discussion about installation chaos&lt;/a&gt; seems like a good topic for a freewheeling session.  I don't know exactly what we'll cover, so bring your questions, answers, and opinions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have an installation issue that's been bugging you? Have you come up with a novel way to solve the tension between Python packages and OS packages?  Just need help getting a particular package to finally work right?  Confused by virtualenv, pip, easy_install, pypi, etc?  Come to the meetup and get into the mix.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we run out of installation stuff to talk about, we'll start on something else, who knows what?  The floor is completely open, bring your Python grievances and adorations. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ned Batchelder</member_name><member_id>1824278</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295538392000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pythonistas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonpython</urlname><id>469457</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Python User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294585481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Updated: Pycon talk 1: "Contributor Outreach"; and installation chaos</name><id>15979297</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295481600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/events/15979297/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/e/8/global_19730024.jpeg</photo_url></item>