<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>172 York St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308254</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-789-8684</phone><name>Bangkok Gardens</name><city>New Haven</city><id>384670</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.931770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I know that many of our members live/work near the New Haven area so here you go!  This restaurant comes highly recommended by quite a few members as well as the Hartford Courant.  Here is the review from the Courant:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Best Restaurants of New England&lt;br /&gt;Web Published: Jan. 2005&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know you're in for something exceptional when mainstream chefs and diners proclaim this as one of the top dining establishments in the city. A favorite of the Yale crowd, it surely is stylish, with faux-marble tables and black chairs in a front conservatory and dining room to the rear. A few elegant Thai artifacts and a courtly, well-spoken staff assure that this is no run-of-the-mill Thai restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Original Thai cuisine is advertised. Start with chicken or beef satay, crispy spring rolls, hot and sour soup or the seafood salad, a concoction of shrimp, scallops and squid tossed with onions, peppers, tomatoes and herbs in lime juice. We like the sound of the tamarind duck, the salmon ginger and the pataya seafood, the last a mix of seafood with onions, baby corn, green peppers, snow peas, bean thread noodles and a spicy house sauce, served with fried rice. In a welcome variation from the norm, you can select your own vegetables, curries and pan-fried accompaniments from an exotic mix-and-match selection to go with your basic chicken, beef, pork, shrimp or tofu. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is interesting stuff and affordable, too.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Annette will be the organizer for this event.  Please email any questions/concerns to her.  Thanks, Annette!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193007803000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190900819000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Time for Thai</name><id>6437810</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192834800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/6437810/</event_url></item>