<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note: &lt;/strong&gt;This program will be starting at 7:30 pm, not the usual 7:00 pm, therefore it might be best to get in line to grab seats at &lt;strong&gt;6:45 pm&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;------&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From an emailed announcement by The Coolidge Corner:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Hide the bird bath!&amp;nbsp; Hitchcock&amp;rsquo;s 1963 classic, about frenzied feathered flocks that terrorize a quiet community, is one of the Master of Suspense&amp;rsquo;s most anxiety-inducing films.&amp;nbsp; After chic socialite Melanie Daniels (Tippi Hedren) meets handsome lawyer Mitch Brenner (Rod Taylor) in a San Francisco bird shop, she follows him to the small California coastal town of Bodega Bay, where he spends weekends with his possessive mother (Jessica Tandy) and younger sister.&amp;nbsp; Shortly after she arrives, a seagull swoops down and pecks her on the forehead.&amp;nbsp; Strange enough, but birdfeed compared to what follows.&amp;nbsp; Gradually, ordinary birds in the hundreds and then thousands alight on the town and start attacking everyone and everything with increasing aggression.&amp;nbsp; The film&amp;rsquo;s leisurely build-up and periods of eerie silence only heighten the emotional intensity of the avian assaults.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; The Birds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Hitchcock capitalizes on a process that really happens in nature &amp;ndash; mobbing &amp;ndash; and takes it to an extreme.&amp;nbsp; Observed in birds and other animals, mobbing is form of anti-predator behavior that occurs when individuals of a certain species cooperatively harass or attack a potential or supposed enemy. Join us as guest speaker Theodore Stankowich sheds light on the rationale, risks, and rewards of mobbing and other types of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;cooperative animal behavior.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Theodore Stankowich is a Visiting Postdoctoral Scientist and Teaching Fellow in the Department of Organismic and Evolutionary Biology at Harvard University and an Adjunct Research Assistant Professor in the Department of Biology at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst.&amp;nbsp; He studies how animals perceive and assess potential threats in their environment, how they decide when to defend themselves or flee, and how historical environments shaped the evolution of traits we see today.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.J. Maher will probably get there by 6:30 pm. Let's try to get there at &lt;strong&gt;6:45 pm&lt;/strong&gt;, pick up our Will Call tickets at the box office&amp;nbsp;and get in the line to grab seats. The line forms at 6:45 pm and doors open at 7:10 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with blue eyes, short brown hair, a "Hello My Name is T.J." nametag and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The doors open at 7:10 pm, but by that time it is hideously difficult to find seats together since the line has wrapped around the building by then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tickets:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Tickets ($9.75 general/$7.75 students, Museum of Science members, and seniors) are available at &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/showtimes"&gt;www.coolidge.org/showtimes&lt;/a&gt;. Tickets also available at the Coolidge Corner Theatre box office, 290 Harvard Street, Brookline. For more information about Science on Screen, visit &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science"&gt;www.coolidge.org/science&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304091204000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Hide the bird feeder! The Coolidge's Science on Screen series pairs Hitchcock's 1963 classic about frenzied feathered flocks with a talk with Dr. Theodore Stankowich, Evolutionary Biology at Harvard University</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300734711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hitchcock's The Birds w/ lecture @ Coolidge Corner, Science on Screen</name><id>17001217</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303771500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/17001217/</event_url></item>