<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Time to venture back to the Harvard Film Archive for Henri-George Clouzot's suspense classic, &lt;em&gt;Les Diaboliques,&lt;/em&gt; "a work of audacious trickery that entirely reinvented the rules for mystery cinema". This is the film he made after his other classic, Wages of Fear, and the film that Alfred Hitchcock wishes he made.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Les Diabolique&lt;/em&gt; is&amp;nbsp;the story of [a] scandalous love triangle between a tyrannical prep school headmaster, played with steely derision by Paul Meurisse, and two women teaching at his school &amp;ndash; Simone Signoret's brooding history instructor and his long-suffering wife, played, ironically, by Mrs. Vera Clouzot. Alfred Hitchcock zealously pursued the source novel of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Les Diaboliques&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;by the famed mystery writing team, Bouileau and Narcejac, only to be beaten by Clouzot who adopted the book into a film that inspired many important aspects of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Psycho&lt;/em&gt;, made five years later, including Hitchcock's "Don't reveal the ending!" campaign which was closely modeled on the cunning marketing strategy that propelled Clouzot's picture into an international box office sensation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Print courtesy of L'Institut fran&amp;ccedil;ais.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and see what the fuss is all about with this Clouzot classic.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we'll venture into Harvard Square for eats, drinks and discussion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wait inside the theater at the end of the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daniel</member_name><member_id>3074431</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324232465000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323839239000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Les Diaboliques</name><id>44404132</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324166400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/44404132/</event_url></item>