<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45-55 Union Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.361576</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Bell In Hand Tavern</name><city>Boston</city><id>1964861</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057068</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;**UPDATE** Please do try to come at 7pm, however for this week, trivia is starting at 8:00pm. Boston Event Guide published the wrong start time so Ryan needs to push back the start time to 8pm.&amp;nbsp; I will have apps available just after 7pm.&amp;nbsp; See you soon!***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After an unusually long hiatus over the holidays, TRIVIA IS BACK at The Bell in Hand Tavern! Join us with Ryan, the wonderful trivia jockey, for some pub trivia THIS WEDNESDAY starting at 7:00pm.&amp;nbsp; This is NOT Stump! trivia, nor is it Geeks Who Drink, it's a whole different unique format designed by the one and only Ryan.&amp;nbsp; First prize is $50 gift certificate to the Bell in Hand! [NOTE: NEW 7:00PM START TIME.]&amp;nbsp; FREE APPETIZERS WHILE THEY LAST.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the holiday break, MeetUp was ruling this room! Sweeping the prizes each week! LET'S DO IT AGAIN!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bell in Hand is super conveniently located in the Haymarket area near the Orange and Green Lines (Haymarket), the Green and Blue Lines (Gov't Center), and a short walk from the Red Line (Park Street).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be there by 7:00pm, if not earlier, on the larger side of The Bell in Hand (the side with the stage).&amp;nbsp; Please get there early to get a good table/seat.&amp;nbsp; I'll try to reserve a couple of tables, but no promises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own food and drink. PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU GO.&amp;nbsp; And please remember to tip your bartender/server.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask bartender for me</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328451379000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327938822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*LAST MINUTE* Trivia Night at The Bell in Hand Tavern</name><id>50224612</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328140800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/50224612/</event_url></item>