<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since I have not seen a single film by Ritwik Ghatak, this is an opportunity for me to correct it. Jihad has already given some introduction in the other meetup event he is organizing, and all I can add is that along with Satyajit Ray, Mrinal Sen and Bimal Roy, he was one of the gifts of Bengal to Indian cinema. He mentored and inspired some of the Indian directors who went on to make movies that became a part of what is known as the &amp;quot;Indian parallel cinema&amp;quot; (art-house) during the 70s and 80s.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the synopsis from &lt;a href="http://hcl.harvard.edu/hfa/films/2008janfeb/ghatak.html#cloud" target="_blank"&gt;HFA website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;Considered Ghatak's masterpiece, this powerful and innovative melodrama revolves around a refugee family from East Bengal, victims of the Partition, who forge a precarious existence on the outskirts of Calcutta. Ghatak captures the complex play of creative and destructive forces at work in the attempt of each family member to survive. At the center of this domestic tragedy is the selfsacrificing Neeta, the family's eldest daughter and provider for all, who struggles away at her job in the city. Closer to home, an elder brother practices to become a singer, while a younger one turns to factory work. Gradually, the father realizes the utter worthlessness of his liberal education in a modern world that has no place for Yeats or Milton and no regard for the ideals of nineteenth-century Bengali liberalism.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be twinkling near the screen/front row of the auditorium.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Because you love films and the discussion that follows.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202079974000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meghe Dhaka Tara (The Cloud-Capped Star)</name><id>7256316</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203724800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7256316/</event_url></item>