<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a full day event, with presentations in the morning, and a hands-on session in the afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Goal&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) is going to present some of the Core technologies that will be part of the future Web technologies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The morning is intended for a general audience, when we'll have relatively high-level overview of the technologies. The afternoon is intended for folks who are not afraid to get their hands dirty with HTML, CSS, Javascript, or SVG.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't intend to stay in the afternoon, that's fine, but it's highly recommended that you follow the morning session if you're interested to attend the hands-on session in the afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pizza and drinks will be available at no cost. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free event and there is no registration fee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Morning: The Next Open Web Platform&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Each presentation will be around 30 minutes with 15 minutes for questions.&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;9:00-9:45&lt;br /&gt;         Introduction to Next Open Web Platform&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;i&gt;Speaker: Philippe Le Hegaret, W3C&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;9:45-10:30&lt;br /&gt;         Introduction to HTML 5&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;i&gt;Speaker: Mike Smith, W3C&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;10:30-11:15&lt;br /&gt;         Introduction to SVG and Canvas&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;i&gt;Speaker: Douglas Schepers, W3C&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;11:15-12:00&lt;br /&gt;         Introduction to CSS 3&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;i&gt;Speaker: Bert Bos, W3C&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Afternoon: Hands-on session&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;13:00-18:00&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;  Requirement: Bring your own computer so you can run one or more Web browsers. You may need to download and install software on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  We would propose one or more projects (ideas are welcome) in an informal way. At the moment, we have only one project in mind:&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;  - Develop a cross-browser HTML5/SVG video player HTML 5 Video and its Media API, Integrating HTML with SVG.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      This is intended for beginners to advanced developers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;b&gt;For the most advanced/adventurous&lt;/b&gt;, we can go into WAI-ARIA, Web Fonts, Captioning in Javascript, and whatever you feel like using from SVG.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      W3C is interested in demonstrating some of the results on the W3C website and in our various talks around the globe (with proper credits of course!). The motto here is &amp;quot;Impress us (and it's that too difficult) and have fun!&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speakers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bert Bos&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Bert Bos completed his Ph.D. in Groningen, The Netherlands, on a protoyping language for graphical user interfaces. He then went on to develop a browser targeted at humanities scholars, before joining the W3C at INRIA/Sophia-Antipolis in October 1995. He is co-inventor of CSS and created &amp;amp; led W3C's Internationalization activity. After working on HTML and XML, he is now leading the CSS and Mathematics activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Philippe Le Hégaret&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Philippe heads the W3C Interaction Domain, which produces client-side technologies in several areas including HTML and CSS. Until July 2008, Philippe was involved in the area of XML, and Web Services. He is a former Chair of the Document Object Model (DOM) Working Group and co-editor of two DOM specifications. He was the co-Chair of the W3C Workshop on Video on the Web, focusing on making video a first class Web citizen, including making it easy to create, link to and from, describe, and search.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Prior to joining W3C, Philippe promoted the use of XML inside Bull in 1998, also focusing on the interaction between XML and object structures. He wrote the first version of the CSS validator in 1997.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Doug Schepers&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Doug Schepers joined the W3C Team in June 2007 as a Compound Document Specialist. He is Team Contact for the SVG and WebApps Working Groups, and Rich Web Client Activity Lead. He was previously AC Representative for Vectoreal and has been creating Web Applications for many years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Michael Smith&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Michael Smith joined the W3C in January 2007, as part of the W3C's Mobile Web Initiative. He's now involved with work on core standards related to browsing technologies; in particular, the phenomenon known as HTML5, as well as other standards related to Web Applications. Mike has been based in Tokyo since 2001, and prior to joining the W3C, worked for Opera Software and Openwave Systems (and was for most of that time involved with design, development, testing, and deployment of software for mobile operators in Japan).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Event will take place in the first floor conference center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philippe Le Hegaret</member_name><member_id>10875499</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>23</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304711100000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Web Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonweb</urlname><id>163691</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Web Design (and Dev) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>71</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268160976000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Looking at the Next Open Web Platform</name><id>12829934</id><headcount>73</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269694800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonweb/events/12829934/</event_url></item>