<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Pleasant St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02367</zip><lat>41.939486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-526-2200</phone><name>Shanti Shala Yoga &amp; Wellness Center</name><city>Plympton</city><id>1084839</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.802394</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/0/2/event_211483522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come join us for a Crystal Healing Web with Amethyst.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;We will learn about the Amethyst gemstone and experience the healing vibrational sounds of the Gongs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;All participants will go home with an Amethyst Crystal for their collection. All welcome from the experienced Crystal Worker to the Beginner.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amethyst Healing Properties&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increases nobility, Spiritual awareness, Psychic abilities, Inner peace and healing&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Healing of body, mind &amp;amp; soul Positive transformation Meditation Balance Relieves stress Communication&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Amethyst is a variety of Quartz and is a 6th Anniversary gemstone.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Chakras - Third Eye Chakra, Crown Chakra&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Birthstone - February&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Zodiac - Virgo, Sagittarius, Capricorn, Aquarius, Pisces&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Planet – Jupiter&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Element – Air&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Typical colors - light slightly-pinkish violet to a deep grape purple&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Amethyst is a powerful and protective stone. It guards against psychic attack, transmuting the energy into love and protecting the wearer from all types of harm, including geopathic or electromagnetic stress and ill wishes from others. Amethyst is a natural tranquiliser, it relieves stress and strain, soothes irritability, balances mood swings, dispels anger, rage, fear and anxiety. Alleviates sadness and grief, and dissolves negativity. Amethyst activates spiritual awareness, opens intuition and enhances psychic abilities. It has strong healing and cleansing powers. Amethyst encourages sobriety, having a sobering effect on overindulgence of alcohol, drugs or other addictions. It calms and stimulates the mind, helping you become more focused, enhancing memory and improving motivation. Amethyst assists in remembering and understanding dreams. It relieves insomnia. Encourages selflessness and spiritual wisdom.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Amethyst boosts hormone production, tunes the endocrine system and metabolism. It strengthens the immune system. Cleanses the blood. Relieves physical, emotional and psychological pain or stress. Amethyst eases headaches and releases tension. It reduces bruising, swellings, injuries, and treats hearing disorders. Amethyst heals diseases of the lungs and respiratory tract, skin conditions, cellular disorders and diseases of the digestive tract.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>@ Shanti Shala</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darnell</member_name><member_id>10396246</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diana Burke</member_name><member_id>13852651</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366419669000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightenment Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ShantiShala</urlname><id>1534948</id><group_lat>41.9599990845</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8099975586</group_lon><name>Shanti Shala Yoga &amp; Wellness Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362584207000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come join us for a Crystal Healing Web with Amethyst.</name><id>107901622</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366414200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ShantiShala/events/107901622/</event_url></item>