<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1 Country Club Road </address_2><address_1>Route 5</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.224295</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-532-1800</phone><name>Delaney House </name><city>Holyoke </city><id>1198883</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.628986</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Ira’s Singles Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ira of the Ira’s Singles events co-hosts this exciting and fun Event. &lt;br /&gt; You may want to Find a Keeper or you may just want to meet new friends – it’s all good.  As the Ira says, “Come Alone, but Never Feel Alone.”  Get out and party with other singles this summer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SINGLES DANCE  AND SO MUCH MORE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                KICKING OF FALL WITH OKTOBERFEST &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Saturday, September 11, 6 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eat, drink, mingle and dance the night away&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plenty of Slow Dances……Yay……&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone’s back from summer vacation and they’re ready to have fun and meet new people!!  And we’re ready to shake things up and make this the best singles event and dance party in Western Mass!!! ( Yes,Wes  You can help make it happen!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ladies, invite your male friends and let’s get more men to party with us and meet all the fabulous women we know who have been coming to Find a Keeper every month!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, we know the summer months were light in attendance, but let’s all get back in the groove, eat, mingle, dance and have fun, fun, fun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR  SINGLES!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE ? OR CLOSE TO FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE&lt;br /&gt;The Delaney House has offered Free Admission to any past participant in the Find A Keeper Series. For this to happen, you must pre register with a phone call for the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALMOST FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register and pay in advance for only $20!!  All that delicious food for only $20, plus DJ and Dancing!!!  $30 at the door, so save money by reserving your space in advance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Delaney House, One Country Club Rd., Holyoke, MA- 413-532-1800&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Find a Keeper, the newest, most personal way for singles 40 and over to meet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00P.M. – 8:00P.M.  Cocktails/Food/Chit Chat          &lt;br /&gt;8:00 P.M. Let the music move you and put you in a party mood. A “cool DJ” will be doing the spinning and happy to play your requested sounds. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food Below is for the Energy to Dance!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fantastic Food Stations!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is at the Delaney House which means the Food will be awesome, and plenty of it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please also send me an email once your ticket has been purchased: mistrchrming@aol.com. Subject Line: September 11. Saturday.  The Singles Dance &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Questions:  860-604-5792. Please see Pictures of events at the Delaney House and other Ira’s events, see: www.the irassinglesevents.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The FoodStuff:::::::&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oktoberfest Menu&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Vegetables with cheese fondue for dipping&lt;br /&gt;Spinach salad with honey mustard dressing&lt;br /&gt;house garden salad with Roquefort dressing&lt;br /&gt;garlic bread&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Food Stations&lt;br /&gt;Grilled Bratwurst and Knockwurst, sauerkraut&lt;br /&gt;rye breads&lt;br /&gt;mustards&lt;br /&gt;German potato salad&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Schnitzel with wild mushroom sauce&lt;br /&gt;Pierogies with sauteed onions and sour cream (cross-cultural, lol!)&lt;br /&gt;Sauteed red cabbage&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dessert&lt;br /&gt;Dark chocolate mousse with raspberry sauce&lt;br /&gt;Strudel with whipped cream&lt;br /&gt;Carrot cake with caramel sauce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A bunch of Singles Having Fun!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284246659000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283442254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira-  Singles Dance, DJ, Great Food, Mingling, Oktoberfest, What  a Night!!</name><id>14632708</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284242400000</time><rsvp_limit>150</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/14632708/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/8/global_11894136.jpeg</photo_url></item>