<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Avenue of the Arts</address_2><address_1>465 Huntington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-9300</phone><name>Museum of Fine Arts </name><city>Boston</city><id>500439</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093620</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Winesdays in Bravo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;A Tasting and Pairing of Spanish Wines and Tapas&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The focus at this tasting will be on Spanish wines, in conjunction with the &amp;quot;El Greco to Velázquez&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Antonio Lopez Garcia&amp;quot; exhibits. There will be an expert on hand to discuss the best wine regions of Spain, as well as tapas-style hors d'oeuvres paired with the Spanish wines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pannotia Vineyard's Garnacha and Verdejo wines will be featured.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$25 per person includes hors d'oeuvres and unlimited tasting of featured wines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No reservations necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, please call Bravo at 617-369-3474. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;For the pre-tasting tour:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;El Greco and Velázquez&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;: This groundbreaking exhibition examines a fascinating period (1598-1621) bracketed by the two giants of Spanish painting, El Greco and Velázquez. Discover the masterpieces of Philip III's court and the artists who flourished during his reign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To separate themselves from Philip II's approach to governing, Philip III and his court &amp;quot;issued in a new style of grandeur&amp;quot; (in the words of their contemporary Gil González d'Avila), where gala celebrations, elaborate religious fiestas, building campaigns, and picture collecting were the order of the day. Much of the art produced at and for the court reflected this style, replacing the austere art created for Philip II with a more naturalistic and emotionally expressive art that became the hallmark of Philip III's reign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;El Greco to Velázquez: Art during the Reign of Philip III&amp;quot; features paintings, sculpture, and decorative arts; including a partial recreation of the camarín of the Duke of Lerma, the most important non-royal collector in Europe at the time and the favorite of Philip III; organized around themes such as portraiture, religion and the court, and the birth of still life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Antonio López García&lt;/b&gt;: It is impossible to describe Antonio López García simply as a painter in the &amp;quot;realist&amp;quot; school. His masterful paintings of the prosaic, familiar places of his world and of the family and friends comprising it reveal an unusual sensitivity to his subject. Through uncompromising study of his subjects, he has imbued the commonplace with a haunting and extraordinary character, seen in his exceptional depiction of light; at once brilliant and subdued, ethereal and fleeting, and palpable. His unrelenting examination and depiction of his subject means that he sometimes spends years to finish a single canvas. This penetrating approach, as well as his exceptional skill, has singled out López García as one of Spain's most revered artists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For those who would like to tour the  "El Greco to Velázquez" exhibit prior to the tasting; I had planned to be in the lobby at 4:15. The Tasting begins at 5:30. However, I may be unable to make it to this event. See my RSVP. Thanks.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221788713000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209432874000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MFA Wine; Tasting, Tapas &amp; Tour</name><id>7832151</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212010200000</time><rsvp_limit>32</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/7832151/</event_url></item>