<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;Honestly, I couldn't decide on which movie to host this Sunday afternoon- Waitress or Paprika.Waitress is a slice-of-life comedy and Paprika is an anime feature concerning dreams. I opted for Paprika on the strength of Ty Burr's review and another reference to this film as  being a more adult-centric version of Howl's Moving Castle (this got me giddy just thinking about it).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the description from AllMovieGuide: Groundbreaking animator Satoshi Kon (whose credits include Tokyo Godfathers, Millennium Actress, and Perfect Blue) directed this visually spectacular adaptation of a science fiction novel by Yatsutaka Tsutsui. Atsuko is a psychiatrist who uses advanced technology to study the human mind. Atsuko has developed a machine that will allow her to enter the dreams of her patients and study their psyches from the inside. Atsuko also does double duty as Paprika, a high-tech detective who uses this new innovation to find out the truth about what the people she's trailing really think. However, Atsuko falls victim to a thief who steals the one-of-a-kind machine, and Paprika sets out to find it as a wave of psychological instability tears through the city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's Ty Burr's rave review: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;amp;id=9986" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be holding a Meet-Up sign near the front row after the film and then we will go to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Actual screening time is 4:40.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182285468000</updated><rating><average>3.79999995232</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181691752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paprika- Japanese Anime at Kendall on Sunday Afternoon</name><id>5884490</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182112200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5884490/</event_url></item>