<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I suggest meeting in the ticket lobby of the AMC at 6:00 p.m. on Saturday evening. It'll be crowded anyway, but screenings only add to the mayhem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for other meetup members there and just ask them if they're part of the movie meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That being said, &lt;b&gt;PLEASE REMEMBER TO RSVP&lt;/b&gt; to this meetup like any other so that people know who to look for. I know a few of you have already told me personally that you're going, but replying on the site helps others know you'll be there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the show! And comment after you see it to tell me how you liked it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Hey, there, movie lovers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be out of town this weekend, but I wanted to pass along to you an invite I just got for a free screening of Katherine Heigl's new movie, &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810126237/details" target="_blank"&gt;Life As We Know It&lt;/a&gt;. Here's the info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Holly Berenson is an up-and-coming caterer and Eric Messer is a promising network sports director. After a disastrous first date, the only thing they have in common is their dislike for each other and their love for their goddaughter, Sophie. But when they suddenly become all Sophie has in the world, Holly and Eric are forced to put their differences aside. Juggling career ambitions and competing social calendars, they'll have to find some common ground while living under one roof.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SCREENING INFO/EMAIL I GOT:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am writing on behalf of Warner Bros. and their upcoming film LIFE AS WE KNOW IT, starring Katherine Heigl and Josh Duhamel.  On Saturday, Oct. 2nd, there is a sneak preview of the film in &lt;br /&gt;Framingham.  I thought your group members may have interest in attending, so I've included a link below which takes you directly to Gofobo.com, where you can enter your zip code to download passes to the Framingham Screening. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.gofobo.com/screenings/life_as_we_know_it/572454?pc=QzlIMzBaM0I%3D" target="_blank"&gt;Gofobo.com to claim your free pass.&lt;/a&gt; (Free reg required.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd recommend you get there super early so that your passes will be honored. There was quite a line for a free screening we attended last December, with over 20 FMM members seeing the show and lots of other groups joining in the fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the show!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I won't be there, but look for other meetup members!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286061405000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285879596000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NoOrg-Life as We Know It -- free screening!</name><id>14954988</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286056800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/14954988/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>