<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>So we will try this again after the crazy weather on June 6.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have planned a section of the Metacomet Trail to hike.  We will start in Farmington on Mountain Road (Fitty Cent's House) and finish on route 372 in Plainville.  This will be a 7.2 mile adventure that will take us by the channel 30 antennas, up Rattlesnake Mt. (there are none up there) elevation 750', past Will Warren's Den (a small cave with a story), and over Pinnacle Rock.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The terrain is rugged and rocky.  There is a fair amount of climbing both up and down.  You do need proper hiking boots and non cotton clothing.  Due to distance and terrain this would not be a beginner hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a through hike so we will meet at the end point and I will need folks help to get all to the beginning.  At the conclusion, those who drove will need rides back to their cars.  The shuttling should go smooth if we all help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need to meet at the end point (440 New Britain Ave Plainville) at 9:30 a.m. I am hoping this should last no longer than 4 hours.  We should be done by 2:00.  But remember we are only as fast as our slowest hiker.  Please do not schedule yourself so tight-really you should be open ended about finish time.  We will be very close to J.Timothy's.  If folks aren't headed out for a hot date and want to hang out for food.  Its a fun place .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is very summer-ish time so bring plenty of water, snacks, bugspray, sunscreen.  This area has longer grasses and plant growth.  Consider long hiking pants or gators.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always with me, no dogs or children please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS PEOPLE- MANY OF OUR HIKES DO NOT HAVE REAL ADDRESSES.  THAT IS WHY I GIVE YOU MAPQUEST LINKS THAT HAVE A MAP SHOWING YOU WHERE YOU ARE HEADED.&lt;br /&gt;I ALWAYS GIVE YOU MY PHONE NUMBER IF YOU GET CONFUSED, LOST, OR JUST FEEL LIKE COMPLAINING.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet here at 9:30 a.m.  This is the ending site and where we will meet.  There is a medical building with a large parking lot.  We will park on the right toward the back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Plainville+&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=440+New+Britain+Ave" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate starting location.  We are going to the end of this road to Fitty's House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Farmington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=%5B1-99%5D+Poplar+Hill+Dr&amp;amp;zipcode=06032&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.714035&amp;amp;longitude=-72.817175&amp;amp;geocode=BLOCK" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276556600000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275772741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking redo for Rattlesnake Mt./Will Warren's Den, Farmington to Plainville, CT</name><id>13709379</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276435800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13709379/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>