<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.359150</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 4, Room 231</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6010332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;a lecture by Prof. Vivek Kumar &lt;br /&gt;

Center for the Study of Social Systems, JNU, New Delhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How have modernization and globalization been experienced by the masses? How has this effected homogenization, pluralization, traditionalization, and hybridization? What about issues of availability, accessibility, and adaptability?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vivek Kumar (Ph.D.) is a Visiting Associate Professor in the Sociology Department at Columbia, and a Fulbright Teaching Fellow in residence at the South Asia Institute. Vivek Kumar is also an Associate Professor at the Centre for the Study of Social Systems, in the School of Social Sciences, at Jawaharlal Nehru University, where he earned his Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His major area of interest is in issues of Dalits, marginalized section in India, and global African community struggles. He has been engaged in comparative issues of Dalits and African Americans. He has been a Visiting Professor at the Universities of Pune, Jammu, and Mumbai. His recent publications include the co‐edited volume Dynamics of Change and Continuity in the Age of Globalization: Voices from the Margins (2009), and the monographs Dalit Society: Old Problems and New Aspirations (2007) and India's Roaring Revolution: Dalit Assertion and New Horizons (2006). Prof. Kumar is currently involved in an ongoing research project, "Social Status and Social Attitudes in India: A Study of Indian College Students," with Professor Jim Sidanius (Harvard) and Arjun Bharadwaj (University of British Columbia). He was also called by the Planning Commission of India and Empowerment and Social Justice Ministry of India for the formulation of upcoming 12th five year plan of India. His areas of specialization are Social Stratification in India, Indian Diaspora, and Social Movements of Dalits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supported by: Alliance for a Secular and Democratic South Asia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;fb: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/384525561598518/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/384525561598518/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336864211000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336617273000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Modernization and Globalization: Understanding Social Exclusion in South Asia</name><id>64183352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336852800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/64183352/</event_url></item>