<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Camp Cachalot is a boy scout camp on the border of Myles Standish State Forest. We have permission to explore this little known corner of Myles Standish. We haven't hiked this area before but we expect to encounter well-worn paths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/6/0/event_122911072.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring water and snacks, bug and sun protection, wear good boots, etc. This hike will be approximately 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/stewardship/rmp/downloads/mssf/rmp-mssf.pdf"&gt;DCR Management plan for Myles Standish&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1998, the DCR and the Massachusetts Division of Fisheries and Wildlife (DFW) jointly purchased  a conservation restriction on Camp Cachalot, a 750-acre property owned by the Moby Dick Council of the Boy Scouts of America. Camp Cachalot encompasses several ponds, miles of trails, significant pitch pine-scrub oak habitat and occurrences of state listed rare species. The property abuts the southeast corner of MSSF. The CR ensures continued Boy Scout camp use, public pedestrian access to the property, hunting during shotgun deer season, use of Abner and Five Mile ponds for fishing, public parking at the entrance to the camp and establishment of a trail in the northeast section of the property to Abner Pond. In consultation with the owner, the DCR and DFW can enter the property to carry out habitat management activities, including the establishment of fire breaks, removal of fire fuels and controlled burns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ecLQoFE1P-s"&gt;1953 Cachalot promotional film (silent)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 8:30 at Panera Bread in the Shops at Five for breakfast. (Exit 5 off Route 3). Please join us if you are able.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Camp Cachalot is on a road near Fearing Pond. Follow the signs to Fearing Pond and then the signs to Camp Cachalot. (Don't go to Camp Squanto, which is also on a road near Fearing Pond.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Bescherer</member_name><member_id>650729</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338919812000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338037243000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camp Cachalot exploration</name><id>66425642</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338472800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/66425642/</event_url></item>