<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our April pick is &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;A Thousand Splendid Suns&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; by Khaled Hosseini.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a brief synopsis from Barnes and Noble of &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;A Thousand Splendid Suns&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Thousand Splendid Suns is a breathtaking story set against the volatile events of Afghanistan's last thirty years — from the Soviet invasion to the reign of the Taliban to post-Taliban rebuilding — that puts the violence, fear, hope and faith of this country in intimate, human terms. It is a tale of two generations of characters brought jarringly together by the tragic sweep of war, where personal lives — the struggle to survive, raise a family, find happiness — are inextricable from the history playing out around them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Propelled by the same storytelling instinct that made The Kite Runner a beloved classic, A Thousand Splendid Suns is at once a remarkable chronicle of three decades of Afghan history and a deeply moving account of family and friendship. It is a striking, heartwrenching novel of an unforgiving time, an unlikely friendship, and an indestructible love — a stunning accomplishment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim G.</member_name><member_id>7110146</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242168383000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236730455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club April Meetup - A Thousand Splendid Suns</name><id>9927255</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239750000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/9927255/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/7/a/global_7630218.jpeg</photo_url></item>