<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>489 Whitney Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.163395</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Startup Helping Hand</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>10190652</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.640808</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jack Clemente, CEO &amp;amp; Founder of Startup Helping Hand will be hosting an open-door event from 6 to 9pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Startup Helping Hand is a new kind of a service for Pioneer Valley entrepreneurs and innovators. For a modest monthly fee, members will be given access to a number of professional resources (funding, lawyer, startup consultant, patent attorney, etc).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a somewhat higher fee amount, members can have a cubicle space and a full-day access to the in-office resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This office space is conveniently located next to the Holyoke Mall, having access from highways 90 and 91.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The flyer for this event can be downloaded here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;http://www.MKRD.info/uploads/tmp/Starup Helping Hand Open House.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Startup Helping Hand is now on meetup! They can be located at this address:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Helping-Hand-Entreprenuer-Resources-Holyoke-Mall/"&gt;Startup Helping Hand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is from the flyer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to provide a resource center rich in support focused on early-stage startups in Western Massachusetts. In an effort to minimize the challenges and obstacles entrepreneurs face, accelerate their growth and stimulate economic development. Entrepreneurs will receive professional assistance and guidance within a robust environment suitable for realizing their ideas. We offer full-service office space to facilitate an open exchange format, and to promote collaborative practices within the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Triaging a concept/Idea&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Legal and Patent advice&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Financial Services&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketing/Brand Development Workshops/Seminars/Innovate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website development&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Funding presentation development&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On-Demand Sales Force – Accelerate market share and sales&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Workshops tailored to address the current needs of startups&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hands-on support and guidance on developing a business plan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assistance with establishing the necessary funding to launch the business 3 Conference Rooms&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prescreening and explore the best funding sources for the venture&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Affordable full-service office space, conference rooms, and cubicles on a needed basis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interactive website, providing access to services from anywhere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collaboration with all other local resources to assist and promote entrepreneurship in Western Mass&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the Real Estate community to locate and fill suitable vacant retail/office space&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Startup Helping Hand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack Clemente, Startup Helping Hand CEO and founder, is a serial entrepreneur. His last company, Convenient Cards, Inc. was a pioneering venture in the Prepaid Debit Card space. But it took him over four years to launch. Even then, he was undercapitalized and unable to take the company to the next level. Beyond financing, he felt somewhat isolated from other resources. He longed for a network of fellow entrepreneurs to bounce ideas off. He has learned a lot and now wants to use that knowledge to help entrepreneurs. Thus his new venture, Startup Helping Hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Suite 308 (3rd floor). If going by Riverdale St, to go Holyoke Mall, office building on left before mall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Kat.</member_name><member_id>8999115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354759516000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352252023000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Startup Helping Hand Open Door Event!</name><id>90297222</id><headcount>20</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353020400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/90297222/</event_url></item>