<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>38 Charter Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01720</zip><lat>42.482914</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Acton-Boxboro High School Auditorium</name><city>Acton</city><id>514452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.458800</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*02/20/2008 TOWN HALL MEETING WITH CONGRESSWOMAN&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TSONGAS IN ACTON*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, February 20, 6:30 - 8 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acton-Boxboro High School Auditorium, 38 Charter Road&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acton, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Message from Congresswoman Tsongas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be hosting a town hall meeting to discuss the war in Iraq and other issues.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I recently returned from a trip to Iraq where met with U.S. service men and women,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General David Petraeus, Ambassador Ryan Crocker, as well as with Iraqi leaders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to share my experiences and the lessons I learned from the trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to hear your views on the war.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I stated throughout my campaign, I want to work to ensure that we bring our&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;troops home from Iraq quickly, safely and responsibly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trip reinforced my belief that the best and most responsible way to do this is to set a&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;timetable that requires the Iraqi government to step up to the plate and that finally engages the international community to bring about a political solution to this conflict.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will soon be introducing legislation which sets a timetable for a safe withdrawal of U.S. forces from Iraq.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note from Herb Chasan:  Please attend this meeting and let her know how you feel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remind her that the best way to end  the war is to stop funding it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remind her also that the threat of impeachment is another way to end the war.  Bush will back down if he thinks that the Dems are serious about holding him accountable.  This happened to Nixon.&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;We need to go and confront her and make our presence known!  A new independent 9/11 investigation people!  We don't need to wait for the democrats to take the Presidency, the Senate &amp;amp; House!  We need one NOW!  6 years is too late!!!  I plan to make a 3 ring binder of hardcore news articles &amp;amp; political documents to bring to her staff, not just dvds.  Anyone wishing to help me on this project, please call (617)987-0738 &amp;amp; ask for Waldo.  Thanks everyone!  Let's not drop the ball!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy demanding a new independent 9/11 investigation be launched!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4883658</member_name><member_id>4883658</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203723344000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Remember the last time when we confronted Congressman Markey at the town meeting in Framingham?!  Priceless!  Everyone should come to this event and make a repeat performance!</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203140936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>***TRUTH SQUAD ALERT*** Town Meeting with Congresswoman Tsongas in Acton</name><id>7340842</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203550200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7340842/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/f/global_3238719.jpeg</photo_url></item>