<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>911 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348186</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 266-3399</phone><name>Foggy Goggle</name><city>Boston</city><id>210753</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084370</lon></venue><fee><label>Suggested donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Socializing for Justice at the Foggy Goggle* for the 3rd &amp;quot;Putting the Social Back in Social Justice: One Year Later.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be our biggest event yet, so if you haven't tried SoJust, now is the time.  If you've already joined us in the past, be sure to come back for the same SoJust fun!  We'll be celebrating our first anniversary and will need all SoJusters there - especially to eat birthday cake!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be drink and appetizer specials - 1/2 price appetizers, $7 pitchers of beer, and $12 fishbowls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program. No speaker. Just arrive and enjoy yourself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers for the free lit table - and there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network while sharing cheap pitchers of beer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Sorry, this event is 21+ and the bathroom is located downstairs (no elevator).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Foggy Goggle is across from the Hynes Convention Center.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>36</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192589242000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187289570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Putting the Social Back in Social Justice III: One Year Later</name><id>6192223</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190242800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/6192223/</event_url></item>