<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Harvard Film Archive is going to be screening the complete oeuvre of influential French film director, Henri-George Clouzot, sometimes known as the French Hitchcock, starting this Saturday. If you're in town, and want to take in some remedial viewing, then this thriller masterpiece, The Wages of Fear, is the place to start. It's going to be a great series, and what better way to start than with one of Clouzot's best known films (the other is Les Diaboliques), which features a youthful Yves Montand as one of several roustabouts hired to transport some explosives to put out an oil well fire. Gripping doesn't begin to describe it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the Archive's blurb:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
The Wages of Fear&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Le salaire de la peur)&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Directed by Henri-Georges Clouzot. With Yves Montand, Charles Vanel, Peter Van Eyck &lt;br /&gt;

France 1953, 35mm, b/w, 147 min French with English subtitles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clouzot chose the exotic and squalid background of an unnamed South American town for the keystone of his oeuvre, an angry parable about 20th century imperialism and masculinity pushed to the absolute breaking point and beyond.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Wages of Fear&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;gave Yves Montand his first leading role as an embittered drifter and iconic Clouzot anti-hero &amp;ndash; jaded, self-deluded and stumbling towards an uncertain redemption in a desperate gamble to return to France. A brilliantly gripping suspense narrative,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Wages of Fear&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;uses bold existential strokes to render the Sisyphean mission of four men hired, at unreasonable terms, to drive rickety trucks of deadly explosives through the dark heart of an untamed jungle. The two-part structure favored by Clouzot is crucial to the tense division between the corrupt backwater village of the film's first section and the savage yet frighteningly indifferent jungle wilderness explored in the rest of the film.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Wages of Fear&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;is presented in a new print acquired by the HFA from Janus Films which restores footage censored from the original US release because of perceived anti-Americanism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And you can see a bunch of raves from Rotten Tomatoes here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/wages_of_fear/"&gt;http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/wages_of_fear/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though it's late notice, I hope you'll want to join me for this great film.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wait inside the theater at the end of the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daniel</member_name><member_id>3074431</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322369601000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322097258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Wages of Fear</name><id>42228422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322352000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/42228422/</event_url></item>