<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Melville Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02124</zip><lat>42.295120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-221-2140</phone><name>Zachary &amp; Nora's House</name><city>Boston</city><id>436316</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064087</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come dressed as a deceased literary figure -- character or author, for those who mean to ask -- and join other penniless literati at our annual Boils and Ghouls bash.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be of the snackish variety. True there will be much of the snackage, but I thought it prudent to warn all that we will not be serving up full meals built around pot roast and gamy duck. You are encoruaged to swell our booze larder with a bottle or a pack of whatever your decaying tastebuds wish they were animate again. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please also bring a bag of candy for the trick-or-treating neighborhood delinquents -- why should we dead have all the fun?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to get to 95 Melville Avenue: Take the Ashmont branch on the Red Line to Shawmut. When you exit the station, do not walk straight -- instead, walk out the main doors and around to the path leading away from the back of the station. Follow this lit path across one street, turning right at the second -- that is Melville. My place is one block down. Listen for the screams of tormented souls; those would be my cats, who are peeved I'm not letting them outside. Call 617-935-4951 for help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will toast with absinthe the beloved departed and the admired fictional! Bring books, booze, friends, and yourselves! We shall terrorize trick-or-treaters with bad haiku, and also dance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257199464000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253547496000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Dead Authors' Party</name><id>11426682</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257026400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/11426682/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/3/0/global_10985424.jpeg</photo_url></item>