<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Foster St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.265118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 755-6800</phone><name>DCU Center</name><city>Worcester</city><id>732028</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.798937</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>On Saturday, February 21, the Worcester Sharks are partnering with Bay State Savings Bank and auctioning off their All Star game jerseys to benefit Project Smile, the non profit organization, during a live and silent auction. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We have a limited amount of free tix to the event. Free ticket includes entrance to the Shark Tank- a pre-party room at the DCU Center where guests can hang out and meet Finz, the Sharks mascot. The game starts at 7pm. We will be meeting in the party room at 6pm. Sharks games are lots of fun, so please join us for a great night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay tuned for more info about post- event get together. If you would like to attend, please RSVP and email Catherine your mailing address so she can send your tix and wristband. Please note that tickets and wristbands are not replaceable if they are lost. The wristband gets you admission to the pre-party room. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please only sign up if you are definitely able to attend this event. I&lt;/b&gt;f you RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and do not attend, you will be removed from the group. If you have already told Catherine you will be attending, please do not sign up on this list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to attend the Sharks game with your own friends or family, discounted game tix can be purchased at &lt;a href="http://www.sharksahl.com/BSSB/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sharksahl....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Project Smile will receive a portion of the proceeds from tickets purchased using the above link. The first 2,500 fans 14 and under receive team trading cards.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235691165000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234214688000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free hockey tix for Project Smile Night at the Worcester Sharks</name><id>9707795</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235257200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/9707795/</event_url></item>