<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-243-0034</phone><name>Samadhi Yoga</name><city>Newton</city><id>115993</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.190002</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Clint Fuhs serves as seminar leader at Integral Institute; he is also an integral coach. Clint designed and taught one of the first undergraduate courses on integral theory and practice in the US. Clint lectures on topics ranging from Integral Post-Metaphysics to integral analysis of post-9/11 world affairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Clint also serves as the Partner Group and Curriculum Coordinator for Integral Institute. This position encompasses myriad roles including: workshop trainer, AQAL content review board lead, content and individual certification coordinator, seminar curriculum development, and partner relationship manager. Clint is currently working on a Ph.D. in Human and Organizational Development at Fielding Graduate University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                            Clint will be offering this 3 hour workshop on &lt;br /&gt;                                                    Sunday, July 29th &lt;br /&gt;                                                              12-3&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;                            A Special Workshop on Advanced AQAL Theory&lt;br /&gt;                                                               $25 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Critical Quadratic Distinctions? such as the correct usage of interior, exterior, inside, outside and internal and external.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~The 8 Zones as Perspectives- a cognitive exploration of 4 term integral calculus equations, which represent all possible 4-p in each of the 8 zones. Then we?ll participate in activities designed to engender a direct experience of these perspectives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Kosmic Address- What is it? How can we use it? How can we incorporate it into our practice?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Dual Center of Gravity of the Self- A glimpse at Ken?s newest (yet to be published!) work. Clint will lead us in delving deeper into human development through states and stages, including: fulcrums (transitions vertically in altitude), switch-points (transitions horizontally through states) and the interaction of altitudes (levels) and states in terms on their impact the development of the individual.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole Trudel Churchill</member_name><member_id>3348175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185898279000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184005804000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Advanced AQAL Workshop with Clint Fuhs</name><id>5996728</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185724800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/5996728/</event_url></item>