<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Spring St Watertown</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02471 </zip><lat>42.366023</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>WATERTOWN HEALING ARTS CENTER</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1195386</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184175</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In this time of dramatic transition, imploding systems and shifting priorities, come for a day retreat to get clear — or clearer — about your life purpose. What are you here to do, at a soul or mission level? If money was not a consideration, how would you spend your time after getting all the traveling and sensual experiences out of your system? What turns you on… spiritually? What kind of legacy will you leave behind?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Breathing into Purpose event is a perfect time to go within and ponder these questions — a time to re-evaluate your life, actions, relationships and activities, and a time to define, review and clarify intentions for the coming year. You will have the opportunity and be gently supported to identify and release, in a safe setting, those obstacles within you that have kept you playing small, in a life of unfulfilled potential.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Includes Transformational Breathwork Session&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $130&lt;br /&gt;Payment Plans Available&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;info@soufulpower.com&lt;br /&gt;www.SoulfulPower.com&lt;br /&gt;(877) 773-7557&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302530798000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>In this time of dramatic transition, imploding systems and shifting priorities, come for a day retreat to breathe and get clear — or clearer — about your life purpose.... </why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Breathwork</urlname><id>1299646</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>Breathwork</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302094540000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breathing into Purpose</name><id>17204073</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302454800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Breathwork/events/17204073/</event_url></item>