<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>76 Arlington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.357.7007</phone><name>The Melting Pot</name><city>Boston</city><id>793176</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070315</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Valentine's Day is right around the corner and it’s not too late to find a special someone to share it with!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you are looking for a potential new soul mate, new friend(s), or just a good time; join us as we present an exciting Singles Party that attracts interesting young professionals from all around Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience multiple first dates in one evening as you join other single, young professionals for a chance to find romance with Things To Do Boston’s Four Minute Dating.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if you don’t get a match, we’ve arranged for you to pass private messages to that special someone you may see across the room!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Here’s how it works:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOUR MINUTE DATING: Each attendee is given a nametag with an I.D. number on it as well as an index card on which they print their name, I.D. number and email address. For the first hour, we line the men and women up opposite one another and rotate every four minutes so that each person gets the chance to meet potential mates. Individuals then write down the I.D. number of anyone they would like to see again and hands the cards to the Things To Do Boston staff. We will sort through them and a few days after the event we email any mutual matches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SECRET ADMIRER: During the evening, you may meet that special someone to whom you want to send a message. But, either you did not quite make a match, or you did not have an opportunity to approach him/her. For the three days following the event, you will have the opportunity to email events@thingstodoboston asking us to help you - the Secret Admirer - make a connection. Simply email us:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) The number of the person (the number listed on their name tag)&lt;br /&gt;2) Your email address&lt;br /&gt;3) A private message for that person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though we will respect the persons privacy and not send you their email address or other contact information, we will pass your email along (with your email address and other contact information you provide) and let fate take over.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, stick around for an evening of socializing and complimentary appetizers. There will be a cash bar available throughout the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Attire: Business Casual -no jeans -no sneakers -no hats -etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ages: 21 - 30's&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: The Boston Park Plaza Hotel and Towers&lt;br /&gt;76 Arlington Street&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02116&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $15.00&lt;br /&gt;If purchased by 2/6/09. Limited space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To purchase a ticket go to:&lt;br /&gt;www.thingstodoboston&lt;br /&gt;click on CALENDAR&lt;br /&gt;then on Valentine's Search Singles Party: Four Minute Dating&lt;br /&gt;on that page (on the right) click on BUY&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>7970205</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235000571000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1382</urlname><id>1275022</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Things To Do: BOSTON</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233339311000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Valentine Search Singles Party: Four Minute Dating</name><id>9635474</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234483200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1382/events/9635474/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/9/global_7123657.jpeg</photo_url></item>