<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Should you have a favorite game please bring it; otherwise, you know we're well stocked. You are also welcome to bring a favorite snack for the evening. We'll have plenty to drink.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who have never attended a traditional game night, we usually split up in different rooms or areas to play smaller games of players' choice and then come together for a larger game or two at the end of the night.  However, sometimes we just play large party games for the majority of the evening.  It depends on the mood of the crowd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* You should know that we are a household with cats, but they will be locked up for the evening. The house is also home to a well-behaved one year old, who will obviously not be locked up for the evening, but she will be in bed after the first hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it is a tight. There is generally more parking available toward Orne St., and more parking is available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Members who have been a &amp;quot;no-show&amp;quot; in the last three months will not be permitted to RSVP for this event. Also, please make sure you've paid your second quarter dues.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1274096337000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271959049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Traditional Game Night</name><id>13260171</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273964400000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/13260171/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/1/global_11205793.jpeg</photo_url></item>