<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>***Sunset hike*** This is a nice mostly clifftop hike we'll limit to no more than 3 miles total. We may get a great sunset if the weather cooperates!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start out at the Route 66 parking lot at the western end of Middlefield at 6:30 PM and hike somewhat steeply in places up to the cliffs. Then things mostly level off as we hike the cliffs for a mile or so with occasional decents and ascents. We'll time the hike such that we'll reach a far point and start back along the cliffs and see the sunset (about 7:38 PM) on the way back. The hike should take about 1.5 hours at a pace people can keep up with given the altitude gain at either end of the hike. So, we should be done by no later than about 8 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are good views to the west. Not as good as the views from the shorter Chauncey Peak and its associated cliffs. Higby Mt. is about 300 feet higher than Chauncey Peak. The last time I hiked there we had a good sunset in the hazy skies. This hike is an &amp;quot;out and back&amp;quot; style hike and not the more typical loop hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given that we will be hiking near the top of the cliff in a number of portions, I don't think this hike is advisable for young children. There are alternate paths in these sections where one can be further from the edge of the cliff if it bothers you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no meal plans for the group after this hike given the late end of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;) is the lead on this hike so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No good map is available online.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Bring a flashlight or headlamp as things could get a bit dark on the way back through the forest to the parking lot. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail is well marked up and along the cliffs. The northernmost portion of the trail, which we wont be hiking, goes into the woods and the blue trail blazes are hard to find and follow there to the end of the trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from the Hartford area:&lt;br /&gt;* Take I-91 South &lt;br /&gt;* Take the MIDDLE ST./COUNTRY CLUB RD. exit- EXIT 20 &lt;br /&gt;* At the stop sign turn LEFT onto MIDDLE ST and go only a &lt;br /&gt;hundred yards or so to another stop sign at COUNTRY CLUB RD. &lt;br /&gt;* Turn LEFT (East) onto COUNTRY CLUB RD. crossing I-91.  Go, a &lt;br /&gt;couple of miles to HIGBY RD. which is opposite Moody Elementary &lt;br /&gt;school on the right.&lt;br /&gt;* Turn right onto HIGBY RD, going South) &lt;br /&gt;Go a couple of miles - through a stop sign and to the traffic &lt;br /&gt;light at the intersection with ROUTE 66.&lt;br /&gt;* Turn RIGHT (West) onto ROUTE 66/MERIDEN RD. (It's the first intersection where you can go right.) &lt;br /&gt;* Go what seems like a couple miles - (about 1/2 mile past &lt;br /&gt;Guida's Restaurant which is on the right).  &lt;br /&gt;* On the right will be a small parking area at the TRAILHEAD.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1155939665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kevin S's Hike at Higby Mountain in Middlefield CT</name><id>5085046</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1156458600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5085046/</event_url></item>