<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>575 S Water St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.817259</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401- 861-9007</phone><name>The Hot Club</name><city>Providence</city><id>937975</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.401745</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series! This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurants bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: The Hot Club on S. Water St. (this is the area where Whiskey Republic and Lola's is across from Narragansett Electric and infront of the hurricane barrier on the water.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE HOT CLUB!!! Okay, so its a notorious Providence institution and since it feels like the very last vestiges of summer, I'm feeling the need to be outside as much as possible before the cool season hits. I know we go here a lot, but honestly, it's always a good time and so very worth repeating! As many of you know already its a great spot, especially out on the deck. So for those who do and those who don't, its worth knowing about and let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there! Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing some kind of scarf (or jacket), but we're hard to miss - look for us on the outside deck!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316556472000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315617225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - The Hot Club!</name><id>32958682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316469600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/32958682/</event_url></item>