<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I had a conversation with a friend of mine about learning English. His first language isn't English, but he speaks it well. He'd like to speak it better, but he's found that after he reached a certain level, people stopped correcting him. He feels like he's reached a plateau and he'd like to go beyond it. After we had the conversation, I corrected him on some small things - things that I wouldn't normally mention, but he specifically said that he wanted to know where to improve. This made him happy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I’m trying an experiment.  This dinner is for other people like my friend - people who manage well-enough in English but would like to improve, and for other people like me who are happy to help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this dinner:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;There will be equal numbers of people who are native speakers of English and people who are non-native speakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;People will talk about whatever they want to talk about, same as at any other dinner, except that in addition to whatever is the topic of conversation the native speakers are also supposed to give feedback about English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;In order to ensure that there is an equal number of native speakers and non-native speakers, you can’t actually register for the event, you can only put yourself on the waiting list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I’ll move people off the waiting list in pairs – one native speaker and one non-native speaker.  (Possibly not in the order in which they signed up.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I’ll contact you by email before I move you off the waiting list, so there won’t be any surprises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I popped in to the restaurant on a Saturday to check the noise level.  If that Saturday is typical, it should be fine for conversation.  I also made the reservation a bit late, in order to avoid the busiest time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE (9July09):&lt;br /&gt;More native speakers than non-native speakers have put themselves on the waiting list for this dinner.  Some people also might cancel between now &amp;amp; Saturday.  If you're interested, don't be put off by the fact that there is a waiting list, particularly if you are a non-native speaker.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for "the Euro group"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>A</member_name><member_id>8074607</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1290133561000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245802118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner with a side of English</name><id>10720529</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247358600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/10720529/</event_url></item>