<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1st Floor</address_2><address_1>45 Carelton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>795736</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086600</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>**the door to the building gets locked somewhere between 6:30-7:00, but for the 1st 15 minutes we wil have someone posted at the door to let people in. If you arrive later than that, it should be easy to get in as there is a lot of foot traffic of people coming and going. If you can't get in just call Ben, at 617-997- 3545 or Becki at 818-523-2518 From the T: Take the red-line to Kendall Square station. If you're coming outbound (from Park Street), exit at the gates at the front of the train. Cross the street. (The street will be behind you if you take the escalator.) Proceed behind the T entrance on the other side to the street behind. Building E25 is the brick building across the street. If you're coming inbound (from Centra Square), exit at the gates at the rear of the train. Take the stairs or elevator straight up. Proceed to the street in front of you. Building E25 is the brick building across the street. Driving directions from Mass Ave.: If you are coming from Boston or Memorial Drive, take a right at the first right past Memorial Drive This is Vassar Street. If you are coming from Cambridge and points west, take a left onto Vassar Street This will be past Central Square about 2 blocks before the river. If you get to the river, you've gone too far. From Vassar, take the first right onto Main Street. Go through two signals then turn right onto far. From Vassar, take the first right onto Main Street. Go through two signals then turn right onto Hayward. You may park in the parking lot on the right side of Hayward. A MIT parking permit is NOT required in the evening, but please do not park in the spaces marked Medical. Exit the parking lot at the rear (opposite from where you entered). Building E25 will be directly across the street. Once you enter, Room 119 is just past the stairs on the right. There is a suggested donation of $1.00 that goes towards site fees. Hayward. You may park in the parking lot on the right side of Hayward. A MIT parking permit is NOT required in the evening, but please do not park in the spaces marked Medical. Exit the parking lot at the rear (opposite from where you entered). Building E25 will be directly across the street. Once you enter rear (opposite from where you entered). Building E25 will be directly across the street. Once you enter, Room 119 is just past the stairs on the right. There is a suggested donation of $1.00 that goes towards site fees. Room 119 is just past the stairs on the right. There is a suggested donation of $1.00 that goes towards site Room 119 is just past the stairs on the right. There is a suggested donation of $1.00 that goes towards site fees&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>see below</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Becki</member_name><member_id>4147212</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265997638000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265406335000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2-8?  No, it is never 2-L8 to play games</name><id>12530722</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265673600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/12530722/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>