<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.855291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978.388.1907</phone><name>Our Neighbors Table</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1411475</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.932291</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Let's help by sorting the food for their May Post Office food drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were asked to go back again and help out!!  May 12, is the day that the Post Office has their food drive. in Amesbury, we will be unloading the trucks when they come back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They will accept kids that are 11 or 12 and up, as long as mom or dad is there to supervise. The stairs into the cellar are a little dicey, so they don’t like taking kids much younger than that. We may be sorting the food in the cellar again so either way remember to come prepared with gloves as you never know what the weather will.  When we did this in November we sorted in the cellar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note: Where we are meeting can be a little hard to find there is a driveway just past the library take that left and follow to the end that is where we are meeting.  If you go past this entrance take the next left, it ends up in the same place.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is: 978-304-2811.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event. If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer".&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Come back to the site and change your RSVP, if your plans change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank You, &lt;br /&gt;

 Donna&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the parking lot waiting, if you arrive late come to the cellar stairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336957194000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333745867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Helping out at Our Neighbors Table</name><id>59555712</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336834800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/59555712/</event_url></item>