<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Serious about owning your own business, have an idea, maybe want to learn more about other ways to develop wealth and income?&amp;nbsp; As the President &amp;amp; CEO of Internet retailer company, an online health and wellness site,&amp;nbsp; A Martial arts school, A Real Estate Investment Partner Group, an few others, let me/us teach you how to create an ongoing/continual income.&amp;nbsp; We have taught many, MANY folks how to create wealth through revolutionary technology on the internet, through workshops, seminars&amp;nbsp;and the power of people, I have helped thousands of entrepreneurs build successful businesses across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But now it's time to create another venture, A Young Entrepreneurs Group of men and women who want to take it to another level. Learn this technology and then learn to teach others the same exciting business of wealth. Come and learn, bring a note book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;M~W~T is building a business entrepreneurial site that seeks to educate aspiring and established business owners on business, leadership &amp;amp; management, success, social media and relevant issues in today&amp;rsquo;s business world. Entrepreneurs turn to M~W~T to seek advice, discuss relevant issues, business and new social media trends. Additionally readers get to follow Me/Us/You on this journey to the top with these businesses that we build together!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between the age of 18-29&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sharp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Savvy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creative&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Focused&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had or are in College or have had owned your own business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then you should be at this group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOW, this is a Free Event, No Cost, Provided you bring a guest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP Today, Feel free to contact me with any questions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony Pasquale &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;AJP&lt;/span&gt; Enterprise &lt;br /&gt;

Mindful Wealth Thinking &lt;br /&gt;

Master Instructor &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

"Live with Purpose and Passion Everyday" !&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>With Desire, Focus and a Plan!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334104045000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New to Network Marketings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1342126</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Network Marketing Support Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331138037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Get Ready to Learn how to Develop many Streams of Wealth.</name><id>55363532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334098800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group/events/55363532/</event_url></item>