<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1400 George's Hill Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06488</zip><lat>41.431843</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 264-5678</phone><name>Kettletown State Park</name><city>Southbury</city><id>936953</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.201523</lon></venue><fee><label>Parking (Weekend Rate)</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per car</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This hike will be at Kettletown State Park, near Southbury.  The purpose of this hike is a little bit different from your typical hike, as we will be geocaching!  There are a number of geocaches in the park, and we can decide on the particular routes we want to take when we get there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A listing of geocaches in the park can be found here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.geocaching.com/seek/gmnearest.aspx?lat=41.427617&amp;amp;lon=-73.201417" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.geocaching...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info about the park can be found here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325230&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;CT State Parks:Kettletown State Park&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will park at the parking area located just down the road from the main entrance.  If you go to the files section, you will see a PDF with a map of the park.  If you have any questions, email me (Beth Rawson) via the link for my name under Assistant Organizers to the left.  Before the hike, I will email my phone number to any yes and maybe RSVPs so if you need to call, you can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.geocaching.com" target="_blank"&gt;Official Geocaching Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Geocaching is one of the best ways that I have found to find new and exciting places to visit, especially when you are unfamiliar with a place.  Below are some of the commonly asked questions about what geocaching is and how the sport works.  More information can be found at the link above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; What is Geocaching?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Geocaching is an entertaining adventure game for gps users. Participating in a cache hunt is a good way to take advantage of the wonderful features and capability of a gps unit. The basic idea is to have individuals and organizations set up caches all over the world and share the locations of these caches on the internet. GPS users can then use the location coordinates to find the caches. Once found, a cache may provide the visitor with a wide variety of rewards. All the visitor is asked to do is if they get something they should try to leave something for the cache. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; What is usually in a cache?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A cache can come in many forms but the first item should always be the logbook. In its simplest form a cache can be just a logbook and nothing else. The logbook contains information from the founder of the cache and notes from the cache's visitors. The logbook can contain much valuable, rewarding, and entertaining information. A logbook might contain information about nearby attractions, coordinates to other unpublished caches, and even jokes written by visitors. If you get some information from a logbook you should give some back. At the very least you can leave the date and time you visited the cache.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larger caches may consist of a waterproof plastic bucket placed tastefully within the local terrain. The bucket will contain the logbook and any number of more or less valuable items. These items turn the cache into a true treasure hunt. You never know what the founder or other visitors of the cache may have left there for you to enjoy. Remember, if you take something, its only fair for you to leave something in return. Items in a bucket cache could be: Maps, books, software, hardware, CD's, videos, pictures, money, jewelry, tickets, antiques, tools, games, etc. It is recommended that items in a bucket cache be individually packaged in a clear zipped plastic bag to protect them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Where are caches found?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location of a cache can be very entertaining indeed. As many say, location, location, location! The location of a cache demonstrates the founder's skill and possibly even daring. A cache located on the side of a rocky cliff accessible only by rock climbing equipment may be hard to find. An underwater cache may only be accessed by scuba. Other caches may require long difficult hiking, orienteering, and special equipment to get to. Caches may be located in cities both above and below ground, inside and outside buildings. The skillful placement of a small logbook in an urban environment may be quite challenging to find even with the accuracy of a gps. That little logbook may have a hundred dollar bill in it or a map to greater treasure. It could even contain clues or riddles to solve that may lead to other caches. Rich people could have fun with their money by making lucrative caches that could be better than winning the lottery when you find it. Just hope that the person that found the cache just before you left a real big prize! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***DO NOT TRY TO PAY THE PARKING FEE VIA PAYPAL!  PAY AT THE GATE.***&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184076480000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182616329000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Geocaching Hike to Kettletown State Park</name><id>5926019</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183903200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5926019/</event_url></item>