<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>82 Lansdowne St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347157</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 351-7001&amp;#8206;</phone><name>Game On</name><city>Boston</city><id>668982</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097890</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives Meetup Group has invited us to join them in watching the Cubs and Red Sox play at Game On in Boston. Come on out and root for your Cubbies! (If you are not a Cubs fan, you are still invited.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Here is the description from the Red Sox Natives site:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Please join the Red Sox Natives on Saturday, June 16 at 7:00pm at GAME ON! for an Exclusive Natives Event as we Watch the Red Sox take on the Chicago Cubs from Wrigley Field with our Invited Guests The Chicago Sports Club of New England Meetup. Robert and a bunch of Cubs fans will be joining us at GAME ON!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Please feel free to arrive between 6:30pm and 7:00pm for pre-game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Game Time is 7:15pm from Chicago.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Red Sox Natives and GAME ON! Employees Deanna and Sonja have given us a Reserved Section on the Ground Floor by the windows behind the servers station. The volume will be turned up. This is also a PRIME People Watching spot!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;The full menu will be available for ordering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;There is a Cash Bar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Please remember to maintain your own bar/food tab and tip your servers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;There is no event fee, however we will require a minimum number of Natives to RSVP in advance for this to take place. We reserve the right to cancel this event due to lack of interest. It would be great if a bunch of Natives attending the Davis Square Pub Crawl could stay sober enough to join us during the game! You know who you all are.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Please RSVP ASAP with your approximate ETA and invite friends, guests and Cubs fans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;As an added bonus, the Red Sox Batting Cages may be available for you to take batting practice. This was a huge hit at our last GAME ON! event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Also Red Sox Native Mario who will be in Chicago with several others and will be calling in via Skype with a live report from the game!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;We have also invited one of our Sponsors Coach Henry to attend and try to sign you up for his Baseball school.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Do not miss your chance to enjoy the company of a bunch of long suffering Cubs fans. Soon it will be their turn to win as long as Theo Epstein does not sign any big Free Agents to long term contracts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;See you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert</member_name><member_id>4121028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344439459000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ex-Midwesterners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Midwesterners</urlname><id>545362</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ex-Midwesterners Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339631473000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Watching Red Sox vs Cubs at Game On</name><id>69071992</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339887600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Midwesterners/events/69071992/</event_url></item>