<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Philip Glass is a mainstay of quirky, edgy American movies.  His list of films includes:  The Fog of War, No Reservations, Koyaanisqatsi, The Thing Blue Line, The Truman Show, The Secret Agent, The Hours, and the Illusionist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MFA is showing Glass: A Portrait of Philip in Twelve Parts by Scott Hicks (Australia/US, 2007, 115 min.). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what they have to say about the movie:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the writer and director of the seven-time Academy Award-nominated film, Shine, comes a uniquely intimate portrait of this virtuoso musician. For eighteen months, Hicks follows Glass across three continents with unprecedented access to his working process, family life, spiritual teachers, and long-time collaborators. Filmed by Hicks himself, the result is a unique glimpse into the private world of a surprising and complex man, and a mosaic portrait of one of the greatest-and at times most controversial-musicians of our era&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look here for another review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.glassthemovie.com/Site/Reviews.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.glassthemo...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll go to lunch somewhere near the mfa - possibly Northwestern, possibly the shwarma place.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be on the side holding a Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216651582000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214310191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Glass, A Portrait of Philip in Twelve Parts</name><id>8203701</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216478700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8203701/</event_url></item>