<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Wattaquadock Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.430644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>http://www.nashobawinery.com</phone><name>Nashoba Valley Winery</name><city>Bolton</city><id>731361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.614016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This festival highlights the hand crafted micro-brewed beers of Thomas Knight.   Relax, sit back, and enjoy some bluegrass music by Southern Rail.  Stroll by the pavilion, visit JAAS snack shack to purchase a cider donut or a caramel apple, savor the smells of barbecue provided by the chef’s from J’s.  And finally, take a tour of the winery or simply taste many of the award winning wines Sign up for the winery tour in front of the wine shoppe at the information table.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Nashoba Valley Winery:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the heart of Massachusetts apple country, Nashoba Valley Winery is a stunning hilltop orchard overlooking the charming town of Bolton.   Always growing and ever-beautiful, we are open daily throughout the year, with the exception of The Fourth of July, Thanksgiving Day, Christmas Day and New Year's Day. Since first producing superior fruit wines in 1978, Nashoba Valley Winery has earned wide acclaim as a pioneering winery orchard and a premier destination for visitors seeking excellent wine, exquisitely prepared food, and a gorgeous country setting.  The family-owned orchard, winery &amp;amp; restaurant, set on 52 rolling acres, boasts a state-of-the art wine-making and distillation facility, an exceptional wine and gift shoppe, a brewery, and a gourmet restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over 100 national and international medals to its credit and accolades from such noteworthy publications as Boston Magazine, Wine Enthusiast, Cooking Light, Food &amp;amp; Wine,  The Yankee Magazine? 2003 Editors Choice, and &amp;quot;Community Newspaper Company 2004 Readers Choice Award, Nashoba Valley Winery is the ultimate destination for any wine connoisseur.  We take the art of winemaking seriously.  And with over 20 varieties of wines, a variety of hand crafted beers and distilled spirits, Nashoba Valley is dedicated to quality and is recognized as a premium producer.  From its beginning until today, Nashoba Valley remains a family owned winery with our focus on quality and value at the forefront of all we do.  Plan a visit to a truly unique American farm and learn why Nashoba Valley was selected as one of the ultimate destination places on the east coast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nashobawinery.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nashobawin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please indicate in your RSVP if you are interested in carpooling from Nashua.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a foil balloon attached to my chair.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287941082000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283777054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bluegrass and Brews @ Nashoba Valley Winery </name><id>14671148</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287936000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/14671148/</event_url></item>