<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Independence Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.619999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Radisson Hotel and Conference Center - Merrimack Room</name><city>Chelmsford</city><id>344860</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360001</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Massachusetts Republican:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Massachusetts Federation of Young Republicans (&amp;quot;MFYR&amp;quot;) will be holding its' State Convention on Saturday, September 29, 2007 at the Radisson Hotel in Chelmsford, Massachusetts (10 Independence Drive).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our State Convention we will be electing our 2007 - 2009 officers, and we are soliciting candidates to run for all our Executive Board positions. We are making a concerted effort to bring in new blood to our organization, and to bring young voters into the GOP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MFYR Board positions that are up for election are Chairman, Vice-Chairman, National Committeeman, National Committeewoman, Secretary and Treasurer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are also numerous appointed positions, and we are looking for people to start and join all our local clubs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have YR clubs in Greater Boston, Greater Worcester, and the South Shore. A new Southcoast(Fall River/New Bedford and surrounding towns) chapter will be starting soon. We are looking for GOP leaders to help us start clubs in other underserved areas (e.g. Western MA, Cape Cod, North Shore, Greater Lowell/Lawrence).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to our elections, we will be spending the afternoon helping the GOP candidate in the special election in the 5th Congressional district, and we hope Republicans from around the state will come to Chelmsford to help us capture this winnable seat. We are planning other activities, including our first ever GOP Iron Chef BBQ/political rally.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details on the agenda for the weekend will be forthcoming shortly, but we wanted to spread the word now that we are open for business, and doing things in a new way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in running for any position, please contact me directly, and I can provide more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the interest of full disclosure, I will be running on that day for a full term as Chair&lt;br /&gt;so we can continue our work to build the MA GOP amongst young voters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regards,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Wheeler&lt;br /&gt;Acting Chair,&lt;br /&gt;MA Federation of Young Republicans&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfyr.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfyr.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mfyr.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick</member_name><member_id>472135</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541941000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>(young) Republicans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>youngrepublicans-43</urlname><id>170358</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston (Young) Republicans Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186977218000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MA Federation of Young Republicans State Convention</name><id>6170654</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191074400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/youngrepublicans-43/events/6170654/</event_url></item>