<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is not a movie but I thought some of you might be interested in a different kind of event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a FREE event.  No tickets are required.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's your chance to experience opera with the moonlit Connecticut River as a backdrop. This year's opera night will feature a Venetian Carnivale atmosphere in downtown Hartford, as seven talented opera singers perform with conductor Brian Sparks and the Hartford Festival Orchestra. You'll be greeted on arrival by professional street performers, and invited to enjoy delicious Italian food and wine before settling down for an evening of popular arias under the stars. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The theme for the evening's concert is Love Triumphs or in Italian - Amore Trionfa ! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Excerpts from four main operas will be played- &lt;br /&gt;Don Giovanni by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart &lt;br /&gt;L'Elisir d'Amore by Gaetano Donizetti &lt;br /&gt;Madame Buttery by Giacomo Puccini &lt;br /&gt;La Cenerentola by Gioachino Rossini &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.riverfront.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.riverfront.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.riverfront...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  the event starts at 7:30 but let's meet no later than 7 so we can find a place to sit.  I'll meet you on the walkway over to the park close to the CT Science Center.  If you're late, just look around for me or call me on my cell phone at 203-812-0705.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking for Mortensen Riverfront Plaza&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available at the Morgan Street Garage, Constitution Plaza Garage, and other area garages for a fee. Alternate parking includes on-street parking in Hartford, or you can park in East Hartford and take the short walk over the Founders Bridge Promenade.  Visit the Hartford Parking Authority website for more complete information at &lt;a href="http://www.hartford.gov/parking/map.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hartford.g...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See below</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217286234000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214681188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opera al Fresco at the Connecticut River in Hartford</name><id>8235336</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217113200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/8235336/</event_url></item>