<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>62 Dunham Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.574697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 232-7200</phone><name>North Shore Music Theater</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1296765</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.868823</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>ANNOUNCING our next theatre night at the North Shore Music Theatre!!  We once again have access to 1/2 priced tickets, for this performance.  I have gotten word from our meetup member Jeane, who has seen this play elsewhere, that it was very enjoyable!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    North Shore Music Theatre - The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;    We are reverting back to a FRIDAY night performance for this particular production, because many Saturdays. in Aug. are already filled up with meetup activities.  This date seems best, as the following weekend is Labor Day weekend, and the play ends it's run THAT very weekend.&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;    Actual curtain time is at 8pm, but we can plan to meet in the lobby at 7:30ish.  Further details to follow.&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;    Call the Box Office directly to pay for your ticket: 978-232-7200. You should reference my name (Jill) and the Merrimack Group. Carol, who works in the Box Office, has been handling our group ticket sales so far this season.  She has set aside 15 tickets for our group for the Friday evening, Aug. 22nd performance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Hope to see you there!!  ~~~~~  Jill  ~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;    The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    August 12 - 31&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    This one got a lot of buzz on Broadway!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Developed in the Berkshires and a long-running hit on Broadway, this Tony® Award-winning musical comedy follows six young people in the throes of puberty, overseen by grown-ups who barely managed to escape childhood themselves, learn that winning isn't everything and that losing doesn't necessarily make you a loser. This tuneful, offbeat and at times heartwarming show offers audience members the opportunity (strictly voluntary) to become part of the action as on-stage spellers. So get out your dictionaries, and get ready for an evening filled with humor and heart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    DO YOU WANT TO BE A GUEST SPELLER? Get to the show early and look for the NSMT staff in the lobby wearing red shirts to sign up for your chance to be one of the 4 guest spellers who join in the on-stage fun for each performance. Sign up starts one hour before the show, people can sign up anytime up until 10 minutes before the start of the show. The winning participants are announced 10 minutes before the start of the show. &lt;br /&gt;Recommended for ages 13 and up.  Running Time:  1 hour, 45 mins.  (no intermission) &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;Book by Rachel Sheinkin.&lt;br /&gt;    Music &amp;amp; Lyrics by William Finn.&lt;br /&gt;    A co-production with Barrington Stage Company&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219620842000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218499293000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> North Shore Music Theatre - The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee       </name><id>8524246</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219447800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/8524246/</event_url></item>