<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's start gathering around 6:45, we are going to want to head in for seats by 7, movie time is at 7:30 for the IMAX show.    Make sure when pre-purchasing the tickets that you select the IMAX show.   It costs more for the IMAX version of movies, but I think that this movie will be visually interesting enough to merit the extra expense.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: July 16, 2010 (conventional and IMAX theaters)&lt;br /&gt;Studio: Warner Bros. Pictures&lt;br /&gt;Director: Christopher Nolan&lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Christopher Nolan&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Leonardo DiCaprio, Ken Watanabe, Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Marion Cotillard, Ellen Page, Tom Hardy, Cillian Murphy, Tom Berenger, Michael Caine&lt;br /&gt;Genre: Action, Sci-Fi&lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG-13 (for sequences of violence and action throughout)&lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://inceptionmovie.warnerbros.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://inceptionmovie...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Acclaimed filmmaker Christopher Nolan directs an international cast in an original sci-fi actioner that travels around the globe and into the intimate and infinite world of dreams. Dom Cobb (Leonardo DiCaprio) is a skilled thief, the absolute best in the dangerous art of extraction, stealing valuable secrets from deep within the subconscious during the dream state, when the mind is at its most vulnerable. Cobb's rare ability has made him a coveted player in this treacherous new world of corporate espionage, but it has also made him an international fugitive and cost him everything he has ever loved. Now Cobb is being offered a chance at redemption. One last job could give him his life back but only if he can accomplish the impossible—inception. Instead of the perfect heist, Cobb and his team of specialists have to pull off the reverse: their task is not to steal an idea but to plant one. If they succeed, it could be the perfect crime. But no amount of careful planning or expertise can prepare the team for the dangerous enemy that seems to predict their every move. An enemy that only Cobb could have seen coming. This summer, your mind is the scene of the crime.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Movie Group Badge.  If movie is upstairs, I will grab a table near the windows at the tope of the escalator, if it is dowstairs I will be near the ropes by the concession stand,</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825608000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275244238000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inception</name><id>13640090</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279406700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/13640090/</event_url></item>