<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/2/a/event_20732810.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Please join us for our monthly &lt;strong&gt;Portland Trading Post&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;swap event. &amp;nbsp;Trading Post events (&lt;strong&gt;now happening in the Local Sprouts Cafe after they close on Sunday&lt;/strong&gt;) are free and open to all (bring a friend!). You can really bring anything to trade: &amp;nbsp;handmade items, tools, books, plants, seedlings, seeds, preserved or fresh produce, etc. are all welcome at Portland Trading Post. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments area of this page to chat in advance about what you might be bringing and/or looking for from others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp;If you are a member of Hour Exchange Portland (&lt;a href="http://www.hourexchangeportland.org/howtojoin.php"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;#65279;&lt;/span&gt;join here if you're no&lt;span&gt;&amp;#65279;&lt;/span&gt;t&lt;/a&gt;) consider bringing more substantial items to trade to time dollar hours! &amp;nbsp;I'll make some "I'll Trade for Time Dollars" table tents for anyone who wants to post one on her/his trading table.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main idea is that we are stepping outside of the cash economy and mutually "gifting" things to each other in a way that turns whatever we have in abundance into a diversity of goodness and good will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The only rules are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No cash changes hands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't start the swapping until everyone's there and has a chance to look around at what's on offer (usually about 15 minutes into the swap, but it's flexible)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can swap with someone or simply "gift" things to each other without taking a return item. Your choice. &amp;nbsp;Make sure you've found a home for all your stuff before you leave (or take home what hasn't been gifted).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you bring a food item with multiple ingredients, pls label.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments area of this page to talk about what you might be bringing or seeking. Food/Snacks/Fiddles/Juggling/Attended Children welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a very relaxed, social atmosphere. &amp;nbsp;Even if you have nothing to trade, feel free to come by just to see what it's all about and meet some members. &amp;nbsp;We are considering combining these with short skill-shares or "show and tell" sessions, too. &amp;nbsp;These are kid-friendly events but in a "keep an eye on your child" sort of way, as the space is also a functioning business with equipment, etc. Join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that gifting and bartering is still something many of us are getting a handle on...it requires different thinking for our society which has been so used to "monetizing" every transaction or product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to &lt;a href="http://www.localsproutscooperative.com/cafe"&gt;Local Sprouts Cafe&lt;/a&gt; for offering their space (after they close on Sunday afternoons!) for the monthly Portland Trading Post events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking for this event is either in the parking lot (free) behind Local Sprouts or on either side of the street in front!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Homa </member_name><member_id>2587064</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aaron Parker</member_name><member_id>6845673</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352768981000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350255722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Trading Post :: Monthly Swap Event</name><id>lccwpyqpbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352667600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/86974682/</event_url></item>