<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>PLEASE  NOTE: These films are screening at Harvard Law School Langdell North  and not  at The Harvard Film Archive. If you are familiar with the Harvard Campus, Harvard Law School Langdell North is  situated past the Science Building towards Mass Ave. Please give yourself some extra time to find the building and room and don't be shy about asking the students for directions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These films are part of this year's Boston Palestinian Film Festival. The feature was shot in 2001 and the three shorts were filmed during this year. There will be an introductory talk by the director of the three shorts, Maryam Monalisa Gharavi, whose series is entitled &lt;b&gt;Inessential (Gaza in Three Pieces)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gaza Strip&lt;/b&gt; USA 2001 74 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gaza Strip&lt;/b&gt; follows a range of people and events following the election of Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon, including the first major armed incursion into &amp;quot;Area A&amp;quot; by IDF forces during this intifada. Almost entirely in a verité style, Gaza Strip is presented without narration and focuses on ordinary Palestinians rather than politicians and pundits. More observation than political argument, Gaza Strip offers a rare look inside the stark realities of Palestinian life and death under Israeli military occupation. Festival Description   Read More Below&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Going to Fish, Going to War&lt;/b&gt; Palestine/USA 6 minutes&lt;br /&gt;This short film records a Gazan fisherman describing the Israeli-imposed economic stranglehold that threatens his livelihood. Once among the proudest and most skilled population within Palestinian society, Gaza’s fishermen are now its poorest. Israel has drastically reduced the nautical miles in which fishermen can make their living, leaving them with nothing to fish and little to do. In this short piece, Hussam al-Habash, a member of the fishermen’s syndicate, describes life under the siege, and common harassment and shooting incidents against Palestinian fishermen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Air Closes In On Us&lt;/b&gt; Palestine/USA 4 minutes&lt;br /&gt;This short film features farmers relating the effects of Israeli blockades on their ability to farm. Long crippled by the effects of Israeli bulldozing, shelling, and sanctions, the farms of Beit Hanoun, located just four miles from Israel, have been shut down. An eerie silence punctuated by occasional Israeli strikes envelops the farm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Mahmoud Family&lt;/b&gt; Palestine/USA 12 minutes&lt;br /&gt;Documents the Mahmouds, a family of seven living in Bureij Refugee Camp. The medical infrastructure in Gaza is unable to adequately support the medical needs of Mounir and his sons. The family tries to live as normal a life as possible, between power cuts and aerial strikes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The films and the discussion by Maryam Monalisa Gharavi should end by 8:15 which will give us time to go to a restaurant afterward. If you can not stay for our talk, please indicate so when you RSVP so I can make a reasonable guess for the group's reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, the films are free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Time Out, London: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gaza Strip is a stretch of land bordering the Mediterranean, measuring a mere 28 miles by four; but it is home to 1.2 million Palestinians (and some 6,000 Israeli settlers). Longley’s film – shot in the spring of 2001 during the second intifada – draws a extraordinary portrait of a country and people under seige, focussing on the (admittedly atypical) exploits of articulate young paper-seller Mohammed Hejazi. If you want to know how it feels to be the victim of Israeli state terrorism, see this film. Footage, included here, of the Khan Yunis ‘black gas’ attack and the testimony of its victims (who suffer spasms and neurological effects untypical of those caused by the usual tear gas bombs) are yet to be accepted as evidence by the Israeli authorities. A vivid view into the nightmare conditions obtaining on this troubled part of the Palestinian diaspora.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Meetup Sign near the front when the films/talk concludes.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222387485000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gaza Strip + 3 Shorts</name><id>8834652</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223416800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8834652/</event_url></item>