<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 South Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.760615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.561.6950</phone><name>West Hartford Public Library</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>942298</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.741979</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The summer series at the WH Main Library focuses on the War of Northern Aggression, also called The War Between the States or the American Civil War. Each Thursday in July view a different movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JULY 29 - SHENANDOAH 1hr. 45min&lt;br /&gt;Jimmy Stewart, Doug McClure, Glenn Corbett, Patrick Wayne, Katharine Ross; Directed by Andrew V. McLaglen Unrated; 1965 -  A  pacifist Virginia farmer (Jimmy Stewart) tries to keep his family out of harm's way during the Civil War. But when Stewart's youngest son is mistakenly imprisoned by Union soldiers, he must make some hard choices.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films start at 5:15PM sharp in the Library Meeting Room, Noah Webster Library, 20 S. Main St. &lt;br /&gt;Park in the Isham Garage and bring your parking ticket to the library for validation. &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the films with your own covered beverage or quiet snack. &lt;br /&gt;Note that the movie may not take up the entire assigned time. We can go out after the movie, many restaurants in the area will be open afterwards. &lt;br /&gt;COST: FREE &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280442204000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275388365000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WH Library Summer Series - CIVIL WAR - Shenandoah</name><id>13654576</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280437200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/13654576/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>