<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Okay, I'm super late in getting it on the calender, but, here is my belated birthday choice for our next read (organization has its privileges :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1- In the Heart of the Sea:&lt;br /&gt;The Tragedy of the Whaleship Essex&lt;br /&gt;By Nathaniel Philbrick&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.nathanielphilbrick.com/heartofthesea/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nathanielp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ordeal of the whaleship Essex was an event as mythic in the nineteenth century as the sinking of the Titanic was in the twentieth. In 1819, the Essex left Nantucket for the South Pacific with twenty crew members aboard. In the middle of the South Pacific the ship was rammed and sunk by an angry sperm whale. The crew drifted for more than ninety days in three tiny whaleboats, succumbing to weather, hunger, disease, and ultimately turning to drastic measures in the fight for survival. Nathaniel Philbrick uses little--known documents-including a long--lost account written by the ship's cabin boy-and penetrating details about whaling and the Nantucket community to reveal the chilling events surrounding this epic maritime disaster. An intense and mesmerizing read, In the Heart of the Sea is a monumental work of history forever placing the Essex tragedy in the American historical canon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come on guys, it's the true story of Moby Dick!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll plan on meeting as usual at the Clear Conscience Cafe, but if you don't see us, and it's super crowded, try the Au Bon Pain kitty corner across Prospect St. at 1100 Mass Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239231887000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234835543000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: In the Heart of the Sea, Nathaniel Philbrick</name><id>9756168</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236639600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/9756168/</event_url></item>