<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Executive Park Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03054</zip><lat>42.843983</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 423-0240</phone><name>Cinemagic Merrimack</name><city>Merrimack</city><id>714982</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.497014</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Let's meet up at 7:15.  This should give us enough time to get our tickets and snack before the 7:30 Show&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Meg Ryan, Annette Bening, Eva Mendes, Jada Pinkett Smith, Debra Messing, Candice Bergen  &lt;br /&gt;Director: Diane English  &lt;br /&gt;Genres: Comedy Drama, Feminist Film, Ensemble Film, Slice of Life  &lt;br /&gt;Runtime:1 hr. 54 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis: Mary Haines (Meg Ryan) is a clothing designer who seems to have it all – a beautiful country home, a rich financier husband, an adorable 11-year-old daughter and a part-time career creating designs for her father’s venerable clothing company. Her best friend, Sylvie Fowler (Annette Bening), leads another enviable life – a happily single editor of a prominent fashion magazine, a possessor of a huge closet of designer clothes and a revered arbiter of taste and style poised on New York’s cutting edge. But when Mary’s husband enters into an affair with Crystal Allen (Eva Mendes), a sultry ‘spritzer girl’ lurking behind the Saks Fifth Avenue perfume counter, all hell breaks loose. Mary and Sylvie’s relationship is tested to the breaking point while their tight-knit circle of friends, including mega-mommy Edie Cohen (Debra Messing) and author Alex Fisher (Jada Pinkett-Smith), all start to question their own friendships and romantic relationships as well....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Preview:&lt;a href="http://" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/premieres/8100523/standardformat/" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.yahoo.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;More information will follow after the Release Date. So, save this date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Meet-up Pin</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte V.</member_name><member_id>3105127</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221952980000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220318863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chick Flick</name><id>8666806</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221779700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8666806/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/e/6/global_5369094.jpeg</photo_url></item>