<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 2-day &amp;amp; 19.25 mile hike on the Appalachian Trail starting just south of North Adams, MA. We will head northbound through North Adams and on up East Mountain into Vermont. As we pass through Clarksburg State Forest and cross the border we enter the Green Mountain National Forest. This part of the AT doubles as part of Vermont's Long Trail. We complete the 1st day's 8 mile hike to the Seth Warner Shelter &amp;amp; Primitive Camping Area where we will spend the night. The trail has generally been upwards so far for most of the trail starting at about 600 ft. &amp;amp; reaching about 2,200 ft at the shelter. The next day we continue the general upward trend for a couple miles &amp;amp; top out at about 3,000 ft. We continue on to Consultation Peak at about 2,800 ft &amp;amp; start a general downward trend past Sucker Pond at 5.75 miles of the 11.25 miles total for that day. We continue on with a gradual decent to about 2,100 ft where we have a rest/lunch at Congdon Shelter at 7.5 miles then gradually back up to 2,500 ft &amp;amp; over Harmon Hill. The final 1.75 miles is gradually downhill with the final .5 mile being steeply downhill to the endpoint on Rte. 9, about 2.8 miles west of Woodford, VT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**5/22 - Sat partly cloudy 70 F; overnight 44 F; Sun partly cloudy 78 F**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet 5/24/08 at 10 AM on the shoulder of Pattison Rd. south of North Adams, MA. We'll hike with rest stops the 8 miles to the lean-to for the night. I figure we'll reach the lean-to at about 7 PM at the latest (more likely 6 PM). We'll have dinner &amp;amp; set up for the night by sundown at about 8 PM. We'll get up &amp;amp; ready somewhat early the second day given the 11.25 miles we need to cover &amp;amp; wanting to do that at a slower pace. We should be hiking by 7:30 AM &amp;amp; reach the endpoint by about 7:30 PM, 5/25/08. We would then shuttle back to the beginning to pick up vehicles. We then could hit a local establishment for dinner before heading home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, &amp;amp; individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike &amp;amp; may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservitive with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equiped we could come in earlier than I estimated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;br /&gt;* Backpack -suitable to hold sleeping bag and all other gear and food, overall weight should be no more than 30 - 35 lbs&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable &amp;amp; broken in &lt;br /&gt;* 2 pair wool socks&lt;br /&gt;* Hat -something good in the rain and/or sun&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cold mornings &amp;amp; possibly hot afternoons, avoid cotton as it stays wet.&lt;br /&gt;* Comfortable underwear -no chaffing!&lt;br /&gt;* Rain poncho/jacket -essential! -rain pants optional&lt;br /&gt;* 3 season sleeping bag -packed&lt;br /&gt;* Bug spay -must have&lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp -or flashlight, fresh batteries&lt;br /&gt;* 2 quart water min. -strongly suggest bringing a water filter to restock on water&lt;br /&gt;* Trail meals -2 lunches, 1 dinner, 1 breakfast. High energy meals should be planned. Only meals time to cook are dinner 1st day &amp;amp; breakfast 2nd day.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks &amp;amp; electrolytes -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, GU energy gel, Gatoraide drink powder, etc.&lt;br /&gt;* Toilet paper -some in plastic sandwhich bag, nothing else may be available when you need it&lt;br /&gt;* Backpack First Aid kit&lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;* Compass&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking cookstove -if cooking&lt;br /&gt;* Something to sleep in -PJ's or shorts and T, etc.&lt;br /&gt;* Matches -if using cookstove&lt;br /&gt;* Games or reading for night activity&lt;br /&gt;* Tent&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling but it is advised to call Kevin S (number in RSVP) so he knows you would like to try to carpool. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so all questions should be directed to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT hike trailhead &amp;amp; parking on shoulder of Pattison Rd. just south of North Adams, MA :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/440+Pattison+rd.+North+Adams+ma/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the ending location on Rte. 9 about 2.8 miles west of Woodford, VT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/2500+Vt+Route+9+woodford+vt/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not sure what vehicle I'll have at the starting point. Look for 6'2" guy &amp; you have my picture on the hiking site.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212007512000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>This segment of the AT is starting to be more of a challenge as we head north and to higher altitudes (start 600 ft, high 3,000 ft). AT hiking with an overnight at a lean-to and the lovely Green Mountains of VT! :-)</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210828087000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike/campout on the AT from North Adams MA to Woodford Hollow VT</name><id>7942653</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211637600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7942653/</event_url></item>