<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>533 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.354057</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-350-5555</phone><name>Felt Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>796302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062321</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=563324866#!/event.php?eid=156491411075335" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=563324866#!/event.php?eid=156491411075335&lt;/a&gt;

Bonjour,
 
The Consulate General of France and its francophone partners is organizing “Mais Oui!,”  the first soirée designed with the college students and young professionals of Boston in mind,  at Felt (533 Washington Street) on Wednesday, March 16th . We’ve planned two different ambiances on two levels:
 
-Starting at 9pm, The Chicken Thieves (a group formed by Julien Machet and other students at the Berklee College of Music) will fill the lower level with jazzy music in a lounge atmosphere of munching on hors d’oeuvres, enjoying cocktails and chatting with new friends and old friends alike.
 
-Upstairs beginning at 10pm, the music heats up with DJ Jean Michel (shipped to Boston straight from Nikki Beach Club in New York) to get you dancing to the beat of French pop with a truly French touch.
 
It will be an evening of elegance and fun, a chance to socialize with French, Americans, and other ‘internationals’ from the area!
 
We hope you’ll join us on March 16th at Felt! 
 
We’d also love you to pass this information along to your friends, whether Francophile or just looking to share in such a festive occasion!
 
For more information, don’t hesitate to call us at: 617-832-4466 
Consulat Général de France à Boston
 
Felt Club Boston  533 Washington Street  in Boston 
Wednesday March 16  -  From 9pm to 2am
 
 T stations:  -Chinatown (orange line) 1min
                  -Downtown crossing (red and orange line) 2min
Parking: Validated parking discount - LaFayette Parking Garage One LaFayette Avenue, Boston
(Directly across from Felt) - $10 all night after 4:00pm - Must get validation from Felt
Felt Club Boston
533 Washington Street
Wednesday March 16
From 9pm to 2am
 
--------
 
Le Consulat Général de France et ses partenaires francophones organisent  "Mais Oui!", le mercredi 16 mars, la première soirée à destination des étudiants et des jeunes professionnels de Boston. Au programme deux ambiances sur deux niveaux :  
 
-Dès 21 heures, The Chicken Thieves (goupe formé par Julien Machet et d'autres étudiants de Berklee College of Music)
distillera une musique jazzy. Ambiance lounge pour papoter, tablées pour grignoter, cocktails pour se rencontrer.
 
-Et à l'étage et à partir de dix heures, avec Jean Michel, DJ  (résidant du Nikki Beach Club à New York),
la musique s'emballe pour vous faire danser au son de la French Touch et pop française. 
 
Une soirée élégante et chaleureuse, une occasion de socialiser entre français, américains et "Internationaux".
 
Nous espérons que vous pourrez vous joindre à nous le 16 mars au Felt!
 
Nous vous serions  très reconnaissants de bien vouloir faire suivre cette information à  vos amis francophiles ou aimant tout simplement partager un rare moment convivial et festif.  
N’hésitez pas à nous contacter pour de plus amples informations : 617-832-4466     
 
 
T stations:  -Chinatown (orange line) 1min
                 -Downtown crossing (red and orange line) 2min
 
Parking: Validated parking discount  - LaFayette Parking Garage One LaFayette Avenue, Boston
(Directly across from Felt) - $10 all night after 4:00pm - Must get validation from Felt</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300327718000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>The Consulate General of France and its francophone partners is organizing “Mais Oui!,”  the first soirée designed with the college students and young professionals of Boston in mind,  at Felt (533 Washington Street) on Wednesday, March 16th . 
</why><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>voulezvous</urlname><id>541017</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Voulez-vous français Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299793209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Dance!</name><id>16876085</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300323600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/voulezvous/events/16876085/</event_url></item>