<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This project from the book Kaleidoscope,(edited by Suzanne Simanaitis), has been a favorite one with our Meetup members.&amp;nbsp; I will be guiding you through the project, "Mail Art to the Self" by Juliana Coles, which is a wonderful exercise in exploring your creative process.&amp;nbsp; It's made up of&amp;nbsp; timed activities: with paint, collage, stamping, scribbling; with images, words and patterns.&amp;nbsp; It's exhilarating, hectic, inspirational, frustrating...and FUN!&amp;nbsp; It's a perfect project for those who want to free the inner child, to relinquish control, and discover their creative potential!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll provide most of the materials and tools. You will need:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* 15 glossy images (photos, pictures from magazines, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* 15 non-glossy images (pictures from old books, newspapers, puzzle books; sheet music, old maps, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'd also suggest:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* two or three favorite rubber stamps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* a good permanent black stamp pad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* scissors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* large glue stick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* brayer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* permanent marker (black sharpie or suchlike is good)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if you arrive with only some, or none of the above, we will have extra.&amp;nbsp; We'll also allow some time for you to find images from our extensive collection of old books, magazines and other ephemera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and join us for an afternoon of creative enjoyment!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/strong&gt; Sunday, June 10 from 1:00 pm to ???? (Really, we'll stay as late as anybody wants to stay!) The first few hours are the most important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom. Dinner in or out, if people are interested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; $20 to help defray the cost of Studio rental and provided materials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/strong&gt; Any member of the NE ATC+ Meetup and up to two guests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt; These smaller sessions are often full with a waiting list. Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. Please RSVP for your guests as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Your own art kit (scissors, glue sticks, x-acto knife, ruler, pencil, pens and markers) will be good to have along. &lt;strong&gt;(Optional)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;See the list above&lt;/em&gt;. Basic tools and supplies -- Paint, brushes, scissors, glue, tape, some rubber stamps. -- are also available for your use. Even if you show up empty-handed, we can get you started on the project.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; In the unlikely event that we need to cancel---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 36&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>emelengy</member_name><member_id>4250560</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310415084000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309283237000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Mail Art to the Self" from the book Kaleidoscope</name><id>23839511</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310317200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/23839511/</event_url></item>