<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Harvard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-459-5145</phone><name>Dudley House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>382297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's nearly that time of year again...Canadian Thanksgiving is in two weeks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, the Canadian Meet-up Group in Boston have been invited to join the Harvard Grad Canadian Club for what we hope becomes an annual feast of food and general Canadian good cheer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Monday 8 October, starting at 6pm&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Dudley House main dining hall (at the corner of Harvard Yard across from the T stop and the Holyoke centre)&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:.... Canadian Thanksgiving is the biggest event on the Canadian Club calendar. So we're looking for tons of help to make sure the event is a big success for the 100-200 people who will show up for food and fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Right now we're looking for volunteers to cook - turkeys, mashed potatoes, vegetarian dishes, and dessert.  If you could help with any of these things, that would be wonderful!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will supply the turkeys, but we need your cooking skills and your ovens. We need you.  Only your turkey-cooking efforts can turn cold, clammy, raw turkey into steaming, aromatic, saliva-inducing, cooked turkey dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only your efforts can guarantee that everyone will achieve gastronomic contentment at the Thanksgiving party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please volunteer if you can help!  Email Ben (bglee@fas.harvard.edu).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are in Boston for Thanksgiving, then you should definitely come and enjoy the food and festivities.  All spouses, non-Canadian friends and non-Harvardians who would like to join us are welcome.  Spread the word to everyone you know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Grad Canadian Club /&lt;br /&gt;Canadian Expatriates in Boston Meetup Group&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew</member_name><member_id>2881088</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192059591000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190694410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canadian Thanksgiving - October 8</name><id>6422620</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191880800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/6422620/</event_url></item>