<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Madison: Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa  11     High   1:54 AM     5.0   5:27 AM     Set  9:29 AM      89&lt;br /&gt;    11      Low   8:02 AM     0.2   8:24 PM    Rise 10:31 PM&lt;br /&gt;    11     High   2:22 PM     5.0&lt;br /&gt;    11      Low   8:22 PM     0.6&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF BAD WEATHER OR NOT GOOD ENOUGH, THEN ITS RESCHEDULED TO MAYBE SUNDAY..HAVE TO SEE CLOSER TO THE DAY..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS LOCATION HAS SOME RIVER AND SOME OCEAN paddling areas DEPENDING ON WEATHER CONDITIONS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Partly cloudy, with a high near 75. South wind between 3 and 10 mph.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Night: Showers and thunderstorms likely between 9pm and 3am, then a chance of showers. Mostly cloudy, with a low around 63. Southwest wind between 9 and 16 mph. Chance of precipitation is 70%. New rainfall amounts between a quarter and half of an inch possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday:  Variable winds less than 5 kt becoming S 6 to 11 kt in the morning. Sunny. Seas 1 ft or less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Night: SSW wind 10 to 13 kt becoming W 6 to 9 kt after midnight. Showers and thunderstorms likely between 9pm and 3am, then a chance of showers. Seas 1 ft or less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A GREaT PLACE FOR THE SNACKS IS THE POPULAR RED LOVE SHACK.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Party:&lt;br /&gt;Barbie-Q and Pool Party..&lt;br /&gt;BRING SOME EXTRA FOOD, ADULT BUGG JUICE, dry clothes, swim clothes, CHAIRS, AND WHATEVER..THE AFTER PARTY IS A BARBARA'S ON OUR RETURN TRIP.&lt;br /&gt;(PARTY DIRECTIONS GIVEN OUT LATER JUST IN CASE THERE IS A LAST MINUTE CHANGE, due to weather or whatever.) Preliminary directions: from the boat launch take left head towards Neck Rd, take a left onto rte 1 go to the second right, Mungertown Rd, take Mungertown Rd to rte 95 N&lt;br /&gt;go for 1 exit (#61) &lt;br /&gt;take left off of exit to get onto rte 79 North.&lt;br /&gt;From here go exactly 10.4 miles and you are real close to the destination on right .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Circle Beach location over the years has been a good paddle spot because there are 2 rivers to explore if the seas are not great..but also if you want to there are a few places along the shore to explore also including some iLands..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its not a great place for a Barbie-q but there is a good spot for a grinder, fruit salad..(portable stuff)..The Red House on the beach...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING TO CIRCLE BEACH:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;91 south to rte 9 south&lt;br /&gt;exit #9 for rte 81 south all the way to the Clinton PremiumOutlet stores, then get onto 95 SOUTH there for a few exits..&lt;br /&gt;Take exit # 60 for Mungertown Road, take left, head to rte 1&lt;br /&gt;At end of Mungertown Rd take left onto rte 1 then first right road turn onto NECK RD..follow rest of directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East: (from Clinton)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 South to exit 60. Turn left off the exit onto Mungertown Road. Travel south on Mungertown Road for approximately 0.6 miles. Turn a slight left onto Boston Post Road (rte 1) . Travel on Boston Post Road for approximately 0.2 miles. Turn right onto Neck Road. Travel approximately 100 yards to an intersection and turn right again (it looks like a little triangle green thing), continuing on Neck Road. Follow the Boat Launch signs. Travel on Neck Road for approximately 1.3 miles. At the end of Neck Road, turn left onto Ridgewood Avenue. Travel on Ridgewood Avenue for approximately 0.3 miles. At the end of Ridgewood Avenue, turn right onto Circle Beach Road (dirt road). Travel on Circle Beach Road for approximately 0.3 miles. The boat launch entrance is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOOK FOR THE ORANGE Traffic CONE ON MY CAR ROOF OR MY ORANGE HAT...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West: Take I-95 North to exit 59. Turn right off the exit onto Soundview Road. Travel south on Soundview Road for approximately 50 yards. Turn left onto Boston Post Road. Travel on Boston Post Road for approximately 2.2 miles. Turn right onto Neck Road. Same as above...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Rain or high wind (10+) , High seas (3+) canceles the event......The back up plan is WEST RIVER&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics on maybe 1 to 3 or so foot waves..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 20 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this ocean all day trip and new carbon paddles &amp;amp; paddle leaches..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub, Recreational Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Pungo 12' with flotation bags installed= &lt;b&gt;Steve Therriault&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper, Short Sea Kayak = Riot Tourlite 15'=  AL-R&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna, Long SOT Sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = ALEX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner, Long sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= DURELLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenlander, Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Fiberglass or Greenland Paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOB'S  Blue Perception Monitor 10 feet, Recreational boat= Karen Mac &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya all there,&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>PIMPED OUT  GOLD Toyota Avalon with a Kayak Trailer and a few Orange Traffic Cones on ROOF</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253195629000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246910217000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sea &amp; Recreational Kayaks, CIRCLE BEACH, West River &amp; Ocean Paddle event, .</name><id>10814972</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247328000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10814972/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/global_474104.jpeg</photo_url></item>