<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fearing Pond Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.824314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 508-866-2526</phone><name>Fearing Pond, Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>987634</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.670242</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;Take Me Fishin'!&lt;/i&gt; is the 4th Annual Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Community Fishing Event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sept. 25, and only at Fearing Pond, everyone can fish without a license. Friends of MSSF runs a fishing derby with great prizes awarded for the largest fish. We'll also help people of all ages learn to fish, organize fun and interesting nature activities, announce the winners of the 2010 photo contest, and organize a work party  (it's National Public Lands Day, after all). Our great DCR staff always helps out. Mass Wildlife supplies ~50 fishing poles and squirmy bait AND they stock the pond right before the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are welcome to come and spend the day at one of the most beautiful ponds in the state. You can fish, BBQ, picnic, swim, or just hang out with people who love the forest and enjoy the wonderful sense of community. Best of all, it's FREE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to help? We need everything: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experienced fishers to teach others how to fish; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ideas for new nature activities and volunteers to run the booths; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Donations of water, juice, and snacks (keep them healthy please) which will be given free of charge to anyone who wants them;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prizes and raffle items (If it's new and you don't need it, how about donating to our raffle? Handicrafts and plants are very popular, so are services), bait, lures and anything to do with fishing is gratefully accepted; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fishing poles and binoculars to lend (we can't guarantee their return but we'll try hard to keep them from getting lost; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Volunteers to help set up (9:00 a.m.), take down (3:00 p.m.) and lend a hand (2-hour shifts available);&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Art supplies, sign painters, and cash (cash is always appreciated-donations are tax deductible)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Help make this another great fishing day at MSSF! Write to friends@friendsmssf.com to volunteer, share ideas or donate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View pictures of previous &lt;i&gt;Take Me Fishin'!&lt;/i&gt; events at &lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com/fishingevents.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com/fishingevents.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.friendsmss...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharl</member_name><member_id>712534</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Vickstrom</member_name><member_id>11406046</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285604700000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283113812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer for "Take Me Fishin'!" —FMSSF Community Fishing Event </name><id>14582456</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285423200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/14582456/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_17610532.jpeg</photo_url></item>