<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>31 Everett St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.379974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stebbins Hall RM 302 -  Lesley Unviersity</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1499680</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117119</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please come on out everyone!! And we can surely do some improv afterwards in this awesome room at Lesley as well! &amp;nbsp;More Details:  &lt;br /&gt;The piece is about one hour 15 minutes long with a 10 minute intermission.  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;You're encouraged to play along and interact when called to throughout the piece &lt;br /&gt;There will be a talk back after the show  &lt;br /&gt;Here is an interactive map to direct you to the venue: &lt;a href="http://www.lesley.edu/campus/campus-map.html"&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lesley.edu/campus/campus-map.html"&gt;Breaking the fourth wall, it addresses the audience as travelers, &amp;ldquo;where are you going?&amp;rdquo; but most crucially, &amp;ldquo;where are WE going,?&amp;rdquo; challenging the audience to focus upon making decisions that affect one another from a holistic stand-point.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A period of time away from my cell phone and constant influx of media, I learned a lot about my own disconnection to myself and discovered my strong material, media, and technology attachments.  &lt;br /&gt;As I faced intense fears in anticipation of graduation, I found clarity when I decided to spend time on a permaculture farm re-connecting with myself and nature, completely immersed in a different culture.&amp;nbsp; I hope my life changing story will help others through the big and over-whelming journey of, &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s next?&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Seed of Spirit GenY  &lt;br /&gt;An Interactive Theater Piece  &lt;br /&gt;written and performed by Caitlin Green &lt;br /&gt;Direction by Jason Jedrusiak &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peformance February 10th, 7:30pm&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;Stebbins Hall RM 0302 &lt;br /&gt;Lesley University &lt;br /&gt;31 Everett Street, Cambridge, MA &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;for those excited to offer greatly appreciated feedback with these questions in mind:..... &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;what is the strongest message I take back from seeing this piece? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;Does the piece speak to high school and college students? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;Where are 3 places I can imagine this piece performed within the next year? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;How might I be willing to offer help in taking the piece to high schools, universities, and other venues? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.lesley.edu/campus/campus-map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lesley.edu/campus/campus-map.html&lt;/a&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for signs, check out the map below! Walk up the stairs!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297387604000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Hi Incuators! Come see Seed of Spirit: GenY @ Lesley 2morrow night! Caitlin &amp; I put a lot of work into it as part of her thesis. An interactive theater performance based on her travels &amp; graduating from college, it's truly unique &amp; admission is free!</why><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297265216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Show Tomorrow @ Lesley! Starring Incubator's own Caitlin Green &amp; directed by me!</name><id>16502760</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297383300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/16502760/</event_url></item>