<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>OUTING ANNOUNCEMENT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: The little attached island jutting into Portsmouth harbor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: 3 hours starting at the posted time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE SCENE: Sensationally beautiful little undiscovered mini-island, jutting out into Portsmouth harbor. Easily accessible from the parking lot. On the island are picnic tables, rest rooms, grass and landscaped bushes. The view includes waterfront and boats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE TO MEET*: At the posted time, with 1/2 hour leeway for late-comers. Let's meet on the island, which is small.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: From Portsmouth center, drive towards the water, bearing right towards Strawberry Bank. With Strawberry Bank on your right, the park along the harbor on your left continue straight about 1/2 mile until you see a left turn going over a small bridge. It's at the end of the park. Take a left, go over the bridge, and the parking area for the island is shortly on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OTHER:&lt;br /&gt;            RSVPs: It's best to let us know you are coming so we can look for you or alert you to any changes. &lt;br /&gt;            THINGS TO BRING WHICH ARE OFTEN FORGOTTEN: &lt;br /&gt;                        Mosquito repellant,  Paper towels,  Sweater, water, food&lt;br /&gt;            IF LOST: If you become lost getting there, call.&lt;br /&gt;            &lt;br /&gt;            *LAX: We meet at the time above. You have 30 minutes additional slack, after which we may leave to the painting site without you.&lt;br /&gt;             &lt;br /&gt;             INCLEMENT WEATHER: It is up to you to determine if the weather makes painting untenable. Although, I will try to leave a message on my voice mail if I myself do not intend to be there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Emerald&lt;br /&gt;617/968-0627&lt;br /&gt;westpointusma@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Emerald, CFA</member_name><member_id>3007793</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188846121000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>painter-84</urlname><id>576650</id><group_lat>42.4500007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Plein Air Artists Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188409272000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portsmouth Harbor, Portsmouth, NH</name><id>6263747</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188673200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/painter-84/events/6263747/</event_url></item>