<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bare Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.866578</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MSSF @ Rocky Pond</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>1285063</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.694725</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Celebrate National Trails Day a day late by exploring a less known section of MSSF near Curlew Pond.  The scenic loop trail departs from a small parking area near cranberry bog trails off Bare Hill Road just before Rocky Pond but there is additional parking on both sides of the road near the power lines.  We will descend to the bog trail but quickly turn off to follow the shore of Rocky Pond before turning back onto a narrow dirt road.  Then it's into the woods for some occasionally steep trails, choosing a fork that will take us to a hill overlooking Federal Pond and then down to a pine needle carpeted glade surrounded on three sides by the pond.  The route back will take us through the woods to another bog and back to the cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will see a sampling 0f varied terrains that the forest has to offer as well as the effect man has had on the forest floor as we follow trails scooped out by motor bikes.  With luck there will also be evidence of some of the more peaceful forest creatures.  Look for deer tracks if there are any muddy areas and turkey tracks in the sandy ones.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hiking will be flat and easy in some places but more strenuous in short uphill climbs.  With sand here and there, hiking boots will help keep it out if sand between the toes doesn't enhance your hiking experience.  Hopefully there won't be any rain to make it muddy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The earlier starting time is out of respect for the recent warm weather but be sure to bring some water and maybe a snack if lingering by Federal Pond is tempting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there despite the late notice, which was due in part to those quirky computers.  My dog Buffett and I fell in love with this area and think many of you will, too.  As always, everyone is welcome.  A small donation will be appreciated as it helps offset the cost of maintaining the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>8840771</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Troll</member_name><member_id>11017991</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275835090000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274928284000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Sunday Meetup Hike</name><id>13609367</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275831000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/13609367/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/7/global_15364743.jpeg</photo_url></item>