<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>FREE w/ Promo tee-shirt</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Headliner Wed-Sun:  Juston McKinney   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Juston Mckinney is one of the hottest comedians in the country. Coming to you from New York City he has headlined many of the clubs in NY such as Caroline's, Comic Strip Live, Dangerfield's, and Stand-up NY. He's been featured at the Toyota Comedy Festival and on the Tonight Show with Jay Leno and had his own show on Comedy Central. He is a U.S. Comedy Arts Festival Award Winner, and delivers a funny, original, high energy performance, which has made him a huge hit at colleges all over the country. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I gather various MeetUp Groups and the &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; for &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot;, whereby we meet a couple of times per month to attend the new Funny Bone Comedy Club inside Manchester's Buckland Hills Mall.   The majority of our attendees are Singles in their 40's-50's, but all (over 21) are welcome to join us!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weekend headliner will cost $20 but by attending the WEDNESDAY show, the one-time $15 purchase of their promo tee-shirt allows access to this, and just about every WEDNESDAY performance, for FREE forever!   Such a deal!  We'll gather @ the Funny Bone Bar @ 6:00-6:30 for a chance to get to know each other and have a drink.  When the doors open @ 6:30, we'll enter together and optionally order drinks, an appetizer or dinner (separate checks have been pre-approved) before the show starts @ 7:30 (lasting to @ 9).  Seating is &amp;quot;first come, first seated&amp;quot;, so even if you RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;, if you show up late without notifying me in advance, we'll not necessarily be able to hold a seat for you, as otherwise there's no way of knowing if you are going to truly join us, or not.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between my various affiliations with different MeetUp Groups and the &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot;, and due to the poor weather forecast, I suspect we'll easily fill all 24 of the seats I've reserved so far.  If more than that RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; soon, I'll try to have them hold more tables/seats for us.  I'm sure you'll have a good time and enjoy meeting new friends!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; IF you arrive after 6:30, buy your promo tee-shirt at the Box Office, THEN request they give you a FREE ticket.  When entering the theater, inform the ticket-taker to seat you with or near &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; group!  I'll post signs at the bar, then move them to our tabletop once we move into the theater.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Also, because I bring in a lot of business to the club, they periodically toss me some freebie tickets to the weekend shows.  I gave away @ 30 FREE ($20) tickets to this past weekend's Alonzo Bodden show.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Even if you can not join us for this Wednesday's show, if desired, please request I put you on my direct emailing list for when I have FREE tickets to distribute.  If so, so your direct contact info is not posted on the MeetUP page, please email me directly with your direct email address plus phone number, especially cell#, so I can get the word out of last-minute changes and/or free tickets being distributed.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney   &lt;br /&gt;live in Meriden / work in Bloomfield   &lt;br /&gt;rep06450@cox.net   &lt;br /&gt;C: (860) 690-9595   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you arrive at the Buckland Hills Mall:  Head toward the Sears / Vinnie T's / Barnes &amp;amp; Noble / JC Penney area.  Between Penney's and Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, you'll see a sign for the &amp;quot;Blue Turtle&amp;quot; - enter via that exterior entranceway.  The Funny Bone Box Office / Bar / Club is immediately inside, to the left.   &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183154891000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182742661000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rob's Wacky Wednesday - Funny Bone Comedy Club</name><id>5931953</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182981600000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5931953/</event_url></item>