<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>88 Beach St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.350986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>6173388813</phone><name>Hei La Moon</name><city>Boston</city><id>669068</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059044</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/f/d/event_47021981.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;As many of you know, I have been reluctant to run this particular meetup event because I anticipated an unmanageable amount of chaos with regard to both the transportation and sorting out the check. However, &lt;span&gt;one of our newest members, Indi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, has talked me into it! She knows a dim sum restaurant in Chinatown that actually offers validated parking as well as what promises to be a delectable dim sum experience in proper old-school, steam-table style. Check out this link and see if your mouth doesn't start watering!!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/hei-la-moon-boston"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/hei-la-moon-boston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While some restaurants use order tickets or slips, Hei La Moon follows the traditional approach of figuring the bill for each table by adding up the number of empty plates. So trying to work out what each person owes could be rather challenging. Indi and I have a solution, though! Instead of the usual $3 reservation fee I typically charge for group meetups, we are asking each person to pay $20 in advance. This is pretty close to what people spend on a dim sum brunch as a general rule.  This way, you all can sit back and focus on your food because I will take care of the bill. (Please bring some cash in case we run a bit short; we will play that by ear if/when it happens. )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hei La Moon is easy to find, it is about a block east of the Chinatown Gate. It is located at the bottom of a large parking garage (bring your parking ticket with you; the restaurant will validate it for $6 worth of parking.) According to Indi, "there is almost always a large crowd of people outside the door." This is a very busy time at the restaurant but it also means the dim sum will be abundant and freshly made -- and we have been able to reserve two tables in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public transportation is also available to Chinatown on the Red Line. Bob and I may drive to the Alewife station and take the T into town -- if anyone else wants to do this and ride with us, let me know!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in front of the restaurant. Try to come early or at least on time to facilitate seating!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368730402000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272920148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dim Sum Sunday in Chinatown</name><id>16228203</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352651400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/16228203/</event_url></item>