<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>DAY/TIME: Monday, May 11 from 10:00am until 4:00 pm or so; finish time is negotiable!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    AGENDA: No scheduled activities. Arrive and leave when you want. Work on your own projects at your own pace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    AMENITIES: Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom; access to Wi-Fi if you need to use your computer while you're there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    COST: $5, regardless of how long you stay. If people are interested in dinner, we can get take-out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    WHO MAY ATTEND: Any member of the NE ATC+ or Altered Art/Assemblage Meetups and their guests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    WHAT TO BRING: Your own materials and projects to work on (just as you do for the regular Meetup; if you're a newbie, see &amp;quot;What to Bring to a Meetup&amp;quot; in the Files section.) A few basic supplies--scissors, glue, tape, etc. -- are available for loan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    HOW TO SIGN UP: You must RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function so we know who's coming and how many to expect. If your plans change, PLEASE switch your RSVP to “no” ASAP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    CANCELLATIONS: If you must cancel less than 24 hours in advance -- or after the Open Studio has started -- PLEASE call the Open Studio host. The cell-phone number will be e-mailed to you after you RSVP &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot; If we need to cancel for other reason, we'll post a message here AND e-mail anyone who's signed up. For your own protection, we suggest checking your e-mail just before you leave the house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    TRANSPORTATION/DIRECTIONS: Sorry, we cannot provide or arrange transportation of any kind. If interested in sharing a ride, you may post a notice on the Message Board to see if anyone can help out. You'll need to do your own research to determine whether you can reach Holliston via public transportation or cab. If driving, we recommend using an online mapping service or GPS to find the best route from where you are. Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>emelengy</member_name><member_id>4250560</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242245140000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241104747000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Studio in Holliston</name><id>10303084</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242050400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/10303084/</event_url></item>