<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>151 Watertown St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.362590</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 799-3781</phone><name>Hibernian Hall</name><city>Watertown</city><id>669408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192270</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Okay, you know you're curious. You've always wanted to attend one of these. So come out to the region's only UFO Conference this October.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a certain stigma that people who believe in UFOs are nuts, but this conference is nothing like that at all. This conference is basically a presentation of some of the more fascinating documented cases. Presentations are made in a fair fashion for the listeners to decide what they think happened. It is like watching a Discovery or History Channel documentary in person. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be several discussions on the evening  by Nick Redfern (&amp;quot;Cosmic UFO Crashes&amp;quot;), Nancy Talbott (&amp;quot;Crop Circles and UFOs&amp;quot;) and Peter Robbins (&amp;quot;The Bentwaters Incident&amp;quot;). Other features include &amp;quot;Black Helicopters&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;The Air Raid of Los Angeles&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The 1909 Airship Mystery&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition there advocates and representatives from various organizations include MUFON. Vendors will be selling books, t-shirts and other memorabilia. There will also be snacks and drinks available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets for this event are available through the www.ufoshow.org for $25. You will need to buy your ticket on your own. If you sign up for the New England UFO MeetUp group,     &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/neufogroup/calendar/11156787/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;  , you can buy your tickets through them. Discounted tickets will be offered to members of this meetup group only. Contact massufoshow@hotmail.com for more details. This is a limited offer for a short time (September 15th). Tickets will also be available at the door on the evening of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come join me for an interesting evening and leave your foil hat at home.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Giovanni</member_name><member_id>2402708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255907186000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250867440000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UFO Show</name><id>11165455</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255734000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11165455/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/5/global_10306245.jpeg</photo_url></item>