<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>253 Harvard Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3983</phone><name>Brugger's Bagels</name><city>Brookline</city><id>317494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121030</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll discuss A Thousand Splendid Suns by Khaled Hosseini at our January meetup. We chose this book at our November/December meetup. If you would like to suggest books for future meetups, please contact Charis, assistant organizer, with your book title and a link describing it from &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;. After I receive several suggestions, I will conduct a poll to decide what to read going forward. I look forward to seeing many of you in January. Happy holidays! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a description of A Thousand Splendid Suns from &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Thousand-Splendid-Suns-Khaled-Hosseini/dp/1594489505/ref=pd_bbs_sr_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1196693818&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;:  &lt;br /&gt;A Publishers Weekly Starred Review. Afghan-American novelist Hosseini follows up his bestselling The Kite Runner with another searing epic of Afghanistan in turmoil. The story covers three decades of anti-Soviet jihad, civil war and Taliban tyranny through the lives of two women. Mariam is the scorned illegitimate daughter of a wealthy businessman, forced at age 15 into marrying the 40-year-old Rasheed, who grows increasingly brutal as she fails to produce a child. Eighteen later, Rasheed takes another wife, 14-year-old Laila, a smart and spirited girl whose only other options, after her parents are killed by rocket fire, are prostitution or starvation. Against a backdrop of unending war, Mariam and Laila become allies in an asymmetrical battle with Rasheed, whose violent misogyny -- &amp;quot;There was no cursing, no screaming, no pleading, no surprised yelps, only the systematic business of beating and being beaten&amp;quot; -- is endorsed by custom and law. Hosseini gives a forceful but nuanced portrait of a patriarchal despotism where women are agonizingly dependent on fathers, husbands and especially sons, the bearing of male children being their sole path to social status. His tale is a powerful, harrowing depiction of Afghanistan, but also a lyrical evocation of the lives and enduring hopes of its resilient characters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This book is hardcover. You may wish to check it out of your local library. &lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Public Library&lt;/a&gt; allows you to request books and hold them at your local branch. You can set your account up so the library emails you when the book arrives.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sabina</member_name><member_id>1638720</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201716344000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196694243000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January book club</name><id>6847323</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201467600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/6847323/</event_url></item>