<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1st St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.816959</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Salisbury Beach State Res.</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>692799</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.868123</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of the North Shore’s sunniest summer beach destinations, Salisbury Beach, kicks-off a series of family-friendly beach fests in 2009. The 3rd Annual Sand &amp;amp; Sea Festival will be action-packed with sand and seaside activities for kids, teens and adults. The Merrimack River Maritime Festival will celebrate it's 2nd year with historical ships, hands-on activities, maritime exhibits, live entertainment and spectacular fireworks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Fun in the Sun&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sand &amp;amp; Sea Festival highlights the many fun seaside recreational uses of our four mile shoreline by showcasing activities such as sea doo-ing, surfing and kayaking, as well as marine aquatic programming.  On the sandside, activities such as kite-flying, yoga, family entertainment, live music on a beachfront stage, and the largest fireworks display north of Boston brought the Salisbury Center Beach alive during the festival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Festival-goers experienced the many shops, arcades, food concession stands and nostalgia that have sustained the legendary beach destination since its beginnings in the1800’s as an elegant oceanside resort.  get more information on their web site: &lt;a href="http://www.beachfests.org/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beachfests...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Action on Salisbury’s Seashore:&lt;br /&gt;Entering its 11th season of racing, the Toyota/Sea Doo U. S. Regional Championship is one of the countries leading personal watercraft racing circuits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each action packed event at Salisbury Beach featured some of the nation’s top watercraft racers doing battle against one another while negotiating buoys, obstacles and pounding waves on a quarter-mile ocean race course.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to children of any age!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: Pay as you go!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time to meet: This may change there are things going on all day check out the website and see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in front of Hobo's Cafe.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246313028000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244382999000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sand &amp; Sea Festival at Salisbury Beach!!</name><id>10595697</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246140000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10595697/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>