<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The actual start time is 4:05.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for the late post, but since I'll be in the area anyway I thought, why not?  (Plus, I'm a sucker for English period films.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About &amp;quot;Easy Virtue&amp;quot;:&lt;br /&gt;The twenties have roared... The thirties have yet to swing. Young Englishman John Whittaker (Ben Barnes) falls madly in love with Larita (Jessica Biel), a sexy and glamorous American woman, and they marry impetuously. But when the couple returns to the family home, his mother—the stoic and neurotic Mrs. Whittaker (Kristin Scott Thomas)—has an instant allergic reaction to her new daughter-in-law. Larita tries her best to fit in but fails to tiptoe through the minefield laid by her mother-in-law. Larita quickly realizes Mrs. Whittaker's game and sees that she must fight back if she's not going to lose John. A battle of wits ensues and sparks soon fly. Co-starring Colin Firth as the war-weary head of the household. Directed and co-written by Stephan Elliott (The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert), based on the play by Noël Coward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for dinner and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the movie I'll be near the front with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244683232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Virtue -- very last minute</name><id>10625875</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244923200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10625875/</event_url></item>