<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>310.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.showsci.com" target="_blank"&gt;Safari Club International's Annual Hunting Convention&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;There is something about safari life that makes you forget all your sorrows and feel as if you had drunk half a bottle of champagne ~ bubbling over with a heartfelt gratitude for being alive.&amp;quot; - Karen Blixen (Author of &amp;quot;Out of Africa&amp;quot;)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Below are just a few of the Seminars at this year's convention:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Two Climate Change Seminars&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;The Sportsman-Environmentalist's Guide to Global Climate Change&amp;quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this dynamic and entertaining presentation, Tom Mullikin, the Sportsman Environmentalist, is going to help us understand the issue and let us know what we can and should be doing to responsibly address the problem. Tom will offer advice on what sportsmen should do to ensure that they will be able to continue to enjoy the great outdoors for generations to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;Why Hunters Should be Concerned About Climate Change and What They Can Do About It&amp;quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a growing scientific consensus suggesting that climate change will dramatically impact wildlife habitat. It is crucial that hunters and anglers are aware of this issue and can contribute to necessary conservation efforts. This workshop will explain some of the latest scientific thinking on this issue. How should hunters respond to the climate change challenge so as to further protect wildlife habitat?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;American Bison Restoration as a Model for the Propagation of African Wildlife Populations.&amp;quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The decimination of American bison over 100 years ago and their spectacular recovery are well documented. Innovative genetic biotechologies now reveal much about this conservation success story. We plan to use this knowledge to help ensure long-term propagation of other wildlife species worldwide. Our proposal starts with a systematic effort to collect genetic material and date from hunter-killed African wildlife and then progresses into a series of detailed genetic studies on selected iconic species. This large genetic repository will facilitate scientific investigations insuring healthy, robust populations that will sustain trophy hunting into the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;Photography on an African Safari - Essential Equipment, Techniques and Pointers&amp;quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jofie Lamprecht, professional hunter and photographer in Namibia as well as owner of Jofie Lamprecht Safaris and partner of Hunters Namibia Safaris, will be presenting this seminar. The seminar will include what equipment is best suited for Africa, techniques to be used as well as pointers to get more out of your photographs on your dream photographic safari to Africa. Various photographic destinations in Namibia will be presented along with a portfolio of Jofie's best shots from the 2007 season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;Your First African Safari&amp;quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The longest-running and most popular seminar. Panelists Craig Boddington, Carol Rutkowski, Beverly Wunderlich, Johan Calitz and Ludo Wurfbain help you save time and money. Learn what to expect from booking agents, outfitters and PHs; how to ship trophies; which calibers and bullet types are best; what to read before leaving home; how to travel with guns and gear; how to cut governmental red tape; and lots more. Moderator: Bill Quimby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;Fare Game; Taking Game from Harvest to Extraordinary Table Fare&amp;quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This seminar is a must for conservationists who share Chef Lisa's passion for fine food, wine and the sporting life. Chef Lisa enlightens us to simple, but informative techniques, tips and ingredients that will help all levels of cooks prepare memorable recipes you will want to share with your friends and family. Please join us for this refreshing and engaging approach to wild game cooking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... And much, much more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221778464000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176725565000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SCI Convention in Reno - (Hunting)</name><id>5675590</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201096800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/5675590/</event_url></item>