<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/f/0/event_232004272.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;In anticipation of the release of Before Midnight this summer&lt;span&gt;, we'll be showing a double feature of Before Sunrise (1995),&lt;/span&gt; and Before Sunset (2004) to catch people up and/or refresh memories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alyssa and I&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;consider this to be one of our favorite film (series) of all time (and we're not alone, on Rotten Tomatoes, the three films in the series have a 100%, 95% and 94% respectively).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before Sunrise (1995) tells the story of Jesse (Ethan Hawke) and Celine (Julie Delpy), who meet on a train while traveling in Europe. They feel an immediate connection, so they decide to spend the day and night getting to know each other while roaming through Vienna before Jesse's flight back to the US the next morning. This is beyond a doubt among the best and most real depictions of first love ever captured on celluloid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/d/4/0/event_232004352.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Before Sunset (2004) catches back up with Jesse and Celine to spend another day with them nine years later (in real-time as well, the films were released nine years apart). To avoid potential spoilers for the first film, I'll not say any more except that this is o&lt;span&gt;ne of those rare sequels that's widely considered as good, if not better than the original.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Sneak peak) Once again reuniting director Richard Linklater to the stars Ethan Hawke and Julie Delpy, Before Midnight picks up after another nine years, in real-time as well as the world of the film. It has screened at a number of film festivals this year to rave reviews (which I've avoided as much as possible). This is one of my most anticipated films of the year. You can expect us to schedule a meetup once it gets a release date here in Worcester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Note: normally, I'd include links to IMDB, Rotten Tomatoes, trailer sites, etc., but in this case, I really think it's better to avoid potential spoilers for the best experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We live in North Worcester, near Indian Lake and Greendale Mall. We'll disclose our real address to attendees (and waitlisters) closer to the actual event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We'll meet here at 6pm, and give some time to chit-chat and settle in before starting Before Sunrise at 6:30pm. Afterwards, we'll take a break and have some pizza for dinner (please bring a few bucks to chip-in if you're interested), then we'll finish off with Before Sunset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you're not interested in pizza, feel free to bring your own dinner. You may use our microwave/kitchen as appropriate. You're also welcome to bring any drinks and/or munchies, though don't feel obligated to. We'll at least have some sort of snack on hand as well as water (or more depending on how industrious we're feeling that day).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space here is limited, so we're capping attendance at 8 (including Alyssa and I), I'm also piggy-backing on &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/movies-579/messages/boards/thread/31505652"&gt;Dan's No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt;. If all slots are full, please join the waiting list and mark your calendars, as folks will often back out as plans change. Hope to see you here!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Tsai</member_name><member_id>12245717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1369672274000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-579</urlname><id>797632</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8099975586</group_lon><name>The Worcester Movie Fans Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367696214000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Before Sunrise/Before Sunset (Double Feature @ Chris &amp; Alyssa's)</name><id>117727152</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369519200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-579/events/117727152/</event_url></item>