<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Federal Street; Greenfield</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01301</zip><lat>42.599998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Pushkin</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>452544</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.599998</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A Music Benefit-Celebration&lt;br /&gt;Independent News &amp;amp; 9/11 Investigation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valley 9/11 Truth and Flyby News are working together to raise awareness for an independent, science-based 9/11 investigation. For the last couple of years these groups have shown independent films at the Media Education Foundation, Colleges, and Churches, exposing government cover-up and disturbing unanswered questions, especially regarding the third World Trade Center building that collapsed on 9/11 in the exact manner of a professionally engineered demolition. To this day, the 9/11 Commission or official reports have neglected to explain how such a building could fall in its own footprint at near free-fall speeds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To support campaigns for truth and justice, and renew the spirit during the winter solstice season, the local groups have organized two music programs. The first one is scheduled for Thursday, December 20th at the Evolution Cafe in Florence, from 7pm to 9pm with local folk hero, &lt;a href="http://johncoster.com/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;John Coster&lt;/a&gt; with Mary Serreze; plus a 9/11 researcher from Vermont, &lt;a href="http://www.heartson.com/musicindex.html" target="_blank"&gt;John Heartson&lt;/a&gt;, will perform, too. No cover charge is requested, but donations will be appreciated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These artists (and others TBA) will also be performing Friday night December 21 in Greenfield MA at &lt;a href="http://www.thepushkin.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Pushkin&lt;/a&gt;, from 8:00 to midnight. An admission cover of $10 is requested to help support campaigns that will hopefully lead to a new 9/11 investigation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to the music event on December 21, Friday, there will be a Solstice Sharing Potluck at Lupinwood, 172 Highland Ave., Greenfield, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be on the beautiful 23 acre property that is slated to become an arts-integrated eco-village over the next couple of years. Come and hang out as early as 4:30 and help set up for the potluck and candlelit Solstice Sharing Circle at 5:30. Potluck will start after the circle, so around 6, and afterwards folks can just head on down the hill to the concert (or to whatever...). Looking forward to seeing everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Lupinwood, 172 Highland Ave. Greenfield, from Rt. 91&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 91, take Exit 26 for Greenfield Center and follow the ramp down to the rotary. Go round rotary and take right onto Rt. 2A East (also called the Mohawk Trail) which is later called Main St. Stay on Rt. 2A East/Main St. through the center of town and then past the Capitol Movie House and the YMCA on right (&amp;amp; the Post Office on left) to flashing lights at end of Main St.  Go straight through the flashing lights onto Crescent St. (note: the St. sign is missing letters and may read as Re - - ent  St.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue curving right on Crescent St. for just 1/10 mi. then veer slightly right onto Highland Ave. (the 3rd right off of Crescent). Stay right on Highland Ave. where the street forks and cont. to the tip-top end of Highland where the road becomes rougher and ends in a round cul de-sac. You can park around the cul-de-sac's edge or take your 1st right off the cul-de-sac onto our sloping circular drive. There are colorful Tibetan Prayer Flags hanging between trees there, marking our driveway entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This home is an old 1890's Peabody family mansion -- and 'hidden' behind the island of trees in our circular drive so you won't see the house from the cul-de-sac, but it?s the obvious 2nd building on the right as you continue down and round the drive. If you have not parked at the cul-de-sac, you might find parking on the right past the mansion where you will see other cars. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to the mansion's main entrance, a bright red door. If no one answers, please push it hard; it sometimes gets jammed even if not locked. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please use Map Quest and/or call John (413) 210-0197 or Maya (413) 774-7322; if you need more info. or directions from other sites. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on benefit and campaigns, visit &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/" target="_blank"&gt;FlybyNews.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.valley911truth.org/" target="_blank"&gt;valley911truth.org &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198454598000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197466367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Music Benefit-Celebration</name><id>6900023</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198281600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/6900023/</event_url></item>