<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As we say every month &lt;strong&gt;we are so grateful to all of those who came out in support for our March Friendly Takeover at the Bell in Hand&lt;/strong&gt;. Though we don't always see every face, we continue to see new faces being added to the community of folks who believe in our mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which I thought this month I'd restate our mission so those who may not have had the opportunity to meet us or reach us can know what these "Friendly Takeovers" are about:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to create and encourage a more inclusive social space for young (and not-so-young) professionals in Boston while beginning a larger conversation about dynamics of race relations among the city’s young people. We aim for this to have a ripple effect that impacts not only "professionals" but everyone in every community here in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where you come in-- It's simple and two-fold: show up and spread the word. Have a drink with us, talk to some real people like you, and be visible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As always:&lt;/strong&gt; Please continue to invite friends, colleagues, family and anyone else interested in making Boston a more socially representative city. We continue to move forward knowing that there is a need to be filled. See you on the 26th!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For more information OR to make suggestions about how you might like us to move forward, please email us at visibleinboston@gmail.com. If you'd like to get on the mailing list send subject "Add to Mailing List".&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Follow us on Twitter @visibleinboston&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be on the main floor around the bar where there are a few tables</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael M</member_name><member_id>10972956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367024661000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365968095000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friendly Takeover w/ Visible In Boston - Apr 2013</name><id>114319552</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367013600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/114319552/</event_url></item>