<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be paddling from my house on Lake Lashaway to the northern end where it meets the Five Mile river...All kinds of wildlife to be seen...Beavers, Otters, Great Blue Herons, Canadian geese,  Sea Ducks, and  various birds.  Bring your fishing pole, there are native trout in the river.  There is a small island  where we can have a picnic lunch and take a swim and on the way back stop off at the Lashaway Inn for a drink  on their deck overlooking the Lake ...At the end of the day stop off at my house for a small cookout and a swim( I'll provide the dogs and burgers, just bring something for the table,   Salad  deserts or whatever) Also if you want another meat item to cook on the grille please bring it!  MUST HAVE YOUR OWN KAYAK OR CANOE...YOU CAN RENT ONE FROM EMS IN MILLBURY...THEY WILL GIVE YOU WHAT YOU NEED TO CARTOP   There seems to be some confusion about this...Please answer the 2 questions in the RSVP column so I can plan accordingly if you have not already...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at my house on Lake Lashaway    I will give out directions later!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247270502000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241138796000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canoe    Kayak   Cookout  and   Swim on Lake Lashaway</name><id>10307627</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246802400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/10307627/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/4/global_7250436.jpeg</photo_url></item>