<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Did anyone else besides me see Paul Rudd, Parker Posey, and Danny DeVito in 
&lt;em&gt;The Oh in Ohio&lt;/em&gt;? I have been a fan of Paul Rudd for a while now. He has more range than his comedies belie, but we will be seeing his comedic talents this time around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Our Idiot Brother&lt;/em&gt; stars Paul Rudd, Elizabeth Banks, Zooey Deschanel, and Rashida Jones. I think all of these actors are great comedians, and I think every one of them has worked with Steve Carell at some point. Kevin Bacon may not be the only one who can play the six-degrees-of-separation game! And Paul Rudd is as likeable a performer as Steve Carell. We can't go wrong!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will purchase my ticket at about 6:00 p.m., then wait in the theater lobby for about 15 minutes. Look for me and my bright red backpack. At about 6:15, I will move into the theater auditorium (can't miss the previews). You can find me there if you are late. 
&lt;em&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;The movie starts at 6:30 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movie, I will wait in the theater lobby to gather everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to attend this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marianne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me and my bright red backpack. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315539404000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314992937000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our Idiot Brother (The Movie)</name><id>32041412</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315519200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/32041412/</event_url></item>