<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1167-3 Providence Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01588</zip><lat>42.097588</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 234-8900</phone><name>The Paw Planet, Inc.</name><city>Whitinsville</city><id>854569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.644552</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>5th Annual Customer Appreciation Day Sunday, August 14th 12 - 4pm Charity Dog Wash Drying service and nail trims $5.00 minimum donation appreciated Please bring your own towel Ice Cream Social &amp;amp; Hot Dogs sponsored by Pirate's Cove, Nature's Variety &amp;amp; Sears Great giveaways, free pet food samples, kid's face painting and more! ALL dogs must be on a 6 foot leash - no retractable leashes allowed Pet Photo Contest Cute pet? Funny Pet? Stylish Pet? Bring in your pet photo for a chance to win 3 great prizes 1st place - $30 gift certificate 2nd place - $20 gift certificate 3rd place - $10 gift certificate All pictures can be dropped off at Paw Planet by August 13th, 2011 at 6pm. Voting will be held at the Paw Planet Customer Appreciation Event August 14th. Winners announced August 15th. 4 X 6 or 3 X 5 photos only please. &amp;amp;copy; Paw Planet, inc. 2007 The Paw Planet, inc. 1167-3 Providence Road Whitinsville, MA 01588 info@thepawplanet.com (508) 234-8900 ~~~SPECIAL INFORMATION~~~ Paw Planet has been kind enough to invite our own club officer, Monica Ferguson, to this event on behalf of the NEBBC. All funds raised at this event will be split between the participating groups. This is a Paw Planet event; the NEBBC is not hosting, and this is not a large venue. While we want ALL of you to come out and support the cause, please bring only your well-socialized, controlled canines with you. Close quarters! Thank you so much, everybody!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313342617000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312236031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come Support the NEBBC at Paw Planet's Customer Appreciation Event!</name><id>27864511</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313337600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/27864511/</event_url></item>