<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street and Center Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Churches</name><city>Northampton</city><id>258995</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.630882</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Special Presentation by Architect Richard Gage&lt;br /&gt;founder of &lt;a href="http://ae911truth.org" target="_blank"&gt;Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9/11: Blueprint for Truth The Architecture of Destruction&lt;br /&gt;Re-examining the 3 World Trade Center High-rise Collapses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event sponsored by Valley 9/11 Truth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, October 10, at 7:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;FIRST CHURCHES&lt;br /&gt;129 Main St; Northampton, MA 01060&lt;br /&gt;(413) 584-9392&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public&lt;br /&gt;Donations for expenses accepted&lt;br /&gt;Local contact Dave Caputo &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Richard Gage, AIA-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation is focused on reviewing data gathered by government reports, videos of the collapses, and eye-witness accounts which have surfaced since 9/11/2001. To fully understand what happened that day, and to prevent this kind of collapse from ever happening again, we must have a full, unbiased, and vigorous examination of all the evidence available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have studied these collapses for 3 years and along with 700+ other architects and engineers, have come to the conclusion that the official story and investigation have ignored a great deal of evidence and left key questions unanswered. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We, the Architects &amp;amp; Engineers for 9/11 Truth, are calling for a new investigation. The information that I have gathered in my years of studying these collapses, and which I will be presenting, has led these engineers and architects to publicly sign a petition calling for a new, fully funded, unimpeachable Congressional investigation with subpoena power.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope you’ll join us for this presentation.  Bring your tough questions (there will be Q&amp;amp;A) and your friends.  For most of us, it takes great courage to even consider this evidence, and I applaud you for your willingness to keep an open mind while you evaluate it for yourself.  It would be impossible for me to overstate the importance of doing so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Richard Gage, AIA, Architect &lt;br /&gt;Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth&lt;br /&gt;Enclosure&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;= = = = = = = = = = = = =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What the Evidence Shows&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WTC Building 7 collapsing in 6.5 seconds&lt;br /&gt;- WTC 7- Unexplained Phenomena&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•  Sounds of explosions at ground floor — a full second prior to collapse &lt;br /&gt;•  47-story steel-frame symmetrical collapse — through the path of greatest resistance — at free-fall speed &lt;br /&gt;•  Collapse into its own footprint — with the steel frame completely dismembered &lt;br /&gt;•  Massive volume of expanding pyroclastic dust-clouds after collapse&lt;br /&gt;•  Tons of molten metal found in the basements by demolition workers &lt;br /&gt;•  Chemical signature of thermite (a high-tech incendiary) found in slag and dust samples &lt;br /&gt;•  Rapid oxidation, sulfidation, intergranular melting, partial evaporation of the steel  —  documented (by FEMA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Twin Towers- Unanswered Questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Why were virtually no floors found at the base of either Twin Tower? There were originally 110 floors – each of them one acre in size. What explains the total dismemberment of 220 acres of four-inch thick concrete and steel decking? &lt;br /&gt;• What was the energy source, and through what mechanism was it applied, that pulverized 400,000 cubic yards of concrete into a fine powder that blanketed Manhattan? &lt;br /&gt;• Why did more than 100 FDNY first responders describe, in great detail, the sounds of explosions and flashes of light that they saw and heard at the onset of and during the collapse? &lt;br /&gt;• How were massive structural steel members hurled from the Twin Towers at 70 mph – some of them landing 600 feet away? &lt;br /&gt;• Given that open-air jet fuel fires and normal office fires both burn at a maximum of around 1,500° F., and the melting point of steel is around 2,700° F., what thermal energy source produced the tons of molten metal observed flowing out of the South Tower shortly before its collapse – and also seen for weeks after 9/11/01 in the basements of the Twin Towers and Building 7 by numerous witnesses?&lt;br /&gt;Notes from a few of the hundreds of Architects and Engineers…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I think we were all shocked when the buildings came down; it just didn't seem right. Richard Gage, AIA, does an excellent job uncovering the problems with the official explanation in a scientific, non-partisan way. It's &amp;quot;An Inconvenient Truth&amp;quot; about 9/11 that everyone should be aware of. Brace yourselves.”&lt;br /&gt;Chris Mungenast, AIA&lt;br /&gt;Somerville, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;WTC Building #7 was not hit by aircraft, yet it collapsed nearly at free-fall speed - similar to the towers. The small fires don't explain this, and the two reports (FEMA &amp;amp; NIST) don't address this or the molten metal found in the basement by the demolition contractors.  Why not?  What happened there?  I have serious questions as a result of Mr. Gage's thought-provoking presentation.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;John Cole, Architect&lt;br /&gt;Walnut Creek, CA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The presentation by AE911Truth.org brings serious doubt to the official story. It is very difficult to understand how all 3 Trade Center buildings could have come down the way they did, solely as the result of the 2 airplane impacts and resulting fires.”&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey G. Arnold, Architect&lt;br /&gt;Orinda, CA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“AE911Truth.org defies the official version of a complete structural failure of WTC Towers 1 and 2. AE911 proves that a free fall of these steel structures into their own footprint is a story without merit and a challenge to common sense.”&lt;br /&gt;Osvaldo Valdes, Architect&lt;br /&gt;New York City&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AE911Truth exposes that a localized failure in a steel-framed building like WTC 7 cannot cause a catastrophic collapse like a house of cards at free-fall speed without a simultaneous and patterned loss of several of its columns at key locations within the building.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Kamal Obeid, PE, Structural Engineer &lt;br /&gt;Fremont, CA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I completely support AE911Truth.org.   Besides the prima facie evidence which they present well, I think there is a hidden truth in the lack of changes demanded by insurance companies and building code agencies as preventative measures. If they don't want to change policy or method as a result of the “collapses,” then there is no truth to the official story.”&lt;br /&gt;Keith Burns, Architect&lt;br /&gt;Warren Grove, New Jersey&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Main Sanctuary (entrance off Main Street)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Caputo</member_name><member_id>9333748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256249309000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253477974000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Richard Gage, AIA, Blueprint for Truth</name><id>11420944</id><headcount>200</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255215600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/11420944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/6/global_10804534.jpeg</photo_url></item>