<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>875 Memorial Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.095152</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 737-2443 </phone><name>Eastern States Exposition </name><city>West Springfield</city><id>726455</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.611998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Enjoy the BIG E but don't enjoy the BIG crowds?? Are you willing to take a day to go during the week to check it out? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There's no better place to enjoy the sights, sounds and taste tempting aromas of the fall season than at The Big E, New England's Autumn Tradition and the largest fair in the northeast. It's a New England extravaganza with top name entertainment, major exhibits, The Big E Super Circus, the Avenue of States, New England history and agriculture, animals, rides, shopping, crafts, a daily parade and a Mardi Gras parade and foods from around the world for 17 glorious days during New England's most colorful season.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Big E runs from September 18 to October 4 and is open from 8am to midnight. Most exhibits and state buildings are open from 10am to 10pm. Admission is $15 at the gate but if you buy your tickets in advance online or at Big Y World Class Markets (8/27 - 9/16) you pay only $10 and can use your tix any day of the fair. Onsite parking is also $10 per vehicle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more details, check out www.thebige.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is scheduled for Thursday, 9/24 with a raindate for the following Thursday, 10/1. We can meet in the Hartford area around 9am and carpool for those who are interested or just meet us in West Springfield around 10am. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to carpool or caravan, say so in your RSVP and we will coordinate a meeting place to either ride or caravan together. My cell number will be given to &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVPs shortly before the meetup so all of us can be sure to find each other at the same gate at the Big E regardless of how we decide to get there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"Susanne will be waiting by the main gate and provide her cell # to "yes" RSVPs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susanne</member_name><member_id>3418594</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254358756000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252464081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The BIG E - The Largest Fair in the NorthEast </name><id>11324567</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253800800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/11324567/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/4/global_10615540.jpeg</photo_url></item>