<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1410 Highland Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06410</zip><lat>41.539088</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 236-3343</phone><name> Cugino's Restaurant</name><city>Cheshire</city><id>772762</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.892842</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;SAT JULY 23&lt;/span&gt; -&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Noon to 4pm&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #660000"&gt;AUDITIONS and Screen Test for Indie Film "A Cheating Heart"&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;to be filmed in Connecticut&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;* Male and Female - Ages 7 -80 needed
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #663300"&gt;OPEN TO EVERYONE - No Acting Experience Is Required&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #990000"&gt;at
 &lt;br /&gt; Cuginos Restaurant
 &lt;br /&gt;1410 Highland Street (Route 10)
 &lt;br /&gt;Cheshire, CT 06410&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #6600cc"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Print application and bring with you along with $10 application fee&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;All applications will be kept on file for future casting opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;APPLICATION AND INFO AVAILABLE AT: 
  &lt;a href="http://www.entertainmentct.com/"&gt;www.EntertainmentCT.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;The shoot starts in early September 2011. The parts for this Independent Film are non-union and non-paying parts,and offer great exposure, experience, and IMDB film credit.&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #9900cc"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;We are aiming for the Tribeca Film Festival in NYC, as well as other Film Festival across the country.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #330000"&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;A husband and wife couple spend their lives happily together until one day they learn that she is terminally ill. They fight as hard as they can but it is useless and the husband who has spent his life feeling like her hero suddenly finds himself useless and weak every time he looks at her. But the nurse is a very needy soul who is slowly rebuilding his confidence and making him feel strong and like a hero again. He finds himself spending more and more time with her and they fall in love. The wife is on her deathbed and her husband comes to kiss her one last time and he leaves to begin a new life with his mistress.&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #330000"&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;But&amp;nbsp;then perhaps through her daughters prayers or perhaps simply through all things right in this world the wife is blessed with&amp;nbsp;a miracle and awakes from her death grip. She becomes stronger and healthier and she goes home to a house that now feels like nothing but a hollow echo. She is sickened by the fact that her husband left her on her deathbed. She asks her daughter where they went to and the daughter tells her they went somewhere warm together. The daughter reassures her mother that he did call and ask about her several times and he would call her himself but he is just confused by the whole situation. Then strange things start to happen to the wife. She starts to see things she can't explain and hear things that come from nowhere. She is haunted by nightmares of the two of them. Her doctor reassures her it's probably just a side effect of the medication and all the emotional trauma she's endured.&amp;nbsp;And maybe he&amp;nbsp;was&amp;nbsp;right&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;maybe there was&amp;nbsp;something more to it than that.
     &lt;br /&gt;
     &lt;br /&gt; Maybe hatred was&amp;nbsp;becoming the&amp;nbsp;new disease that was eating her away.&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;APPLICATION AND INFO&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;AVAILABLE AT: 
&lt;a href="http://www.entertainmentct.com/"&gt;www.EntertainmentCT.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Inside Cuginos- look for the cameras and film crew</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311442318000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310665105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SAT JULY 23 -  Noon -4pm AUDITIONS &amp; Screen Test for Indie Film A Cheating Heart</name><id>25742121</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311437700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/25742121/</event_url></item>