<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Cashing In On Discounted Notes and Pre-Foreclosures&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00pm - The Future Trends of Real Estate Investing - Find out what the future holds for real estate investors!&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm - Bring your Deals!&lt;br /&gt;7:00pm - Speaker Donna Bauer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can you do using Donna Bauer’s proven strategies?&lt;br /&gt;Put $10,000 or more in your pocket in the next 30 to 60 days.&lt;br /&gt;Use your IRA to build incredible wealth tax free starting with as little as $100.&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy all the security and high rates of return of real estate investing.&lt;br /&gt;Immediately start acquiring properties for 40 to 70 cents on the dollar.&lt;br /&gt;Make a personal fortune in real estate without owning a single piece of property. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna Bauer is the nation’s most recognized authority on note buying and the booming pre-foreclosure market.  Donna’s exclusive short sale strategies have produced stunning results, time after time, in all areas of the country. But Donna goes beyond short sales and teaches you how to buy the defaulted note from the bank. Without question, buying the note is always the superior strategy. When you buy the note, you become the bank, which means you make all the rules! Once you learn how to buy the note, you will be able to close those “impossible” deals that other investors walk away from.  Don’t let common short sale obstacles kill your deals. Buy the note instead!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=106" target="_blank"&gt;Register Now for the Monthly Meeting with Donna Bauer!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna Bauer is nationally recognized as the leading authority on discounted notes and the pre-foreclosure market. She founded The NoteBuyer, Inc. in 1990 to provide a wide range of educational and support services to real estate investors. Donna has become one of the most sought-after instructors in the industry and has taught at events with fellow wealth experts Donald Trump, Anthony Robbins, and Robert Kiyosaki. In addition to her duties as president of the corporation, Donna serves as consultant to a number of investment firms, pension plans, and high-net-worth investors.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her personal investing career spans 25 years and includes thousands of note purchases and property transactions. Donna has also managed large-scale commercial developments, including a downtown highrise, office park, and 500-unit apartment complex. She frequently appears on television and radio as a distinguished expert on note buying, pre-foreclosures, IRA investing, and general real estate issues. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=106" target="_blank"&gt;Note Buying…The Ultimate Short Sale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Learn how to build your personal fortune in the booming pre-foreclosure market! You’ll receive comprehensive instruction on acquiring properties through both short sales and buying defaulted notes from banks—a niche strategy that is Donna’s trademark. Buying the note gives you complete control over your deals and empowers you to legally close those “impossible” deals that other investors walk away from. As you’ll soon discover, note buying really is the ultimate short sale!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;·        Acquire properties for 40 to 70 cents on the dollar!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;·        Put 10, 20, even $30,000 in your pocket in the next 60 days!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;·        Close high-profit deals that other investors can’t!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;·        All without using a dime of your own money!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;I’ve closed over ten deals and made a minimum of $100,000 on each one. &lt;br /&gt;Donna Bauer’s system made me a millionaire in less than a year!” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                          —J.S., New York City&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=106" target="_blank"&gt;Register Now for the Monthly Meeting with Donna Bauer!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We usually have around 300-400 people at our monthly meetings, so finding where</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242638343000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237242761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Association April Meetup</name><id>9968415</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240263000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/9968415/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/9/6/global_5505990.jpeg</photo_url></item>