<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It looks like it the weather will hold out until late afternoon - it will be cloudy and low 60's - perfect weather for hiking. We will plan on hiking for 1.5 - 2 hours at a moderate pace.   We will plan on hiking at least part of the time on the Skyline so bring hiking boots if you have them and water.  My cell is 508-472-7900 if you are lost or running late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a map of the Fells, check this link: &lt;a href="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/1/7/highres_4104343.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;http://photos4.meetup...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Skyline trail is the white trail on the left side of I-93. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Useful info on the Fells is available at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/strenuous2.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://home.earthlink...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpooling encouraged!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to Wellington Station, MBTA bus #100 to Roosevelt Circle Rotary, walk south to the rotary, turn right on South Border Road, Bellevue Pond is 1/5 mile right on South Border Road. Sheepfold section exit on Elm Street, walk north on Route 28 about one mile underneath the overpass, sign is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Car:&lt;br /&gt;From North 93 South to exit 35 at stop take a left under highway at next stop sign take a right at first set of lights (rt28) take a right for Sheepfold entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From south 93 North to exit 33(RT28N) for Sheepfold - go N 1.8 miles to reservation entrance. Follow the road inside to the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dogs&lt;/b&gt;  Well behaved dogs are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet at the bulletin board - my cell is 508-472-7900</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244383720000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244162903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>middlesex Fells - Sheepfold</name><id>10579795</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244210400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10579795/</event_url></item>