<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366062</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 482-1632</phone><name>The Garment District</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>281879</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.092800</lon></venue><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Need a break from the stress of (looking for) work, the economy, and everyday life? Looking for something to do that is fun, cheap, and progressive?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're heading to the Garment District in Cambridge for Thrifting for Justice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be combing the basement floor for some &amp;quot;reduce-reuse-recycle&amp;quot; fashion.  That's right, you sift through the clothing heaps and find your treasures - all at only $1.50 per pound.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 8pm we'll head over to the Cambridge Brewery for a review of our thrifty finds and more socializing - (&lt;a href="http://www.cambrew.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.cambrew.com&lt;/a&gt;).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So look no further if you want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while finding great bargains, you're seeking like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in.  If you want to build a strong cross-issue social justice movement, SoJust is for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events?&lt;/b&gt; Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the 'Message Board' and are encouraged to suggest and co-host events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt;  Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and learn about our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/pages/Annual_Membership_Fee_details/"&gt;Suggested Annual Membership Fee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238108112000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235925053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thrifting for Justice</name><id>9851208</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236895200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/9851208/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/4/global_7530692.jpeg</photo_url></item>