<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Intervale Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01543</zip><lat>42.415409</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rutland Prison Camp</name><city>Rutland</city><id>2149101</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.989708</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From 1903 to 1933 the Commonwealth of Massachusetts ran a farm and hospital for prisoners with tuberculosis in Rutland, MA. For 30 years it was a thriving farm, worked by the prisoners. It was believed that the fresh air and outdoor exercise would help to cure them of tuberculosis.&amp;nbsp; Here's a map showing the property when it was an active farm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rutlandland.org/gallery/PrisonCampBefore/slides/map.html"&gt;http://www.rutlandland.org/gallery/PrisonCampBefore/slides/map.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, all that remains of the farm and hospital&amp;nbsp;are the cellar holes of the hospital and other buildings, the root cellar, and a small building that served as solitary confinement.&amp;nbsp; A small cemetary also existed on the property. When the state closed the prison camp, it is rumored that the grave markers were removed but the bodies remained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This property is considered to be haunted, and many paranormal groups have conducted investigations here. Now it's our turn :')&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet at 7pm at the Intervale Road entrance. Intervale Road is off Route 68 in Rutland, not far from the Hubbardston line. Follow Intervale Road for a few miles. You're looking for a dirt road on the right. The pullout is marked by a bulletin board that has maps and information about the Ware River Watershed. Please park outside the entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By meeting at 7pm, we'll have a chance to walk to the cemetary before dark and also to explore the area and decide which parts to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT: It's about a half mile from the entrance to the prison camp. Wear comfortable shoes and be prepared to walk a fair amount. If anyone has trouble walking, we can use a car to reach the main part of the investigation. I just don't know if the gates are locked at dark and I wouldn't like people's cars to be locke inside the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INSECT REPELLANT!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flashlight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any equipment you want to use&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This needs to be a fair-weather event. If it looks like it'll be raining on the date, I'll&amp;nbsp; send out a note and reschedule it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandy&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at the Intervale Rd entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy </member_name><member_id>7992934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309361559000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>footsteps-paranormal-meetup</urlname><id>1305459</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0</group_lon><name>Footsteps Paranormal Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307993779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rutland Prison Camp Investigation</name><id>22048401</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309129200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/footsteps-paranormal-meetup/events/22048401/</event_url></item>