<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;MADE IN DAGENHAM (R)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(UK, 2010) Directed by Nigel Cole. Screenplay by Billy Ivory. Cast: Sally Hawkins, Rosamund Pike, Miranda Richardson, Bob Hoskins, Rupert Graves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In a refreshing change from British cinema&amp;rsquo;s perennial preference for, if not royalty, then the country manor set, Made In Dagenham is a true story about 187 female machinists at the Ford Motor Company in the London suburb of Dagenham who took up the fight for equal pay (and respect) for women. The chief rabble rouser, played by Happy-Go-Lucky&amp;rsquo;s Oscar&amp;reg; winner Sally Hawkins, draws her cheeky nerve from the Swinging 60s wave of music, miniskirts and Beatles-style irreverence towards her &amp;lsquo;betters.&amp;rsquo; A who&amp;rsquo;s who of English acting talent, from Bob Hoskins to Rupert Graves to Rosamund Pike, come together in a sparkling ensemble that brings to light one of the important steps towards justice for working women everywhere. &amp;ldquo;Sally Hawkins is just plain irresistible in this funny, touching and vital salute to women in the work force.&amp;rdquo; Peter Travers, Rolling Stone. 113 min.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sonyclassics.com/madeindagenham"&gt;http://www.sonyclassics.com/madeindagenham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I wear a long black or purple coat, and I knit.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297187077000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>I've been wanting to see this movie, and know weeknights are not popular but Sunday is the Super Bowl!  They have the movie only Sunday-Tuesday, so Monday night it is (break in the Jack Lemmon series).</why><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296657409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Made in Dagenham" @ CineStudio</name><id>16411861</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297124100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/16411861/</event_url></item>