<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Cumberland Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.792103</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Eden's House</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1616922</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.534050</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Raw &amp;amp; Living Foods Chef Eden Love for Class 5 of a 5-class series!  This class will feature Macadamia Cheeze Spread, Parsley-Pumpkin Seed Dressing,  and Sunflower-Herb Pate. Very versatile, easy recipes, these will become some of your raw staples!  All classes held at Alchemy Juice Bar Cafe, 203 New Britain Avenue, Hartford, CT, and run from 7:00-8:30 pm.&amp;nbsp; To register, please RSVP to this Meetup or e-mail Eden at: LoveAliveforLife@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Eden Love:  Eden Love is a super-nutritarian chef-goddess, mama-preneur, passionate teacher of the high-vibration lifestyle, and co-author of the soon-to-be-released Mama-licious: Recipes for a High Vibration Lifestyle, which is a book empowering women and mothers with the information and inspiration to be their most healthy, vibrant &amp;amp; authentic selves.  She is also the owner of the company, Love Alive: High-Vibrational Living Foods for Ecstatic Super-Beings.  She hand-crafts nutrient-dense, ecstatic living foods, superfoods, chocolates and elixirs made with the frequency of love, joy, and bliss!  Eden teaches classes and workshops on a regular basis, empowering others to nourish their whole selves with the most nutrient-dense foods on the planet!  Eden is the mother of a very special being of light, Indigo, who is her most profound teacher, and for whom she is immensely grateful.  She lives her life every day with the question, &amp;ldquo;What would love do?&amp;rdquo;  The answers are about opening to her most sacred self &amp;ndash; to the creative, succulent, radiant, powerful, light-filled, ecstatic being that she is.  In the name of personal and planetary transformation, she urges you to awake, remember who you are, and join her in being LOVE.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eden Love</member_name><member_id>2826675</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303431500000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295842363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raw Spreads, Dressings &amp; Pates</name><id>16160619</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303426800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/16160619/</event_url></item>