<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We'll hike the section of Mohawk Trail that some of the Trails Day work was done on earlier in the month. This trail over Coltsfoot Mountain used to be part of the original AT and has several great views and the opportunity to explore a feature called Baldwin Cave. The hike will be a thru-hike of higher effort over a 6.5 mile distance and taking up to an estimated 5 hours. The hike is not recommended for novice hikers due to a steep descent at one point that requires extreme caution. We'll meet at the hiker parking lot on Rt. 4 on the east side of Cornwall Bridge (details below) and finish at the small hiking parking lot off of Essex Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please meet at 2 PM at the hiker parking lot on Rt. 4 (Furnace Brook Rd.) on the east side of Cornwall Bridge. Parking for 10 or more vehicles. Unpaved parking lot marked with &amp;quot;Hiker Parking&amp;quot; sign. Located immediately northeast of triangle at junction of Rt. 4 and Rt. 7. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should complete hiking by 7 PM. A shuttle vehicle will be at the end point to return us to the larger lot at the start. Additional vehicles may need to be positioned if we have a larger turnout.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given the late end and the end of the weekend it is not anticipated we will stop for dinner as a group but this is open for modification.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; for meetup starting location via MapQuest (Furnace Brook Rd./Rt. 4, Cornwall Bridge, CT):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Cornwall+Bridge&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=%5B300-360%5D+Furnace+Brook+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06754&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.81875&amp;amp;longitude=-73.36775&amp;amp;geocode=STREET" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(Lat=41.81875, Long=-73.36775) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; for the ending point (Essex Hill Rd, Corner of the Pines {near Cornwall), CT):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=West+Cornwall&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=30+Essex+Hill+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A rough topographical map if Coltsfoot Mountain from Google Maps (starting point marked):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=350+Furnace+Brook+Rd,+cornwall+bridge,+ct&amp;amp;sll=41.819576,-73.364575&amp;amp;sspn=0.010314,0.014462&amp;amp;g=320+Furnace+Brook+Rd,+cornwall+bridge,+ct&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.82634,-73.348932&amp;amp;spn=0.041253,0.05785&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=14" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at event location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245510665000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243667637000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on Mohawk Trail from Cornwall Bridge to Cornwall CT</name><id>10528400</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245002400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10528400/</event_url></item>