<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>OK, let's join the NE Pilots group on this one. They'll be there as well as lots of others and events. For those that have never landed on the ice, it's worth doing and adding to your logbook. Besides, you might &amp;quot;have&amp;quot; to someday!!! Anyhow, this will be a good day to fly into there and join our local friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We have Paul LaRochelle, an Alton Bay non-pilot local, to thank for reviving the Alton Bay iceport. The former manager gave up on maintaining the iceport, but the locals discovered that they missed their winged friends, so Paul, a contractor that lives right along the shoreline, picked up the ball and now plows the runway and taxiway for us (uncompensated). Can you believe that it can take 8 hours to plow 16 inches of snow to form a 2400 ft x 80 ft runway with taxiiway?&amp;quot;, &amp;quot; Note: when you see Popsicle the Penguin walking around at the festival, be sure to shake his flipper.&lt;br /&gt;Popsicle is the reason why we can all land there. Despite being a flightless bird, he is our very own Paul LaRochelle, the airport manager and chief plow operator! &amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;            from NEPilots Group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.airnav.com/airport/B18" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.airnav.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, the NEPilots group is always flying out somewhere. There is no reason to have a plane on the ground not flying these days. They are also a Meetup group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Sam Mirsky for reminding me about this place. In 2009 it was closed due to good wx??? A reverse metar I guess.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AOPA's recent article:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aopa.org/members/files/pilot/2010/january/feature_icerunway.html?WT.mc_id=ebrief%20" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aopa.org/m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alton Bay's flyer for the event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/392518/alton%20bay.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hotline to call is 603-875-3498&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Toby, Gregg, Jim, Jack Pinder, Ed Murphy, Myself and a bunch of others have many landings here. The trick is to come in slow, low, and STRAIGHT. You don't want to use your brakes if possible. Snow banks are on the sides. There are lots of snow mobiles and ice fishing going on. Most of the time when departing, we might zoom over the lake at 100 feet or so, but be careful there, others are out there also! Best is to depart and go..&lt;br /&gt;There are all kinds of planes there. Some on ski's, some as big as saratoga's. ( Course, high wings have it easier )...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a landing I did there that Dave took one time. Good thing I didn't know it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pTEDX1PMdBA"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya V Day,&lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266325994000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261837154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Alton Bay Iceport (B18) Fly In.... sort of...</name><id>12147605</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266152400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/12147605/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/c/global_12385484.jpeg</photo_url></item>