<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/strong&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;strong&gt;answer all questions that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself and others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/6/event_118862902.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;During a ride along the Minuteman Bike Path last year we got to talking about local places to get some good food after the ride, and while we didn't go there that night the idea of getting some ribs at Redbones in Somerville, MA entered the conversation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Not sure whose idea it was but I can say that it sounded like a great one. So a new random tradition was born that night - &lt;strong&gt;The Random Rib Ride&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This year's (second) ride will be on July 30th because Redbones will be having one of their huge cookouts - they close down the street and put up a tent. This will be their Annual Pig Pickin' &amp;amp; Benefit for the Somerville Homeless Coalition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Exercise. Food. Friends. Live Music. Support a good cause. Not a bad night.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Redbones Pit Master will fire up the custom made, portable 'pig rig' Sunday night in front of the restaurant and slow smoke a couple of hogs 'til they're ready for pickin' hours later at the party!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dinner includes smoked pork pulled off the bone with all the fixin's and a beverage for $25.00.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Live Music by The Springhill Rounders, The Frank Drake Band &amp;amp; The SLSAPS.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you would like to meet us only for the dinner then just meet us there - don't even bother signing up here on the site. We plan to arrive at about 7:30.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The objective is to ride at about a &lt;strong&gt;12 - 15 MPH pace&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will meet at street level on the west side of the building past the pick-up and drop-off area. Monica and I will be near the large wooden circular bench between the street and the bike rack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will start at Alewife Station in Cambridge and ride out towards Bedford, MA before turning around and heading back. We will turn around so that we get to Redbones at about 7:30.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Redbones is about 1.5 miles from Alewife and while we will have a car parked at Alewife we will likely ride our bikes to and from Redbones. If you would rather drive, walk or take the T (Redline from Alewife to Davis Square) that's up to you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While I have been on this trail many times before I did all of my current research for this trip using the Internet. You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The Minuteman Bikeway is a former railroad right of way that travels about 11 miles through the historic area where the American Revolution began in April 1775 - Bedford, Lexington, Arlington, and Cambridge. It offers a 12-foot wide paved surface for the entire length and offers several resting stops along the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.minutemanbikeway.org/Pages/intro.html"&gt;Click here for information about the Minuteman Bikeway&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the ride and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?CityName=Bedford&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;site=BOX&amp;amp;textField1=42.4833&amp;amp;textField2=-71.2667&amp;amp;e=1"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to share with you once we begin. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Helmet&lt;/span&gt;: You must wear a properly sized and adjusted bicycle helmet that has been tested and meets the uniform safety standard issued by the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;: High-energy snacks and enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;: White headlight and red taillight. A multi-purpose tool or small repair kit. A spare tube.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the bike safety tips at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://sameroadssamerules.org/tips/bike-tips/"&gt;Same Roads, Same Rules&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343746980000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340584264000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Random Rib Ride - July 30, 2012</name><id>70569742</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343682000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/70569742/</event_url></item>