<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join fellow Members of the SSFMG for our 3rd Anniversary Celebration!  The Greater Boston Running Company is hosting a Gait Analysis and Sneaker Shopping Clinic for the SSFMG's 3rd Anniversary Celebration.  Come learn about proper biomechanics, what your individual foot strike is like, and what type of sneakers would best fit your individual needs.  Try on sneakers from a variety of brands until you find the perfect fit! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GBRC is offering 20% off all merchandise purchased at the event (excluding electronics) so a $100 pair of sneakers will only cost $80.  In addition, 5 members will receive $10 gift cards for you to put towards your purchase at this event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one fun event you will not want to miss.  If this event is successful we will consider running this event again in late Fall or during the Winter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gait Analysis and Sneaker Shopping Clinic&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, July 9th @ 7-8:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Greater Boston Running Company&lt;br /&gt;94 Derby Street Shoppes&lt;br /&gt;Suite 213&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043&lt;br /&gt;781-749-3800&lt;br /&gt;www.greaterbostonrunningcompany.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela and Organizer Team&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: All Members are FREE!  Guests, if allowed, will be $2 each and are not eligible for the raffle.  (This is a great incentive to join the Group!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: There is no minimum.  The maximum is 30 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Please finalize your RSVP by NOON on Thursday, July 9th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: This event will be held indoors, rain or shine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview: Located in the Derby Street Shoppes off Route 3 at Exit 15. Greater Boston Running Company is in the row of shoppes near Whole Foods, located to the left of Rustic Kitchen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 3 to Exit 15/Derby Street, Hingham. Driving Northbound, take a left at the end of the ramp; Southbound, take a right at the end of the ramp. Take a right at the next light into the Derby Street Shoppes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet inside the store!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247372084000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243799354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gait Analysis and Sneaker Shopping Clinic</name><id>10537245</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247180400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/10537245/</event_url></item>