<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-482-7799</phone><name>Gypsy Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>669047</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our own Red Sox Native member Kim was on the Auction Block for Project Smile two years ago and Whitney and Brett were on the block last year.&amp;nbsp;Please contact us if you are registered to be in the auction this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Project Smile for a Red hot and fun evening and bid on a date with Boston's finest and most desirable singles. Project Smile will be auctioning off dates with police officers, firefighters and some of Boston's most eligible guys and ladies during their&amp;nbsp;5th Annual Charity Date Auction from 6:30 - 9pm on Friday, September 16.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ladies need to know that every guy will come with a pair of sexy high heel shoes just for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guys need to know that every lady will come with a high quality necktie for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each couple receives a gift certificate to some of Boston's hottest spots to use on their date - including restaurants, comedy shows, sports tickets and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event also includes a silent auction and raffle featuring Spirit Airline tickets, autographed Red Sox, Bruins, and Patriots items, theatre tickets, gift baskets and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are not single you can still hang out, enjoy the fun and support a great cause. All proceeds benefit Project Smile the non profit organization dedicated to help children involved in traumatic events. Over 400 people participated last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event also features live music, light appetizers and a full cash bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets&amp;nbsp;are available now and at the door.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information and to purchase tickets or sponsor this event go to the Project Smile website.
&lt;a href="http://www.projectsmile.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or contact our friend Catherine Pisacaine at cpisacane@projectsmile.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVPs will be E Mailed</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>6918204</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316362893000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>A Red Sox Native has been on the auction block each of the last 2 years.</why><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297544562000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Project Smile 5th Annual Charity Date Auction at Gypsy Bar</name><id>16542524</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316212200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/16542524/</event_url></item>