<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Saturday, November 8, 2008 10:00 AM &lt;br /&gt;Details &lt;br /&gt;ADMISSION TO THE WORCESTER ART MUSEUM IS &lt;b&gt;FREE!&lt;/b&gt; Saturday mornings from 10-12. &lt;br /&gt;The museum cafe is open Saturdays from: 11:30 - 3pm for lunch, beverages, desserts and more. &lt;br /&gt;For info: www.worcesterart.org/Services/cafe.html&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;**NOTE: &lt;/b&gt;This event has been cross-posted with other groups I am involved with. So, hopefully there will be a good turnout! Usually for this type of venue people break off into smaller groups. If this is a problem for you? it may not be the right one for you to attend. Some members like this, others do not. &lt;br /&gt;*The shop at the museum..... very nice : ) &lt;br /&gt;* The cafe at the museum is very nice, however there are several places to head to very close by. Where we go will need to be decided due to the number interested. So, let's take a vote and decide on that......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DESCRIPTION: &lt;br /&gt;World-renowned for its 35,000-piece collection, WAM features must-see masterpieces spanning the globe from ancient mosaics to Contemporary Art. Special exhibitions showcase masterworks, seldom-seen gems, and important works on loan. &lt;br /&gt;NOW ON VIEW! : Heavenly and Earthly Delights: The Essence of Nature in Brush and Ink | Wall at WAM: Alexander Ross | Sepia Memories: Nineteenth-Century Photographs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEPIA MEMORIES: Nineteenth-Century Photographs &lt;br /&gt;William Thurston Allen, Women at the Dedication of the Civil War Monument, Leominster, Massachusetts, detail, 1867, Albumen print, Sarah C. Garver Fund, 2008. &lt;br /&gt;Since we are all surrounded constantly by photographic images, early photographs are fascinating. The subjects’ relationships to the camera are so well known to us. Glimpses of a schooner’s deck, a busy street in Canton, and the deserted commons of New England towns reveal worlds long vanished. Some of the earliest photographic landscapes of the Egyptian desert and the jungles of India hang near views of Boston, New York, and Paris. On view are images from the American Civil War, the first conflict to be extensively documented in photographs. Authors were among the celebrities of the era, and the show will include portraits of Walt Whitman and Dorthea Dix. This installation from the Worcester Art Museum collection, created from about 1840 to 1900, transports visitors to times gone by and exotic places. The exhibition includes many of the earliest photographic media, from daguerreotypes and paper prints from calotype negatives, to albumen prints from wet collodion negatives, the photographs that give these images their distinctive sepia hue&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HEAVENLY AND EARTHLY DELIGHTS &lt;br /&gt;The second rotation includes six-panel and two-panel screen paintings, in the colorful and quintessentially Japanese ukiyo-e (“floating world picture”) genre and Rinpa school styles. The screens depict an array of pleasurable pursuits, customs and stylish kimono enjoyed by the townspeople of the flourishing city of Edo (present-day Tokyo). From the 17th century onwards such lively, decorative scenes, often complemented with gold or silver leaf backgrounds, were commissioned by patrons from the increasingly wealthy middle class.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup inside the New Lancaster St entrance. Look for the metup logo</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273543730000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223072465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HEAVENLY DELIGHTS - SEPIA MEMORIES &amp; MORE! </name><id>8891447</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226156400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/8891447/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/9/global_5731817.jpeg</photo_url></item>