<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is one in a series of presentations that Phillip Werner, a co-organizer with the random group, will be making this summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;While you can use our site to coordinate with other randomites you MUST register for this event with REI by &lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/event/24873/session/30707?avad=3816_d1bab883&amp;amp;cm_mmc=AL-_-3184-_-3816-_-ale&amp;amp;avad=3816_d1bab883&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.rei.com%2Fevent%2F24873%2Fsession%2F30707%3Favad%3D3816_d1bab883%26cm_mmc%3DAL-_-3184-_-3816-_-ale"&gt;clicking here&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Act fast, seats are limited.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking the White Mountain 4000 Footers (educational series)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Time:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;7:00 p.m. - 8:30 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Presenter:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Philip Werner&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;REI Reading &lt;br /&gt;279 Salem Street &lt;br /&gt;(exit 40 off Route 128) &lt;br /&gt;Reading, MA 01867&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone: (781) 944-5103&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're interested in taking your day hiking skills to the next level, climbing all 48 mountains on the White Mountain 4000 footer list is an exciting undertaking and an excellent way for hikers of all ages to learn new outdoor skills. It doesn't matter how old you are or whether you're in shape or not, anyone can climb these peaks with a little inspiration and perseverance. In this talk, Philip Werner will give an overview of the 4000 footer peaks, explain the gear and skills you need to learn, and discuss several different strategies for climbing them. Philip Werner is the author of SectionHiker.com, a popular hiking and backpacking web site. When he's not section hiking the Appalachian Trail, he spends most of his time roaming the White Mountains and writing about backpacking, hiking, camping, and mountaineering.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip</member_name><member_id>5187997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310170095000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307571443000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking the White Mountain 4000 Footers (educational series)</name><id>21511561</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310166000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/21511561/</event_url></item>