<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Mirriam St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02420</zip><lat>42.449947</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Church of the Redeemer</name><city>Lexington, MA</city><id>13455862</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.228981</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Deborah &amp;amp; Jim M. are organizing this event. Thanks Deborah &amp;amp; Jim!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us (and others) on Friday evening, 17 May for casual, social, and energetic fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contra Dance&lt;/strong&gt; – sometimes referred to as New England &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;f&lt;/span&gt;olk dance – refers to dances in which couples dance in two facing lines with easy walking steps to energetic, live music and a caller. Contra Dances are sort of like “opened‑up” Square Dances, but more sophisticated and more fun. &lt;strong&gt;Don’t confuse Contra Dances with Line Dancing – they could not be more different.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contra dance is a folk dance tradition that began many centuries ago in England and Europe. In the late 1600’s English Country Dances spread to France, were modified, and termed contredanse. Eventually these dances spread throughout Europe – Mozart and Beethoven wrote contredanses – and were reinterpreted throughout the Western world. The French form of the name, contredanse, became associated with American folk dances, especially in New England.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You don’t need to bring a partner&lt;/strong&gt;. You can obtain (ask for) a partner for each dance and you are encouraged to change partners after every dance. Women get to dance with every man. And men get to dance with every woman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All dances at the First Parish (on the Green), Lexington center with music by the &lt;strong&gt;Roaring Jelly&lt;/strong&gt; volunteer band are easy – &lt;strong&gt;ideal for beginners and intermediate level dancers&lt;/strong&gt; – and are “taught” by a simple walk-through just before the dance begins. As they say, “If you can walk, you can contra dance”. The more experienced dancers are helpful and encouraging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is an instruction session for beginners at 7:45 pm at First Parish. It will be very helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The dance fee is only $ 7 and includes refreshments during the break. Pay at entrance. Paypal is NOT accepted at this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear comfortable clothes – typically a sport shirt and slacks or shorts for men or a skirt and blouse for women – and low soft-soled shoes. You will get warm after a few dances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you can make it, come to the optional Chinese Buffet dinner at the Yangtze River restaurant across the Green at 21 Depot Square, Lexington 02420 at 7 pm. Cost is only $ 13.95 plus $ 3 tax and tip ≈ $ 17 total.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let Jim Matthiesen know if you plan to attend the buffet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;djma@alum.mit.edu , 617-527-7825 cellular&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368846367000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366242602000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Beginner/Intermediate Contra Dance in Lexington</name><id>114880802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368835200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/114880802/</event_url></item>