<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This hike is maybe 3-4 miles in each direction. Terrain is wooded and hilly, on a combination of dirt and (very old) paved roads. We will hike from the highway through the woods to the ruins of Dana Common, which was part of the town of Dana before the Quabbin Reservoir was built. After Dana Common, we will continue on another trail to the wreckage of a fighter jet which crashed in the woods in the 1950s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/5/a/event_76367962.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a lunch and/or snacks! We will picnic at the jet wreckage, where there are plenty of rocks to sit on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Reservoir is a state reservation around a water supply. Please *remove all trash* from the premises. Animals are not allowed. Where we are going, there are no facilities except an outhouse w/santizer at the beginning of the old road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gate 40 is north of the Hardwick/Petersham line on Rt 32A. Pass through the center of the small town of Hardwick, then on a long rural stretch again, before you get to Gate 40. Gate 40 is about 1 mile north of Dana Rd, but on the southbound side of 32A. Your GPS will be helpful, but I will be there at least 15 minutes before 10am so my white car will be a landmark. It may be hard to see in the shaded parking area, but I'll stand near the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, Gate 40 is on the southbound side of Route 32A, about 1 mile north of Dana Rd. in Petersham, MA. There is no address I can put in Google Maps that fixes the marker correctly.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>GPS: N42 degrees 26 minutes 45.3 seconds by W 72 degrees 12 minutes 57.0 seconds</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323168518000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322793754000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Dana Common to Jet Wreckage (Quabbin Reservoir)</name><id>43107062</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323097200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/43107062/</event_url></item>