<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What is a Puggie Sunday Stroll?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going to be taking a walk through the woods for the enjoyment of our Pugs and ourselves.  We won't be moving very fast, because some of our Pugs don't move very fast, and neither do some of our Pug owners.  Dress comfortably, wear comfortable shoes, and bring water for the Pugs.  Bring pick up bags for the Pugs.  Bring 2 one dollar bills to feed the parking machine.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The park trails are shady, and our walks should not exceed a mile or a mile and a half in length.  The path pictured above is the actual path we'll be taking at Borderland.  We are all responsible Pug owners here - we are not going to let anything bad happen to either our Pugs or their owners!  Nobody is going to be left behind, panting, at the side of the path.  Won't you please join us?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your Pug rides a stroller or wagon over long distances, feel free to bring it along.  Don't be surprised if one or two (or three) Pugs end up as passengers before the walk is over.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the Pet Policy from Borderland - be sure your Pug is wearing his rabies tag (or bring the paperwork), and no extendaleashes...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;? Pets are permitted. Must be on a 10 ft maximum leash and attended at all times. Must have proof of current rabies vaccine.  Mutt mitts are provided for pet waste pick up.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210104355000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209291083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Puggie Sunday Stroll</name><id>7820418</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209931200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/7820418/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/6/b/global_3935483.jpeg</photo_url></item>