<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beach St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02882</zip><lat>41.436949</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Narragansett Beach</name><city>Narragansett</city><id>777623</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.454519</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Liberty Walk Sunday 1pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;October 24, 2010,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Narragansett town beach&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One Hour “Liberty Walk” Where Patriotism Meets the Road&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday, Patriots across the Country will step up&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;in their own hometowns and walk one mile in support of our&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;founding documents and the American Dream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk will be an opportunity for We the People to come together out of love for America, and to encourage each of us to take personal responsibility for ensuring that honor, honesty and integrity are returned to “our”government by electing representatives who demonstrate through deeds their respect for both our State’s and the Nation’s Constitutions. The Liberty Walk will take place from 1-to-2 pm in every time zone across our great nation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Liberty Walk is not about party politics. It’s about love of Country and our duty to the same. The walk will be a great way to network with others, and to help pave the way for a healthier and more independent future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Narragansett, the walk will start at Narragansett Town Beach and head south along the historic Narragansett Seawall to Monahan’s dock at the intersection of Ocean Road and South Pier Road and then return back to the gazebo near Narragansett Town Beach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upon completion of the walk, a small ceremony will be held to honor our State, our Country, and the Constitution. Patriotic hats, T-shirts, flags and pocket constitutions will be available at the start. People can print out the program at home from the&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LibertyWalk.us website and bring it with them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be “A Great Day for FREEDOM.” Please, invite family, friends, and neighbors to join, if you can’t make it to Narragansett, join a group closer to you, or start one of your own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also help by sharing this information Visit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://libertywalk.us/category/rhode-island/narragansett" target="_blank"&gt;http://libertywalk.us...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Narragansett contact: Randy Swanson – beemermeup@verizon.net or 952-5015&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.O. Box 2221&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;East Greenwich, RI 02818&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Swanson</member_name><member_id>9165041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347732910000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers</urlname><id>1425841</id><group_lat>41.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287460442000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1 MILE LIBERTY WALK</name><id>15155595</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287939600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers/events/15155595/</event_url></item>