<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>181 Boston Post Rd W</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.339233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 519 2297</phone><name>Best Western Hotel (Rt 20)</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>704305</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.588776</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Buy your tickets today at www.shunyamproductions.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Yoga and Chant Fest is the annual pilgrimage for yogis, bhaktas and spiritual seekers.  It will also run the largest kids clothes collection drive for the non-profit organization Cradles for Crayons located in Quincy, MA - www.cradlesforcrayons.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;24 Hours of Kirtan with: Wah!, Shyamdas, Sean Johnson &amp;amp; the Wild Lotus Band, Prajna, Irene Solea, Karnamrita Dasi, DJ Mantra, SrutiRam &amp;amp; Iswari, Dave Russell, Kirtan Rabbi, Simrit Kaur, The Mayapuris, Shubalananda, Ashara, Clair Oaks and Tom Lena. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;24 Hours of yoga with: Daniel Orlansky, Guruatma Khalsa, Sara Ivanhoe, Kim Valeri, David Vendetti, Richard Lanza, Soni &amp;amp; David Anderson, Dharam Singh, Siri Bani Kaur, Gurusangat Singh, Toni Bergins, Ame Wren, Krista Basis, Victoria Haffer, Nicole Churchill, Karen Kenney, Wendy Putterman, Margaret Kornack, Lauren Fuller, Beth Gold-Bernstein, Pamela McIntyre, Rachel de Almeida, Christine Fortier, Leslie Jones and Bonnie Argo. &lt;br /&gt;The yoga classes will be in the following styles: yoga of energy flow, kundalini yoga, yoga for detox, bhakti vinyasa, yoga spirit flow, ritual yoga, kosmic flow, journey dance, afro flow, vinyasa, svaroopa, yoga for athletes, laughter, fuller, dynamic vinyasa flow, divine moves, gentle yin yoga, abhyasa, tri-yoga prasara, kripalu and gentle vinyasa.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spiritual discourses by: Sai Maa Lakshmi Devi, Radhanath Swami, Mirabai Devi, Prem Prakash and other teachers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many presentations on holistic and yoga topics, Indian dance performances, over 100 exhibitors, sacred pujas for peace, prosperity and removal of obstacles, children's yoga, kirtan and other activities, affordable on-site hotel accomodations, delicious vegan, vegetarian and Indian food and so MUCH MORE! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Fest is sponsored by Mass Yoga Network, Wisdom Magazine, Circles of Wisdom, Samadhi Yoga, Inner Arts Institute, Coconut Bliss, Revitalive Café, Judith Fogarty (Psychotherapist), Dreamvisions 7 Radio Network, Tandoori Grill and The Art of Living Foundation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308411676000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>24 hours of music &amp; yoga with: Daniel Orlansky, Guruatma Khalsa, Sara Ivanhoe, Kim Valeri, David Vendetti, Richard Lanza, Siri Bani Kaur, Toni Bergins, Ame Wren, Victoria Haffer, Leslie Jones, Bonnie Argo and many others.  www.shunyamproductions.com</why><group><who>Yogis</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonyoga</urlname><id>169595</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Yoga</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299038446000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Yoga and Chant Fest - The Annual Pilgrimage for Yogis - June 18 &amp; 19</name><id>16762693</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308405600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonyoga/events/16762693/</event_url></item>