<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>AKA Rte 16</address_2><address_1>White Mountain Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03581</zip><lat>44.361156</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great Gulf Trailhead Parking</name><city>Gorham</city><id>590304</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183716</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>An opportunity to climb NH's Northern Presidential peaks from routes less-travelled...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is a challenging 16-mile loop of the Northern Presidentials (Mts. Jefferson, Adams and Madison).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting on the Great Gulf Trail from the Great Gulf Parking Area on Rte. 16, we will follow this to the Wamsutta Trail then the Six Husbands Trail, which will lead us to the summit of Mt. Jefferson.  Please be aware that the Six Husbands Trail is a notoriously strenuous and steep route which requires some scrambling.  If not familiar with this trail, please read a detailed description of it in AMC's White Mountain Guide Book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After summitting Mt. Jefferson, we will take the Gulfside Trail and continue on to the summits of Mts. Adams and Madison.  After Madison we will begin our descent back into the Great Gulf via the Osgood Trail, weather and conditions permitting.  (Should wind or weather become an issue, we have the option of descending via Madison Gulf Trail).  The Osgood Trail follows the Osgood Ridge, which although very rugged and exposed, offers spectacular views into the Great Gulf and across the Notch to the Carters and Wildcats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are confident of your hiking ability and stamina, and want to experience the beauty, solitude and unique landscape of the Great Gulf, I invite you to join us for a long and rewarding day!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erica</member_name><member_id>9524999</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246970367000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245428651000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northern Presi's from the Great Gulf</name><id>10688975</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246797000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10688975/</event_url></item>