<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 North St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.281070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Medical School</name><city>Worcester</city><id>688100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.805450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Walk to Cure Cancer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please offer a helping hand! We've been asked to photograph this event and share our images with the Organization... just like last year. You can see some of the members images from last years event at &lt;a href="http://www.walktocurecancer.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.walktocure...&lt;/a&gt; You'll be asked to give us a cd of your images from the day...Here are the details!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year's event...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, September 13, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration: 10am-Noon  There is an Entrance off of Plantation Street as well....&lt;br /&gt;The Walk to Cure Cancer consists of a five mile loop around Lake Quinsigamond in Worcester, MA. A one-mile route is also optional. Several water stops and rest areas are available around the route. Course monitors are placed throughout the five miles, directing and motivating walkers! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Walk to Cure Cancer is the largest, single-day fundraising event in Central Massachusetts benefitting the UMass Memorial Cancer Center at the University of Massachusetts Medical School. Funds raised support cutting-edge research and wide-ranging preventive and behavioral studies to provide advanced cancer care to oncology patients. The center integrates some of the most vital cancer research and treatment activities available today The Center encourages innovative collaborations and actively promotes the development of projects dedicated to bringing the work of the bench to the bedside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To date, the five mile walk-a-thon has raised over $6 million enabling cutting edge cancer research, bringing us one step closer to finding a cure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll need folks to photograph teams again this year- is anyone interested in doing this? They looked like this last year:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.walktocurecancer.org/2008_Team_Photos.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.walktocure...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you'll come out and join us for this amazing event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna and Scott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS there is a Walk to Cure Cancer Kick off Breakfast on Thursday July 16th from 7:30am to 9Am at the Hogan Campus Center at the College of the Holy Cross 1 College Street Worcester MA 01610. If you'd like to come down and take photos this morning as well! Please join us!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please Meet us at the volunteer tent.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253027485000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246559925000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk to Cure Cancer- Click and Shoot</name><id>10790145</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252854000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10790145/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/3/global_9462595.jpeg</photo_url></item>