<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>N 44.102, -71.683 W (WGS84) </address_2><address_1>Rt 3</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03580</zip><lat>44.188220</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>take exit 34A off I-93/Franconia</phone><name>Mt Liberty: Whitehouse trailhead </name><city>Franconia </city><id>1106616</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.682055</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us on a hike to two 4000 ft summits on the NH 48 highest list. Flume and Liberty  to the peaks of Liberty and then over Flume and down Liberty Spring Trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hikers will meetup at the Flume parking lot at 7:00 am &lt;/b&gt;  We would like to try to finish before sunset  4:27pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is moderate/strenuous.&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance  8.66 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time 7 hr 54 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +4270 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -4270 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers should dress for winter conditions and must pack traction/stabilicers for icy conditions and headlamps.  Sunset is at 4:27 p.m.     This hike is weather sensitive. Official weather advisories, High winds or rain cancels.  Please watch your email  for changes and cancellations. We need a minimum of 4 hiker RSVP's for a successful  hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hike details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to Pemi Trailhead (Flume Visitor Center) and Whitehouse Trailhead&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to the junction of Cascade Brook Trail and Pemi Trail&lt;/b&gt;. hike 0.70 mi/23 min/+20 ft on the Whitehouse Trail&lt;br /&gt;The trail leaves the bike path, passes over a minor ridge, and runs south parallel to the main highway until it terminates at the Flume Visitor Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to the junction of Whitehouse Trail&lt;/b&gt;. hike 0.03 mi/1 min/-13 ft on the Whitehouse Trail&lt;br /&gt;The Whitehouse Trail begins where the Liberty Spring Trail diverges off the bike path. The trail continues across the bridge over the Pemigewasset River. The Cascade Brook Trail diverges right just after the bridge. The trail then follows the bike path.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to the junction of Flume Slide Trail&lt;/b&gt;. hike 0.60 mi/30 min/-386 ft on the Liberty Spring Trail&lt;br /&gt;The Liberty Springs Trail continues on the old main logging road from the former Whitehouse Mill. It descends moderately southwest through hardwood growth and terminates at the recreation path.&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/5/1/event_5764177.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to Liberty Spring Tentsite.&lt;/b&gt; hike 1.20 mi/1 hr 21 min/-1509 ft on the Liberty Spring Trail. Leaving the campsite, the Liberty Springs Trail descends a steep, switchbacked section with rough footing. After the switchbacks, the trail takes a sharp left and then a sharp right, meeting with an old logging road.&lt;br /&gt;hike 0.08 mi/20 min/-572 ft on the Liberty Spring Trail. The trail descends the road moderately and crosses a fairly large brook. It soon reaches a junction with the Flume Slide Trail on the left (south).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to the junction of Liberty Spring Trail&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.30 mi/20 min/-361 ft on the Liberty Spring Trail. The Liberty Spring Trail begins at the Franconia Ridge Trail in a Col between Mt. Lafayette (north) and Mt. Liberty (South). The trail descends fairly steeply through conifers and reaches Liberty Spring Campsite (3,800 ft.) on the right and the spring (first sure water) on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to Mt Liberty&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.30 mi/15 min/-192 ft on the Franconia Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;The Franconia Ridge Trail reaches the summit from the east, then makes a hairpin turn and descends to the east just a few yards north of its ascent route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to Mt Flume&lt;/b&gt;  hike 1.12 mi/47 min/+117 ft on the Franconia Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;From Mt. Flume, the trail descends across a lesser knob, crosses two small sags, and climbs at a progressively steeper grade to the open summit of Mt. Liberty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;return on Liberty Springs Trail&lt;br /&gt;rt: 10.2 miles, 4,250 feet, 7:15)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you go about 100 yards beyond the flume visitor center parking lot on Rt 3, there is another parking lot that is at &lt;br /&gt;the whitehouse trail head that has a ton of parking spots.  Please park here and not the flume visitor center which is next door.  Arrive early to find the trailhead if this is new for you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the New England Hiking Meetup bumper stickers  Diane 603-477-5116   take exit 34A off I-93/Franconia Notch Parkway, about .4 miles from foot of ramp take third R to hiker parking lot, then turn L to park in upper portion of lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258641526000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256166693000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Flume  and Liberty   via Liberty Springs Trail</name><id>11681561</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257681600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11681561/</event_url></item>