<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>938 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.315056</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fitness Haven</name><city>New Haven</city><id>8369982</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.910866</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction to Yoga&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us the Fitness Haven for this $10 introductory class followed by a discussion about the benefits of breathing deeply during yoga practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yoga combined with meditative breathing will not only develop strength and endurance, but also concentration. Your ability to focus will increase all aspects of your life. It is also great for preventing injuries and aiding muscle repair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deep breathing also helps bring in more O2 to the body, helping tissues to heal and function better with an abundant blood and oxygen supply. Focusing on your breath during yoga postures, as a type of meditation, also calms the mind. And it helps develop a mind-body connection so you become more aware of what is happening within your own body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class starts with light stretching, then a 30 minute session with very gentle postures held quietly for up to 1-2 minutes while focusing on the breath. Afterward, there will be a short talk and Q &amp;amp; A. Tea and snacks will be served.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This meetup is for those interested in meditative yoga practice... not a power workout or muscle toning class. ; )&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the style of Yin or Taoist yoga, this practice can have a powerful effect on health and well-being, especially when practiced consistently over time. Participants will receive handouts with additional information about upcoming programs and other reading materials to take home with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please let us know you are coming by signing up on meetup, then be sure to go to the Fitness Haven website to register as well...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just go to www.thefitnesshaven.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; click Schedule &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt; Events tab &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt; Introduction to Yoga &amp;amp; Breath Meditation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click the Sign Up Now button!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358286073000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355439776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Yoga ...                       Renew, Revitalize, Relax</name><id>95269422</id><duration>5400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358107200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/95269422/</event_url></item>