<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>900 Boylston street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02199</zip><lat>42.347767</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hynes Convention Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>4415352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084885</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>massmouth has been invited back to celebrate First Night with Story Slams. massmouth says good bye to 2011 with two, back to back story slams at Boston&amp;#146;s biggest party, First Night! &amp;#147;the end&amp;#148; is the theme along with prompts* from past slams.(emergency,supernatural,wheels,idols,where I'm from, and gifts) Bring your story or come to listen. People with a 4 minute story on the theme &amp;quot;the end &amp;quot; or any of the season's themes will practice their stories and then drop their names in the &amp;#147;hat&amp;#148;. 4 lucky tellers will be drawn at random to tell and be awarded prizes according to an &amp;#147;applause-o-meter&amp;#148;. On April 26th, 2011 all the winners of all the monthly slams will gather for a BIG MOUTH OFF story slam at Rabb Hall at Copley Square Library. massmouth will award the lucky winner of this contest with a fabulous prize. If you've lived it, you have a story. Bring it. Details to follow... About story slams Like a poetry slam, a story slam is a performance based contest where volunteer judges choose the best true story on the theme. Anyone may sign up at the venue for a chance to tell their true, 5-minute, first- person narrative and a lucky 8-10 tellers will be chosen at random to perform their stories. About First Night First Night, Inc. is a private nonprofit organization dedicated to building community and celebrating diversity through the arts. With 35 years under its belt, the organization has grown into an internationally-renowned festival presenter and more &amp;#150; delivering high-quality arts programs to large diverse audiences, offering vital arts education opportunities to underserved children and teenagers, and providing unique planning and production services to the field. Listen to our podcasts at iTunes and podcast webpage. And check out our video archive to get an idea about 5 minute stories &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/video" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; COMING SOON: see eventbrite to reserve tix for the FINALS below On April 11, 2012, 7-9PM All the finalists will gather at Coolidge Corner, main Theater to compete for a week in a medeival townhouse in Tuscany and other prizes. &amp;quot;Because have a life, you have a story. Bring it!&amp;quot; Listen to our podcasts at iTunes and podcast webpage. And check out our video archive to get an idea about 5 minute stories &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/video" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/forum/topics/story-slam-rules-pr-what-is" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/forum/topics/way-to-be-sure-to-tell-at-a" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &amp;#8232;Other massmouth slams this season: Mondays: Club Passim in Cambridge, MA and Semi finals in March 2012 Tuesdays: Somerville, Cambridge and other venues Semi-finals in March 2012 Semi Finals: in March 11th for JP events Finals: WED APRIL 11th the Finals will be at Coolidge Corner Theater main theater Brookline, 7-9PM&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325879745000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322771607000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate First Night w/ massmouth</name><id>43065042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325379600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/43065042/</event_url></item>