<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Win New Hampshire for Ron Paul</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.193851</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Any City You Chose in New Hampshire</name><city>Any City</city><id>4455252</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.572395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>New Hampshire Republicans are holding their state's presidential nominating caucuses on Jan. 10, 2012. We the People must realize that we are at war for our nation. Right now, this is a passive war and we are still hoping to win the 2012 election for the most Constitutional candidate in the race by playing within the rules of those that control our Federal Government. Putting everything we have into this is what will be needed to ensure victory. The nation has risen in debt dramatically. In 1980, over 200 years as a nation, we had $940 Billion in Debt - under a Trillion over a 204 year period. In 2000, Debt escalated $5 Trillion in just 20 years ! In just 20 years, 5X what was accured over 204 years ! Under the Bush administration, Debt increased $5 Trillion in 8 years and now $4 Trillion in just over 2 years with Obama ! See a pattern here that is escalating quickly? We are now close to $15 Trillion in Debt ! 15 Times what the debt was just 30 years ago ! Please don't be so naive to think that this is just by chance. We the People only have to look in the mirror to see who has allowed this to happen on their watch. Fortunately for us, there is a 12 Term Congressman named Ron Paul who has never voted for an unbalanced budget in 23 years ! We the People must make sure that he gets elected. Make plans to make phone calls starting now ! Make plans to be in the state of New Hampshire on Jan 10 ! Go to whatever city you choose. Research what city you plan to be in and make your voices be heard for days before the caucus and then with your bull horns the day of the caucus outside the voting facility at the exact legal distance, no more, than required by law. Let everyone know how principaled Ron Paul is and that he is regarded The Champion of the Constitution and the closest candidate to a founding father you will ever get to vote for. Personally, I have tons of ammunition on the other candidates but feel only educating others of how special Ron Paul is is all that is needed for the average American to see the need to vote for him. I am in Florida and went to Davenport Iowa for the 2008 caucus. I urge every Ron Paul supporter in the nation to consider flying or driving into New Hampshire for this very important early state vote. Pick your city, contact the local Ron Paul meetups beforehand and spend a few days there and make a difference ! I am on the lookout for inexpensive flights and will be announcing them to the group when I see them. In the meantime, join and make calls for Ron Paul at www.rp2012.org/ Surrounding states Ron Paul supporters should pour into New Hampshire days before the election to help New Hampshire residents not miss the chance to vote for the most Constitutional Presidential candidate in their lifetimes. Decide on a city in New Hampshire and look up the local Ron Paul groups on meetup.com. I am sure they will appreciate all the help that they can get. I know Florida is a long distance, so I am focusing this more towards Ron Paulers in surrounding states, even though some of us may choose to drive or fly there. If you stay in Florida, please phone bank for Ron Paul at www.rp2012.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326244415000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321478393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Operation: "Win New Hampshire at All Costs".</name><id>41430352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326240000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/41430352/</event_url></item>