<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hunt Room</address_2><address_1>405 Pine St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>42.992096</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-624-6550</phone><name>Manchester City Library</name><city>Manchester</city><id>884929</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.459190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear great members, it is time to have a meetup again. Our next meetup will take up the topic of Actions and their importance in our life. The aspects of the laws that govern our actions and the return/fruit they bring us are very deep. This meetup is not to miss. Please find a short writeup as a preview...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All over the world there exists a simple precept that has the power to end conflict and banish strife. It is the Golden Rule, a prescription to “do unto others as we would have them do unto us.” The meaning of this is clear: Only treat other people in ways that you would want to be treated yourself.  The Golden Rule gently guides us to never let our actions toward others be out of harmony with our own desires.  If we honor others in this way, we also honor ourselves.  Yet, this rule invites us to do more than simply not harm others.  It suggests that we look for opportunities to connect with others in loving ways, and in doing this we honor our own deep understanding of interconnectedness.  Being considerate, caring for the less fortunate and giving generously all bring back to us a “golden return.” &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please go to Winchell room to find us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>10101462</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269284762000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Great Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight</urlname><id>1499616</id><group_lat>43.0</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Owning Greatness Through Raja Yoga  Manchester Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263689955000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Golden Rule</name><id>12339791</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269111600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight/events/12339791/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/4/b/global_12647707.jpeg</photo_url></item>