<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ideal for the beginner or advanced hiker and also learn plenty of local history! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group will hike in just 2.5 miles up easy grades to see the spectacular 80 foot falls and the scores of cascades along the way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bridal Veil Falls, one of the more captivating waterfalls in the White Mountain National Forest (WMNF), tumbles down Coppermine Brook in the ravine between Cannon Mountain and the Cannon Balls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the hand cut log shelter the C.C.C. built in the mid 40's and learn the history of the area where Betty Davis was lost and where local hero Art Ainsworth rescued her. They fell in love and he became her 2nd husband! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can you find the hidden &amp;amp; historic bronze plaque dedicated to Bette Davis's rescue, &amp;quot;the keeper of stray ladies?&amp;quot; Hint: It's in Coppermine Brook on a side trail.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://farm1.static.flickr.com/56/125234128_2c566383d1.jpg?v=0" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes: This easy hike is just 5 miles round trip, 1100' of elevation gain in 4 hours. &lt;br /&gt;Trekking poles helpful for 2 brook crossings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;History: The star of her day, Bette Davis is responsible for bringing at least one person to Sugar Hill, NH . Hayward said the woman he grew up calling Aunt Ellie came to town on a train from Beverly, Mass., arriving at the Homestead and declaring that she was going to call on Ms Davis. &amp;quot;She came here solely because of Bette Davis,&amp;quot; Hayward said. &amp;quot;She said she was going to call her and because her number was in the book, that`s what she did.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;She called Bette Davis and asked if she could visit and she said yes. She went over and had tea and came back and told everyone that she stayed until she asked me to leave.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mission accomplished, Eleanor Scherr decided to stay, living and working at the Homestead to the end of her life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another tangible legacy of her life here is in the woods of Franconia. Davis met her second husband, Arthur Farnsworth, when he was the assistant manager at Peckett`s.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to the lore and legend, Davis was immediately smitten and even got herself lost in the woods of Franconia, knowing that Farnsworth would be the one to come searching for her. They married in 1940, but their union brief, ending with his death in 1943.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two weeks after falling down a flight of stairs and knocking his head at Butternut, Farnsworth collapsed on a Hollywood sidewalk and died a few days later. After that, Davis` visits to Sugar Hill were less frequent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Butternut was sold about 20 years after she first came to the town and it`s said that after that, a plaque appeared on a large boulder in Coppermine Brook, which can still be seen today. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets see if you guys can find it without getting wet! Take a photo and show us.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Coppermine Trail parking lot at 10 am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243865203000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241819463000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bridal Veil Falls Trail     Keeper of Stray Ladies Hike</name><id>10370582</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243692000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10370582/</event_url></item>