<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join our own local locavore Alison Page for an in-depth workshop, including hands-on, on &lt;b&gt;preserving food using lacto-fermention&lt;/b&gt;.  This ancient and effective method is a low-energy, low-tech way to create deliciously preserved foods.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This session (AM) is likely to fill up fast so please see the afternoon (PM) session which is a repeat of the same workshop.  Email the organizer if your desired workshop is full and we can add you to the waiting list.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each attendee will gain a &lt;b&gt;thorough understanding for how this process works&lt;/b&gt;, work as a group on the preparation of at least two different lacto-fermented recipes and have the opportunity to &lt;b&gt;take home at least one jar of the finished product&lt;/b&gt; at cost (we will secure fresh organic ingredients at farmers market the week of the workshop).  Based on the date we will most likely make a salsa and a carrot-ginger recipe but that may change based on availability of fresh ingredients.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:  A Portland Public or Community Kitchen TBD (email me if you have suggestions)&lt;br /&gt;9am to noon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$25 Fee Per Person&lt;/b&gt; - includes our expert instructor, mid-session refreshments and handouts.  You are encouraged to bring a notebook as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our Meetup Event RSVP Guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://permaculture.meetup.com/58/messages/boards/thread/5233158#20208623"&gt;http://permaculture.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event fee is only refundable up to 14 days before the event (unless we have to cancel it for some reason).  If you cannot attend you can certainly transfer your spot to someone else and we will provide a list of names on the waiting list, if there is one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can &lt;b&gt;learn more about Alison LePage&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mofga.org/Publications/MaineOrganicFarmerGardener/Winter20072008/AlisonLePage/tabid/861/Default.aspx"&gt;here &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="http://localfoodie.livejournal.com/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251755034000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241458599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop: Fermenting for Deliciously Preserved Foods (AM)</name><id>10334695</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251550800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/10334695/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/1/8/global_8945144.jpeg</photo_url></item>