<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Emmy Award-winning actress Megan Mullally (from Children's Hospital, Party Down and, most famously, Will &amp;amp; Grace) met fellow actress Stephanie Hunt (Friday Night Lights, Californication and How To Live With Your Parents For the Rest of Your Life) while in Austin filming an independent movie. The minute the two started singing together they realized they had something special, so they formed a new band called Nancy and Beth. Which, yes, is a little confusing given that those aren't their names, but word on the street is that you won't care after hearing these two perform. Their music has been described as a mixture of the Andrews Sisters, honky tonk, country-western and Joni Mitchell. Be sure to catch them in their East Coast premiere at Boston's Wilbur Theatre. I haven't bought my ticket yet, tickets are only $12.50 on Goldstar, please let me know if you'd like to go so we can try to buy seats together, thanks! We can coordinate meeting for dinner as well if you'd like. Should be a great show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show starts at 7pm.  We will be meeting at Intermission Tavern&lt;a href="http://www.intermissiontavern.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.intermissiontavern.com/&lt;/a&gt;  right nearby at 5:30pm for dinner/drinks and at the theater at 6:30- 6:45pm ish.  Hope you can join us! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.goldstar.com/e/67003"&gt;http://www.goldstar.com/e/67003&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.ticketmaster.com/venue/8252?tm_link=edp_Venue_Name_2"&gt;http://www.ticketmaster.com/venue/8252?tm_link=edp_Venue_Name_2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a red hat!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Marie</member_name><member_id>7853624</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363226541000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362422060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>See Megan Mullally at the Wilbur Theater in Boston!</name><id>107560002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1362954600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/107560002/</event_url></item>