<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Church Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374447</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Cambridge Unitarian Universalist</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1558733</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119555</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Renewable Revolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-large"&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forum and Book Signing &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 12, 2011 - 7:30pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First Parish in Cambridge Unitarian Universalist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3 Church Street, Harvard Square Cambridge, MA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doors open at 7:00 p.m.; Presentation begins at 7:30 p.m&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sajed Kamal, long-time BASEA member and board member, will discuss his most recent book: The Renewable Revolution: How We Can Fight Climate Change, Prevent Energy Wars, Revitalize the Economy and Transition to a Sustainable Future (Earthscan, 2011).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;During this past year alone the world has witnessed some of history's worst catastrophes related to nonrenewable energy uses: the Gulf oil spill, a nuclear disaster in Japan, coal mine collapses, and natural gas explosions; cyclones, tornadoes, floods, droughts, and melting of the Arctic due to climate change; oil wars turning the Middle East into a killing field; and collapsing economies around the world due to skyrocketing energy prices. The question is, is there a solution? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Conceding that time is critical, Dr. Kamal asserts that the answer is yes, and, from a holistic perspective, charts the transition to a sustainable path of innovation, renewable energy, and peace. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;He will show examples of exciting applications of renewable energy technologies-including photovoltaics, wind turbines, hydroelectric generators, solar thermal systems, solar greenhouses, solar cookers and biogas plants-combining innovative policies, incentives and financing options, which are opening up new possibilities around the world, inspiring solutions to our self-destructive reliance on fossil and nuclear fuels, while providing energy resources for an increasing quality of life in growing economies.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Dr. Kamal&lt;/strong&gt;: Dr. Sajed Kamal, EdD, teaches in the Sustainable International Development program at Brandeis University.&amp;nbsp; He has been involved in the field for more than thirty years, setting up projects in the United States, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Armenia and El Salvador.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;In 2007 he was awarded Boston "Mayor's First Annual Green Award for Community Leadership in Energy and Climate Protection", and in 2008 a "Lifetime Achievement Award" by the U. S. Environmental Protection Agency.&amp;nbsp; "The Greener Issue" of The Boston Sunday Globe Magazine on September 28, 2008, featured him as one of the "Six local heroes whose work is having rippling effects-at home and far away-in making the world a better place."&amp;nbsp; An award-winning poet, artist, translator, educational consultant, psychotherapist and author of more than a dozen books and many articles in a wide range of areas, his most recent book is, The Renewable Revolution: How We Can Fight Climate Change, Prevent Energy Wars, Revitalize the Economy and Transition to a Sustainable Future (Earthscan, 2011).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305247092000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304514520000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Renewable Revolution</name><id>17539783</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305243000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/17539783/</event_url></item>