<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-990-7411</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213795</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Why have the churches for centuries created so many rules and regulations that have stripped the spirit out of worship and praise of God? Why is it if you do all the &amp;ldquo;right things&amp;rdquo; you still feel incomplete or wrong? Isn&amp;rsquo;t it time you understood the truth? Meet Mother Clare, Christian Master Teacher, she will teach you the difference between spirituality and religion and guide you to the return of a deep spiritual consciousness.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare Watts is an ordained Priest and Master Teacher in the Order of Christ-Sophia. She began her early training in the late 1970's and was ordained a Minister-Deacon in 1984. She served as such in Kentucky and in Massachusetts, where she was ordained a Priest in 1996 and a Master Teacher in 2001.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare founded the Boston Center of Light, formerly called the Christ-Sophia Center, where she continued to serve until 2001. At that time she moved to Seattle to begin a new Center of Light. Mother Clare has now moved to Dolores Colorado, where she is busy building another Center of Light with Reverend Meira, as well as helping develop the Sophia Peace Center. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare worked as a Certified Professional Midwife for 18 years, having her own midwifery practices in Kentucky and Massachusetts. She received her Masters Degree in 1996 in Counseling Psychology. Mother Clare attended three years of postgraduate training in Jungian Analysis at the Boston Jung Institute. She had her own psychotherapy practice alongside her midwifery practice until she ended both in 2001 in order to attend full-time to her work as a Priest and Master Teacher. Mother Clare has four grown children. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare is the author of an autobiographical book chronicling her life of spiritual seeking and the process that led to her being ordained into spiritual Mastery in the Christian mystical tradition. Please visit www.MotherClareWatts.com, to read excerpts and order her book, Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path to Enlightenment. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Suggested Donation: $35 - Lunch Included - Bring a Friend for Free!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307805886000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306370786000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spirituality Not Religion with Mother Clare</name><id>19758351</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307800800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/19758351/</event_url></item>