<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Cushing Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.583423</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1285089</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802296</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let’s meet at &lt;a href="http://www.chaibo.com" target="_blank"&gt;Chaibo &lt;/a&gt;in Fitchburg to discuss &lt;i&gt;Persuasion&lt;/i&gt; by Jane Austen. This downtown coffee, tea and fondue bar features plush comfortable seating areas perfect for a book club! They also serve an assortment of Cheesecake Factory cheesecakes, or if you're hankering for something more substantial try one of their many unique Paninis, grilled cheese or plain ol' PB&amp;amp;J! Chaibo is located directly behind Destare, where we had our April book discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a description of the book from Amazon.com:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Anne Elliot, heroine of Austen's last novel, did something we can all relate to: Long ago, she let the love of her life get away. In this case, she had allowed herself to be persuaded by a trusted family friend that the young man she loved wasn't an adequate match, social stationwise, and that Anne could do better. The novel opens some seven years after Anne sent her beau packing, and she's still alone. But then the guy she never stopped loving comes back from the sea. As always, Austen's storytelling is so confident, you can't help but allow yourself to be taken on the enjoyable journey.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And from an Amazon reviewer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; Persuasion is a great literary work, and, to my mind, Jane Austen's finest book. This was her final completed novel before her death, and was published posthumously. As is often the case with Ms. Austen's fiction, &amp;quot;Persuasion&amp;quot; deals with the social issues of the times and paints a fascinating portrait of Regency England, especially when dealing with the class system. Rigid social barriers existed - and everyone wanted to marry &amp;quot;up&amp;quot; to a higher station - and, of course, into wealth. This is also a very poignant and passionate story of love, disappointment, loss and redemption. The point Austen makes here, is that one should not ever be persuaded to abandon core values and beliefs, especially for ignoble goals. There are consequences, always&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservations will be under "Heather" or "Book Club". </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277485543000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275187362000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Persuasion by Jane Austen</name><id>13636487</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277420400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/13636487/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/1/global_11643361.jpeg</photo_url></item>