<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi, Everybody -  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This day sounds perfect for a great hike, bird watch, and picnic in the wilderness areas surrounding the Ipswich River!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link to the Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/Ipswich_River/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massaudubo...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The directions that are on the web site are fine; only thing being that you have to look carefully for a very small white sign on the turn off Route 97 - and again for the turn into the wildlife center, which is about another mile or so after you make that turn. The address is 87 Perkins Row (not Perkins Lane). Just send me an e-mail if you have any questions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure and pack along a big picnic lunch and beverages (suggestion:  pack lunch in a lightweight cooler or with dry ice to keep your lunch cool until we eat).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the leisurely and relaxing pace of this outing, I am estimating that the hike (including the picnic) will last approximately 4 hours, depending on how often we stop to watch for birds.  Bring along your camera and binoculars - and of course a can of bug spray!!.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My best estimate for total hiking distance is about 6 miles give or take.  This hike is best designed for those that have no day end deadlines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that the sanctuary does charge a $4 per person entrance fee. For those who wish to carpool, there is a convenient Park and Ride lot which is located at Exit 57 off Route 95, which is the Newburyport / West Newbury / Route 113 ramp.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will look forward to seeing you then!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy  &lt;br /&gt;RandyS@maine.rr.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Once you turn left into the parking lot, go straight and turn right towards the back and look for a silver Subaru Forester.  We will meet near there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1280788106000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277634828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike and Picnic Lunch in Ipswich!</name><id>13923527</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280584800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/13923527/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/d/global_6592605.jpeg</photo_url></item>