<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>128 Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.130001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>University of New Hampshire, Whittemore Center</name><city>Durham</city><id>351772</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.980003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Just Announced:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Support Ron Paul at this presidential debate co-hosted by Fox News, the University of New Hampshire and the New Hampshire Republican State Committee. Held at the Whittemore Center on the campus of the University of New Hampshire the debate will be aired live on Fox News, Fox Radio and four NH radio stations; WGIR, WGIP, WGIN, and WTSL. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to one source at www.ronpaulforums.com as of  Sept.2 there were 114&lt;br /&gt;Ron Paul supporters with tickets for the debate. Organizers are planning for an audience of 4000. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THERE IS A PRE-DEBATE RALLY AT 5:30 FOR ALL RON PAUL SUPPORTERS. SEE &lt;a href="http://ronpaul.meetup.com/6/calendar/6219217/"&gt;http://ronpaul.meetup...&lt;/a&gt; FOR DETAILS. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets to the debate and the pre-debate reception are now free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All tickets will be provided at will call  and a valid drivers license will be required. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to the debate the New Hampshire Republican State Committee is co-hosting a pre-debate reception which all debate attendees are invited to attend.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ron Paul rally: 5:30&lt;br /&gt;6:00 pm- 8:00 pm Pre-Debate Reception featuring prominent political and media personalities&lt;br /&gt;8:30 pm Doors close to the Whittemore Center (no guests will be admitted after this time)&lt;br /&gt;9:oo pm- 10:30 pm First in the Fall Presidential Debate &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE  TICKETS HERE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you are aware, this Wednesday September 5th the NH GOP has the distinct pleasure of hosting the First in the Fall presidential debate with Fox News at the University of New Hampshire?s Whittemore Center. A number of the debates sponsoring organizations that purchased large blocks of tickets are not going to be using them all, and as a ticket holder, we wanted to first offer them to you. Do you have a family member, relative, or friend that would like to attend but does not have a ticket yet?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Let us know today! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: NH GOP &amp;amp; Fox News Presidential Debate&lt;br /&gt;When: Wednesday, September 5&lt;br /&gt;Time: Pre-Debate Reception 6-8, Debate 9-10:30&lt;br /&gt;Where: The Whittemore Center, The University of New Hampshire&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please find information on ticketing, attendance, parking, etc. below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen DeMaura&lt;br /&gt;Executive Director&lt;br /&gt;NH Republican State Committee&lt;br /&gt;Office: (603) 225-9341&lt;br /&gt;Cell: (603) 801-7620&lt;br /&gt;steve@nhgop.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: All tickets are available at will call. Will call will be setup at both the Pre-Debate Reception (Lundholm Gymnasium) and the Whittemore Center. Tickets MUST be in the name of the person receiving them. A photo identification is necessary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: Event parking is in LOT A at the Whittemore Center. Police will be at the entrance to direct the flow of vehicles. In the case of overflow, shuttle buses have been setup to bring people to the Whittemore Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Pre-Debate Reception: Join the NH GOP for a fun pre-debate reception featuring some of the top political personalities in the country. A pasta buffet and cash bar will be available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ureneck</member_name><member_id>4211251</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189211742000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187730488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presidential Debate in New Hampshire</name><id>6220103</id><headcount>649</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189038600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/6220103/</event_url></item>