<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Salem State Series 2010 Presents: Dr. Deepak Chopra&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acknowledged as one of the world's greatest leaders in the field of mind body medicine, &lt;br /&gt;Deepak Chopra, continues to transform our understanding of the meaning of health.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Thursday, September 23, 2010&lt;br /&gt;General Admission $20 for Bleacher seats&lt;br /&gt;Programs begin at 8 pm in the&lt;br /&gt;Salem State O'Keefe Sports Center&lt;br /&gt;225 Canal Street, Salem, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets Contact Candita at 781 834-2728&lt;br /&gt;Please note that a $4 handling fee is applied to all purchases&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;California in 1996, Dr. Chopra established a formal vehicle for the expansion of his healing approach using the integration of the best of western medicine with natural healing traditions, in both conventional and complementary healing arts. Dr. Chopra’s work is changing the way the world views physical, mental, emotional, spiritual, and social wellness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Chopra is known as the prolific author of over 56 books, more than 100 audio, video and CD-ROM titles. Many know him from his regular work with PBS, which includes The Happiness Prescription, Soul of Healing: Body, Mind, and Soul and Body, Mind and Soul: The Mystery and The Magic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Chopra’s popularity as an international presenter and keynote speaker is exemplified in an impressive list of honorariums. As the keynote speaker, he appeared at the inauguration of the State of the World Forum, hosted by Mikhail Gorbachev and the Peace and Human Progress Foundation, founded by the former president of Costa Rica and Nobel Peace prizewinner Oscar Arias. In 1995, he joined the distinguished company of President Nelson Mandela, Congresswoman Barbara Jordan, Tom Peters, and Garrison Keillor as a recipient of the Toastmasters International Top Five Outstanding Speakers award.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through The Chopra Center, Dr. Chopra is revolutionizing common wisdom about the crucial connection between body, mind, spirit, and healing. His mission of “bridging the technological miracles of the west with the wisdom of the east” remains his thrust as he and his colleagues conduct public seminars and workshops and provide training for health care professionals around the world.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>rain phillips</member_name><member_id>7240421</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>7932349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285291095000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285078322000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salem State Series 2010 Presents: Dr. Deepak Chopra</name><id>14844119</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285286400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/14844119/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/c/global_18140044.jpeg</photo_url></item>