<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ok You Nature Lovers- This one is for you. I love Eddie Soloway's photography- I've been trying for years to get him to come and lecture with us here in Central MA- and since he was in Boston with the National Geographic Lecture Series- I've lured him to Worcester! Yes- he's finally finally he has agreed to come to Worcester! Please- Please come to this event! It's going to be a fun and unique lecture!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Memories, Moons, and Imagination:  Re-kindling a Passion for Photographing the Landscape&lt;br /&gt;with Eddie Soloway&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you like the outdoors yet find that your images keep looking like pretty postcards? Or perhaps you’ve been distracted by cameras, pixels, and software at the expense of building your vision. Join Eddie Soloway for a fun presentation meant to re-charge your sense of wonder and help stretch your vision into new image-making.  At the end of the presentation Eddie will take a behind-the-scenes look at fifteen photographs, giving you concrete ideas and tools to break out of your box.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Eddie Soloway’s photographs (www.eddiesoloway.com) are the expression of his passion and commitment to the natural world. His eye has developed during a lifetime of exploring the earth’s wild places. Former positions in educational workshop design, wilderness program development, and custom fine photographic printing have further honed his expertise. In 1998, Eddie was the first recipient of the Excellence in Photographic Teaching Award presented by the Santa Fe Center for Photography. Today he divides his time between making fine-art prints, teaching, speaking on creativity and the photographic life, and furthering photographic publishing projects. His first book, One Thousand Moons, was published in the summer of 2004, and the dvd, A Natural Eye – Big Sur was released in December, 2009. An impassioned teacher, Eddie brings experiences in both nature and photography to his workshops and seminars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $20.00 at the door - so if you RSVP please show up! Other wise someone else could have been there!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.eddiesoloway.com&lt;br /&gt;eddie@eddiesoloway.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you come in the door, head to the Right and enter the tavern!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270078774000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268665329000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Re-kindling a Passion for Photographing the Landscape with Eddie Soloway</name><id>12880671</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269702000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/12880671/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/3/global_13676755.jpeg</photo_url></item>