<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1627 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.339172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-566-3340</phone><name>Restaurant Vernissage</name><city>Brookline</city><id>964524</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.135521</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello, everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As some of you may notice, I stepped up as an organizer of this Meetup couple of month ago.  I have to admit that while being busy with summer real estate market I was not very available to create any new discussion groups or seminars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, with the summer season slowly wining down (I know, I know...{)- I am really looking forward to organize, lead and facilitate some fun, informal and informational events which will lead us to more great sales and purchases in my beloved field of Real estate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also lead Boston Real Estate Salon Meetup and for September seminar I would like to combine both Meetups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thus, I will post below the description from the Boston Real Estate Salon Meetup and I am really looking forward to see you all there, get to know you and your real estate needs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September, 28 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seminar:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO FIND A BARGAIN IN REAL ESTATE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Where: Restaurant “Vernissage”, 1627 Beacon street, Brookline &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Program: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;7-7:30 pm:       refreshments &lt;br /&gt;7:30- 8 pm:      presentation in current topics/trends/news/market updates  &lt;br /&gt;8-8:30 pm:       Q And A &lt;br /&gt;8:30-9:30 pm:  eat, mingle, and network &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come, eat, drink, have fun, meet people and learn!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll discuss a variety of topics that are related to building your understanding of real estate so that you can participate in the market the way you've always wanted to. If you want to be not only engaged in short-term transactions of your interest (e.g. selling, buying, renting) but to do so with knowledge, vision and long-term planning for your desired outcomes in the field of Real Estate-this is the place for you! Join us for series of ongoing events, workshops and monthly updates and learn, plan and build your successful Real Estate Portfolio! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  VISIONARY FOUNDER  &lt;br /&gt;Olga is a distinguished licensed Real Estate Professional with more than 15 years of experience and numerous awards in her field. She is a top broker, real estate coach, and consultant. Olga has assisted hundreds of clients to successfully reach their goals in Real Estate. Olga enjoys teaching Real Estate basics and principles as well as new and innovative up-to-date strategies. In addition to having her own weekly radio show, she has led the Boston Real Estate Salon for the past 2 years and has conducted numerous seminars on a variety of real estate topics. Olga is not only a broker-she has been a homeowner, landlord and developer of many years. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olga</member_name><member_id>4801208</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285719397000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New Normal RE Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>GreaterBostonREIClub</urlname><id>320990</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Real Estate Investing Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282864930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Find a Bargain in Real Estate</name><id>14555798</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285714800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/GreaterBostonREIClub/events/14555798/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/global_8928220.jpeg</photo_url></item>