<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear friends:&lt;br /&gt;  Mary Alice and Ben would like to invite you to their house at Lexington for Tao Te Ching discussion on 4/10.&lt;br /&gt;  Here is the information.  Please mark your calendar.  RSVP if you are able to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date:    4-10-2010 (Saturday)&lt;br /&gt;Time:    &lt;br /&gt;         1:30 to 2:00: Social time&lt;br /&gt;         2:00 to 4:00: Discussion&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;br /&gt;Chapter: 63&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;         Chapter 63 &lt;br /&gt;Translations by S. Mitchell &lt;br /&gt;Act without doing; work without effort.&lt;br /&gt;Think of the small as large&lt;br /&gt;and the few as many. &lt;br /&gt;Confront the difficult while it is still easy; &lt;br /&gt;accomplish the great task by a series of small acts. &lt;br /&gt;The Master never reaches for the great;&lt;br /&gt;thus she achieves greatness. &lt;br /&gt;When she runs into a difficulty,&lt;br /&gt;she stops and gives herself to it.&lt;br /&gt;She doesn't cling to her own comfort;&lt;br /&gt;thus problems are no problem for her. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Translations by Goddard &lt;br /&gt;One should avoid assertion (Wu Wei) and practice inaction. One should learn to find taste in the tasteless, to enlarge the small things, and multiply the few. &lt;br /&gt;He should respond to hatred with kindness. &lt;br /&gt;He should resolve a difficulty while it is easy, and manage a great thing while it is small. &lt;br /&gt;Surely all the world's difficulties arose from slight causes, and all the world's great affairs had small beginnings. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Therefore the wise man avoids to the end participation in great affairs and by so doing establishes his greatness. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Rash promises are lacking in faith and many things that appear easy are full of difficulties. &lt;br /&gt;Therefore the wise man considers every thing difficult and so to the end he has no difficulties. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Translations by Legge &lt;br /&gt;(It is the way of the Tao) to act without (thinking of) acting; to conduct affairs without (feeling the) trouble of them; to taste without discerning any flavour; to consider what is small as great,&lt;br /&gt;and a few as many; &lt;br /&gt;And to recompense injury with kindness. &lt;br /&gt;(The master of it) anticipates things that are difficult while they are easy, and does things that would become great while they are small. &lt;br /&gt;All difficult things in the world are sure to arise from a previous state in which they were easy, and all great things from one in which they were small. &lt;br /&gt;Therefore the sage, while he never does what is great, is able on that account to accomplish the greatest things. &lt;br /&gt;He who lightly promises is sure to keep but little faith; he who is continually thinking things easy is sure to find them difficult. &lt;br /&gt;Therefore the sage sees difficulty even in what seems easy, and so never has any difficulties. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#31532;63&amp;#31456; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#28858;&amp;#28961;&amp;#28858;&amp;#65292;&amp;#20107;&amp;#28961;&amp;#20107;&amp;#65292;&amp;#21619;&amp;#28961;&amp;#21619;&amp;#12290; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#22823;&amp;#23567;&amp;#22810;&amp;#23569;&amp;#65292;&amp;#22577;&amp;#24616;&amp;#20197;&amp;#24503;&amp;#12290; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#22294;&amp;#38627;&amp;#26044;&amp;#20854;&amp;#26131;&amp;#65292;&amp;#22294;&amp;#22823;&amp;#26044;&amp;#20854;&amp;#32048;&amp;#12290; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#22825;&amp;#19979;&amp;#38627;&amp;#20107;&amp;#65292;&amp;#24517;&amp;#20316;&amp;#26044;&amp;#26131;&amp;#12290; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#22825;&amp;#19979;&amp;#22823;&amp;#20107;&amp;#65292;&amp;#24517;&amp;#20316;&amp;#26044;&amp;#32048;&amp;#12290; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#26159;&amp;#20197;&amp;#32854;&amp;#20154;&amp;#32066;&amp;#19981;&amp;#28858;&amp;#22823;&amp;#65292;&amp;#25925;&amp;#33021;&amp;#25104;&amp;#20854;&amp;#22823;&amp;#12290; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#22827;&amp;#36629;&amp;#35582;&amp;#24517;&amp;#23521;&amp;#20449;&amp;#65292;&amp;#22810;&amp;#26131;&amp;#24517;&amp;#22810;&amp;#38627;&amp;#65307; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#26159;&amp;#20197;&amp;#32854;&amp;#20154;&amp;#29494;&amp;#38627;&amp;#20043;&amp;#65292;&amp;#25925;&amp;#32066;&amp;#28961;&amp;#38627;&amp;#30691;&amp;#65281; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://spirituality.meetup.com/149/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You can call me at 617-223-7166, if you can not find the place</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan</member_name><member_id>4981726</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271096083000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spirituality-149</urlname><id>670379</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5999984741</group_lon><name>The Westborough Spirituality Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270003289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TaoTe Ching April discussion</name><id>13044256</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270922400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/events/13044256/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/6/global_2055446.jpeg</photo_url></item>