<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 Main St #14</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.346626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Earthsong Yoga</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>1510084</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.549316</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: Class cancelled due to storm clean up, etc.  Please join us instead on March 22nd for the same class!  See calendar to RSVP.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Are you aware of the many benefits of meditating, but can’t get yourself to do it or you think it’s too difficult?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meditation can be one of the easiest and most effective means to living with greater harmony, happiness and well-being. It’s an opportunity to peacefully transform your problems, your fears, and any pain and stress in your life into something more positive and to allow what you desire to manifest! And, it's a great way to set or shift into the perfect mood for your day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don’t have to sit in silence for long periods of time to gain the multitude of emotional and physical benefits!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;By participating in this Introduction to Meditation Class, you’ll experience how simple, delightful and easy it can be. You’ll learn:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some simple techniques you can easily do for yourself for any length of time that is comfortable for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to easily get into a meditative state and create pleasurable feelings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to get yourself to use it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What you can use meditation for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to make it easy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We will &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not&lt;/span&gt; be doing traditional silent meditations. The class will consist of 2-3 guided meditations, with discussion and instruction in between. All you have to do is listen to Ann’s voice as she leads you through the process, like listening to a good story.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP "yes", please be considerate of Ann and others, and either show up, or let us know of your change in plans so we won't be waiting for you or leaving someone on a waiting list unnecessarily. Anyone is welcome, so please feel free to invite others to join you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;“I'm new to guided meditation, but figured, why not? Ann walked us through three meditations that seemed to go by very quickly. I was surprised how easy it was, and how relaxed I was at the end of the first one. Since putting these simple techniques into practice, I feel like I can screen out external noise much more effectively, and I've been able to reach amazing levels of peace and even joy and wonder while meditating already. Thank you, Ann!” Chuck M.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;“I have never meditated before. It has always been hard for me to get difficult thoughts out of my head. Tonight I really relaxed and seemed to go into another world. It was great. Thanks!” Susy C.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;“Your meditations showed how easy it can be to focus – something I usually think of as an effort. Thanks, it was really nice!” John H.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann can coach you to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, you’ll become able to more easily create the happiness you desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This free public event is being co-sponsored by Earthsong Yoga and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service, and is being shared with you because of it's relevancy to being an effective, joyful, deliberate creator. Thank you Earthsong Yoga!  &lt;a href="http://www.earthsongyoga.com"&gt;www.earthsongyoga.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's the big, old Corey building, only sign is on sidewalk.  Studio is upstairs, in room 14. Easy parking</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362794513000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361136211000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE experiential class on Meditation Can Be Easy!</name><id>105057812</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>6300000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362788100000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/105057812/</event_url></item>