<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Intersection of Rt 1 and 128</address_2><address_1>950 Providence Hwy</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02026</zip><lat>42.232470</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-232-8900</phone><name>Legacy Place</name><city>Dedham</city><id>1028960</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.179692</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT UPDATE: Due to weather forecast of high heat this event has been moved inside with AC at Legacy Place next to PF Changs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please Update your RSVPs and answer the ticket purchase question for this event. A Yes RSVP with the Natives does not give you event admission. You must purchase a ticket on line for this event. See the link below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/4/0/0/event_119913792.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Legacy Place in Dedham is excited to present their first outdoor event on the roof top of the Legacy Place parking garage. Taste of Legacy Place Under the Stars will take place on Thursday, June 21st, 2012 from 630pm-9pm. Proceeds from the event will benefit The Italian Home for Children. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Major sponsors of the event: Subaru of New England, Carmen &amp;amp; Karen Monks &amp;amp; Whole Foods Market Dedham. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Guests can expect to feast on delicious tastings from the following establishments: &lt;br /&gt;

Aquitaine, Au Bon Pain, b.good, Chocolate Therapy, Genki Japanese Restaurant, J.P. Licks, Kings, Legal C Bar, Met Bar &amp;amp; Grill, P.F. Chang's China Bistro, Qdoba Mexican Grill, Studio 3 Restaurant &amp;amp; Bar, Sugar Heaven, Wicked Restaurant &amp;amp; Wine Bar, Whole Foods Market, Williams-Sonoma and Yard House. Enjoy music, try your luck at the Legacy Raffle, and bid on marvelous “Experience” Live Auction packages. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The Italian Home for Children offers its help to children ages 4-14 in their residential &amp;amp; day treatment programs and through educational services. These children may have learning disabilities or emotional, behavioral and mental health concerns brought on by trauma in their home, school or community. Unfortunately, many children and families are faced with overcoming these situations alone, but with help from the Italian Home, these issues are oftentimes resolved. The Italian Home for Children provides these boys and girls with the best education, care and treatment so they can thrive at home or in their community. With individualized therapies and around-the-clock nurturing, The Italian Home helps children to rebuild their lives - emotionally and academically. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Tickets: $30 per person / $35 at the event. For information &amp;amp; to purchase tickets on-line, please visit: &lt;a href="http://ihc.convio.net/site/PageServer?pagename=TasteofLegacyPlace" class="linkified"&gt;http://ihc.convio.net/site/PageServer?pagename=TasteofLegacyPlace&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Tickets can also be purchased by calling The Italian Home for Children at 617-524-3116 and ask for Julie Clerc. Due to inclement, the event will take place at 430 Legacy Place (next to P.F. Chang’s). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Celebrate the beginning of summer Under the Stars while enjoying great food, mingling &amp;amp; tapping your feet to great music and supporting a worthy cause. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will E Mail RSVPs the day before the event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol O'Connor</member_name><member_id>9130755</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340769136000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337100911000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taste of Legacy Place Under the Stars</name><id>64896652</id><headcount>270</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340317800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/64896652/</event_url></item>