<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's an opportunity to spend the evening making art with friends!&lt;/strong&gt; journal, work on your chunky-book pages, sketchbook, ATC's -- or tackle any other art project that tickles your fancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIME:&lt;/strong&gt; 7 p.m. to 10pm (with an opportunity to stay later if there is an interest!). Come and leave whenever you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; Yourself, your art supplies and whatever project you’d like to work on. Bring your own beverage. Feel free to bring a snack to share—but that’s entirely optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; $10, regardless of how long you stay. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;This fee helps keep ArtStudio 360 open, so we can't accept IOUs or partial payments&lt;/span&gt;; please plan to pay when you arrive. We're happy to direct you to a nearby ATM if you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.) and some supplies including acrylic paints, collage materials, embellishments, paper and more. Access to a microwave, toaster oven, refrigerator, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND&lt;/strong&gt;: Anyone (18+ only, please). Just RSVP through the NE ATC+ Meetup Group. Membership in the Meetup group is free; joining simply allows you to reserve a space in events at ArtStudio 360.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt; These smaller sessions often fill quickly. Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly so that your space becomes available to someone else. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; In the unlikely event that we need to cancel due to bad weather or other reasons---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;NEW POLICY REGARDING RSVPs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Your RSVP is a reservation, and we're trusting that you'll honor it. If you can't make it, please change your RSVP from "yes" to "no" before the event start time. Everybody forgets once in awhile, but repeated no-shows--people who RSVP "yes" but then don't show up--may be asked to pay in advance for future events.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>emelengy</member_name><member_id>4250560</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342886132000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342311512000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Studio Time: Start your weekend with Art</name><id>ddzcxcyqkbbc</id><duration>10800000</duration><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342825200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/73371622/</event_url></item>