<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The CTNites.com VIP Entertainment Club Has Invited Us:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEETUP IS BETWEEN 6:30and 6:45, SEATING STARTS AT 6:30. The Show starts at 7:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VIP CLUB FUNNY BONE REGULARS - PLEASE KEEP AN EYE OUT FOR THE NEW PEOPLE AND HELP THEM GET SEATED AT OUR TABLES.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wacky Wednesday At The Funny Bone Comedy Club&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Buckland Hills Mall&lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06040&lt;br /&gt;(860)-432-8600&lt;br /&gt;www.HartfordFunnyBone.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is FREE every Wednesday Nite with a Funny Bone T-Shirt (T-Shirts cost $15)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for Our CTNites.com VIP Entertainment Club Table Signs, and Join Us For A Great Nite Of Comedy!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After the show, join us at: &lt;br /&gt;Time-Out Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill &lt;br /&gt;346 West Middle Turnpike &lt;br /&gt;(Manchester Parkade) &lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06040 &lt;br /&gt;649-7400 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All CTNites.com VIP Clubbers will receive a 10% discount on everything!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The food is much better and less expensive than at the Funny Bone, so save your appetite for Time-Out after the Comedy show! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Time-Out from the Funny Bone Comedy Club:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:Start out going SOUTH on BUCKLAND ST toward TOLLAND TURNPIKE.&lt;br /&gt;0.1 miles&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;2:Stay STRAIGHT to go onto ADAMS ST.&lt;br /&gt;1.1 miles&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;3:Turn LEFT onto MIDDLE TURNPIKE W.&lt;br /&gt;0.5 miles&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;4:Take A Right at light to Manchester Parkade, Time Out is on Left by the Stairs&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Total Est. Time: 4 minutes     Total Est. Distance: 1.75 miles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you get lost, call Robert at (860) 569-8094&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Headliner: J. Medicine Hat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is the best way to maximize your entertainment dollar? Combine two types of entertainment! Stage Hypnosis &amp;amp; Standup Comedy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J. Medicine Hat has been a fixture in the comedy club scene for over 20 years. He started his career in the early 80's as a Stand-up Comedian, Star Search soon followed along with Showtime, HBO, MTV and VH1.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a gig in 1993 as an opening act for another hypnotist J. had the so-called-light-bulb-moment. Add Hypnosis and be the King. Comedy and Hypnosis in tandem... Hypo-Comedy was born.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since rust never sleeps, J. has become the pacesetter not the follower in the area of hypnosis. His shows are sold out over and over in venues across the country. Colleges, casinos and comedy clubs sing the praises of his ability to out sell and out perform any other entertainer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.CTNites.com/Events/FunnyBone.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Click Here For Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542507000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193945964000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy Nite- Wacky Wednesday At The Funny Bone Comedy Club Nov 7</name><id>6657504</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194478200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6657504/</event_url></item>