<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIme:&lt;/strong&gt; 11am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt; Gate 8 (boat launch area) past Gate 5 to shore (we'll spot a car at Gate 5).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate with some hills; 7 miles (estimated)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The boat launch should give us some gorgeous southern views. Normally, you pay and park in the lot on the shore, but boat-launch season is over, so we'll park at the gate. (You won't be able to drive all the way to the shore as shown on the map.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll walk to the launch and enjoy our first view of Quabbin Reservoir. Then we'll head up and along the ridge, parallel to the shore and 202, to Gate 5. Past Gate 5, this shoreline is as far south as we can get before we hit the DCR restricted area. We'll be able to see both Winsor Dam and the Visitor's Center from here! Then we'll head back to Gate 5 and carpool back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No wading nor pets; Quabbin is a public water supply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please remove your trash from the premises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dress in light layers; walking hills makes you warm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bug repellant highly recommended; there are still deer ticks in some areas, though we'll be on old roads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring enough to drink and a snack or lunch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There may or may not be an outhouse near one of the gates...I haven't been to this one yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Northeast and Northwest:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 122 or 2 to Route 202. Head south on 202 for about 20 minutes. Roughly 10 miles down, you'll pass a flashing yellow light at the intersection of 202 (Daniel Shays Highway) and Amherst Rd (where the Pelham Historical Society is inside an old white church on the right). Continue straight about 2.5 miles. You will see a blue sign for "Swift River Candle Company." Turn left onto Packardville Rd. Drive to the yellow gate and park in the cleared area on the side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from South, West, and East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 east or west to Route 202 north and continue straight about 4.5 miles. Look for a blue "Swift River Candle Company" sign and a "Caution: Low Salt Area" sign. Turn right onto Packardville Rd. Drive to the yellow gate and park in the cleared area on the side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just drive down Packardville road as far as you can (until the yellow gate)!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324397766000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324096011000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Hike @ Quabbin Resevoir: Gate 8 to Gate 5</name><id>44714402</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324310400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/44714402/</event_url></item>