<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Due to circumstances beyond our control, Roomba was not able to accommodate our group's very discriminating palates. Roomba operates with limited seatings and being an intimate restaurant, is not an ideal setting for our very well-attended dining group event. I didn't have the heart to randomly remove eight RSVPs to accommodate Roomba. Perhaps we'll try Roomba again in the near future with a limit of 12 members. So, when you see the event posting, get your RSVP out there fast! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite the technical difficulties, I remain undaunted and have a reservation for 20 at Bentara, a very well review Malaysian restaurant in New Haven. I've attached a review for your convenience. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Same plan, different restaurant. We'll be stepping out after for drinks and dancing - FYI! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DINING OUT; Stylish Decor, Abundance of Asian Fare  &lt;br /&gt;Print Save  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By PATRICIA BROOKS  &lt;br /&gt;Published: October 18, 1998 &lt;br /&gt;AS a university town, New Haven has long had a concentration of ethnic restaurants, but we can't think of any as stylish as Bentara. The space is warehouse large, with high ceilings and well-spaced tables in several dining areas. A cavernous look is avoided by extremely sophisticated decorating: shadow puppets projected onto three screens in the rear, Malaysian baskets stacked in a corner near the large front windows, a bamboo screen separating the bar area, niches displaying subtle, well-chosen handcrafts.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Malaysian is one of the lesser known Asian cuisines, but diners with a hankering for Chinese, Indonesian, Indian and Thai cooking will find certain compatible ingredients and culinary styles.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each dish is carefully described to avoid confusion. As a safe haven of familiarity, beef satay was one of our starters -- marinated, grilled and skewered beef, prettily served with red onions, cucumber slices and coconut-peanut sauce -- deeply flavored but predictable. We opted also for the less familiar roti murtabak: small squares of unleavened ghee bread filled with a mixture of ground beef, onions and eggs, jazzed up by two zesty dips, curry and chopped sweet-sour red onion.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other worthy appetizers were the curry mussels (with slivered onions, green peppers and tomatoes in a delicate curry sauce), Manila clams (with onions and pimientos in a clear broth redolent of lemongrass, garlic and scallions) and pechal (a warm salad with blanched water spinach, bean sprouts, green beans, hard-boiled egg slices and a sassy shrimp paste-peanut sauce).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of our entrees were standouts. Especially notable were rendang (chicken sprinkled with black sesame seeds, tofu, Chinese eggplant chunks and green beans in a lemongrass-spiked coconut curry) and Asam pedas seafood (a fish/shrimp/ calamari stew with Chinese eggplant, green beans and tomatoes in a subtle hot-sour tamarind broth).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also worth one's attention was udang goreng pedas, which consisted of hot and spicy shrimp with slivered onions and green beans.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu is attractive to vegetarians, with many noodle dishes and soups. We were keen on goreng kang kong -- stir-fried water spinach (kang kong) with onions, garlic, roasted red pepper strips, and hot chilies, with a shower of black sesame seeds on top. We ordered it with a piquant shrimp paste, but it is available without.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our most controversial dish was nasi lemak, a mixture of hot and spicy stir-fried beef and dried anchovies fried until crunchy, tossed with pulverized hot chilies, garlic and ginger. The plate was adorned with whole peanuts, hard-boiled egg and cucumber slices, with a mound of sweet-tasting rice (boiled in coconut milk) in the center. On balance, we liked all the taste and textural challenges, though the anchovy-beef mixture was certainly a novelty to Western palates. We punctuated our feast with coconut sorbet, fittingly served in a bowl resembling an inner coconut shell.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner for two, three courses apiece, came to $45.80, before tax, tip and drinks. The wine list had many interesting choices from France, California and elsewhere, extremely well-priced from $14; there is also a surprisingly good beer selection.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bentara  &lt;br /&gt;76 Orange Street, New Haven.  &lt;br /&gt;(203) 562-2511  &lt;br /&gt;Very Good  &lt;br /&gt;Atmosphere --A spacious ground floor corner dining room with high ceilings and exposed brick wall, in a restored building, decorated with Southeast Asian artifacts.  &lt;br /&gt;Service -- Skillful, friendly and professional.  &lt;br /&gt;Recommended dishes -- Roti murtabak, Manila clams, curry mussels, satay, pechal, rendang, kerutuk, asam pedas seafood, goreng kang kong, udang goreng pedas, nasi lemak, coconut sorbet.  &lt;br /&gt;Price range -- Lunch entrees $5.95 to $9.95, dinner entrees $5.95 to $20.95.  &lt;br /&gt;Credit cards -- Most major cards.  &lt;br /&gt;Hours -- Lunch 11:30 A.M. to 3:30 P.M. daily, dinner 5 to 10:30 &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165192455000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1162829128000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A taste of Malaysia (Asian Fare) - Bentara in New Haven!!!</name><id>5247914</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165019400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/5247914/</event_url></item>