<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everybody,  &lt;br /&gt;I've been looking forward to seeing this movie for a few years and missed its recent run at The Brattle. I won't miss this screening and hope our group will include members like me who have never seen it and those that wouldn't mind re-visiting this movie one more time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At first banned in France and then released in an edited format &amp;quot;Rules of the Game&amp;quot; , is now considered a milestone of 20th century film-making. &amp;quot;There are about a dozen genuine miracles in the history of cinema, and one of them is Jean Renoir's supreme 1939 tragi-comedy &amp;quot;The Rules of the Game. &amp;quot; The Chicago Tribune &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.ew.com/ew/article/0,,1556658,00.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ew.com/ew/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dont be put off by Regle du Jeus daunting rep as the masterpiece of French cinema. This is a very accessible, freewheeling kind of classic: at times it even feels almost light-weight and trivial. Almost  but not quite, as its clear theres a lot more going on than just a boisterous weekend party in a country house (the latest examples of Regles influence include Altman's Gosford Park and Bogdanovich's The Cat?s Meow).   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whatever stubborn fragments of the &amp;quot;old&amp;quot; world before the first World War will surely be swept away: this house party is the end of an era. Renoir nimbly deploys the classic elements of French farce: cuckolded husbands, shenanigans above and below stairs, the low comedy of costumes and pratfalls ,  while reminding us that such &amp;quot;innocent&amp;quot; concerns will soon be relegated to the history books.&amp;quot; Neil Young's Jigsaw Lounge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row and then we're off to a local cafe to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175006151000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173395789000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Rules of the Game" at the MFA</name><id>5550629</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174833000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5550629/</event_url></item>