<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>THE FILM WILL BE SHOWN IN THE SCREENING ROOM, THEATER 3.  THIS IS THE SMALL ROOM UPSTAIRS WITH APPROX. 50 SEATS.  PLEASE PURCHASE YOUR TICKET BEFORE RSVP'ING YES.  THE FILL WILL ALMOST CERTAINLY SELL OUT IN ADVANCE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=615521cb-c61a-41c9-abd2-f75643670013&amp;amp;evtinfo=6282~3c2614bd-0781-48b8-a8a2-e21eaa37e962&amp;amp;" target="_blank"&gt;KISSES TICKETS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two kids on the fringes of Dublin, Kylie and Dylan, live in a suburban housing estate devoid of life, color and the prospect of escape. Kylie lives with five other siblings and her overworked mother. Next door, Dylan lives in the shadow of an alcoholic father and the memory of an elder brother who ran away from home two years earlier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a violent altercation with his father, Dylan runs away from home and Kylie decides to run away with him. Together they make their way to the magical night time lights of inner city Dublin, to search for Dylan's brother, and in the hope of finding, through him, the possibility of a new life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Lance Daley, w/ Kelly O'Neill, Shane Curry, 1h12m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the New York Times:&lt;br /&gt;The music of Bob Dylan winds through Lance Daly’s “Kisses” like the call of a twangy pied piper beckoning two preteen runaways deeper into the night as they wander through the streets of Dublin after dark at Christmastime. A small slice of Irish kitchen-sink realism embellished with fairy-tale fantasy, “Kisses” may strike you as either ingeniously magical or insufferably cute, depending on your taste. But more than the story, which circles back on itself, the natural performances of its young stars, Shane Curry and especially Kelly O’Neill, nonprofessional actors, lend the movie a core of integrity. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This '2010' film was screened at the &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Telluride by the Sea Film Festival&lt;/span&gt; in 2008 and I found it to be 'ingeniously magical'.   With an 86% rating on Rotten Tomatoes, it would seem that many agree.  Assistant Organizer Chris and I have talked about this film for two years, and it did have one showing at the Brattle, last year.  Must be something magical to it if it is now getting a wider release. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film is much like &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;The Wizard of Oz&lt;/span&gt;.  A film that begins in  black and white (with subtitles until we get used to the dialect) and becomes an evening in which the children meet the Scarecrow, the Tin Man, the Lion - and the Wicked Witch - all while searching for 'home'.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check to see which theater in which this will be shown.  A small, precious film, &lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kisses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; will be shown in Theater 3.  If so, You MUST purchase your ticket ahead of time, or it will be sold out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=615521cb-c61a-41c9-abd2-f75643670013&amp;amp;evtinfo=6282~3c2614bd-0781-48b8-a8a2-e21eaa37e962&amp;amp;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets for Kisses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a magical evening in Dublin, we'll go to either Zaftigs or Pho Lemongrass to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279239562000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kisses</name><id>14116483</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281292200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14116483/</event_url></item>