<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Hilton Garden Inn, 420 Totten Pond Rd., Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;January 17, 2008 - Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;FLIP THIS HOUSE&amp;quot; STARS FROM CT HOMES - JD ESAJIAN AND JEREMY BLACK &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30 PM - Networking and Meet the Vendors &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 PM - More time to network! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Hilton Garden Inn, 420 Totten Pond Rd, Waltham, Ma. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?How to Flip Home?s in Today?s Real Estate Market?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear Fellow Real Estate Investors, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you looking to jumpstart your real estate investing career and want to learn from two of the nations most successful investors?  Are you interested in learning how systems can make your business run itself without your constant attention?  If so then you will not want to miss the next monthly meeting! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven?t noticed the real estate market has changed drastically in the past 18 months. In fact, it doesn?t look very good out there to the average eye! Prices are flat and some markets are actually declining. Sub-prime lenders have gone out of business by the boatload. Many investors are trying to unload properties as we speak and some are having trouble doing it. Likewise, we know many investors who are sitting on the sidelines just waiting to see what unfolds. Maybe you are too?&lt;br /&gt;So why are we so damn excited?!! The reason we are so excited is because we know the real ?Secret? about how to make money in any market whether it?s going up, down, or sideways. This ?Secret? is what most ultra-wealthy real estate investors don?t want you to know. You see the truth is we have been waiting for years for a market like this to appear. Now that it is finally here we have put on our party hats. The reason is we know there is MORE money to be made in down markets than there is in any market that is on the rise. The reason is there are more buying OPPORTUNITIES because the market has softened. This is why you see the most successful investors buying properties when everyone else is selling.&lt;br /&gt;Why should you take advice from us? Because using these trade secrets over the past four years, the company we have helped build bought and sold over 300 properties in the past few years.&lt;br /&gt;Take a step back and re-evaluate your approach to what you?re doing! You see what stops most people from truly achieving their dreams of financial freedom is their inability to step back and look at the big picture. Most people are stuck in a box. They start down one career path and then get so wrapped up in their work they never step back to see if there is a better way.  We want you to learn how to work smarter not harder! &lt;br /&gt;What if we told you we could show you how to double, triple, or even quadruple your income?  What if you could optimize the changes in the market and make your income GROW!  Well, attend this event! The knowledge we will share with you will revolutionize your business.  &lt;br /&gt;Here?s a Sample of What We Will Cover At the Event:&lt;br /&gt; Rehabbing Properties&lt;br /&gt;? How to acquire rehab deals at 50 cents on the dollar&lt;br /&gt;? How to do the proper due-diligence on when buying wholesale and rehab properties&lt;br /&gt;? How to structure deals using other peoples funds&lt;br /&gt;? How to not get burned when managing a rehab &lt;br /&gt;? How to prepare a property to sell for full price every time&lt;br /&gt;Selling Properties&lt;br /&gt;? Little known strategies to guarantee your property gets sold in today's market &lt;br /&gt;? Marketing techniques to build a huge buyers list &lt;br /&gt;? Today's top mortgage programs for your buyers&lt;br /&gt;? How to automate all of your marketing systems so you can get properties sold at full price!&lt;br /&gt;? How to utilize the power of the internet to get properties sold at lightning speed!&lt;br /&gt;Let us put this event in perspective for you....last year our company bought and sold 104 properties in the State of Connecticut with an average profit of $27,000 using the systems and concepts we will teach you at this event. You do the math and figure out if it is worth the time? When you leave this conference you will be armed with the knowledge of how to rehab and sell properties for HUGE PROFITS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- JD Esajian &amp;amp; Jeremy Black&lt;br /&gt;   CT Homes, LLC &amp;amp; FortuneBuilders Inc.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200781944000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198193651000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association January Meetup</name><id>6946579</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200609000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/6946579/</event_url></item>