<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It was 1985, and Italian chef Crispi Falconeiri had maxed out the space he was renting for his catering business. He was doing too well and needed a bigger stage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He found it on Route 18 in Bridgewater, transforming a small restaurant called Costello's into a chef-owned, family-run Italian dining destination that has been drawing a loyal clientele ever since.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Choosing Crispi's continues our recent run of Italian dining experiences (a theme that we will likely rest for awhile after this event) while giving us a chance to go a bit farther south than we have in some time. Of course we are much more concerned with food than geography, but Crispi's online menu features plenty of interesting items and the kitchen's fulfillment of the menu's promise is expounded upon with real enthusiasm in a couple of &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/crispis-italian-cuisine-and-catering-bridgewater" target="_blank"&gt;Yelp reviews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be heading there at 7:00 PM on Friday, June 12th and look forward to seeing you at the table.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Crispi's Italian Cuisine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;136 Broad Street (Rte 18), Bridgewater&lt;br /&gt;(508) 697-6733&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crispisrestaurant.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crispisres...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maximum number of attendees:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Half-a-dozen pasta dishes come with a house salad and cost $12.00 or less. The majority of entrees run between $15.00 - $18.00, with the menu topping out at $24.00 for a surf &amp;amp; turf.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; No Event Fee for current Annual Members. Other Members and Guests: $2.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Thursday, June 11 at 7:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Crispi's is located on Broad St (Route 18) in Bridgewater, at the point where railroad tracks intersect the road directly across from a strip mall/plaza w/ Roche Brothers, Dunkin Donuts and Burger King.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: The best route to take is Route 18 South.  Follow through East Bridgewater Center, past the movie theather, past a couple sets of lights and into Bridgewater Center.  It is about 1/4 mile before the Bridgewater Center Rotary across from a strip mall on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 24: Take Exit 16 off Route 24 towards Bridgewater.  Follow all the way to the intersection of Route 18.  following Route 18 into Bridgewater Center.  Crispi's is about 1/4 mile before the Bridgewater Center Rotary across from a strip mall on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: Take Route 18 North thru Bridgewater Center.  Crispi's is about 1/4 mile north of (or after) the Bridgewater Center Rotary across from a strip mall on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take the Weymouth Exit (16) towards Route 18 South.  Follow directions 'From the North' as noted above.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246126025000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244005706000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Make Mine Crispi's!</name><id>10563397</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244847600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10563397/</event_url></item>