<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>59 Jfk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.491.9851</phone><name>Redline</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692091</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120694</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us for dinner before the lecture at Redline on the Science of Cheese Making! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the folks at Science in the News:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rachel Dutton, a microbiologist at Harvard, will be talking about the Science of Cheesemaking at this Science by the Pint, and how microbes in the process influence the smell, flavor and texture of cheese. It appears that she has appeared a few times around Boston as a panelist talking about exotic cheeses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rachel introduces her topic at Science By The Pint as such: &amp;quot;I will talk about how the microbial world thrives all around us- even in our food- and why this is a good thing!  Did you know that microbes play an important role in making and aging cheese? And that many of the flavors, smells, textures and appearances of different cheeses are products of the metabolism of microbial communities living inside and on the rind of cheese?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Also:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Buy 1 get 1 free appetizers and a door prize courtesy of our sponsor, Narragansett Beer!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lecture starts at 7:00 pm at Redlines in Harvard Square. Let's grab dinner at 6:15 pm here at Redline. T.J. will be making reservations under &amp;quot;T.J. Maher&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The Nerd Fun Meetup&amp;quot;, and needs a mostly accurate count probably by Monday so he has made this event YES/ NO. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, wish short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and will be placing red MEETUP table tents on the tables he has reserved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science by the Pint:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'Science by the Pint' is SITN's [Science in the News] rendition of a nationwide project called 'Science Cafes', a movement to provide more informal discussions between scientists and non-scientists on relevant scientific and social issues. Rather than the usual seminar format we provide during our fall lecture series, Science by the Pint will feature one or more leading researchers who give no more than a 5 minute, conversation stirring, introduction to their work. The rest is up to you! After the short introduction, you may ask our researchers questions, bring up discussion points and see where it all leads&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Gee... I wonder which tables most of the questions will be coming from?  ;)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science in the News:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We are a graduate student public service organization at Harvard University. Our mission is to delve into the science behind the media reports we hear everyday and to bring that information to you so you can better distinguish scientific fact from pure speculation and put the knowledge to use in your daily life. We accomplish our mission through the following avenues:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Evening seminars&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Each fall, Science in the News hosts a free, 9-week evening seminar series for the public aimed at explaining and discussing today's hottest scientific topics without hype, exaggeration, or over-simplification. The program is run entirely by graduate students from the Harvard community. Each seminar consists of three individual 30-45 minute interactive presentations on a single topic; an introduction to the background you need to understand the topic, a presentation about recent research or innovations, and a discussion of the ethical or societal ramifications of this research. Different graduate students present each section.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A major benefit of our seminar series is the accessibility of the speakers: we take as much time as needed to discuss and answer your questions! Often, the audience plays as large a role in the seminar as the speakers themselves&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;American Society for Microbiology honors Rachel J. Dutton&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Physorg.com, 3/11/2010&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.physorg.com/wire-news/29790916/american-society-for-microbiology-honors-rachel-j-dutton.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.physorg.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A 2010 American Society for Microbiology (ASM) Raymond W. Sarber Award is being presented to Rachel J. Dutton, a Ph.D. candidate at Harvard Medical School, Boston, MA, for her work on disulfide bond formation. It is presented in honor of the late Raymond W. Sarber and his contributions to the growth and advancement of the ASM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dutton's work has focused on disulfide bonds which are covalent bonds between cysteine residues that aid in the stability and folding in many secreted proteins. She received her undergraduate degree at the University of California, San Diego and now is a graduate student. She has used genetic, bioinformatic, and phylogenetic methods to analyze pathways for disulfide bond formation across the bacterial tree of life. She has analyzed 400 bacterial genomes for homologs of the known disulfide bond formation pathway and watched for a bias of even numbers of cysteines in exported proteins. Her bioinformatic analysis formed her hypothesis that a large group of bacteria must have an alternative pathway for disulfide bond formation. She discovered that this alternative pathway utilizes a homolog of the warfarin (Coumadin)-sensitive blood coagulation enzyme from humans, vitamin K epoxide reductase (VKOR)&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rachel Dutton will also be speaking Monday, April 5th, at the screening of &amp;quot;The Cheese Nun&amp;quot;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.food24fps.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.food24fps....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to the site &lt;b&gt;Food at Twenty Four Frames Per Second&lt;/b&gt; &amp;quot;A semi-regular series, located in Cambridge, MA, of classic and obscure films about food&amp;quot; where &amp;quot;Films introduced by guest speakers from Cambridge, Boston, and other points exotick&amp;quot; Rachel Dutton will be a panelist, representing Harvard Medical School, along with Ihsan Gurdal, the owner of Formaggio Kitchen, just before the screening of &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;The Cheese Nun&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;.  The free screening is at the William James Hall 105 at 33 Kirkland Street wil be followed by a free cheese tasting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;About the film&lt;/u&gt;: &amp;quot;Sister Noella Marcellino makes Bethlehem cheese in a Benedictine abbey in Connecticut until she goes for a PhD in biochemistry and then travels across France on a Fulbright sampling milk and mold in cheese caves, all in order to understand the microbes that give cheese their complex flavors&amp;quot; (PBS, 2001). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Redlines:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.redlinecambridge.com/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.redlinecam...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Located in the heart of Harvard Square, Redline caters to a hip cross-section of the city with its casually refined menu, buzzing bar scene and late night entertainment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Redline's 'approachably stylish' cuisine is as diverse as the clientele it draws, boasting creative entrees as well as a variety of apps and sandwiches perfect for sharing, makes Redline a great choice for a social gathering or a casual dinner for two&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Every Monday evening, Redline has stump trivia at 8:00 pm. On Social Fun, Amy Hughes has been getting together people every Monday since June for what has to be the longest running continuous weekly event in the Boston area meetups. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Redline menu&lt;/b&gt; (in Adobe Acrobat PDF Format): &lt;a href="http://www.redlinecambridge.com/menu/menuContent.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.redlinecam...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;TAKING THE T&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Follow the platform upstairs. Exit the platform  by following signs for Harvard Square. Head down JFK Street between Citizens Bank and The Curious George Store. Redline is three blocks on your right, just after Winthrop Park. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Redlines has free parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As our way of saying thanks, we offer patrons free parking between the hours of 5 PM - 11 PM, Monday - Wednesday in the Harvard Square Parking Garage. The garage is located at 20 Eliot Street, directly above Redline Food and Drink. Simply bring your parking ticket into the restaurant and ask your server or hostess to validate it after your meal. Feel free to park early and enjoy Harvard Square's varied attractions such as shopping, movies, theater and more!&amp;quot; Parking Garage Website: &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/Home/Services/Harvard-Square-Parking-Garage.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvardsqu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271095372000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270132676000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rachel Dutton, Science of Cheese Making @ Science By The Pint, Redline</name><id>13057863</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270592100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13057863/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/0/global_14062832.jpeg</photo_url></item>