<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone likes a mystery. The unexplained disappearance, abandoned dwellings, a glimpse of something uncanny, the hint of strange events. . .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the mid 1700s, the area known as the Commons Settlement was home to Cape Ann&amp;rsquo;s burgeoning upper crust. As many as 200 people lived in this boulder-strewn flatland until just after the Revolutionary War, when the wealthy moved nearer to the coast. The neighborhood spiraled downward after that, earning the dubious moniker Dogtown; authorities evicted the last holdout in 1830. Walk the dirt road into the old town square, now just a hole-pocked clearing, and bear right at .3 mile to wind past motto-inscribed, glacier-deposited stones on the Babson Boulder Trail. Then wander the 10-plus-mile network of abandoned roads and trails that winds through sparse woodlands. Watch for cellar holes and chiseled exhortations to &amp;ldquo;get a job&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;stay out of debt&amp;rdquo; that feel oddly judgmental for a town that couldn&amp;rsquo;t help itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[img]&lt;a&gt;http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/th...&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[divider]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogtown&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(also&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Dogtown Commons&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Dogtown Common&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Dogtown Village&lt;/strong&gt;) is an abandoned inland settlement on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cape_Ann"&gt;Cape Ann&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Massachusetts"&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt;. Once known as the Common Settlement and populated by respectable citizens, the area later known as Dogtown is divided between the city of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gloucester,_Massachusetts"&gt;Gloucester&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and the town of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rockport,_Massachusetts"&gt;Rockport&lt;/a&gt;. It is in an area not particularly suited to agriculture, due to its poor and very rocky soil. Nevertheless it was settled, beginning in 1693, because its inland location afforded protection from&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pirates"&gt;pirates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and from enemy natives. Another attraction was the fact that the area lay on what was originally the only direct land route between Sandy Bay (Rockport's original name) and Gloucester. The peak of population, from about 1750 to the turn of the nineteenth century, has been estimated at around one hundred families.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After new coastal roads were opened, and especially after the conclusion of the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/War_of_1812"&gt;War of 1812&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and its attendant risk of coastal bombardment, most farmers moved away from Dogtown. Their abandoned houses were for a few decades occupied by itinerants and vagabonds, giving the area its bad reputation. Many of the widows of sea-goers and soldiers who never returned kept dogs for protection and company. As these last inhabitants died their pets became feral and wild, roaming the moors and howling, possibly giving rise to the nickname "Dogtown." An equally likely reason for the area's name is that residents of surrounding villages considered the inhabitants of the decrepit area to live like dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the last occupants were suspected of practicing&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Witchcraft"&gt;witchcraft&lt;/a&gt;, including Thomazine "Tammy" Younger, whom some knew as the "Queen of the Witches." Tammy lived on Fox Hill, by Alewife Brook, and would reputedly place a curse on teams of oxen carrying fish from the harbor as they crossed the bridge there, unless their driver paid her a "toll". A reputed witch often associated with Dogtown was Peg Wesson, but in fact she lived in Gloucester, not Dogtown. The last resident of Dogtown, a&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Freedman"&gt;freedman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;named Cornelius "Black Neil" Finson, was found half-dead living in a cellar-hole in the winter, and was removed to the poorhouse in Gloucester in 1830; he died shortly afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[img]&lt;a&gt;http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/th...&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[img]&lt;a&gt;http://www.dogtownecologywalks.com/images/D...&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the area of Dogtown is now a dense woodland, criss-crossed and bisected by trails and old roads. An ecological guide to some trails can be found at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.dogtownecologywalks.com/"&gt;http://www.dogtownecologywalks.com&lt;/a&gt;. Dogtown Road off of Cherry Street in the western section (the Gloucester side) is even lined with the remains of the cellar holes of the settlers, many of which are numbered in correspondence with names from John J. Babson's book of the history of Gloucester. Babson's grandson,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roger_Babson"&gt;Roger Babson&lt;/a&gt;, is known for, among other things, his commissioning of unemployed stonecutters to carve inspirational inscriptions on approximately three dozen boulders in Dogtown during the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_Depression"&gt;Great Depression&lt;/a&gt;. Babson also mapped and numbered the cellar holes left from the homes of Dogtown's former residents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the land is held in trust by Gloucester and Rockport and is therefore protected in perpetuity. The current state of Dogtown affords rich recreation opportunities to hikers and bikers, dog-walkers, nature lovers, cross-country skiers, geologists and historians. The area is peppered with house-sized boulders, including one named "The Whale's Jaw," which it formerly resembled before collapsing after a picnic's campfire got out of control in 1989.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will end our day at the Pub/ Restaurant with &amp;nbsp;a bowl of red-and-white clam chowder at Halibut Point in Gloucester. About 3PM? if you just want to meet for dinner. &amp;nbsp;289 Main St (978) 281-1900&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;cd=4&amp;amp;ved=0CDYQFjAD&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.halibutpointrestaurant.com%2F&amp;amp;ei=CoSLTpawBOn20gH1tfnZBA&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHjlzPeQir1JhjRbyDjnqYrEw5Mgg&amp;amp;sig2=g7kISwqFo0gHIKuBxT2r2A"&gt;http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;source=w...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Way From Gloucester, go north .7 mile on MA 127, right on Poplar, left on Cherry, and right on Dogtown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've always wanted to do this. If you are familiar with the area, I'd love to get your input. This event was reprinted from Backpacker Magazine &amp;amp; Wikipedia.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Since We are exploring for the first time, we will meet at the restaurant and go from there with our map.  We can walk up to 10 miles,wooded flat trails. A casual Sunday hike, all adventurers are welcome</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318859362000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317640813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GHOST TOWN HIKES:DOGTOWN, MA</name><id>35913062</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318775400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/35913062/</event_url></item>