<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Northern Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.813284</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Plum Island Point</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>706565</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.814106</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;*******YOU MUST PURCHASE YOUR TICKET NOW FOR THIS EVENT.  THE EVENT SOLD OUT IN 2 WEEKS LAST YEAR********/color]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6.22.10 UPDATE: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;/b&gt; We have found out that there is no trolley or service that runs from downtown Newburyport to Plum Island, so we will be changing the meeting place to the pier/boat! Last year when we attended this event parking was hard to find, so we suggest that you get there early get a parking spot and we will meet you either on the pier or on the boat!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few of us went on this beach party boat last year and had an awesome time.  This event will sell out fast so make sure you reserve your tickets today......see below for details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beach party boat leaves Plum Island Point, Newburyport MA promptly at 7:00pm.  Once the boat is out in the water a full buffett will be served and then the party begins.  Some of the pictures from last year are posted on this site so if you are questioning whether you will have fun please look back on the 7/4/09 party.   The boat will continue out along the shores and when the fireworks begin you can see all the towns from Hampton NH down the coast of MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boat leaves at 7pm and will return approximately at 10:30pm. Ticket price includes buffett and there is a cash bar on board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price:  39.00 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket Reservation:  Call 978-973-4515, tell them you are reserving a ticket for the Meetup group&lt;br /&gt;                                 Once you have your reservation, please include in your RSVP on this site that you&lt;br /&gt;                                 have reserved your ticket&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:  Parking was tough last year, so Donna &amp;amp; I are looking into a shuttle from NBPT to Plum Island so watch the site for updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on the party boat&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the end of the dock</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278422290000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273450246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beach Party Cruise ***THIS WILL SELLOUT FAST***</name><id>13432318</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278280800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/13432318/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/0/5/global_14937845.jpeg</photo_url></item>