<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nicholas Carr &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;explores&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;The Shallows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What the Internet Is Doing to Our Brains&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: : :&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome technology commentator NICHOLAS CARR for an exploration about the psychological impact of the internet and his new book The Shallows: What the Internet Is Doing to Our Brains.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Is Google making us stupid?” When Nicholas Carr posed that question in an Atlantic Monthly cover story, he tapped into a well of anxiety about how the Internet is changing us. He also crystallized one of the most important debates of our time: As we enjoy the bounties of the internet, are we sacrificing our ability to read and think deeply? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weaving insights from philosophy, neuroscience, and history into a rich narrative, The Shallows explains how the internet is rerouting our neural pathways, replacing the subtle mind of the book reader with the distracted mind of the screen watcher.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Ultimately, The Shallows is a book about the preservation of the human capacity for contemplation and wisdom, in an epoch where both appear increasingly threatened. Nick Carr provides a thought-provoking and intellectually courageous account of how the medium of the internet is changing the way we think now and how future generations will or will not think. Few works could be more important.” —Maryanne Wolf (Proust and the Squid: The Story and Science of the Reading Brain)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DATE: Monday, June 28th &lt;br /&gt;TIME: 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: Harvard Book Store &lt;br /&gt;1256 Massachusetts Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is free; no tickets are required&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Carr writes on the social, economic, and business implications of technology. He is the author of the 2008 Wall Street Journal bestseller The Big Switch: Rewiring the World, from Edison to Google and Does IT Matter? He has also written for many periodicals, including The Atlantic Monthly, The New York Times Magazine, Wired, The Financial Times, Die Zeit, The Futurist, and Advertising Age, and has been a columnist for The Guardian and The Industry Standard. His essay “Is Google Making Us Stupid?” which appeared as the cover story of the Atlantic Monthly’s Ideas issue in the summer of 2008, has been collected in three popular anthologies:The Best American Science and Nature Writing, The Best Technology Writing, and The Best Spiritual Writing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296256057000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274304839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Future of Thought</name><id>13535682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277766000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/13535682/</event_url></item>