<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>; see directions below</address_2><address_1>182 Memorial Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.358536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building 6, Room 120</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>408704</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TITLE: THE CHINA MARKET, presented by DAVID YEIN, FOUNDER and MANAGER OF ABACUS GREATER CHINA FOCUS FUND&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DESCRIPTION: DAVID YEIN will talk about the history of this Chinese bull market and the reasons why he expects this market will continue - by comparing it to Japan, Taiwan and Thailand. He will explain the differences between the various Chinese stocks - A shares, B shares, H shares and the ADRs. He will explain how to use different ETFs and funds to take advantage of the types and will give 2-3 ADR ideas that he likes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DAVID YEIN is the founder and manager of the Abacus Greater China Focus Fund, a fund he launched in March 2007. If you attended our July meeting you may remember that he attended and spoke up about CAF during that meeting. David received his MBA from Boston College in 2001, became an analyst for Off Wall Street a firm specializing in recommending shorts. He became the fifth employee of Delta Partners, a global long short hedge fund (called Prism Fund) that was on its way from managing $400 Million to managing $2.5 Billion. He went to Benchmark Co in 2005 specializing in structured products before starting Abacus Greater China Focus Fund this past spring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will change these details as the agenda evolves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRE-MEETING Announcement:&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Tiger Meeting of the Tiger Financial Network meets during the hour from 6:00 PM to 6:50 PM. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; to see the full announcement. For questions, see Bob Pod at bpodd@softwareresults.com. The meeting is the same room as the 7:00 meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The agenda for the meetup will be:&lt;br /&gt;6:00 - 6:50 Pre-Meeting with Boston Tigers, led by Bob Podd&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 8:00 Meeting Starts with Fred Sears's Q&amp;amp;A, Doug's Market Talk, Stockpicks&lt;br /&gt;8:00 Feature Presentation by David Yein&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT Campus map to find Building 6: &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?zoom=level3;selection=6;selectlayer=Buildings;selectfield=facility;centerx=711161;centery=495670" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193542706000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>73</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187647755000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Business Daily October Meetup</name><id>6214236</id><headcount>68</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193266800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/6214236/</event_url></item>