<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Amory</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.316804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>Center Of Light</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>196692</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102484</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>April Conscious Movie:  Hotel Rwanda&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, April 17th • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hotel Rwanda is an intense movie; but sometimes we need to face the reality of things before we can change them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Description: Amid the holocaust of internecine tribal fighting in Rwanda that sees the savage butchering of hundreds of thousands of men, women and children, one ordinary man (Oscar nominee Don Cheadle) musters the courage to save more than 1,000 helpless refugees by sheltering them in the hotel he manages. Sophie Okonedo, Nick Nolte and Joaquin Phoenix co-star in this powerful film (sort of an African version of Schindler's List) directed by Terry George.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we will welcome a guest speaker who will talk to us about the Organizatiion &amp;quot;Invisible Children&amp;quot; that offers a way to participate in spreading awareness about the situation in Uganda and other countries in Africa where thousands and thousands of children are abducted to be children soldiers. Come and learn more on what you can do!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is free, but donations are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>2 mins from Stony Brook T-stop Orange line.; parking available at school across</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242428934000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Consciousness movie members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>consciousness-65</urlname><id>355065</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Conscious Movie Meetup!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236192933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie:  Hotel Rwanda with a guest speaker for the ttalk</name><id>9880557</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240011000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/consciousness-65/events/9880557/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/6/5/global_7545429.jpeg</photo_url></item>