<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>73 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.867889</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Captains Corner</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>2249141</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.886772</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;No kidding we had such a good time at this event in July we are going to do it again!&amp;nbsp; If you wanted to go the 1st time but missed it....here is your chance to join us at this FUN event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come on out to Captain's Corner where we can eat Seafood at Lena's, play mini "glow" golf, batting cages and Go Karts the question is WILL we make it across the street this time to get Hodgies 2 for an ice cream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waiting time:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to arrive at the meeting place, please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&amp;nbsp; 978-304-2811.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you park in Lena's lot or Captain's Cove you will find a spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;, we thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&amp;nbsp; Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you all at the Captain's Corner for some MORE summertime fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be around our cars in the parking lot of Lena's!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315144016000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310343628000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lena's, Glow golf and Ice cream (we hope)!</name><id>25266281</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315087200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/25266281/</event_url></item>