<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>98 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.843979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Ocean Music Hall</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>1558779</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.877045</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Comedy Hypnotist Tim Triplett&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We have seen a different Hypnotist and had a lot of fun, a little recap of the last time we went: one of us TRIED to get hypnotisted, one of us was known as "give or take an inch" and we saw and most of all laughed a lot so come on out and make some more lasting memories.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little about Tim Triplett:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once a national sales trainer and impersonator of such celebrities as David Letterman, Howard Cosell and even Anne Richardson from "The Weakest Link" (he's not necessarily proud of that one), Comedy Hypnotist Tim Triplett has spent years entertaining clients all across America. Inspired by laughter, Tim turned to entertaining his audiences using hypnosis. This "shift" has allowed Tim to now perform in men's clothing 100% of the time, which, according to his mother, "has done wonders for his self-esteem." &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; With diplomas in Advanced Stage Hypnosis, Complete Mind Therapy, and Hypnotherapy &amp;amp; Psychotherapy, Tim Triplett is an experienced and knowledgeable performer. As a member of the Royle Institue of Hypnotherapy and Psycotherapy as well as the Professional Organiztion of Stage Hypnotists, Tim is a master of engaging his audiences, getting them up on stage and turning them into the stars of the show. His favorite quote is: "Do unto others, and then quickly leave the building." Not very deep, but very useful. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Nothing stirs the imagination and entertains like Stage Hypnosis. Volunteers are never asked to do anything that would embarrass themselves. At least not like Tim did at his last family reunion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some information about ordering your ticket for this event:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ordering is easy and only takes a few minutes, so order your seat soon so we are sure to sit together!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Table #'s that we will be sitting at will be table #'s 29, 30 &amp;amp; 31. BUT note they are not reserved for us, they are only suggestions that we sit at those table(s) and be prepared that if you don't order your ticket quick enough other people may be sitting at the table with us or us at a table with them.&amp;nbsp; If those seats are taken then try to get a seat that is near us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ticketing fee:   &lt;br /&gt;Every  ticket sold has a fee associated with it. The fee is over-and-above the  posted ticket price. All fees are clearly outlined in our ticketing  system. Fees are charged for each ticket, regardless of how the ticket  was purchased.  &lt;br /&gt;To reserve your seat go to &lt;a href="http://tickets.blueoceanhall.com/default.asp" class="linkified"&gt;http://tickets.blueoceanhall.com/default.asp&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Click on schedule,   &lt;br /&gt;Scroll down to Comedian Tim Triplett   &lt;br /&gt;Click Buy Now,   &lt;br /&gt;Click  on either one of those tables and you will see a grid of 6 yellow  framed empty squares (as seats are being reserved at that table you will  see that the squares get highlighted &lt;span&gt;red&lt;/span&gt; which means that seat is sold).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To reserve your seat click on one of those squares that is not highlighted red.   &lt;br /&gt;Then all you have to do is put in your credit card billing information and you are all set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;Please remember to change your RSVP on the site to &amp;ldquo;reserved seat&amp;rdquo; so we know to look for you on the night of the event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are only: $20.00 all seats (please note you are responsible for ordering and getting your own ticket).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What if I cannot attend a show that I have purchased tickets for?&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;We  fully recognize that sometimes life throws us a curveball and are aware  of the fact that it stinks to buy tickets that you find yourself stuck  with. Having said that, all sales are final. There are no refunds or  exchanges for purchased tickets unless the show has been rescheduled or  cancelled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you cannot attend a show but would like someone  else to use your tickets, they will need your physical tickets to do so.  Picking up tickets at the box office requires the photo ID and credit  card of the purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;978-304-2811.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Looking forward to seeing you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside at our table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307282319000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299898143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy Hypnotist Tim Triplett</name><id>16891338</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307229300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/16891338/</event_url></item>