<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Eisenhower &amp;amp; Monroe&lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;Mounts Eisenhower 4780ft and Monroe.  Our group will hike up Edmunds Path (approximately 3.6 miles) to Mt Eisenhower (4760' on the 48 list). The trail is never very steep, and the footing is good. This hike gives excellent views for a very reasonable effort, but remember that the summit is fully exposed to the weather. Pack some warm clothes! There are astounding 360 degree views from this treeless peak as you are now in the Alpine Zone! &lt;br /&gt;After tagging Eisenhower, we'll head north along the Crawford Path to Mount Monroe (approximately 1.5 miles).  This section of the Crawford Path is above treeline and offers spectacular views!   After we summit Mount Monroe, we will hike down to the Lake of the Clouds Hut.  We will then take a break, and then hike around Mount Monroe back to the Edmunds Path and down.  Total hiking distance is approximately 10 miles.  Total hiking time, including taking breaks, should be about eight hours.  &lt;br /&gt;This is truly a spectacular hike and is truly rewarding.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the trailhead: This is where we will meet.:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For simplicity we will meet at the Ammonoosuc Ravine parking lot located on the Cog Railroad Base Road about  ½ mile west of the Cog Railroad parking lot in Brett Woods, NH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will drive the short distance (about 4 miles) to the Edmund Path lot, then gear up to hike on Edmund Path. These trails have great footing with gentle elevation gain.&lt;br /&gt;Since this hike is mostly above tree level, rain will cancel.  The hike will be a go if it is only cloudy. &lt;br /&gt;A WMNF Parking pass is not needed at this trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dianne and I will be in a black four door Toyota Echo with Maine License Plate</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222299898000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218482385000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Eisenhower &amp; Monroe</name><id>8522512</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221915600000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8522512/</event_url></item>