<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Practice self and assisted rescues at Hopkinton State Park,  Monday, July 13, 6:00PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT we will be DOING/what you NEED to have for kayak and gear:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an informal practice session to help each other learn and practice self and assisted rescues.  The group size is limited, but there will be several more opportunities throughout the summer, and as more of us learn, then we can help each other out at similar practice sessions or with some practice time at the end of some of the trips.  So if you can't make this one, don't worry, there will be more opportunities!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You either must have a kayak with bulkheads, or if your kayak does not have bulkheads then it must have some flotation in the back - beach ball, dry bag, or a real float back.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Things to bring: Boat paddle and PFD obviously. Dress for the water and bring a towel and a warm change of clothes. Other stuff it would be good to have include: paddle float (for self rescue), Pump, spray skirt.  I also highly recommend nose plugs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The LOCATION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are links to the place...  &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dfwele/dfw/habitat/maps/ponds/pdf/dfwhopk.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/hpsp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a fee to enter the park, but there may not be at that time of day on a weekday, I will try to find out before the trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you get there, follow the signs for the boat rentals and that will get you to the concrete launching area.  We will meet at the parking area at the far end of the ramps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rte. I-495 (north or south) to exit 21A, Main Street Hopkinton. Travel on Main Street until the third traffic light located at the heart of downtown Hopkinton. Turn left, traveling North on Route 85. Proceed approximately 2 miles to the Hopkinton State Park entrance on the right (do not enter the Field Office on the left).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To locate Main Entrance by MAPQUEST:  268 Cedar Street, Hopkinton, MA 01748&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4219141</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247938128000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246320868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rescues practice at Hopkinton State Park</name><id>10764954</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247522400000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/10764954/</event_url></item>