<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Valley Falls Rd.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.827274</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(860) 872-6118</phone><name>Valley Falls Park</name><city>Vernon</city><id>128048</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.451020</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>***Weather update 8/8/09: &lt;b&gt;0% chance rain!&lt;/b&gt; Lower 70's, mostly cloudy, humidity 60%***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A nice after work hike I'm starting a little later so more people can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiking roughly a couple miles of very pleasent forest and cliffs. We'll be starting at the pond, hike around a bit in the valley, then going up a hillside to the Hop River Linear Trail (i.e. Rails-To-Trails in Vernon area). Then we'll head up to the cliffs over the park to relax and enjoy the view... and good weather (so far &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;). It's a short hike after that back to the start.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the parking lot at 6 PM and head out to hike the trail. The hike should take no more than 2 hrs. and we should be done by 8 PM at the latest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 8.5 miles of blazed trails in the park, as well as a playground, picnic pavilion, toilet facilities and a swimming beach. Portions of the park contain riuns of textile mills and an early trout hatchery and have been declared a national historic site. The park is heavily used for swimming, picnicking, hiking, x-country skiing, fishing, wild flower &amp;amp; wildlife observation and a scenic vista.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information see (park map can be found on page 13):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rockvillect.us/Vernon_Rails-to-Trails.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://rockvillect.us...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directiions to park (312 Valley Falls Rd, Vernon, CT):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Valley+Falls+Park&amp;amp;city=Vernon%2C+Town+Of&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=312+Valley+Falls+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06066&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.82367&amp;amp;longitude=-72.44383&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=1017302171" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat.=42.82367, Long.=-72.44383]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249769356000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249218827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Valley Falls Park in Vernon CT</name><id>11013789</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249596000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11013789/</event_url></item>