<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Wall Street, Burlington, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.510000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>PapaRazzi</name><city>Burlington</city><id>619915</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.200000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Retirement, Social Security, and You?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosted By:     &lt;br /&gt;Alexandre M. Oliveira, CRPC, Financial Advisor, &lt;b&gt;Ameriprise&lt;/b&gt;          &lt;br /&gt;Joseph Walsh, Senior Vice President, &lt;b&gt;Fidelity Investments Institutional Serv&lt;/b&gt;ices&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven Richardson, &lt;b&gt;Social Security&lt;/b&gt;, Director of New England , Deputy Communications &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How comfortable are you answering these questions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; How comfortable are you that you will be able to re-create your paycheck in retirement?&lt;br /&gt; How comfortable are you that you will have the means to realize your dreams?&lt;br /&gt; How much can you withdraw at retirement without running out of money?&lt;br /&gt; How do you appropriately navigate a turbulent market?&lt;br /&gt; How will health care costs affect your retirement lifestyle in the future?&lt;br /&gt; How much of your retirement income will come from social security?&lt;br /&gt; How would your future lifestyle be affected if social security vanished?&lt;br /&gt; How would a divorce, spousal death, or pension affect your social security benefit?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you having difficulty answering some, if not, all of these questions? Would it be worth making sure that you can answer all of them with certainty?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If so, then come join us at this informative dinner:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 24, 2008&lt;br /&gt;                                    Time: 7:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;                                    Place: PapaRazzi Trattoria, 2 Wall Street, Burlington, MA&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cissy</member_name><member_id>3279099</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214521567000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Free meal, informal, can ask any questions, and lots of laughs!</why><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211555481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Retirement and You</name><id>7998355</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214348400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/7998355/</event_url></item>