<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Boston's Entrepreneurs Network - "An Indispensible Network for Building Buzz, Developing Collaborations, Gaining Customers and Getting Financing"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting a new business is like entering the frontier.  For any adventurer, breaking a new trail requires the best people, tools, skills, and sometimes just plain luck.  Many of the world-changing entrepreneurs are in Massachusetts where you’ll find a deep well of creative thinking, networking, marketing, customers, financing and an eco system of entrepreneurship.  Having a map and guidance to help access these resources can be the difference between success and failure. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our next Entretech forum, we will bring together the “startup toolbox” of  leading organizations and support resources in the Boston area.  Every Entrepreneur working to succeed and avoid the pitfalls of starting a business will want the best startup tools available.  These organizations provide that utility and guidance. Please join us for this exciting and powerful discussion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panelists include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Sept2012Mtg/harthorn.jpg" width="100" height="115" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;John Harthorne &lt;br /&gt;

Founder and Chief Executive Officer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Harthorne is the Founder and CEO of MassChallenge, a startup accelerator and competition designed to catalyze a startup renaissance by connecting high-impact startups from around the world with the resources they need to launch and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John received his MBA from the MIT Sloan School of Management in 2007. While at school, John received Grand Prize in the 2007 &lt;a href="http://mit100k.org/"&gt;MIT $100K Business Plan Competition&lt;/a&gt; and received the 2007 Patrick J. McGovern Award for impact on quality and visibility of entrepreneurship at MIT. He also led the 10th annual &lt;a href="http://mitgsw.org/"&gt;MIT Global Startup Workshop (GSW)&lt;/a&gt; held in Trondheim, Norway. In September 2011, the Boston Business Journal identified John as one of Boston's &lt;a href="http://www.bizjournals.com/boston/news/2011/09/22/bbj-announces-the-power-50-list.html"&gt;50 Most Influential Business Leaders&lt;/a&gt; alongside the CEOs of Akamai Technologies, Blue Cross Blue Shield and the Boston Celtics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John is a life-long Massachusetts resident and an avid Red Sox fan. He currently lives in Somerville with his wife Natalia, their 6-year old son Max and their baby girl Yulia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Sept2012Mtg/hammar.jpg" width="89" height="105" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Sam Hammar joined TCN after four and a half years of working for the City of Boston at the Boston Redevelopment Authority on the City's &lt;a href="http://www.innovationdistrict.org/"&gt;Innovation District&lt;/a&gt; initiative. She joined the BRA's Economic Development team in late 2007 to market the City for business attraction and found herself  helping craft the vision, strategy, and communications plan for the Innovation District upon its announcement by the Mayor in January 2010. With a strong belief that the entrepreneurial community and its connectivity could drive the success of the area, Sam has built a global communications infrastructure that has proven her case. Since its inception, over 100 businesses and 3,000 employees have moved to the District.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her passion for transparent and accessible organizations prompted her to advise several other City departments on revolutionizing the way they communicate with their constituencies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam is leaving a job she loves for a greater opportunity to help entrepreneurs actualize the vision for their companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has an M.A. in Global Marketing Communications and Advertising from Emerson College and a B.A. in Political Science from the University of Florida. Before joining the City, Sam used her marketing and community engagement skills for fundraising at the American Cancer Society, teaching Social Activism at a Boston Public High School, and producing trade shows for The Merchandise Mart in Chicago. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Sept2012Mtg/Adler.jpg" width="100" height="117" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Alexandra Adler, &lt;br /&gt;

Northeast Regional Director, CleanTech Open&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexandra is a skilled project manager, organizer and connector with a comprehensive understanding of the clean technology sector. Her enthusiasm for addressing the world’s energy and environmental challenges, for coordinating teams, and for connecting people to key resources and contacts to help them succeed led her to the Cleantech Open. Alexandra’s professional experience includes project management, communications and relationship management at both public and nonprofit organizations related to clean technology, energy and sustainability. In past roles she has overseen a wide range of projects including international trade missions, industry research and reports, new media communications and campaign organizing. Alexandra graduated with a degree in Sociology and Certificate in Environmental Policy from Commonwealth Honors College at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst. She enjoys practicing yoga, reading, eating Thai food, and watching TV sitcoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Sept2012Mtg/farmer.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Martha C. Farmer, PhD – President and CEO, North Shore InnoVentures&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to founding NSIV Martha had a consulting practice in medical ethics and drug development. Martha was a recent Fellow in Medical Ethics at Harvard Medical School and worked with the Harvard Embryonic Stem Cell Research Oversight Committee. She serves on the Ethics Committee and Institutional Review Board of Beverly Hospital. She also serves on the Board of Trustees of the North Shore Community College and on the Board of Directors of the North Shore Technology Council. Formerly with Baxter Healthcare’s Hemoglobin Therapeutics Division for eleven years, she transitioned from managing the research laboratory to directing product development, marketing and communications. Subsequently she co-founded the radiopharmaceutical start-up, BetaGamma LLC, serving as Vice President of Marketing. She has a BS in zoology and PhD in physiology and pharmacology from Duke University, postdoctoral training in biophysics from Johns Hopkins University, and is an author on more than 30 publications and three patents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Sept2012Mtg/bleck.jpg" width="100" height="105" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;James Bleck, President - bleck design group&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James Bleck is founder and president of bleck design group, a product development firm with thirty years of experience in medical device, business equipment, and consumer electronics. bleck design group has a client base that is 80% start-up companies. Jim's role at bleck design group is developing design plans that integrate with each client's unique situation. Jim is also a co-founder Chairman of the Merrimack Valley Venture Forum (MVVF) which holds monthly events focusing on start-up technology companies in southern New Hampshire and Massachusetts. Prior to founding Bleck Design Group, Jim was a senior industrial designers at Latham/Brefka of Boston and also Digital Equipment Corporation. Jim Bleck received a degree in Industrial Design from the University of Illinois, and completed post graduate studies in management at Northeastern University. Jim has been a design juror for the Industrial Design Society of America/Business Week International Design Competition, and the CES (Consumer Electronics Show).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;View the upcoming &lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/2_calendar.htm"&gt;2012 - 2013 calendar&lt;/a&gt; and SAVE THE DATES!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting Cost:$25 public, $10 students and active military: &lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promotional Registrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 - 9:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;

Location: Emerging Center at Foley Hoag the Bay Colony Corporate Center, Waltham, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfsept12.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348022584000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346578347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston's Entrepreneurs Network - "An Indispensible Network for Building Buzz, De</name><id>80474292</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348007400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/80474292/</event_url></item>