<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02045</zip><lat>42.304688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jo's Nautical Bar</name><city>Hull</city><id>1637816</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.916374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We can take up to 30 people (and their dogs), so&amp;nbsp;please come and join us as we've had a few cancellations.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;For all of you that are going... my number is (860) 861-1511.&amp;nbsp; Please give me a call for any RSVP updates or questions.&amp;nbsp; Can't wait for tomorrow!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OK, final update (I HOPE!!!).&amp;nbsp; Please read all the updates below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;We are set up for &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;10:00 May 14th.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please update your RSVP if you cannot or are not going on Saturday&amp;nbsp; ASAP. &lt;/span&gt;Anybody who wants to go on Sunday may want to call the captain (see the website), it sounds like he may also be able to go on Sunday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;There is a leash law, but since we should be the only ones on the island, it shouldn't be a big deal.&amp;nbsp; I can't really say much more- there is a leash law, I can't advise you to break the law.&amp;nbsp; However, I also know we will probably be the only ones on the island.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;It's $35 per person (this does not include any sort of tip), 1 dog per person.&amp;nbsp; This will be important because of space issues- please let me know if you have more or less than one dog per person.We may be able to fit a couple of extra dogs.&amp;nbsp; So if you have more people than dogs or vice versa, please let me know and we'll work it out.&amp;nbsp; Sounds like we're good for the numbers at this point with the people who have let me know they have an extra dog.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Because of all the people who have signed up to go, we are going to take 2 boats.&amp;nbsp; Because we're going to take 2 boats, we're going to leave from Hull, MA...125 Main St.&amp;nbsp; The captain says it's a perfect place for our group of dogs- beaches and laid back- and the bar will probably be open when we get back.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;It's going to be about a 20 minute ferry ride, and about 3 hours of island time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Be sure to bring water and food for the dogs!&amp;nbsp; And probably yourself, too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;I can't wait to meet all of you!&amp;nbsp; This is going to be a blast!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Danielle&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307586511000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Boat ride, island time, and lots of pups to play with!</why><group><who>trail seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NE-Trail-Dogs</urlname><id>1347727</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>New England Trail Dogs</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303951615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ferry to an island</name><id>17460982</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305381600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-Trail-Dogs/events/17460982/</event_url></item>