<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(A few hundred feet East of Mt. Clinton Rd)</address_2><address_1>Rte 302</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.234306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Highland Center at Crawford Notch</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>1839181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.421936</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #339966 ; font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Jim Ryan (617-642-8810)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are climbing three 4K peaks--Mt. Willey then Mt. Field and Mt. Tom. After this we take a nice, leisurely 12 mile loop visiting a beaver pond, Zealand Falls, Thoreau Falls and Ethan Pond. Total trail distance is 17.6 miles with 4961 ft of elevation gain.&amp;nbsp; Book time is 12 hours but my goal is to finish in 10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a 
&lt;strong&gt;moderately fast paced hike&lt;/strong&gt; with an average speed of 2 mph. My philosophy is to enjoy the hike and the surroundings but still finish as quickly as possible.&amp;nbsp; I will not be cracking a whip on the steep uphill sections but we also will not be taking frequent breaks.&amp;nbsp; If you can't sustain a 1.5 mph pace uphill for 2.5 miles then you should reconsider.&amp;nbsp; On the flat sections we will stop to enjoy the ponds and falls but otherwise will keep up a 2 mph or faster pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Trip Details&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the AMC Highland Center at Crawford Notch at 7AM to spot a car or two (in case anyone bails after Field or Tom) then head to the Ethan Pond Trailhead a further 5 miles south on the 302.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start hiking at Ethan Pond Trailhead, following Ethan Pond Trail to Willey Range Trail and the summit of Mt. Willey. This section of trail is very steep (gains 2700 ft. in 2.5 miles) and culminates in "the ladders" but luckily after this the day is mostly gentle.&amp;nbsp; From Mt. Willey we ride the saddle over to Mt. Field, which is only 19 feet higher. From Field we descend about 600 feet to cross the A-Z trail and climb 350 feet to Mt. Tom. From the summit we return back to the saddle and the junction with the A-Z then head West towards the Pemigewasset Wilderness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point you will have the option to bail out and head east 2.2 miles downhill along the A-Z and Avalon Trails to the AMC Highland Center.&amp;nbsp; There is no safe place to bail after heading west on the A-Z, so consider carefully if you're up for another 12 miles at this point.&amp;nbsp; I will assess your condition at this point and may "strongly encourage" you to bail if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we've gotten our third 4K peak, the rest of the day is mostly flat, fun and falls! We hike west on the A-Z which descends gently 1200 feet over 2.6 miles to Zealand Trail, where we take a short detour to see Zealand Falls.&amp;nbsp; After Zealand Falls we return to the main trail, which is now Ethan Pond again though it's a continuation of the A-Z.&amp;nbsp; Just over two flat and easy miles down the trail we take a short detour to see Thoreau Falls. Back on the Ethan Pond Trail we have an easy 2.5 mile flat section to Ethan Pond where we may decide to hike in 0.15 miles and check out the amazing view of the pond and Mt. Willey.&amp;nbsp; After that it's another 2.6 miles with 1400 feet of elevation loss to bring us back to where we started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you just want to bag these three 4k peaks, this trip is not for you since we tack on an extra 12 miles after bagging all three, but it's worth it.&amp;nbsp; After Tom the rest of the day is mostly flat or downhill and the scenery is amazing with several ponds and falls along the way.&amp;nbsp; This is the fun section where we can just relax and enjoy the surroundings.&amp;nbsp; Please do not start the day with the intention of bailing after Tom, it's not fair to the rest of the group.&amp;nbsp; At any rate those who bail will have to hang out at the trailhead and wait for the rest of us to finish!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike covers a total of 17.63 miles with 4961 ft of elevation gain.&amp;nbsp; However, almost all of the elevation gain is in the first 5 miles.&amp;nbsp; Book time is just under 12 hours but since most of the hike is flat I expect we'll finish in 10.&amp;nbsp; Nonetheless, everyone is required to bring headlamps with extra batteries just in case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Important Details - Please Read&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have hiked these trails before but not this specific itinerary.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did all of my current research for this trip using the AMC's&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;White Mountain Guide&lt;/em&gt;, a trail map, and the Internet. I am the trip organizer but am not a guide or chaperone.&amp;nbsp; You should become familiar with this information since 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;you are ultimately responsible for your own safety&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #339966 ; font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it&amp;nbsp;prior&amp;nbsp;to this trip.&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;I will be conducting spot inspections of equipment at the trailhead. Anyone lacking the minimum required equipment will not be allowed to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
    &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Footwear&lt;/span&gt;: Sturdy hiking boots or trail shoes - no sneakers.&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
    &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Clothing&lt;/span&gt;: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater (even in summer). ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when dry it doesn't dry easily and is a great conductor when wet.&amp;nbsp; Bring a hat to protect you from the sun!
     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
    &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Outerwear&lt;/span&gt;: Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood and rain pants.&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
    &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip. There are abundant natural water sources on the trail and I will be bringing a backcountry filter so we can restock. I'd appreciate if others can also bring filters (please indicate when you RSVP). At any rate you should start with at least 2 liters of water.
     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
    &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;: Map and compass. Plastic whistle and signal mirror. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Bug repellant. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
    &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Optional Items&lt;/span&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera. GPS. Face net and bug mitts.&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #339966 ; font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I will be driving up on Saturday and camping at the Zealand campground.&amp;nbsp; I can accommodate up to three others in my Jeep and at the campground.&amp;nbsp; Please email me if you are interested.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Please note my cell phone number and call me if you have any questions or difficulties finding me.&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;We will not wait for people who arrive late.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
      &lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;Trail Map&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/3/d/event_48872061.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;--Jim Ryan&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>AMC Highland Center at Crawford Notch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim</member_name><member_id>1036335</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314148333000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313553879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Willey, Mt. Field and Mt. Tom...then Zealand and Thoreau Falls [Advanced]</name><id>29801931</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313924400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/29801931/</event_url></item>