<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a walk on level terrain along a dirt road and paths through forest and marsh, along the Neponset River. We walked some of this on the Hyde park walk and everyone liked it, so we will go back and walk the entire length of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;Take 93 to exit 2A or 2B for 138 North (depending on which direction you are coming from). Continue 1 mile and take a slight right at the fork in the road for Canton Ave, then make an immediate left on to Brush Hill Road. Continue 1 mile to a parking lot on the left side, just before the next intersection. The street address is approximate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10:30. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a 2 hour walk we will have lunch at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Village Manor&lt;br /&gt;427 Sprague St &lt;br /&gt;Dedham &lt;br /&gt;781-407-9191 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Capsule review: A rarity: a family-style restaurant that serves good food. Traditionalists will love the creamy Caesar salad, the teriyaki steak tips, and the baked scrod. The more inventive will love the blackened chicken fettuccine in a jalapeno cream sauce, and the Cajun quesadilla. The sports-minded will enjoy the big laser-projection TV. &lt;br /&gt;Cuisine: American &lt;br /&gt;Prices: $10-$14 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Neponset River, unlike the Charles and Mystic Rivers, remains a natural estuary with extensive marshlands at its mouth and significant freshwater wetlands along much of its upstream length. It provides an unusually rich and diverse habitat for both plants and animals including a number of threatened and endangered species. The estuarine portion of the Neponset River upstream of Granite Avenue is characterized by extensive tidal marshes. Granite bound for Boston from Quincy was transferred by early railroad to boats at a pier on the Milton Shore. This segment of the river offers interesting canoeing and nature study opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193754784000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191946817000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Neponset River State Reservation</name><id>6518118</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193581800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6518118/</event_url></item>