<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>277 Broadway Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02145</zip><lat>42.391606</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Elizabeth Peabody House</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1191261</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091778</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here's an odd twist on the Sweetheart theme: The Theatre@First Community theater in Somerville is putting on a performance of Dracula over the next few weekends. It is NOT the traditional story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.theatreatfirst.org/shows/dracula/dracula.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.theatreatf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The theater is the Elizabeth Peabody house, located at 277 Broadway in Somerville.  A note about parking.  Somerville has instituted citywide permit parking on all streets, with the exception of main streets like Broadway.  However, there is a parking lot nearby where a Shaws used to be.  That may be free to use.  You can also take the Orange Line to Sullivan Square and then the 101 bus along Broadway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As pointed out by fellow member Laurie, groups of 10 or more qualify for discounts on tickets.  Individual tickets go for $15.  I spoke with the director of this production and he said that the theater is pretty small (seats about 70 people).   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update:&lt;/b&gt;  I spoke to the House Manager at Theatre@First.  He said the group discount is $2/ticket.  I have made a non-binding reservation for 15 tickets at that price so far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update 2&lt;/b&gt; I spoke to the director again.  For those who are interested to know more about how this production of Dracula differs from Bram Stoker's original, this is what he said:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The characters of Lucy and Mina are reversed for the most part (Lucy&lt;br /&gt;is engaged to Jonathan.  Mina is engaged to Arthur.)  I haven't the&lt;br /&gt;slightest idea why the author did that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Lucy is the sole reason Dracula is coming to England, rather than&lt;br /&gt;the idea that he is simply looking for new feeding grounds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The character of Quincy Morris isn't in this version (which is a&lt;br /&gt;shame, because he's one of my favorite characters).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The tone is, by necessity, somewhat different.  The novel is more of&lt;br /&gt;a suspense story.  The play is more of an adventure story with&lt;br /&gt;elements of comedy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Apparently, these last few shows are selling well.  So, if all maybes want to come, please change your RSVP to yes soon so I can reserve more tickets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I, Jason, am about 6 ft with a thin build, thinning hair and glasses.  I will be in front of the theater at 7:30 PM with a shirt that reads:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I shall have to invent a new classification of a lunatic for you.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that want to get together after for a drink or a bite, there are a few eating/drinking establishments in the area.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason Mazzotta</member_name><member_id>2504796</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268157136000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266253991000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A theatrical performance of Dracula</name><id>12609113</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267232400000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12609113/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/e/e/global_12706334.jpeg</photo_url></item>