<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Winthrop St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.517300</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-744-7644</phone><name>Leticia and Robert</name><city>Salem</city><id>1192729</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.899900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us, Leticia and Robert, for a game night at our house in Salem.  We are mainly interested in Euro games but have other games too.  We really enjoyed some of the games people brought last time, so feel free to bring your own again and we'll leave it to the group to choose.  We'll be breaking up into two groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have drinks and snacks and the option of ordering pizza if the the group decides.  Our fridge died and I don't know if we'll have the new one delivered by then.  I'll try and get some ice but won't have the costco goodies this time :(   Don't worry, I'll have something else equally yummy, yet to be decided.  Thank you all for your generosity in bringing snacks.  We saved most of them, so we still have some regular chips, cheesy poofs and a liter of regular coke.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note we do not have a lot of the traditional games, so if you have a fav, please bring it.  If you are a Catan player or Rio Grande games in general, we probably have it.  And if you haven't heard of Medici, Guillotine, Puerto Rico, Chronology, Vinci or the like, maybe you'd like to try something new.  And for all you Risk fans, that's still Robert's #1.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have two cats that are mostly in the basement.  Please email or call me with any questions or concerns.  978-744-7644.  Thanks and can't wait to see you all!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leticia</member_name><member_id>10156175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270505969000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269532972000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Games</name><id>12989863</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270251000000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/12989863/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/b/global_13157947.jpeg</photo_url></item>