<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Central St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01960</zip><lat>42.526542</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-531-5744</phone><name>Fire Bull Steakhouse </name><city>Peabody</city><id>727927</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.927166</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE 2/2/11:&amp;nbsp; we are leaving the rsvp's open for one more day to give everyone the opportunity to rsvp.&amp;nbsp; If you would like to go and havent rsvp'd please do so no later than Thursday 2/3/11.&amp;nbsp; We will be making a reservation on Thursday night for this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meat on a stick? Yes I said Meat on a Stick and plenty of it. Lets go check out the Rodizio and see if just maybe they might have Pineapple on a stick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is a Rodizio you ask: Rod&amp;iacute;zio (pronounced [&amp;#641;o&amp;#712;d&amp;#658;iziu] in Brazil, is a style of restaurant service in Brazilian restaurants. One pays a fixed price (prix fixe) and the waiters bring an offering of food to each customer at several times throughout the meal, until the customers signify that they have had enough&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year we tried Midwest grill and had a great time and alot of pineapple on the stick. This year we are going to go out to Peabody to Fire Bull, below is a little about Firebull:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fire Bull Restaurant is a premier Brazilian Steakhouse on Boston&amp;rsquo;s North Shore and well known throughout New England. We are located in Peabody Square in the City of Peabody - MA bordering the historic City of Salem - MA, approximately 14 miles North of Logan Int&amp;rsquo;l Airport..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We continuously roast over 10 types of meat including top sirloin, roast beef, chicken wrapped in bacon, steak tips w/garlic, whole pork loin, ribs, lamb and more, seasoned and roasted to perfection on our custom built BBQ grill&amp;hellip;.over 50 swords of mouth-watering BBQ ! During dinner hours, our BBQ chefs carve the meats right at your table from 3-foot roasting swords&amp;hellip;all-you-can-eat ! Unlike most Brazilian Steakhouses, the Fire Bull also has a full service kitchen and full menu for dinner hours offering excellent choices of pastas, chicken, pork, hand-cut steaks and a variety of seafood entrees including Moqueca - traditional Brazilian seafood brought to your table simmering hot, intensely aromatic and flavorful. We also have our own Surf &amp;amp; Turf with colossal shrimp, top sirloin carved per order, asparagus &amp;amp; rice plus lobster ravioli and several signature dishes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Desserts&amp;hellip;don&amp;rsquo;t forget to ask about our homemade desserts&amp;hellip;the flan is incredible !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Price: $23.95pp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will need to make a firm reservation in order for our group to be seated. If you RSVP for this event and your plans change, please make sure you change your RSVP. We will be closing this event on Wed Feb 2, 2011 in time to make the reservation. If your plans change at the last minute, you are lost or running late please call the Meetup Cell phone to alert one of the organizers. The meetup cell number is 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you at the Rodizio with a great big appetite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;..&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the MeetupTable</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297006347000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295816833000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rodizio - Brazilian Buffet</name><id>16155905</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296864000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/16155905/</event_url></item>