<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 amherst street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361046</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>N/A</phone><name>MIT Building E51, Room 372</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>111875</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084526</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ruby, Rails, and MySQL: Bringing your data-driven apps to the web, presentation/discussion by Brian DeLacey&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the March meeeting, Brian DeLacey will take us on a tour of MySQL and Ruby on Rails. This meeting will show you how MySQL works seamlessly as a data engine driving with one of today's most popular open source web development frameworks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Picking up where the February meeting left off, we'll begin by taking a look at MySQL encryption in a Ruby on Rails application. From there, we'll take a closer look at how MySQL integrates with Ruby on Rails data models. You'll see how easy it is to develop powerful data-driven web applications with these open source tools. Brian will also demonstrate Ruport, an open source reporting framework written in Ruby which makes it easy to produce versatile reports from your MySQL databases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open source code will be used throughout and it should be easy for inspired attendees to get started using Ruby and Rails with MySQL after this session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, not to be missed: Door prizes!  Through the generosity of O'Reilly Media's User Group Program, we'll have a number of MySQL and Ruby/Rails books to raffle off to some lucky meeting attendees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be about 10 minutes at the beginning for questions and announcements, similar to the September 2006 user group meeting, but we will stop at 10 minutes.  If you have a real-life issue, please submit or bring descriptions of all relevant queries, tables, data samples, etc.  See &lt;a href="http://www.sheeri.com/index.php?114" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sheeri.com...&lt;/a&gt; for more details &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting on MIT campus, close to Kendall Square on the Red Line (subway).  There is plenty of free parking -- you can park in ANY MIT lot after 3 pm, even if it says &amp;quot;parking by permit only&amp;quot;.  We are in building E51, room 372.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the URL for MIT's Map with the location of this building:&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=E51&amp;amp;Buildings=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   This map shows the MBTA Kendall Stop:&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=L5&amp;amp;Landmarks=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(the stop is in red on that map, and you can see E51 in the bottom right)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Here are the URL's for the parking lots:&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P4&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P5&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free pizza and soda will be served, so please RSVP accurately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To RSVP anonymously, please login to the Meetup site with the e-mail address &amp;quot;admin at sheeri dot com&amp;quot; and the password &amp;quot;guest&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://mysql.meetup.com/137/events/5077666/"&gt;&lt;a href="http://mysql.meetup.com/137/events/5077666/"&gt;http://mysql.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheeri Kritzer Cabral</member_name><member_id>2380684</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174087107000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Boston-Metro MySQL Users</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mysqlbos</urlname><id>212864</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171328750000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston MySQL March User Group</name><id>5476227</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1173740400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/events/5476227/</event_url></item>