<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Electric St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03102</zip><lat>42.992676</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>West Side Ice Arena</name><city>Manchester</city><id>869463</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.493240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The start of this event is intentionally scheduled later in the day so you could still attend the Mutt Strut in the morning if you chose to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will hike along trails both next to the Piscataquog River and on the Goffstown Rail Trail.  There will be some street crossings in places so bring a leash. The dogs will have a chance to play in the water if they choose to.  Some of the paths along the river will be footpaths and in other places the trails are wide enough for a car to drive on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will park in front of the West Side Ice Arena near the beginning of the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369156321000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368289232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Piscataquog River/Goffstown Rail Trail Hike - 5 Miles - Easy</name><id>118892302</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368982800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/118892302/</event_url></item>