<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Maple Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.296818</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>St Andrews Episcopal Church</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1035894</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.431651</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Place where this program is happening has been changed!! Please note the new address!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jack Reznicki - If it doesn't talk, don't shoot it! Photographing people and kids &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday Sept. 1, 2009 7:15PM &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Humor, wit, and more than a passing familiarity with the absurd have all helped Jack Reznicki become one of the most sought-after illustrative photographers in New York and one of the most popular program presenters in the photo community. Over his 30-year career, he may be best known for his expressive photographs of kids or as he says, “Kids as kids”.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jack’s photography is in demand by agencies representing a &amp;quot;who's who&amp;quot; of blue chip advertisers, such as Toys &amp;quot;R&amp;quot; Us, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, Playtex, Hyatt Hotels, Kodak, AT&amp;amp;T, and many, many more. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In this entertaining and educational program, Jack will show how he takes a concept and makes it come alive in the studio or on location. He will describe, step-by-step, from concept, set up, to lighting, just how these shots are created. Jack will explain his thought process when lighting with either studio strobes or natural light. “Lighting Essentials” as he calls it, as he explains not just lighting, but how to think about light itself. He will also go over some of his personal work and show how it connects with his commercial work.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jack as often said, &amp;quot;Be a photographer because of the way you think, not because you're someone with a camera.&amp;quot; Come and see how Jack thinks and what he does with a camera. Jack will also have a Q&amp;amp;A at the end of his presentation, including any copyright questions, one of the areas he loves to discuss. Never one to duck a hot question, these are always very entertaining and illuminating sessions with Jack. If you don’t know Jack, you will after this presentation.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jack Reznicki is commercial people and children photographer based in New York City. His creative problem solving has helped promote products and services for many companies such as Toys “R” Us, Tylenol, The Wall Street Journal, Hyatt, Kodak, Reader’s Digest, Crest, AT&amp;amp;T, Playtex, and several Time Magazine covers.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jack is the author of several books on commercial photography including “Studio and Commercial Photography- A Kodak Pro Workshop” book. Jack will have a new book on copyright and legal issues for photographers that will be in bookstores in early 2010.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He currently writes a column in Photoshop User Magazine called “The Copyright Zone”. For many years, Jack’s insights to professional photography could be found in Petersen’s Photographic magazine with his popular “Pro Vision” column. His writings have also appeared in many other photography magazines.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Believing that photographers should be pro- active in the photo community, he has been very busy in that community. In the past Jack has served as President of Professional Photographers of America (PPA), President of the New York chapter of Advertising Photographers of America (APA), sat on the Joint Ethics Committee in New York, and served as Board Member of ASMP/NY.  Along with many other awards, Jack was very proud to twice receive the IPC (International Photographic Council) Leadership medal for “Excellence in Studio Photography” at the United Nations. Jack was appointed a guest professor at Shandong University of Art and Design in Jinan, China and named a Mo-Tse Grand Master Photographer in China. He is also proud to be named an Honorary Fellow of the &lt;br /&gt;New Zealand Institute of Professional Photography.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;He is one of the original  “Canon Explorers of Light”, an “Epson Stylus Pro”, host of the Epson Print Academy’s Track One, and a Sandisk “Photo Master”. Jack has also does testing and consulting with Canon, Epson, Mamiya, Microsoft, X-Rite, Leaf digital backs, and Adobe. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Address!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;Address&lt;br /&gt;St Andrew Episcopal Church&lt;br /&gt;3 Maple Street &lt;br /&gt;Framingham, MA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252857214000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250081883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>If It Doesn't Talk, Don't Shoot It! - Photographing People and Kids- A Talk </name><id>11093858</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251846000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11093858/</event_url></item>