<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Al's Kayak rent donati0n</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per kayak loaded up.</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ok here is an easy trip down the river..&lt;br /&gt;Might as well do a cookout at the end with the gas grille..and the fire pit at the weslean boat ramp shelter area..picknick tables are there..&lt;br /&gt;Cops seem to have left us alone so far...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have to reserve a kayak before the event..because i wont go home to get them, they will be on the car at work..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We still have to move the cars to the boat ramp and that takes time anyway..someone has to stand guard with the yaks and equipment..&lt;br /&gt;but we cant waite forever...besides bar people park in the boat launch area..so the earlier the better...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boat launch area to take out is at harbor park restaurant on the weslean boat house side..rte 9 south exit 14..DeKoven rd..&lt;br /&gt;take a left at the end of the exit..= Dekoven road..the next left at the light is  Union St, take that left..go under the bridge..take the left on to..Harbor Drive..Parking lot is on the right..if full use the one on the left..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This river has a lot of interesting features,&lt;br /&gt;I hope to put in in one place and retrieve from the Weslean boat launch making it a one way trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will need some time to do the car switching thing..so we wont take off on the water right away. Someone will be there gaurding the yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING THERE, from the north, &lt;br /&gt;Look at your map first.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;get onto Rte 9 south, (to and in Cromwell/Middletown) go to exit 19 &lt;br /&gt;Turn (right) off the exit, =west toward Kmart and Stop and Shop &lt;br /&gt;At the first light you see (intersection of rte 372 and rte 3) take the left (south toward stop n shop) onto rte 3= shunpike rd &lt;br /&gt;There is a KFC, MackDonalds, and a Drunkin Doonuts while heading to the next traffic light. Use Drunkin Donuts (driveway) there is an empty lot which is coned off sometimes but since there is construction going on , park down in the far back of the Drunken Donuts lot if necessary. &lt;br /&gt;There is a water trail sign showing the most dangerous animals and what not to feed the animals...including the banjo boys... &lt;br /&gt;I will have  spare kayaks with me for anyone that wants to use them. BUT YOU MUST KNOW WHICH ONE...since most of em are ocean types and not very stable for beginners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;oNE KAYAK i found EMPTY after the last person became dinner for some wild animal.. &lt;br /&gt;No sinGing &amp;quot; Har... Paddling in a dead mans kayak, looking over my back, in case the gohst wants it back..&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip usually takes 2 hours or so but if we do some exploring ..then its over when its over provided you have not been eaten by wild creatures....&lt;br /&gt; iF YOU SURVIVED..WE CAN EAT AT THE LITTLE CANOPY BY THE WESLEAN BOAT RAMP after loading up and stuff like that..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a light for your boat..we will most likely be going back in the dark the last portion of the trip..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain Back up Plan: Have to waite till the day gets closer..&lt;br /&gt;but rain cancles the event...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tu   7      Low   6:11 AM     0.2   5:51 AM    Rise 12:01 AM      38&lt;br /&gt;     7     High  10:12 AM     1.7   8:02 PM     Set  4:08 PM&lt;br /&gt;     7      Low   6:05 PM     0.2&lt;br /&gt;     7     High  10:54 PM     2.4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its low tide at the put in so plan accordingly...&lt;br /&gt;For GPS, Mapquest and others use 17 Shunpike Road to get you close enough...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186697058000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186083676000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Kayak Trip on the Mettabassett River Cromwell/Middletown CT</name><id>6116051</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186524000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6116051/</event_url></item>