<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>EDIT - Ok seems like noone is coming along? Tom is heading out on his own. &lt;br /&gt;So if noone is coming to meet up to go I won't be there at the Marriott I'll just head down from Quincy&lt;br /&gt;after I loop to Plymouth and do my shocks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://scootercentrale.com/pages/posts/may-31st-open-house-cancelled--rain-date-in-effect12.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://scootercentral...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MORE ABOUT THE EXCITING PLACE WE ARE GOING   &amp;quot;Join us for our 6th Annual Open House next Saturday, June 7th from 10 a.m. - 6  p.m. and be sure to bring your scoot!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At noon, we'll depart for a ride over hill and dale to Barkhampsted reservoir and return to Vespa Hartford around 2:30 p.m. for a barbeque starting at around 3 p.m.  Be sure to return to the special scooter parking lot to take part in our contest for Best-Dressed Vespa, Best Overall Scooter,  Best Plastic Scooter, Most Hideous, and more.  We'll also feature a side-by-side &amp;quot;slow race&amp;quot; in our parking lot where the more &amp;quot;balanced&amp;quot; individuals among us will attempt to dethrone our own Doug Day for the 2008 Plainville Industrial Center World Championship.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The side routes would take too long for to get down there (in my opinion) so lets haul some butt to get down there on either a mini superslab or a superslab&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone with anything that can go highway speeds would be good (55mph+). For those that can't there may be an alternate route to go down there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so who's up for this?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scooter Centrale&lt;br /&gt;161 Woodford Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Unit 54&lt;br /&gt;Plainville, CT 06062&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find the silver skywave ;)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213016723000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Have some quality time with your scoot and others!</why><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212195687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scoot Centrale Open House</name><id>8045982</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212843600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/8045982/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/2/global_4080722.jpeg</photo_url></item>