<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>180 Berkeley St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349699</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)236-1199</phone><name>Back Bay Event Center</name><city>Boston </city><id>722953</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072321</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Boston Comic Con (&lt;a href="http://www.bostoncomiccon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.bostoncomiccon.com&lt;/a&gt;) is being held Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday October 24-25 from 10am-5pm at the Back Bay Events Center (180 Berkeley Street, Boston, MA). The cost of admission is $10 for the day. I went last year and it was somewhat small as convention go; I got through the entire convention in a little over an hour. There were comics and comic related items for sale as well as some very good artists scattered around drawing. You can check out the link for a full list of artists that will be there- I've put some of the artists I'm personally interested in seeing below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone is interested in catching a drink or something afterward, let me know. I'm not familiar with the area in terms of venues, but we can play that by ear if people are interested. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;STEPHANE ROUX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Making a trip across the Atlantic to showcase his talent at the BOSTON COMIC CON - STEPHANE ROUX is a HOT French comic book artist who is known mostly for his cover work for MARVEL, DC and SEMIC comics. He has worked on such titles as WITCHBLADE: BLOODOATH as well as SIBILA and STRANGERS in the SEMIC pocket publications-His most recent works have included cover artist on BIRDS OF PREY, and COUNTDOWN TO FINAL CRISIS for DC comics. Let’s show this continent hopper what a real AMERICAN comic show is like! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; MIKE McKONE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIKE McKONE has penciled many titles including JUSTICE LEAGUE OF AMERICA and JUSTICE LEAGUE INTERNATIONAL and PUNISHER WAR ZONE for MARVEL COMICS.- However it was his work of Marvel's EXILES which brought him instant attention, and led him to work on DC's TEEN TITANS and Marvel's FANTASTIC FOUR. - His most recent credits include AMAZING SPIDER-MAN and is working on covers for DEADPOOL: SUICIDE KINGS and PUNISHER. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;KHOI PHAM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The BCC is proud to bring to the city KHOI PHAM, one of MARVEL COMICS' finest artists; A superstar who is considered to be one of Marvel's &amp;quot;YOUNG GUNS. From X-FACTOR to the INCREDIBLE HERCULES to his whirlwind run on the SECRET INVASION flashback chapters of MIGHTY AVENGERS - it is hard to believe that Khoi has had no formal training! - Come meet this artist whose career in the comic field may have come quick, but by no means will it be a short one. Welcome to Boston, KHOI PHAM&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My profile pic is recent and accurate. I'll be waiting out front with a red 8x11 sci-fi meet-up sign somehow attached to my person.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn</member_name><member_id>9373103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256580619000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255477188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Comic Con</name><id>11620701</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256407200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/11620701/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/global_8154265.jpeg</photo_url></item>