<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Monument Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.482584</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Old North Bridge Parking Lot</name><city>Concord </city><id>921963</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.339009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;I may be out of town at the time of this event. If that happens, this will turn into an &amp;quot;informal&amp;quot; meetup. By that I mean those who are interested may still utilize our Meetup site to see who is planning to attend, and arrange to connect at the event. Please make good use of our message boards. If you plan to attend, and would like to help organize this event, please contact me asap!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, Dave, for bringing this event to our attention! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CAPE Group will meet at 10:30a.m.&lt;/b&gt; at the parking area near Hartwell Tavern for the second part of this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BATTLE ROAD&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date:&lt;/b&gt;  April 17, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt;  8:30 AM to 5:30 PM (Please note: CAPE Group will meet at  7:30a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt;  North Bridge, Concord, and Hartwell Tavern/Captain William Smith House, Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission:&lt;/b&gt; Free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Details:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minute Man National Historical Park, in partnership with hundreds of Colonial and British reenactors, celebrate the openning battle of the American Revolution with a day full of exciting living history activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Hartwell Tavern, Lincoln, 9:30 a.m. - 5:30 p.m., you will have the chance to talk with reenactors and park rangers, see a historic home and tavern that stood witness to the events of April, 19, 1775, and enjoy a variety of 18th century activities including drill and musket demonstrations, 18th century artillery demonstrations, crafts, games and more! The Captain William Smith House (British Headquarters) will also be open from 9:30 a.m.  - 12:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bloody Angle Tactical Demonstration&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hartwell Tavern, Lincoln &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/mima/upload/MIMA%20Park%20Map.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Please click HERE for map.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Bloody Angle Tactical Demonstration features hundreds of British and Colonial Reenactors encamped at the Hartwell Tavern and Captain William Smith house. They will stage a running tactical weapons demonstration along a half-mile of the original Battle Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hartwell Tavern is located on Rt 2A in Lincoln. NPS staff will direct you to parking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271688385000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268277644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Part II: Battle Road Reenactment at Minute Man National Historical Park</name><id>12845443</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271514600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/12845443/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_3584529.jpeg</photo_url></item>