<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; this band and they're here for the weekend again @Haluwa!  Great music and dancing! (Four on the Floor is also @Princeton Station, but seeing our experiences THERE lately, I put THIS up! lol)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be in the mood for chinese!  (I love their Peking Ravioli, Rice w/Shrimp and Chicken Fingers!)  Watch their Scorpion bowls, they seem to have a REAL affect! lol  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They always do a great job and they have a great group of regulars.  They love the Meetup group whether its for our dancers or just group support!  They'll have the big TVs on local games as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Haluwa is off exit 6w in Nashua in the Nashua Mall, just beyond Denny's &amp;amp; Radio Shack, but before Shortys.  We'll start at 8, the band is at 9, til closing around 1!.  &lt;b&gt;We're probably going for the far corner of the club this time&lt;/b&gt;, where we can add tables as we add people thru the night, as its hard to get the center section we usually get on a band night!  So don't be afraid to come late if you have to.  We've had some big crowds there and the late comers keep us up to the end! And we have fun with other groups there too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom D'A 603-521-7610 before, c603-682-2412 during&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meetup signs on table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291610656000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291483232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dancing, to Rock City Band, at the Haluwa tonight?</name><id>15640657</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291510800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/15640657/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/b/global_20011163.jpeg</photo_url></item>