<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius (ISBN 0-330-48455-9) is a memoir by Dave Eggers released in 2000. It chronicles his stewardship of younger brother Christopher &amp;quot;Toph&amp;quot; Eggers following the cancer-related deaths of his parents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;n Lake Forest, Illinois, Dave Eggers and his siblings, Bill, Beth and Toph (who is 13 years younger than his next-eldest sibling, Dave) endure the sudden death of their father due to lung cancer. Their mother dies a month later from stomach cancer after a long struggle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards, Dave, Beth and Toph move to California. Bill, who does not play a large role in the plot, eventually moves to Los Angeles. The rest of the family live in the San Francisco Bay Area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave and Toph begin living on their own in a dilapidated, untamed fashion. Dave struggles between moments of feeling that his approach to parenting is calculated and brilliantly designed to make Toph well-adjusted, to worrying that his hands-off approach and commitment to personal projects will make Toph maladjusted. Dave's own attempts to lead a normal life as a young adult often involve surreal encounters with women and alcohol. He feels both guilty for leaving Toph and damaged by his parents' death, and this fuels his pursuit of sex and irresponsibility.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a table and the book.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258677731000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256695605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius by David Eggar</name><id>11729151</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258504200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/11729151/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/e/global_11479726.jpeg</photo_url></item>