<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;may be&lt;/span&gt; the strangest theme yet, in fact I will go out on a limb and say &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;it is&lt;/span&gt; the strangest theme yet. Ghouls and Boys we are having goasts out on a limb for dinner this February. Goasts? What?   &lt;br /&gt;A goast, according to google ( and we know google is the word or is that grease, no bird is the word...anyway...) is a ghost of a goat that one may want to roast ergo goast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a saying about skinny branching that I have loved since I first heard it. A person I know was afraid to try something new, she was afraid to "go out on a limb" but her coach told her that life was about "skinny branching." This is when you climb a tree and and you move out on the limbs away from the safety of the trunk the branchs get thinner until you are balancing on a skinny branch that may bend under your weight. Any goat will tell you this is where to find the tenderest leaves for munching. You may land in a place you have never been by simply holding on to the skinny branch as it bends. But first you have to take the chance an crawl out there on the limb to the farthest skinny branch that can hold you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goast has a few other meanings, one of which as few of us may have heard of, but which we will not discuss further because we are all ladies and gentlemens here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goast also can mean Greatest of all S Things with the S filled in withwhat ever you are doing, i.e These cake pops are the goast. (Greatest of all sucker things)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever goast you create make it something that stretches your boundries, skills, knowhow and senses. Go out on a limb, in fact just spend the month skinny branching and see if life isn't just a bit more exciting overall.&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif" alt="love struck" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn&amp;rsquo;t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1298679105000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271720908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Goats out on a Limb - did u say ghosts? Yes.</name><id>vmbmnypdbpb</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297468800000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/16029247/</event_url></item>