<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Our second seminar of the weekend has a compelling title for those who long to go deeper in their spiritual development: Are You Ready to be a Student of the Spiritual Path? &lt;br /&gt;The student:teacher relationship has been a model for passing along the wisdom of the ages for centuries. This relationship takes a person from where they are now to however far they want to develop spiritually in the current lifetime. How would you know if you are at a place in your life where it's time to take a teacher? What does it mean to be ready for that relationship? Come and discover how the student:teacher relationship is meant to work and how to find a teacher if you're ready for one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the presenter: &lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes has devoted his life in service to God; for over 20 years, he has served as a Priest and Master Teacher. Currently, he serves as Co-Director of the Order of Christ/Sophia, teaching spiritual students, and guiding the operation of fifteen schools of meditation around the country. He travels between these Centers year-round, teaching and lecturing, as well as performing his music as a singer-songwriter of Mystical Christian folk rock. Many of the elements of the Mystical Christian teachings can be heard and experienced in Father Peter's music, encouraging the listener to seek and discover the Truth within. Listen to his music on Sophia Radio. When not traveling, Father Peter lives at the Center of Light in Chicago, IL.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256572358000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255674279000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Are You Ready to Be a Student of the Spiritual Path?</name><id>11640073</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256340600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/11640073/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/f/global_1078639.jpeg</photo_url></item>