<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Spring is right around the corner - so let's get out of the house, meet some great people and get your groove on!  Saint is one of my favorite spots in Boston, with dancing in one room and a lounge area in another.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR NEW MEMBERS:  You know who you are.  Perhaps you joined but never got around to coming to an event.  Perhaps you are a little shy about meeting new people.... or you are not so sure about this meetup thing....  well, put ALL of that aside.  This is a great opportunity to meet other new members and see what this group is all about!  Please arrive at 8pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR RETURNING MEMBERS:  To those who have come out with us previously -  you are the heart of the group and it has been a pleasure meeting everyone.  One of the best parts about this meetup is getting people together and seeing new and lasting friendships being formed on the spot.  I expect to see you this Friday at 9pm!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AS ALWAYS, feel free to bring friend or two, and we will see you FRIDAY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: New member meeting time is 8pm / Returning members meeting time is 9pm.  Meeting spot is Domani Bar at the Copley Square Hotel (47 Huntington Ave at Exeter St).  We will head over to Saint around 9:45-10pm to beat the lines. Please meet us before 9:30pm, as you may not find us later. Cover: $15-$20. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site.  For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saint is an upscale venue, so please dress appropriately.  Domani and Saint are right around the corner from each other, at Exeter St and Huntington Ave.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174867762000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174271401000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Member Meetup and More @ Saint THIS FRIDAY!</name><id>5582772</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174694400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/5582772/</event_url></item>