<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This one-day canine festival will be held from 11 a.m. to 4 p.m. Saturday, Oct. 18, on the Plymouth waterfront featuring games and prizes, food for dogs and their owners, demonstrations, live entertainment, and vendors offering dog-related services and items. Other events include a pet/owner photo look-alike contest, a pet costume contest, a dog-trick competition, an adoption presentation and obedience training. For the safety of animals and owners, all dogs must be on a leash at all times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information: &lt;a href="http://www.plymouthbarktoberfest.com./" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.plymouthba...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dog costume contest begins at noon. Prizes will be awarded for funniest costume, most beautiful costume and crowd favorite. There is no fee to enter and event day registrations will be accepted. Then enter the dog trick competition. All contestants must preregister by Oct. 10 by visiting www.plymouthbarktoberfest.com. All tricks must be performed in a safe manner for dogs, owners and spectators. is sure to be a crowd-pleaser. If you bear a striking resemblance to your loyal companion, enter the dog/owner photo lookalike contest; enter as above by Oct. 10. Prizes will be awarded to the winners, which will be announced at the festival. Corporate sponsorships are also available. For more information, contact Sarah Radigan at 508-830-1620 or sarah@plymouthchamber.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224515265000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>packwalk</urlname><id>1030709</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dog Lovers Pack Walk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223382265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Barktoberfest!</name><id>8914223</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224342000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/packwalk/events/8914223/</event_url></item>