<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dice games are controversial. &amp;nbsp;Often times, these games are believed to be purely luck based and lack the level of choice found in say, strategy games. &amp;nbsp;In addition, these games often have a strong gambling feel to them, invoking the sense of being a casino right in your own home. &amp;nbsp;Depending on the type of gamer you are, these traits can either be offputting or be exactly your cup of tea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who do enjoy dice games or want to give them another a chance, this event is for you. &amp;nbsp;:-) &amp;nbsp;If you want to find others to play the classics with (Yahtzee, Bunco, Farkle, etc.) we will definitely accomodate. &amp;nbsp;However, in addition we will also try and show off games that challenge the negative stereotypes associated with dice games. &amp;nbsp;In other words, today will be a afternoon of celebrating games whose primary mechanic is dice rolling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you're on a roll, I hope to see you! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;. Anyone can sign up, but I would please ask that you&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;allow new or previously inactive members get a slot if they are on the waiting list since there is limited seating. &amp;nbsp;Thanks.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;See this&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food theme:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme for this event will be "food that rolls". &amp;nbsp;Please bring a food item to share with the group that fits that theme. &amp;nbsp;Interpret that however you want, but here are some examples to stimulate your brain: &amp;nbsp;Jelly roll, oranges,&amp;nbsp;frankfurters, a can of Pringles, etc. &amp;nbsp;I will try to have also generic, healthy snacks on hand for all diets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

This event will be hosted at a private residence,&amp;nbsp;conveniently&amp;nbsp;located at the intersections of Route 1 and Route 95. &amp;nbsp;If you need directions, just ask. &amp;nbsp;This is a housing complex, so please do NOT park in any numbered spaces. &amp;nbsp;There are no animals on the premises. &amp;nbsp;Look for Unit 901 since Meetup doesn't display addresses correctly! :-(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Unit 901</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318247790000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316974532000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: On a Roll</name><id>34899202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318183200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/34899202/</event_url></item>