<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok here are the options:&lt;br /&gt;(1) Start from the River Street and rte 75 put in..&lt;br /&gt;its a nice 9 mile trip to the windsor boat launch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) Start from the BARTS put in on Pleasant st and rte 159..&lt;br /&gt;continuing down to the boat launch. 3.6 mile trip&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(3) Just go to the Rainbow Dam upstrem portion of the river which is very calm and easy to turnaround if the weather takes a turn towards rain...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on wether the dam is releasing water, the river street part of the river is usually low and not well passible, with the release on..there is some whitewater..NO FIBERGLASS kayaks for that start location.&lt;br /&gt;From BARTS on down..fiberglass is fine..its flatwater....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEET AT THE RIVER STREET LOCATION FIRST  to assess the situation, drive to BARTS or to Rainbow as we choose..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford or from the north, &lt;br /&gt;take 91 to exit #38  this is rte 75, go north...(towards poquanock and bradley apt.)&lt;br /&gt;from the exit off of 91..... River Street is about 2 miles on the right, you will cross the river by bridge, then take the right on to River st..go less than a quarter mile and on the right is a driveway/parking lot to the put in area. I think its called Strawberry Park on the sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the Blue Toyota Avalon with a few yaks on a trailer..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest or GPS directions , use 76 River street, Windsor, ct &lt;br /&gt;that will get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancells this event, so i will be checking prior to heading out.&lt;br /&gt;Light spotty rain back up plan... meet at River street lot anyway unless i see a storm comming and cancel the event..then We can go to BARTS for lunch or somewhere else.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180969288000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180628053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak trip on the Farmington River BEFORE it rains</name><id>5836628</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180796400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5836628/</event_url></item>