<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You have to walk the old Moseley family estate along the Merrimack River to believe it. The full grounds include 480 acres with the ruins of a 19th century estate and gardens, rolling hills, enormous trees, and in-season, the state’s largest mountain laurel display. The scenery moves swiftly from riverside views, to deep pine woods, to open meadows – with lots of hidden spots once reserved for the rich and famous.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may be surprised by the extent and crumbling beauty of the land and surviving outbuildings. There are extraordinary trails, but no posted explanation whatsoever about the family that once owned this rambling acreage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;History of Maudslay &lt;br /&gt;The Harvard Alumni page is the source for the information that follows. It seems that the former Fredrick Moseley Estate was originally called &amp;quot;Maudesleigh&amp;quot; and was built atop an early 19th century farm. There were up to 40 staff and 30 structures including separate houses for the head gardener, coachman and estate forester. Most of the newer buildings were built from 1895 to 1910. The 72-room mansion was demolished in 1955. Landscape archtect Martha Brookes Hutcheson was among the first three women members of American Society of Landscape Architects. There were extensive gardens, extensive stone walls, many cold frames and greenhouses, a large bunker, an animal cemetery and an enormous rhododendron collection that blooms annually.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of the above information is borrowed, for the most part, word for word, from the following website, should you like to read more: &lt;a href="http://www.seacoastnh.com/Travel/Scenic_Walks/Maudslay_State_Park/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.seacoastnh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although I can't make any promises for this walk, we spotted a bald eagle circling above us last time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Walk &lt;br /&gt;We will start the hike at 1:10. This walk will be about 4 miles long; possibly a little longer, depending on our pace.  We will move at a slow pace and stop at times to enjoy our surroundings.  For a trail map, use the following link: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/maud.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the Walk&lt;br /&gt;We will go to the Grog following the walk.  If you'd like, check out their website which includes a menu:  &lt;a href="http://www.thegrog.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thegrog.co...&lt;/a&gt;  I have made a reservation for 5:00 PM for 11 people.  As such, please let me know in advance if you plan on coming  to dinner after the walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Bring &lt;br /&gt;A Wind Breaker with a fleece underneath would be a good idea.  Keep in mind that it can be quite breezy and chilly next to the Merrimac River.  We want to enjoy these trails now, before some of them are closed for the nesting pair of bald eagles in Novemeber!  They close a portion of the park for these amazing creatures every winter, as part of a movement to help increase the number of bald eagles.  Please wear hiking boots or sneakers. Water, a snack, binoculars and a camera would also be good. There is an automated machine in the parking area- Please be sure to &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;bring exactly $2 in cash for parking&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; in case the machine has run out of change. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There &lt;br /&gt;Maudslay State Park &lt;br /&gt;For those with a GPS, the parking lot is located between 85 and 89 Curzon Mill Rd. in Newburyport, MA. If you don't have a GPS, please use mapquest or some other mapping program. I have included directions from I-95. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. From I-95, merge onto STOREY AVE/RT-113 W via EXIT 57 toward W. NEWBURY. 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;2. Turn RIGHT onto GYPSY LN/HOYTS LN. 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;(I believe the sign is for Hoyts Ln) &lt;br /&gt;3. Turn right onto CURZON MILL RD. 100-200 ft. &lt;br /&gt;4. 87 CURZON MILL RD is on the RIGHT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the parking lot is diagonally across the street from the Park Headquarters building, a historic white house. The restrooms are located in a little cement building at the back of the parking lot. Here is the phone # for the park: 978 465-7223 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Grog Restuarant&lt;br /&gt;Located at 13 Middle Street, Newburyport, MA 01950.  978 465-8008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Maudslay to The Grog: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting Point at Maudslay: 87 Curzon Mill Rd Newburyport, MA 01950  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Head east on Curzon Mill Rd toward Daniel Lucy Way  0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;2. Take the 1st right onto Daniel Lucy Way  0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;3. Turn left at Storey Ave (Route 113)  1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;4. Storey Ave turns slightly right and becomes High St (Route 113)  1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;5. Turn left at Fruit St (Route 113)  0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;6. Continue onto Fair St (Route 113) 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;7. Turn left at Middle St&lt;br /&gt;Destination will be on the right  495 ft &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Final Destination at The Grog: 13 Middle St, Newburyport, MA 01950 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note:  If this small parking area is full, you may park in the public lot&lt;br /&gt;on the waterfront, off of Merrimac Street.  I believe the lot is near 'Not Your Average Joes'&lt;br /&gt;located at 1 Market Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking lot with meetup stickers on.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>12</waitlist_count><updated>1288050653000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286834822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Walk at Maudslay State Park-many stops- followed by Dinner at the Grog </name><id>15076437</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287853200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15076437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/c/global_13071644.jpeg</photo_url></item>