<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1033 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.351951</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.787.4242 </phone><name>Brown Sugar</name><city>Boston</city><id>906361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121927</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I, Mark Shar, will be presenting "&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Emotions Defined and Understood Correctly: Tools of Self-Awareness, Not of Cognition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am astonished when I read definitions of emotions presented by most psychologists. They are as bad in their conceptualization and understanding of emotions (and their origin) as anthropologists are in understanding what makes humans unique among living species. All one has to do is read Rand and Branden to get wonderful and clear definitions of emotions. It is our conceptual faculty, our ability to reason and think conceptually, that makes humans unique among all species. And it is this same faculty that drives or sets the sail of our emotional mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be summarizing both Rand's and Branden's views and definitions of emotions. I will be adding my own thoughts about emotions and how our superb mind and emotional mechanism can become corrupted -- and how our emotional mechanism can be set against our rational self-interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will also discuss how emotions -- and one's day to day, let alone, minute to minute, experience of emotions can be used to uncover bad ideas and help us make conscious values we have accepted subconsciously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at Noon on Sunday, April 22, 2012 at the Brown Sugar Cafe on Commonwealth Ave in Boston for as brief a presentation as I can make -- followed by a lively discussion and great camaraderie. All &lt;em&gt;reason based&lt;/em&gt; criticisms, questions, witticisms, confusions, exasperations, metaphors, epanalepses, cheers, jeers, hyperboles, etc. are welcome! The &lt;em&gt;expression&lt;/em&gt; of emotion will also be welcome!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for our familiar faces... look for the table with the "Meetup Group" sign or ask a waiter/waitress</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Shar</member_name><member_id>9291676</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338728491000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326263828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Emotions Defined and Understood Correctly: Tools of Self-Awareness, Not of...</name><id>47620942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338652800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/47620942/</event_url></item>