<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Stevens Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01845</zip><lat>42.691586</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Weir Hill</name><city>North Andover</city><id>922750</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110088</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a short notice event. Due to this fact, you will need to email me if you want to go. I will add you manually. If there is sufficient interest in doing this, I will set up a recurring series starting next week (with open RSVP).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would like to acknowledge Karine for getting me thinking about this with the Fells ones she lists. However, the fells is just too far for me to drive so instead of joining that group I may be starting one in the North Andover area. Since I know Weir Hill inside out, I will be offering to lead a run this Friday instead of just going solo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to know what the mud pits are all about? Or go running through a stick fortress? The best parts of Weir Hill are off the map to the north of the reservation in quasi-public land. There are some fun areas to zoom through! I am looking to do between 4 and 8 miles, depending on group pace. Most likely route is an hour long 6. Please be prepared to do a 12 minute pace or faster and this is all off trail. And be ready to get rained on. The rainy days are when the mud pits are deepest and when I enjoy it most :-) you will get muddy this week and have been warned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will go about 1/2 mile, then stretch, then get to the main event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear sneakers or trail shoes - or flats or whatever you are comfortable trail running in. My advice is that hiking boots are going to be way, way too heavy. I recommend bringing some water as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask when you get there</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew B</member_name><member_id>4803051</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308971380000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308796859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trail Run at Weir Hill</name><id>23204331</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308909600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/23204331/</event_url></item>