<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Behind Woodstar Cafe</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01063</zip><lat>42.317646</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation Community Room</name><city>Northampton</city><id>508449</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.638031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>5:30 to 8:00 pm (program 6:00-7:30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments: Light snack provided, drinks/sandwiches can be purchased from Woodstar Café next door&lt;br /&gt;Cost: Suggested Donation at the Door: $10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the first time in history, RR Bowker, keeper of the international Books-In-Print database,&lt;br /&gt;reports the number of US books published in 2009 exceeded the 1 million mark, more than three&lt;br /&gt;times the books published just five years ago. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While traditional book publishing growth has come&lt;br /&gt;to a near standstill, print-on-demand and e-book publishing are experiencing unprecedented growth.&lt;br /&gt;Find out about the differences, advantages, and options these three publishing models offer.&lt;br /&gt;Landing a book deal with a coveted traditional publisher is more difficult than ever, yet not&lt;br /&gt;impossible, while the other publishing options are getting easier and garnering respect.&lt;br /&gt;Explore how you can join the publishing revolution and the best publishing options for you.&lt;br /&gt;Traditional Publishing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What does it take to get a book published by a major publisher such as Random House, McGraw-Hill, or Wiley? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How can you find out what publishers would be best for you in terms of providing support? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the advantages and disadvantages of landing a book deal?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POD and Self-Publishing. What are the different options for publishing outside of the traditional&lt;br /&gt;book publishing arena? How do you avoid getting ripped off? What are the advantages and disadvantages&lt;br /&gt;of the different models? How do you select the model that is right for you?&lt;br /&gt;E-Book Publishing. What are the differences between print books and e-books in preparation and &lt;br /&gt;display?  What are the different conversion and hosting options for e-book publishing? What are &lt;br /&gt;the advantages and disadvantages of publishing e-books compared with or in addition to print?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Panel:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Claudia Gere:&lt;/b&gt; (www.ClaudiaGereCo.com) helps entrepreneurs, speakers, and consultants develop their &lt;br /&gt;best writing strategy and realize their dreams of becoming an author--through her webinars, workshops, &lt;br /&gt;and individual coaching. She has launched many first-time authors using many different publishing &lt;br /&gt;strategies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Shel Horowitz:&lt;/b&gt; Award-winning author of Grassroots Marketing for Authors and Publishers, Shel Horowitz &lt;br /&gt;recently published his eighth book, Guerrilla Marketing Goes Green (co-author: Jay Conrad Levinson). &lt;br /&gt;Shel helps authors, publishers, and entrepreneurs with marketing plans, book jackets, website copy, &lt;br /&gt;press releases, etc., and turns unpublished writers into published authors. Shel's been quoted &lt;br /&gt;repeatedly in the NY Times, Wall Street Journal, Entrepreneur, etc. An expert on Green, ethical, &lt;br /&gt;and effective marketing, he's been using social media marketing since 1995. Shel speaks frequently &lt;br /&gt;on social media, book publishing, frugal/ ethical marketing, and Green/ethical business success. &lt;br /&gt;He's the founder of the international Business Ethics Pledge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason Mark: (&lt;/b&gt;www.GravitySwitch.com) Jason has both written and collaborated on a handful of children's &lt;br /&gt;books (both for himself and for a couple of clients). He's also created ePub books, some of which are &lt;br /&gt;currently available in Apple's iBookstore. Always with a passion for teaching and learning, Jason was &lt;br /&gt;one of the first dozen professors of website design in the country, where he had students who commuted &lt;br /&gt;from as far away as California to take his class. His web development company, Gravity Switch, &lt;br /&gt;continues to be the leader in the region for web, iPhone and iPad development. Twice a day, you can &lt;br /&gt;see him on the bike path between his Northampton office and his Florence home -- even in winter. His &lt;br /&gt;wife is also super smart, and if you're interested in distributing your book on the Apple iPad, you &lt;br /&gt;should read her &amp;quot;mini-guide&amp;quot; about your options: &lt;a href="http://www.gravityswitch.com/epub" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gravityswi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hidden-tech.net/events.html" target="_blank"&gt;Link to Hidden-tech upcoming events page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285103124000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284082608000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BOOK PUBLISHING IN THE DIGITAL AGE</name><id>14718673</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285018200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/14718673/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/d/global_17979373.jpeg</photo_url></item>