<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>New London at Exit 7 Park'n'Ride West Greenwich, RI 02818</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>54961</zip><lat>41.656900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Big River Managment Area</name><city>West Greenwich</city><id>1603718</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.551470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Last minute planners. We are a small group of people and dogs who like to hike in dog friendly/off leash places. If you have a dog who likes to run amuk and/or like dogs and like hiking please feel free to join us. We are not really numbers people, so we don't know exactly how many miles we will be hiking. I would say somewhere between 2-10, we will basically hike until it looks like it is time to head back before it gets dark and then possibly grab a drink or something afterwards. Things always work out fine, but I am guessing if you are hell bent on planning, and/or are a bit of a control freak hell bent on control freaki-ness, this might not be comfortable for you. Though we are not hiking nazis, we like to hike, so if you are looking for a leisurely walk, this might not be great for you either. People who join are welcome to hike part of the way, and decide when you want to go back, or hike with us the whole way. We aren't your mothers and won't tell you what to bring, but hiking boots or sturdy shoes are good and PLEASE bring enough water for both you and&amp;nbsp; Rover (backpacks are great).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get to Big River Management area take exit 6 off 95. There are lots of woods and trails and lakes and it is never too crowded. We will meet in the big parking lot. Don't worry, you will see us.&amp;nbsp; If you reply to this email we will make sure to look for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trails.com/trail-big-river-state-management-2026466.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.trails.com/trail-big-river-state-management-2026466.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://www.trails.com/trail-big-river-state-management-2026466.html</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Danielle</member_name><member_id>7105895</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309623569000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309528363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>people + dogs hiking amuk through woods.  Kent County Big River Management area</name><id>24217521</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309618800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/24217521/</event_url></item>