<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Lang Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.898380</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>237586</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.701836</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that we have some daylight after work, I'm going to start offering some short, after work hikes, probably mostly at Northwest Park, as that's convenient to both home and work for me.  These will be more of a walk in the woods than a serious hike.  For these spring ones, we'll only walk about an hour at a social (slow) pace, in order to insure we are back before sunset.  As we gain more daylight, we can do slightly longer times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The walks here will cover rolling trails, and most have water views. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet in the parking lot at 5:30.  With the sun setting around 7:00, we will only wait about 10 minutes for latecomers so we can get in a good walk.  Expect to be out on the trail about an hour and a half or so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kids and leashed dogs welcome.  I'll have my two dogs with me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check back that morning to see if I have updated the plans based on weather or other factors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone is interested, pizza after at the nearby (and very good) Tunxis Grill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be re-posting this walk on a regular basis weeknights, generally Tuesday or Thursday, in the coming weeks.  Hope you can join me sometime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Gloria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note about dogs: While this is a dog-friendly hike, the dog owners need to be responsible. Park rules require leashes. If you choose to break that rule and let your dog off the leash, please be sure it is okay with the other hikers (some of whom may not be dog people) and be sure you can control your dog when off leash. Finally, please be prepared and clean up after your dog when needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me with my dogs in the parking lot area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365209851000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363555459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northwest Park in Windsor</name><id>109718752</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364938200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/109718752/</event_url></item>