<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 138</address_2><address_1>945 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02072</zip><lat>42.119707</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-297-7510</phone><name>Zachary's</name><city>Stoughton</city><id>1433427</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101596</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for a pre-holiday Breakfast for Lunch at our Z Restaurant: Zachary's!  Breakfast is served all day here and almost everything on the menu is under $10.  This is our last restaurant in our A-Z Restaurants quest that we started nearly 3 years ago.  We have dined at restaurants beginning with every letter of the alphabet and have enjoyed quite an array of restaurants, meals, and travelled to quite a few towns along the way.  We started with a Japanese Dinner in Marshfield on a Saturday night and will close the menu with a Breakfast in Stoughton on a Sunday afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope you will join us in celebration of eating our way through the alphabet with a Breakfast for Lunch as we wrap-up this weekend of Thanksgiving.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, November 28th @ 12:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Zachary's Breakfast &amp;amp; Lunch&lt;br /&gt;945 Washington St &lt;br /&gt;Route 138 (southbound side)&lt;br /&gt;Stoughton, MA 02072&lt;br /&gt;(781) 297-7510&lt;br /&gt;No website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: Please meet outside the front door.  We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: &lt;br /&gt;1. We may be separated into two tables.  &lt;br /&gt;2. They may not seat complete parties if they are extremely busy.  If you are running very late or not attending please call the restaurant so they can let us know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Alison and Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: [Current] Annual Members - FREE, Members - $2 each; $12 to become a 2011 Annual Member ($10 if you are a 2010 Annual Member, a past 2-year Annual Member or Former AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: No minimum.  Alison and Angela will dine by themselves if need be.&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;  Due to the size of the restaurant, the max is set at 10 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Sorry, this is members-only as there is a high interest among Group Members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 8pm on Saturday, November 27th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Zachary's is on Washington St. (Route 138) in Stoughton, just south of Stoughton Center on the right side of the road.  Routes 139 and 27 intersect in Stoughton Center.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travelling South on Route 138:  It is located just after the interection of Brock Street (and Kinsley Street).  If you pass Crescent Street or Town Spa Pizza (on your right) you have gone too far south.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travelling North on Route 138: You will pass by Town Spa Pizza on your left and then Crescent Avenue on your right.  If you pass Brock Street (or Kinsley Street) or arrive in Stoughton Center you have gone too far north.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the front door or at our table after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison </member_name><member_id>9429931</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291161623000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289866568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast for Lunch! </name><id>15458614</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290963600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/15458614/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/b/global_14765243.jpeg</photo_url></item>