<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total distance is approximately 11 miles.  Estimated time is 8:48.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers are expected to know their abilities.  I am rating this hike a 5.  All partcipants are required to read and agree to the Liability and Waiver policy on this WEB site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Either a White Mountain year long decal or a one day parking permit (available there) is required to park in the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lincoln Woods Trail and the Wilderness Trail forms the central artery from which numerous trails diverge and lead to various parts of the Pemigewasset Wilderness and to the adjoining mountains. Originally, the entire trail was called the Wilderness Trail, but the USFS changed the name of the first segment to Lincoln Woods Trail because that part of the trail lies outside the Pemigewasset Wilderness. For most of its length, the trail follows the bed of a logging railroad that last operated in 1948. This trail receives extremely heavy use, particularly in the few miles nearest the highway, and camping is strictly regulated. Details concerning such restrictions can be obtained at the Lincoln Woods Information Center, located next to the parking area, or from other USFS sources. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail begins on the west side of the Lincoln Woods Trail. It heads west, following a brook in a flat area, then climbs the bank to the right and soon enters a section of an old incline logging railroad grade at one of its switchbacks. It continues up the valley on this grade and then on old logging roads not far above the brook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It turns right and climbs by switchbacks to the top of the ridge above the valley to the north, then ascends the ridge—winding about at first, then climbing by zigzags as the ridge becomes steeper. At the top of this section are several wooden staircases, and a side path (sign) leads right to a “downlook” with a very fine view of Mt. Bond. Soon the trail reaches the top of the ridge, and its grade becomes easy until it reaches the crest of the Franconia Ridge in an unusually flat area. The trail turns sharp right here and ascends near the crest of a narrow ridge to a junction with the Flume Slide Trail on the left and the Franconia Ridge Trail straight ahead.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dianne and I will be in a black four door Toyota Echo with Maine Plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242078480000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237829114000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT. FLUME</name><id>10016669</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241874000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10016669/</event_url></item>