<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Taking in the evergreen forest of late Fall as Christmas approaches, the rippling stream, and the soothing din of the waterfall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A very easy and lovely fairly level 2-3 mile hike at the Belding Trout Management Area in Vernon. This roughly 1.75 hour long hike is very pleasant and is great for beginners and is scenic enough with the forest, stream, and dammed pond to interest more advanced hikers. This area is a hidden gem and even connects to Valley Falls, the Hop River Linear Trail, the Schinipsit Trail, and some Northern Connecticut Land trust property! How's that for location? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at trailhead parking (end of cul-de-sac on Tamarac Ln., Vernon, CT) but this can be somewhat limited depending on the number of attendees. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids and dogs on leash welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunset around 4:18 PM but we will be done by no later than 4 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail guide and map&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/wildlife/pdf_files/maps/maps_other/BeldingTrailGuide.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate trailhead parking&lt;/b&gt; for hike: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=99+Tamarac+ln&amp;amp;city=vernon&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1292898944000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291359783000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Belding Wildlife Management Area, Vernon CT</name><id>15629343</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292785200000</time><rsvp_limit>38</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15629343/</event_url></item>