<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Spectacular Now (2013)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directed By: &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/celebrity/james_ponsoldt/"&gt;James Ponsoldt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Written By: &lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/celebrity/1184325-michael_h_weber/"&gt;Michael H. Weber&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tim Tharp's unsentimental tale of adolescent frustration comes to the screen in this comedy drama following the story of a sociable high school senior whose self-delusion shattered by his emerging friendship with an unpopular classmate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;TY Burr:  The festival’s opening night presentation comes to Boston after going over big at SXSW and especially Sundance, where costars Miles Teller and Shailene Woodley shared a special jury prize for “rare honesty, naturalism and transparency.” Translation: The movie’s a teenage romance with characters who seem like actual teenagers. Based on a novel by Tim Tharp, “Now” stars Teller (“Rabbit Hole”) as a life-of-the-party senior whose bravado masks insecurity; Woodley (“The Descendants”) is the class nobody he dates first out of pity and then — oh, you know. It’s an oft-told tale — a dab of John Hughes, a dash of “Perks of Being a Wallflower” — made fresh by the gentle realism of the playing and the levelheaded direction of James Ponsoldt (“Smashed”).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Rotten Tomatoes:  86%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As this is opening night of the Boston Independent Film Festival, I strongly encourage you to &lt;a href="https://prod1.agileticketing.net/websales/pages/list.aspx?epguid=2203ac9e-c5b3-41ff-b03e-5ed5c8fd1fac&amp;amp;"&gt;purchase your tickets in advance&lt;/a&gt; to avoid getting stuck in the Rush Line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opening Night has annually been among the funnest film events of the year.  According to Chase Whale, &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Spectacular Now&lt;/span&gt; is "&lt;span&gt;The most important adult-oriented film about the victories and woes of high school life in the last decade."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opening Night can be a chaotic seating event.  Seating is likely to begin around 7:00 for Pass Holders, but the line for ticket holders starts forming around 6:15, and is well around the block by 6:45.  We gather at Mr. Crepe in Davis Square, next to the Somerville Theater, starting at around 6 to enjoy a bite to eat and to get into the line, together, when it begins to form for real, usually between 6:20 and 6:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will gather at Mr. Crepe in time to get in line at 6:30</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366858048000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366497415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Spectacular Now - Opening Night of BIFF</name><id>115345112</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366846200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/115345112/</event_url></item>