<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Soldiers Field Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.360067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree Suites</name><city>Boston</city><id>968618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/2/6/event_146776422.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Generating Leads Online &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Ralph Plumb is a seasoned and experienced internet marketer with a focus on generating organic (FREE) traffic. Ralph’s marketing methods and systems are recognized as the most effective by the experts and gurus around the world. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Ralph is passionate about entrepreneurship and is self-proclaimed ‘entrepreneurial enthusiast’ with a passion for never working for ‘The Man’ and is passionate about sharing his strategies with others. Ralph’s systems allow entrepreneurs and business owners&lt;span&gt;...&lt;/span&gt; to release themselves of the day to day grind of generating leads to fuel their businesses allowing them to close more deals. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Ralph’s systems and processes for generating leads online are so effective students from all over the country, in every market, are seeing unheard of success. Ralph prides himself on taking what many people think of as technical or advanced, and simplifies the process to a few clicks of the mouse. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Ralph Plumb is a graduate of Yale University where he studied economics and computer science. Aside from his academic studies Ralph left Yale as the All-Time Leading Receiver on the football team and later signed a two-year contract with the Oakland Raiders of the NFL. Ralph immediately transitioned from football to real estate development. In his career in real estate Ralph has completed over 200 real estate transactions in 6 years as a part-time investor. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Monthly Meeting &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

5:30 pm, Thursday, August 16, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Doubletree Guestsuites, 400 Soldier's Field Road, Boston &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

free for members; $25 for non-members and meetup members &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

free parking&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345213559000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Generating Leads Online with Ralph Plumb</why><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>75</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344354478000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston AREIA Monthly meeting</name><id>lpnmqyqlbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345152600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/76709812/</event_url></item>