<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Salem Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.260864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-799-1655</phone><name>Worcester Public Library</name><city>Worcester</city><id>999847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.800133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Framing Party!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nov 10th 9am to 11:30am Banx Room Worcester Public Library&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If your image appears in this gallery:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/photos/11099542/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/photos/11099542/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;you need to make a print and have it matted to a 16x24 outside dimensions. Please use a white mat... read on for more details...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This meeting will be for the members who are participating in the upcoming show "Let There Be Light" to get details, learn about framing the prints, and discuss the opening of the show.The opening of the show is going to be on Friday Nov 30th around 5:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Participants; We will have your frame ready for you at this meeting. We will show you how to take your matted print and put it in the frame with the glass and how to seal it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you need to bring to the meeting:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please bring with you a Flat Head Screw Driver!! Everyone will need one to put the frames together.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your Print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your Mat - cut to fit your print.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your Print should be mounted to a back board and attached to your mat. (or we will do it there with you) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our frames are 16x24 in size. This means- All accepted photographs must be matted to a 16x24 outside dimensions - we will accept white mats only. You must come to the framing party on November 10th at the Worcester Public Main Library to frame your own matted pieces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are responsible for labeling the artwork on display with artist name, title and price (if your image is being offered for sale). So you need to supply this information at the framing party.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So, Bring your matted print. This means you need to have a mat cut! The frame size is 16x24 so the over all mat must fit into a 16x24 frame.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We suggest making your prints 11x14 or 9x12 so they can have a nice white boarder around the image. We will not be accepting images that are not matted. SO no flush mounted images.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;VERY IMPORTANT:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;IF YOUR IMAGE IS SQUARE---- PLEASE MAKE THE MAT VERTICAL!! David Snay, and Rebecca W This means you! Email me if you have a question.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We want everyone to sign the mats in the lower right corner of the mat's opening- if you do not know what this means -don't sign it- just bring it to the meeting and we will discuss where to sign the mat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You will need a back board to mount the print to and then place the mat over it. This back board should be the exact same size as the mat you had cut for your print. I recommend it be the same material as the mat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Simply tell whomever is cutting the mats that they need to fit into a 16x24 frame.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please check in with me about the title of your print and the price you want to sell it for before you leave this meeting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I look forward to our next show...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cheers,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donna&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;PS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As for the this show. We are trying to coincide it with the City's Festival of Lights, which will take place Friday, November 30th. We had talked about a theme of &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let there be Light&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;- which is very open for interpretation. The skating rink ion the Worcester Common will open that night in addition to the lighting of the tree will take place that day at 5PM. It would be great if we could have the next exhibition open on this date. There will be allot of people downtown. The downtown biz association is thinking about the idea of getting businesses to light up their windows, which would be a good compliment to the exhibitions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the banx room on the left as you enter from the parking lot doors</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Lane</member_name><member_id>5229126</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352768304000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351648076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framing Party for the Let There Be Light show at the City Hall Gallery</name><id>89269592</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352556000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/89269592/</event_url></item>