<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;JOIN US FOR OUR FIRST ANNUAL YANKEE SWAP HOLIDAY PARTY!  G. Williker's is chosen as we can have our own large room that has both tables and booths.  Everyone enjoyed the place when we had our event there on 10/30/09.  Many have asked to return to Williker's as the food is great and so are the prices.  It's the perfect place for a Meetup event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the Yankee Swap playing rules:  &lt;u&gt;Gifts are wrapped, but are not labeled&lt;/u&gt; to reflect a specific  recipient. Gifts should be around $10.00 in value and are humorous items or really nice gifts!  So bring a wrapped gift with no label as we will 'somewhat' exchange the gift! All the gifts will be placed on a long large table to start the game.  All participants draw a number (from a hat, perhaps) to determine their order. The participant with #1 ticket unwraps any gift from the pile and then shows it to everyone. Each successive participant, in the order determined from the drawing can either 1) &amp;quot;steal&amp;quot; an already opened gift (if there's one they really like) or 2) be adventurous and go for a wrapped gift from the pile. If the participant chooses to steal, the person whose gift is stolen now repeats his turn and either 1) steals another person's gift (he cannot immediately steal back the gift that was just stolen from him) or 2) unwraps a new gift.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A new gift is chosen, at which point the turn is passed to the participant with the next number from the drawing.  Since items can be taken, the item in your possession is not yours until the game is over.  The game is over once all names have been withdrawn from the hat.  Whomever had the ticket #1 gets to pick at the end of the game from any of the unwrapped gifts! Please remember that gifts should be valued at $10.00 at least. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that we want to get RSVPs in as soon as possible so we can all plan our gift buying accordingly.  PLEASE REPLY WITH YOUR 'YES' RESPONSE AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.  This will be a great time:  Dinner, Yankee Swap, Shooting Pool (yep they have a room with pool tables right there), and a great band for dancing!  Join us for our FIRST ANNUAL YANKEE SWAP!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the Hostess for the Meetup Group!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1260723150000</updated><rating><average>4.73999977112</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>48</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257209006000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FIRST ANNUAL YANKEE SWAP HOLIDAY PARTY!</name><id>11776566</id><headcount>56</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259973000000</time><rsvp_limit>55</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/11776566/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/c/7/global_11615575.jpeg</photo_url></item>