<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>141 Middlesex Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.488703</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 270-4800</phone><name>Guard Up! Family Swordsmanship</name><city>Burlington</city><id>803767</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.222199</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Adventure Night: Can You Hear the Silence?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Satuday, January 24, 6:30-8:30pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bustling town of New Vigil has been a trading and market hub for many generations. It has always been known as a loud and busy area where sleep is rare and silence is unheard. But recent traders have reported just the opposite. New Vigil has fallen into complete silence...except for the sounds of snoring. There have been numerous rumors: nightmares coming to life, strange creatures wandering the village, and a malevolent force feeding off the dreams of the sleeping village. What is the source of the eternal sleep that has taken hold? What are these creatures? Is there any way to break the spell? The heroes must make their way to New Vigil and rouse the village...or succumb to slumber themselves...&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pre Reg*: $15/members and friends $25/non&lt;br /&gt;At Door: $25/members and friends $35/non&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Live Action Roleplaying Event (medieval fantasy in theme). Durable and safe costuming is allowed. If you have not attended an Adventure Night before and played a character, you will be given a pre-generated character to play. Once you have played one event, you can opt to create your own character. Arrive at least 30 minutes early (at 6pm) so that you may have time to look over the rule book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Previous swordsmanship experience is not required. We provide the padded weapons (and spell packets). This is a family event with adults, teens and kids (ages 6+). If not in costume, Sweats and T-shirts are suggested. No shorts or tanktops allowed. Under 18 must have signed waiver by parents. 18 and over must have their own signed waiver. Waivers can be downloaded here: &lt;a href="http://www.guardup.net/sword/documents/event_waiver.doc" target="_blank"&gt;Waiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $15 for Meet Up members (and their friends) who pre-register ($25 for non). Pre-registration required as these events DO fill up and we cannot take anyone else after our capacity is reached. To pre-register you must call (781) 270-4800 and pay ahead with a credit card or cash. Make sure to tell them that &amp;quot;Meghan sent you&amp;quot; so that you get the Meet Up rate which is the same as the Member Rate (a savings of $10).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: RSVP with YES does NOT PRE-REGISTER. You MUST call (781) 270-4800 and pay ahead to complete the pre-registration process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At-Door is $25 and you may be turned away if there is not enough room. Since we fill up before the event more than 1/2 the time, pre-registration is highly recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure to be ontime for required safety instruction at start of event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the front desk... they can help you!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>5106555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235777629000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Sword Fighters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Swordsmanship-and-Fencing-for-Beginners</urlname><id>1313138</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Swordsmanship and Fencing for Beginners</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230611274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Adventure Night: Can You Hear the Silence?</name><id>9406088</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235259000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Swordsmanship-and-Fencing-for-Beginners/events/9406088/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/1/global_6770993.jpeg</photo_url></item>