<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-225-0888</phone><name>Tommy Doyle's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>835734</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This month: Mistakes Were Made (But Not By Me) by Carol Tavris&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A revelatory study of how lovers, lawyers, doctors, politicians--and all of us--pull the wool over our own eyes. The politician who can''t apologize, the torturer who feels no guilt, the co-worker who''ll say anything to win an argument--in case you''ve ever wondered how such people can sleep at night, a new book by Carol Tavris and Elliot Aronson supplies some intriguing and useful insights. Thanks, in part, to the scientific evidence it provides and the charm of its down-to-earth, commonsensical tone, Mistakes Were Made is convincing. Reading it, we recognize the behavior of our leaders, our loved ones, and--if we''re honest--ourselves, and some of the more perplexing mysteries of human nature begin to seem a little clearer. By the book''s end, we''re far more attuned to the ways in which we avoid admitting our missteps, and intensely aware of how much our own (and everyone''s) lives would improve if we--and those who govern and lead us--understood the power and value of simply saying, ''I made a mistake. I''m sorry.''&amp;quot; (O Magazine )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B000SEHKHO/ref=pd_lpo_k2_dp_sr_2?pf_rd_p=486539851&amp;amp;pf_rd_s=lpo-top-stripe-1&amp;amp;pf_rd_t=201&amp;amp;pf_rd_i=0151010986&amp;amp;pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&amp;amp;pf_rd_r=1T45QZ9136C42AW08JKP" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boston Atheists Table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276989060000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271878066000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book &amp; Brew (Mistakes Were Made (But Not By Me) by Carol Tavris)</name><id>xxtmnynjbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276984800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/13250437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>