<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>555 Asylum Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767876</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-978-2622</phone><name>ArtSpace</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1045061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.682486</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff99"&gt;Around this time of year, it can be challenging to eat healthy when there’s temptation all around you. If your diet is different from that of your family and friends, it can be hard to turn down food lovingly made for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff99"&gt;We hope you’ll join us for a discussion about how to create a healthy, delicious, joyful holiday. We’ll discuss food challenges people faced during past holidays and share solutions people found.   We will do some role playing to help you practice gently but firmly saying “no” to the foods you want to avoid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff99"&gt;Also, we will discuss alternatives to standard holiday food for people with dietary restrictions, such as gluten-free, sugar-free, or vegetarian diets. Lastly, we’ll talk about how to shift the focus off food issues and place it on celebrating the foods you can eat, feeling deep gratitude, and nourishing connections with others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff99"&gt;The discussion will be facilitated by Renee Canada, holistic health coach, and Laura Le, the founder of CT Health Foodies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;BIOS: Renée Canada is an AADP-board certified holistic health coach for The Mind-Body Shift, with training from the Institute for Integrative Nutrition and UConn's School of Public Health. In her practice, clients learn to improve their health and lifestyle through a holistic approach to wellness that encompasses the body, mind and spirit. To learn more about how you can create the healthy, rewarding and happy life you’ve always desired, visit Renee’s website at &lt;a href="http://www.themindbodyshift.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.themindbodyshift.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Laura Le founded CT Health Foodies, a supportive community for people interested in healthy eating, in September 2012, because she recognized the power of positive peer pressure to help her “just say no” to foods that didn’t love her back. She is proud that she has made many positive changes to her diet and lifestyle this past year, and she’s feeling stronger and healthier than ever. She is looking forward to the holidays, because she loves to bring people together using creative games, conversation, and rituals that strengthen bonds and allow people to share their collective wisdom. Laura is a certified Laughter Yoga instructor, and you can check out her website here: &lt;a href="http://www.ctlaugh.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.ctlaugh.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schedule for the evening:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;7:15 pm: Delicious Potluck Dinner begins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;7:45 - 9:00 pm: Discussion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;9:00 pm - 9:30 on: Hanging out and cleaning up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;About the potluck dinner:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;-Many people have dietary restrictions. Please be mindful as you prepare your dish, and list the ingredients on a note card. Note cards will be available at the event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;-This a zero-waste event. Please bring your own plate, utensils, and water bottle.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 *********************************************** &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #fbf0ee"&gt;Donations between $2-$5 requested. No pressure to donate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE PARKING!&lt;/strong&gt; In the back of the ArtSpace building. Ignore "Resident Parking Only" signs. Parking is allowed during this event. Enter through the back entrance by the murals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************************************** &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ffffff"&gt;This CT Health Foodies event is part of an ongoing series of monthly potluck dinners and talks held on the second Tuesday of the month at ArtSpace in downtown Hartford.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;***********************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter through the back entrance by the murals.  Walk down the long corridor.  At the end of the corridor, on the right, you will see the room where we will be meeting.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>13105264</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352866591000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351894162000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck Dinner &amp; Discussion: "How to Have a Healthy, Delicious, Joyful Holiday"</name><id>dhwmcdyqpbrb</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352852100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/89701612/</event_url></item>