<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>255 Grossman Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.211508</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Border's Books &amp; Cafe</name><city>Braintree</city><id>715069</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.999105</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I am most likely going to have to miss this meeting myself, but feel free to join the rest of the crew as they discuss &lt;b&gt;Lipstick Jihad&lt;/b&gt; by Azadeh Moaveni. Denise has agreed to act as hostess in my absence. &lt;br /&gt;The group will meet in the cafe area of Borders Bookstore in Braintree. Someone will put a copy of the book on the table so that new folks can find the group more easily. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book Synopsis: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Azadeh Moaveni was born in Palo Alto, California, into the lap of an Iranian diaspora community longing for an Iran many thousands of miles away. As far back as she can remember she felt at odds with her tangled identity. College magnified the clash between Iran and America, and after graduating, she moved to Tehran as a journalist. Immediately, Azadeh's exile fantasies dissolved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Azadeh finds a country that is culturally confused, politically deadlocked, and emotionally anguished. In order to unlock the fundamental mystery of Iran-how nothing perceptibly alters, but everything changes--she must delve deep into Tehran's edgy underground. Lipstick Jihad is a rare portrait of Tehran, populated by a cast of young people whose exuberance and despair bring the modern reality of Iran to vivid life. Azadeh also reveals her private struggle to build a life in a dark country--the struggle of a young woman of the diaspora, searching for a homeland that may not exist.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To see all past books read by this group, see our goodreads page here: &lt;a href="http://www.goodreads.com/group/show/1091.South_Shore_Readers" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.goodreads....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the cafe area with a copy of the book on the table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265677387000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260997154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Shore Readers: Lipstick Jihad</name><id>12098672</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264356000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/12098672/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/4/global_12273652.jpeg</photo_url></item>