<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>So, very sadly, our go-to location, Boloco in Davis Sq., has closed permanently.  But, we have found another awesome location (yay Jenni!), an MIT conference room.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please make sure you read the details/directions below as to how to get there.&lt;/b&gt;  While it will not have the wonderful burritos, smoothies and such available at our fingertips, we can bring stuff in as long as we leave the room spotless when we leave.  Also, there is no &amp;quot;curfew&amp;quot; with this location - there will be no kind Boloco employee hoping we will leave at 10pm (or 9pm, as has been the recent case.)  We can stay as long as we need to satisfy our gaming obsessions.  So, that is a huge plus.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that are new to the group, welcome and please come join us for some gaming fun.  We play all kinds of games (please feel free to bring some, it's always good to have large selection!), from &lt;i&gt;Cranium&lt;/i&gt; to &lt;i&gt;Taboo&lt;/i&gt; to &lt;i&gt;Bang&lt;/i&gt; to &lt;i&gt;Shadows over Camelot&lt;/i&gt;.  It's a pretty diverse gaming group and there is always someone up for a new game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Directions&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT &lt;br /&gt;Building E25 room 119&lt;br /&gt;45 Carleton Street&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA 02142&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;**the door to the building is locked, but for the 1st &lt;b&gt;15&lt;/b&gt; minutes we will have someone posted at the door to let people  in.  If you arrive later than that, it should be easy to get in as there is a lot of foot traffic of people coming and going.  If you absolutely have to, you can call me, 617-710-9733.  But please, please wait at least a few minutes to see if someone is coming through and you can get in.  Thanks.  =)  ******&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the T:&lt;br /&gt;Take the red-line to Kendall Square station.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're coming outbound (from Park Street), exit at the gates at the front of the train.  Cross the street.  (The street will be behind you if you take the escalator.) Proceed behind the T entrance on the other side to the street behind.  Building E25 is the brick building across the street.  Once you enter, stay to the right, Room 119 is the 3rd set of doors past the elevators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're coming inbound (from Central Square), exit at the gates at the rear of the train.  Take the stairs or elevator straight up.  Proceed to the street in front of you. Building E25 is the brick building across the street.  Once you enter, stay to the right, Room 119 is the 3rd set of doors past the elevators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions from Mass Ave.:&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming from Boston or Memorial Drive, take a right at the first right past Memorial Drive.  This is Vassar Street.&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming from Cambridge and points west, take a left onto Vassar Street.  This will be past Central Square about 2 blocks before the river.  If you get to the river, you've gone too far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Vassar, take the first right onto Main Street.  Go through two signals then turn right onto Hayward.  You may park in the parking lot on the right side of Hayward.  A MIT parking permit is NOT required in the evening, but please do not park in the spaces marked Medical.  Exit the parking lot at the rear (opposite from where you entered).  Building E25 will be directly across the street. Once you enter, stay to the right, Room 119 is the 3rd set of doors past the elevators.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jenny</member_name><member_id>4106132</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222298730000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220388660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Game Night ***New Location***</name><id>8673149</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221087600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/8673149/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>