<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE:&lt;br /&gt;Whats this i hear about rain ??&lt;br /&gt;Well, i have a back up plan..provided its not blasting lightening and pouring rain..the light stuff...no problem..&lt;br /&gt;I got just the thing for  keeping us dry, something to add ambiance to the event..oh and i got something else..&lt;br /&gt;too cook up something, I got some ethnick food..last time was Hebrew National stuff..this time something Polish....its already loaded in the  Company Gas Hog...&lt;br /&gt;the nearby location..yep i got that too...if its not good to hike up the path in some rain..there is something real close that is what i call a Geological Feature, a good place for us..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, still meet at the location outlined below..the other place is at the bottom of the hill if we decide its not good for a short hike in the rain...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, since I have to work this weekend, Saturday most likely and maybe Sunday too..??....So I can?t post a decent enough kayak trip. &lt;br /&gt;Most Likely next weekend will be Chapman Pond and WaleBone Cove located near the Goodspeed Opera House Or the Bantam River in Bantam CT..not sure yet.. If I dont work Sunday and its good out..then i will post one of em..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO instead wouldn?t it be nice to have a short hike to a nice flat area near the first set of open area at the top path of the Heublin Tower (Talcott Mountain) for a small dinner, snacks and wine (other beverage too for non wino?s) for a sunset socializing event? &lt;br /&gt;I don?t plan on going to all the way to the tower, but its an option if there is enough time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can?t stay up there too much past sunset since im not sure how strict the rules are enforced for a park closing at sunset? &lt;br /&gt;We can find out im sure?.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;Look for the signs for Talcott Mountain/Hebulin Tower State Park area (south side of rte 185), its right across from Penwood State Forest if you missed it.. &lt;br /&gt;Go up the entrance way for a short distance, you will see the parking area off to the right across from the trail head on the left. I will have the Red Chevy Blazer with the plate WWU&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is in an odd location for most of your routs of travel.. &lt;br /&gt;Please check your maps. &lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest, GPS or others, 130 Hartford Road (rte 185), Simsbury, CT will get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181599301000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181190063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine and Cheeze Sunset at Talcott Mountain</name><id>5863707</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181426400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5863707/</event_url></item>