<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>5:30 to 8:00 &lt;br /&gt;(Informal Networking 5:30 to 6:00, Program 6:00 to 7:30, Informal Networking 7:30 to 8:00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:Media Education Foundation (MEF) Community Room, 60 Masonic Street, Northampton, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food: Drinks and snacks will be provided&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investment: $10. Rick Forgay commands well over $1,750 for 1.5 hour coaching, conference keynotes and strategic planning facilitation. He is offering Hidden-Tech a complimentary,one-time, information-packed workshop, with all proceeds donated to Hidden-Tech.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This customized content-rich, hands-on coaching program will focus on the rarely shared secrets of Business Leadership Mastery for immediate application and profitable results. If you are serious about leading an extraordinary business and life, you will not want to miss this one-of-a-kind opportunity to reach the levels of success you most desire. Shhhh… Our secret will be that growing a business in any economy can also be great FUN!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants will learn and apply the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * The Power Of Results-Driven Business and Marketing Plans&lt;br /&gt;    * The 3 Rules For Turning Coal To Diamonds In Business &amp;amp; Life&lt;br /&gt;    * How To Set And Achieve Your Ideal Revenue Goals&lt;br /&gt;    * Value-Based Rules For Generating True Wealth &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to the public: For Small Business Leaders who want to excel at growing companies where people and profits thrive in any economy.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Growing a successful business requires building a community of loyal internal and external customers who are rallied around a compelling purpose. This high energy, hands-on program will teach you the rarely shared secrets of business leadership mastery for immediate application and profitable results:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Executive Leadership and Team Effectiveness&lt;br /&gt;    * Community for Small Business Advancement&lt;br /&gt;    * Sales and Marketing for Million Dollar Results&lt;br /&gt;    * Applied Goal Setting and Achievement&lt;br /&gt;    * Culture-Driven Customer Amazement&lt;br /&gt;    * Innovative and Creative Teamwork&lt;br /&gt;    * Strategic Planning and Implementation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://live.hidden-tech.net/index.php/Events/TOP-SECRETS-FOR-GROWING-YOUR-BUSINESS-IN-ANY-ECONOMY.html" target="_blank"&gt;More Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225409862000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221003539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hidden Tech Presents: Growing your business in any economy</name><id>8724894</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224797400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/8724894/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/7/global_1616503.jpeg</photo_url></item>