<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you’re having trouble getting everything done, but you’re not ready to hire or add a full-time employee to your business, maybe it’s time to think about hiring an intern or part-time assistant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next Thursday, October 8, at noon Eastern, I’m hosting a free webinar featuring the co-founders of Urban Interns. If you’d like to attend, please register below. Here are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Using Interns &amp;amp; Part-Time Assistants In Your Small Business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a Webinar on October 8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve your Webinar seat now at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www1.gotomeeting.com/register/735311497" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www1.gotomeeting.com/register/735311497" target="_blank"&gt;https://www1.gotomeet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a small business owner or solopreneur, you may be short on help but wary of taking on the responsibility of a new employee. In this webinar, hosted by freelance writer and small business consultant Traci Feit Love, Cari Sommer and Lauren Porat (co-founders of Urban Interns) will teach you:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) when it makes sense to consider hiring an intern or part-time assistant;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) what types of work interns and part-time assistants can handle;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(3) how to find the right person for your business’ needs;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(4) how to properly supervise interns and part-time assistants, especially when they are working virtually; and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(5) what you can expect to pay for interns and part-time assistants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cari and Lauren will also give you a tour of UrbanInterns.com, where you can find part-time help for your business in a cost-effective and efficient manner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Title:  Using Interns &amp;amp; Part-Time Assistants In Your Small Business &lt;br /&gt;Date: Thursday, October 8, 2009 &lt;br /&gt;Time: 12:00 PM – 1:00 PM EDT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After registering you will receive a confirmation email containing information about joining the Webinar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;System Requirements&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PC-based attendees &lt;br /&gt;Required: Windows® 2000, XP Home, XP Pro, 2003 Server, Vista&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Macintosh®-based attendees &lt;br /&gt;Required: Mac OS® X 10.4 (Tiger®) or newer&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Traci</member_name><member_id>5213003</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256248844000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Smart Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>growingsmallbusiness</urlname><id>1425260</id><group_lat>42.4599990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Growing Small Businesses</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254515886000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Webinar: Using Interns &amp; Part-Time Assistants In Your Small Business</name><id>11531668</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255017600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/growingsmallbusiness/events/11531668/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/global_7956080.jpeg</photo_url></item>