<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Calling All Reactive/Aggressive Dogs! This-One's-For-You-Wednesdays!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://sphotos-b.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-snc6/262189_1872090881178_5015061_n.jpg" width="398" height="298" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This repeating workshop is for our reactive or aggressive dogs. Those of you who have continuously given your support even when you couldn't attend our events, our canine buddies who can't be trusted around other dogs (just yet), our rescues who have made such a difference to their people but with checkered pasts to overcome... This one's for you!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;re·ac·tive : adj : readily responsive to a stimulus; occurring as a result of stress or emotional upset&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ag·gres·sive : adj : tending toward or exhibiting aggression ("aggressive behavior"); marked by combative readiness ("an aggressive fighter"); marked by obtrusive energy; marked by driving forceful energy or initiative&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that the word "reactive," although it may, does not always refer to unfriendly aggressive behavior. If your dog whines, (cries, squeals.. whistles.. growl-barks, growl-barks.. screams.. any of the crazy noises our guys can produce in a fit of frenzy!), lunges, jumps, walks on its back legs or fixedly targets other dogs/strangers on leash or in the house, whether it is because he/she "wants to play" or not, you have what is commonly referred to as a Reactive Dog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This workshop's for all of you! The focus of this weekly course will be to integrate you "bad boys" with other dogs and people, to give you handlers more confidence in previously tense situations, &amp;amp; (arguably) most importantly, to minimize/eliminate stress in handlers &amp;amp; dogs and return all of you to a more peaceful mindset! (It is NOT fun for your dog to act like that either.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercises to include: controlled walking past other dogs, pretty stays around other dogs/in crowds, focus on handler amid triggers, trust exercises and confidence building/"conquer your obstacle" type drills!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This workshop will take place every Wednesday at 7:00p. The cost is $20 per dog per drop-in. Meeting at 182 Hayden Rowe Street in Hopkinton, MA (01748) - unless otherwise noted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING IS UNFORTUNATELY ON-STREET ONLY, TO THE RIGHT OF MY DRIVEWAY IF YOU ARE FACING IT OR YOU MAY PARK ON THERESA ROAD.  THEN WALK AROUND BACK (BACKYARD) TO MEET WITH YOUR DOG &amp;amp; YOUR GEAR! :)  See you then!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipment: &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt; dog back pack (can be purchased at PETsMART, PetCo, other pet supply stores, or here, &amp;amp; this is the least expensive I have found: &lt;a href="http://www.petmountain.com/category/729/1/dog-backpacks.html?Brand=211" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.petmountain.com/category/729/1/dog-backpacks.html?Brand=211&lt;/a&gt;. Backpack can be weighted with soup cans, water bottles, etc.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt; 4-6 foot fixed leash (NO flexis) &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt; supply of SUPER high-value treats (read: cheese, hot dog, chicken, steak... you get the picture) &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt; muzzle, if necessary - (Remember that there is no shame in this. This 'shop is to work on our social skills responsibly &amp;amp; safely. Do not be embarrassed or hesitant to bring your dog on a muzzle. Our goal will be to work up to removing the muzzle &amp;amp; training your dog muzzle-free with confidence, but do not be afraid or ashamed to start out with one. Safety first.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt; portable water bowl/water (optional) - "community" water will be provided on premises, but class will often be on the move! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 If you plan on attending this 'shop, before you do so, email me directly regarding collar/harnesses &amp;amp; combos thereof for your individual dog: justcassie101@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***This workshop is also open to handlers of dogs who are NOT reactive or aggressive. Not only is this an opportunity to work your dog around very heavy distractions, your calmer canine will be a huge help to reactive dogs in need, and both of you will learn how to help socialize those less fortunate. Thank you in advance!***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's get you tough guys out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cassie-Leigh Stock &lt;br /&gt;

 President &amp;amp; Founder &lt;br /&gt;

 NEBBC &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.hexdogs.weebly.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hexdogs.weebly.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/hedogtraining" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/hedogtraining&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.higherexpectations.net" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.higherexpectations.net&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hedogtraining" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/hedogtraining&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346298098000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345718727000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Calling All Reactive/Aggressive Dogs!  This-One's-For-You-Wednesdays!</name><id>qtwcddyqlbmc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346281200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/78998352/</event_url></item>