<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>My Personal Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>787702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome BestMatchClub members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is closed to women unless you are accompanied by a gentleman. We have reached our women quota. Please invite a high integrity gentleman you know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The price of this party is $20, and it includes professionally catered food. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the romantic atmosphere of Ricardo's Ristorante (my Home), with soft romantic music in the background, while enjoying stimulating conversation with the most friendly, gregarious, high quality singles who, like yourself, are searching for a Life Partner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This suggestion was given to me months ago by many members to improve the quality of my party. I will initiate it at this event. We need to reach a higher level of quality in many ways. This is the first step, and there’s more to come. The goal is to wow my guests (you). Will the extra time, effort, and money add value to this event for both you and me? This is a pilot, so please give me feedback at the end of the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I’ll supply the catered food. The only contribution in addition to the $20 fee is I will ask a few men to bring a bottle of wine. Then, at the next party, I’ll select a few women to bring a bottle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My two other Singles Events competitors, who also introduce singles to each other, had events recently. One charged $45 and the other $65. I feel good that we continue to maintain the most inexpensive fees and highest value for our members by hosting the parties in the warm atmosphere of my home. In the future, when we grow enough to move to Temple Shalom Emeth, I’ll obviously increase the fees somewhat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check the Sign-Up List, and count the number of men and women. The objective is to have 50 guests, with no more than 30 women. Ladies, to improve your chances of meeting your Life Partners, please invite gentlemen equal to your level of quality and integrity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This party is for Singles 30-65. Our mission is to have fun, laugh, meet other Singles who share your interests, and develop friendships which lead to a Lifetime Partner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Values: Be nice, kind, cheerful, friendly, and respectful to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make this a truly memorable party.&lt;br /&gt;*** Entry fee $20 ***&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION – The warm, loving, supportive, and relaxing environment of my home. &lt;br /&gt;DRESS CODE – &amp;quot;Professional Casual&amp;quot; &amp;amp; Comfortable. First impressions are most meaningful. &lt;br /&gt;TIME – 7:00pm to 10:00pm &lt;br /&gt;DATE – Saturday - Oct. 9, 2010&lt;br /&gt;MAX ATTENDEES – 56 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION &lt;br /&gt;My Home &lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road &lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;1. Rt. 128S&lt;br /&gt;2. Take Exit 16B (Rt. 109 ) toward Westwood &lt;br /&gt;3. Go 2 miles &amp;amp; take a left onto Pond Street (It’s just past the Middle School on left - if you go by Dunkin Donuts on the right, you missed it).&lt;br /&gt;4. Go 1 mile &amp;amp; take a left onto Oak St. (Note: Google search says go right, but this is incorrect.)&lt;br /&gt;5. Go 1.5 miles to the end &amp;amp; take a right onto Brook St. &lt;br /&gt;6. Go 100 feet &amp;amp; take a right onto Woodridge Road. &lt;br /&gt;7. My home is the 3rd house on the left (cream colored)&lt;br /&gt;See you Saturday, Oct. 9th at 7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Best is Right Now! &lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287875971000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Curious Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dinner-parties</urlname><id>1245686</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Singles Dinner Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282484355000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Welcome to Ricardo's Restaurante </name><id>14500511</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286665200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dinner-parties/events/14500511/</event_url></item>