<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The place where singles ages 30 and over meet! &lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Are you tired of throwing money away at cash bars?&lt;/span&gt; Then join us this Friday at Daniels Hall, Rt 4, Nottingham, NH., where single people meet and dance in a friendly &amp;amp; fun environment. Very inexpensive, no need to purchase expensive drinks or tip bartenders, bring your own liquor, non alcoholic drinks can be purchased or bring your own and enjoy a fun evening for singles over 30. Join us and maybe meet that special person. Safe place for women attending alone. Visit our &lt;a href="http://www.singlesdanceparties.com" target="_blank"&gt;web site&lt;/a&gt; for more info and directions or call 603 942-8525 for verbal directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, there is no need to buy expensive drinks or tip bartenders, just bring your own liquor, free drink set-ups and hot buffet are included in the $11 admission. Casual dress is a plus which puts people at ease and makes it easier to join in the fun atmosphere. This dance has been working it's magic for 15 years and is the most heavily advertised singles dance in NH, so there are always new singles to meet at Daniels Hall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No need to RSVP just join us!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dave McDermott&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Remember at Daniels Hall your family.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the hostess where the meetup tables are located.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David McDermott</member_name><member_id>8730064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271823424000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles (ages 30 to 60).</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Daniels-Hall-Singles-Parties</urlname><id>1495923</id><group_lat>43.0900001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Find someone new this Friday! Ages 30 to 60.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>112</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270360078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Dance Party at Daniels Hall.</name><id>13081342</id><headcount>128</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270855800000</time><rsvp_limit>185</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Daniels-Hall-Singles-Parties/events/13081342/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/8/global_14126328.jpeg</photo_url></item>