<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-345</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>337655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Boston Investors Business Daily Group December Main Meeting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP ASAP! We will be in E51-345, so there's plenty of room to bring guests! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=E51&amp;amp;Buildings=go" target="_blank"&gt;Map of MIT campus&lt;/a&gt;, Building E51, we meet in Room 345&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;FEATURE TALKS: GREETING THE NEW YEAR WITH A TRIPLE HEADLINER OF FRED SEARS, CHARLIE SILK AND RONDEAU FLYNN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Talk 3: Winning Strategies in a Losing Market by Rondeau Flynn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investor/Trader Rondeau Flynn will take us through the mine field of the current market and show how to trade while minimizing losses. He will use sectors, equities, ETF's, and a disciplined hedge fund money management technique that put the odds in your favor on your trades.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rondeau will cover the following points:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Picking leading/lagging sectors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Going long or short equitites &amp;amp; ETF's&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hedging for the conservative investor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowing when to get in, and when to sit on the sidelines&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A disciplined approach to the markets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expectations for 2009, why history repeats itself&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rondeau Flynn is a commercial airline pilot and a former professional athlete. He has written two trading manuals this year - the V1 Trading Strategy &amp;amp; The I.G. Trading Strategy. Rondeau is a fan of discipline that fits a conservative approach to these current market conditions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Talk 2: The Effects of Mutual Fund and Hedge Fund Redemptions on Fallen Angel Candidates by Charlie Silk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie Silk makes the point that fallen angels are rising in number because of the massive increase of mutual fund and hedge fund redemptions. He will show current stocks currently of interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Charles Silk's interest in the stock market has thrived for 60 years, beginning in his teens. He studied accounting and finance at the University of Michigan, receiving a Bachelor and MBA.  He served as a Naval Officer in the Korean War, went to Arthur Andersen, IBM and in 1962 he opened a computer service bureau. His interest in the stock market continued and his fallen angel theory came together. In 1987 he became a full time investor, instilling the knowledge he gained to his children. He made guest appearances on CNBC. At nearly 70 years of age he passed the Series 7 exam and opened the doors along with his sons Marc and Stephen, to C. Silk &amp;amp; Sons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Securities offered through Delta Equity Services Corporation, Bolton, MA. Member FINRA, SIPC (978) 779-5361. Advisory services offered through Delta Global Asset Management, a registered investment advisor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Talk 1: Market Talk by Fred Sears&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Market Talk gives the speaker's perspective recent action in the markets - especially the US exchanges - and makes predictions for the next month and often farther out. Although stocks are the normal asset class topic, any asset class - oil, gold, real estate, etc - could be the speaker's focus. Members are encouraged to probe the speaker's insights and add their own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Long time members of Boston IBD know and love Fred Sears. He started attending meetings back at Buddha's Delite and delivered a regular talk every month until October 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fred Sears is a 4 Star (AFTER 5.75% load, 1.5% management fee) Morningstar rated Mutual Fund Manager. FYI stars are earned after 3 years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has made more than 75 worldwide television appearances – CNBC – interviewed by Maria Bartiromo, Tyler Matheson, Dylan Ratigan, Bloomberg Television, TechTv, Fox Television – interviewed twice by Neil Cavuto, Reuters Televison, quoted and or interviewed in the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, Investor’s Business Daily, The Street.com, New York Post, Kiplingers, plus frequent radio appearances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING of the Tiger Financial Network starts at 5:30 PM.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; See &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;the announcement here&lt;/a&gt;. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda:&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:50 Pre-Meeting with Boston Tigers by Bob Podd&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Doug&lt;br /&gt;7:15 Market Talk by Fred Sears&lt;br /&gt;7:45 Stockpicks&lt;br /&gt;8:15 Break&lt;br /&gt;8:25 The Effect of Mutual Fund and Hedge Fund Redemptions on Fallen Angel Candidates by Charlie Silk&lt;br /&gt;8:55 Winning Strategies in a Losing Market by Rondeau Flynn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to join our online discussion!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join our virtual trading, go to &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/browse_thread/thread/ff5e030eb15a6c7c" target="_blank"&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; for instructions and signup links&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own decisions about investing your money. Investment ideas and recommendations made in our meetings and our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are open to the public, there is no admission fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231203963000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>85</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227670161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors December Main Meeting</name><id>9232632</id><headcount>91</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230595200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9232632/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>