<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Sugarloaf Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01373</zip><lat>42.467663</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sugarloaf Mountain</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>9160472</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.595016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/2/c/event_157204652.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Does your pup proudly strut his/her stuff when walking down the street? I have noticed that my 2 girls do. As the mom of my 2 little girls, I am proud when they are proud. I believe everyone else in this group is proud of their pup(s) too. &lt;br /&gt;

We can park and meet at the base of Mt Sugarloaf in the parking area. I am not planning on this walk to go up the mountain, I am thinking that we could walk the sidewalk on Sugarloaf Street towards the center of South Deerfield, turn around and come back down the opposite side of the street. This is a pretty street with some old houses with lots of character. This is definitely an On-Leash walk. It is approximately 1 mile from the parking area to the center common in South Deerfield. We can then either return to the parking area or head north on North Main St for some more "Sidewalk Strut"down another pretty street. &lt;br /&gt;

We must be careful of street traffic, although this has always been not very busy and the speed limit is low here. We must pick up after our dogs and be respectful of the town residents (as we always are that I have seen). &lt;br /&gt;

So come join myself and my pups Maggie and Apache on this Proud Pups Parade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions from Northampton are to take 91 North to exit 24 and head North on route 5 and 10.  Take the first right onto route 116 towards Sunderland/Amherst.  Go about 1 mile and take a left onto Sugarloaf Street at an intersection with a light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions from Greenfield are to head south on route 91 and also take exit 24.  Head North on route 5 and 10.  take 1st right onto route 116 towards Sunderland/Amherst. ﻿ Go about 1 mile and take a left onto Sugarloaf Street at an intersection with a light. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will see the entrance to Mt Sugarloaf at this intersection while still on route 116. &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348233403000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347211484000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Proud Pups Parade on Sugarloaf St in South Deerfield</name><id>81590062</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347715800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/81590062/</event_url></item>