<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rifamiliesinnature.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/NHC_cityview_web.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.rifamiliesinnature.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/NHC_cityview_web.jpg" width="300" height="300" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcRWiwYuSZDf18Vom5X_z60oMmB4JIPJd2x-7d2nNzRuX5fF86i5nA" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DURATION: 1.5 to 2 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DISTANCE: 3 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIFICULTY: moderate / short but very hilly terrain as the name implies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before signing up for this hike please read the entire write up.By signing up for this hike you are agreeing to the liability waiver below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flying over the densely populated Silver Lake/Olneyville area in Providence, with its unique, tightly-woven pattern of streets lined with multi-family residences, you will see an oasis of 88-acres of green –  This wilderness park, situated in the heart of the most densely populated area of the City, unique in the Providence Park System,  88 acres of trees, fields, and wild flowers, interspersed with valleys, ravines, glacial boulders, stone walls, fresh water springs and brooks. The Hill is the natural habitat for a multitude of small woodland animals including deer, fox, and wild turkey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhill.org/wss/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/city-vies-web.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Rich in history, the Great Hill of Neutaconkanut was the northwest boundary in the land agreement between Roger Williams, founder of our state, and the Narragansett Sachems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hill is the highest point in Providence. (Elevation: 296 feet above sea level.) From the hilltop meadow and from several hiking trails are spectacular views of the City and nearly a quarter of the State.The forested woodlands, with several miles of hiking/walking trails*, provide a panorama of picturesque stone walls, unique geological formations, natural springs and brooks, wild flowers and berries. *The WPA originally created the recently restored paths in the 1930s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring plenty of water and a snack. Remember ticks are already out and active, bring spray if you have it. should be sunny and mid 50's they say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Neutaconkanut Recreation  Area / parking lot. I drive a tan Altima</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366037724000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365466075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HIKING 101- NEUTACONKANUT HILL</name><id>113385822</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365951600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/113385822/</event_url></item>