<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;This event is new to us and thus experimental&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;We will be exploring various rivers and streams in southern Vermont looking for good spots to do test panning for gold! These tests are in preparation for a larger gold panning event our group will offer hopefully soon. A number of areas in Vermont and even New Hampshire have had demonstrated finds of gold in small quantities. There is no guarantee we will find gold in our test areas but you will learn how to select promising sites and how to pan for gold. If you find any gold you get to keep it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be tooling around lovely rivers and streams with some shorter hikes to get to some sites. We will have some very nice views! One site we will try requires a 2 mile hike in and the same out again. We will have to hike in the small amount of equipment (shovel, pails, gold pans, etc.). &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;I will be providing the equipment&lt;/span&gt; for our small group to use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the Walmart in East Windsor, CT by 9 AM to all pile into my Ford Escape to carpool and drive about 2 hrs. to the first test site. We will be testing several sites with processing of a few pans of material at each site. The testing/panning will be over a 6 hr. period. You may wish to bring a bag lunch so you have something to eat as it is uncertain if we will be near any eating establishment to grab a bite but we can try to find one. The drive back will be about 2 hrs. All told, this is a 10 hr. event (including the 4 hrs. of transportation to/from). We would get back by 7 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to go need to have: &lt;br /&gt;

 * A daypack - for carrying water &amp;amp; lunch/snacks, removed layers, some equipment &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1 - 2 quart(s) of water &lt;br /&gt;

 * Lunch and snacks - don't know if we will get to a place to eat otherwise &lt;br /&gt;

 * Shoes you don't mind getting wet as in and near water (e.g. gators, sandles) &lt;br /&gt;

 * Dress in layers - So you can take off as you heat up, no cotton &lt;br /&gt;

 * Dress in clothes you don't mind getting wet and/or dirty&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional equipment: &lt;br /&gt;

 * Bug spray &lt;br /&gt;

 * Camera&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs are NOT allowed on this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; to Walmart parking lot carpool location - in front of Walmart (69 Prospect Hill Rd., E. Windsor, CT): &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://mapq.st/KgTZ8z"&gt;http://mapq.st/KgTZ8z&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Ford Escape SUV with CT plates, meet at carpool location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337742632000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337371191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exploratory GOLD Panning in Southern VT/NH</name><id>65376402</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337432400000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/65376402/</event_url></item>