<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This workshop is a combination of classroom conversation followed by hands on practice in an outdoor setting. We are going to cover the methods and techniques of landscape photography and then head outside with our cameras. We will being walking through Mine Falls park which is about 2 miles from the studio and has many landscape features.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;New England’s natural setting offers an endless source of photographic inspiration.  This is especially true when the fall foliage season comes around.  This workshop will give you inspiration and a jump start into your autumn photography adventures.  We are timing it early in the season so you can apply what you learn to when the fall colors are out in force. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you are considering joining us on the overnight trip to the WHITE MOUNTAINS on October 16 $ 17 ( &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/calendar/14304042/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;) and  feel your skills are limited then I would urge you to sign up for the class to tune up your landscape skills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LANDSCAPE PHOTOGRAPHY is a primary subject for photographers.  Capturing the form and drama of the world around us, making great images that grab the viewer’s attention is a really exciting and fun way to get outside with your camera.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For directions go to my website -- http://www.testoftimephoto.com/DIRECTIONS.html</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284774947000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281805534000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LANDSCAPE PHOTOGRAPHY – Get ready for fall foliage season!</name><id>14421756</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284314400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/14421756/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/e/global_16414110.jpeg</photo_url></item>