<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For those of you who have seen  &lt;b&gt;Jules and Jim&lt;/b&gt;, The &amp;quot;Plus One&amp;quot; in this event's title does not refer to  Catherine, portrayed by Jeanne Moureau. This is a double feature of films starring Moureau- as The Brattle is also screening &lt;b&gt;The Lovers&lt;/b&gt;  directed by Louis Malle . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jules and Jim&lt;/b&gt; France 1962 104 minutes&lt;br /&gt;Hailed as one of the finest films ever made, legendary director François Truffaut?s early masterpiece Jules and Jim charts the relationship between two friends and the object of their mutual obsession over the course of twenty-five years. Jeanne Moreau stars as Catherine, the alluring and willful young woman whose enigmatic smile and passionate nature lure Jules (Oskar Werner) and Jim (Henri Serre) into one of cinema?s most captivating romantic triangles. An exuberant and poignant meditation on freedom, loyalty, and the fortitude of love, Jules and Jim was a worldwide smash upon its release in 1962 and remains as audacious and entrancing today.  The Criterion Collection&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His third and most popular film, François Truffaut's adaptation of the Henri-Pierre Roché novel is a lyrical, elliptical meditation on the possibilities of love. Shot in widescreen black-and-white by Raoul Coutard in beautifully detailed pre- and post-World War I settings, the central ménage à trois of Jules, Jim, and mercurial Catherine reveals the limits placed on a woman's freedom by the men's desire to mold her to their fantasy ideal. Catherine remains an enigma to Jules and Jim, though they adore her, as they tragically misjudge how absolute her refusal to choose between them will be. Truffaut's eclectic technique (bolstered by Georges Delerue's score) evoked the shifting emotions in this ultra-modern romance, ranging from kinetic handheld shots communicating the trio's joie de vivre to freeze-frames briefly suspending Catherine's beauty in time. An international smash and instant classic, Jules and Jim cemented Truffaut's reputation as a cinematic artist.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://rogerebert.suntimes.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/20040620/REVIEWS08/406200301/1023" target="_blank"&gt;http://rogerebert.sun...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Lovers&lt;/b&gt; will screen at 3:15.  I'll be taking a pass on this one, but if you will be attending this film as well, please indicate so when you RSVP- that way you can meetup with other members from our group before the screening of Jules and Jim.  Here's a review for The Lovers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.slantmagazine.com/film/film_review.asp?ID=3649" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.slantmagaz...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there and we'll be going to restaurant after &lt;b&gt;Jules and Jim to&lt;/b&gt; discuss,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the screening of Jules and Jim.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213221049000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210034136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Truffaut's Jules and Jim Plus One</name><id>7880107</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211663700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7880107/</event_url></item>