<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Westwood Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.386767</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-6600, x2985</phone><name>Somerville Museum</name><city>Somerville</city><id>712142</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104612</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is more of a viewing event than a Portuguese language practice Meet-Up.&lt;br /&gt;Th City of Somerville will be show casing Portuguese and Brazilian culture.  &lt;br /&gt;Read the details in the forwarded message below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you already know Bill and Anna, from the Meet-Ups at the Sunset.  They will be performing the Brazilian music at this event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see some of you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the Somerville Arts Council, anthropologist Andrea Allen, and members of the local Portuguese and Brazilian community for a presentation and celebration of the cultural traditions within Somerville's Brazilian and Portuguese populations. Allen will present her recent ethnographic research within these communities, complete with images; there will also be a brief discussion regarding how the Arts Council can support these cultural traditions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next, the local group, Receita de Samba (image above), will perform bossa nova (1960s), early acoustic samba  (1920s-50s) and choro (instrumental music). While many people are familiar with traditional samba, also known as &amp;quot;Samba de Raiz&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Samba de Roda,&amp;quot; choro music is less known outside of Brazil. Choro music is like the jazz, blues, or ragtime of Brazilian music; improvisation is key. The core members of Receita de Samba are Anna Borges, lead vocalist and percussionist and Bill Ward, vocalist and guitarist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rounding out the evening, the Somerville-based Rancho Folclórico Corações Lusíadas will perform folkloric dances from Portugal and the Azores, accompanied by musicians. Representing the group are Sergio Soares, the director, and Melanie Soares, the lead dancer and choreographer. Sergio Soares will provide a history of the group and discuss Portuguese folkloric music and dance. Melanie Soares will display and explain the traditional outfits worn by the female dancers and demonstrate dance techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is the culmination of a year-long ethnographic research project. As a part of the Somerville Arts Council's mission to better understand the cultural needs of Somerville residents, SAC hired folklorist Andrea Allen to conduct an ethnographic research project about two important and sizable populations in the city: the Brazilian and Portuguese communities. The project was funded by the National Endowment of the Arts, with additional funding by the City of Somerville/Somerville Arts Council. The data gathered has provided SAC the means to strategize about how it can better serve these communities. In addition, the project offered SAC a template for how to assess and serve other immigrant populations in the city.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217025651000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216147404000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebration of local Brazilian and Portuguese Culture</name><id>8345985</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216852200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/8345985/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/2/global_4803746.jpeg</photo_url></item>