<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03846</zip><lat>44.261830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-466-2721</phone><name>Pinkham Notch Visitor Center</name><city>Pinkhams</city><id>911093</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.245675</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>****I have closed RSVPs.....if you are interested in joining this hike please email me*****&lt;br /&gt;            -John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;The mountains are calling and I must go.&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; -John Muir (1838-1914)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join us on Saturday August 7th, 2010 to hike Mt. Washington.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the hike we have been building up towards all year! We are going to do a loop, ascending via the Tuckerman's Ravine Trail and descending on the Boot Spur Trail. This gives us a total distance of 9.5 miles and an elevation gain of 4,300 feet. This is significantly more than any of the hikes we have done this year. To give those of you that have joined us recently something to compare with:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;            Mt Cannon 6.3 miles, 2,400 feet&lt;br /&gt;            Mt Moosilauke 7.5 miles, 2,600 feet&lt;br /&gt;            Mt Pierce/Jackson 8.3 miles, 2,700 feet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be moving at a moderate pace as we are covering a lot of ground. Please make sure you are comfortable with a hike of this length with this elevation gain at a moderate pace before signing up! For reference with a recent hike, the Mt Cannon hike was estimated at 5 hours....and we took 7. So we are going to have to move at a faster pace than the Mt Cannon hike in order to come close to the AMCs White Mountain Guide estimate of 7 hours for this hike. For those of you that have not come with us on any hikes recently or are new to the group....this is NOT a beginners hike. Please make sure you have done a hike in the range of those listed above before signing up for this hike. I don't mean to discourage people from signing up, but just to make sure this hike is right for you as it is very challenging. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiking group size is limited to 10 in the White Mountains....so we will be dividing up into several groups as we have a massive number of people signed up (I suspect that number will shrink as we get closer to the date).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting place: Pinkham Notch Visitor Center, Route 16, Gorham, NH.&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the front door to the visitors center at 8:30 and plan to be on the trail by 9AM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Pinkham Notch Visitor Center: (from AMC website)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take Interstate 95 North to Spaulding Turnpike North (at Portsmouth, N.H.). &lt;br /&gt;2. Take Spaulding Turnpike North to Route 16 North. &lt;br /&gt;3. Take Route 16 North to Pinkham Notch Visitor Center/Joe Dodge Lodge, which is located on the left side of Route 16 approximately 12 miles north of the Glen intersection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take Interstate 93 North to Route 104 East (Exit 23).&lt;br /&gt;2. Take Route 104 East to Route 3 North (near Meredith).&lt;br /&gt;3. Take Route 3 North to Route 25 East (intersection in Meredith).&lt;br /&gt;4. Take Route 25 East to Route 16 North (near West Ossipee).&lt;br /&gt;5. Take Route 16 North to Pinkham Notch Visitor Center/Joe Dodge Lodge, which is located on the left side of Route 16 approximately 12 miles north of the Glen intersection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Equipment List&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Synthetic shirt and pants. &lt;b&gt;No cotton.  No jeans.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sturdy Hiking Boots.  &lt;b&gt;No Sneakers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rain / Wind Jacket. &lt;b&gt;No Ponchos.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Warm fleece layer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hat and gloves&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Something warm for the summit.  Expect it to be very windy, and expect much cooler temperatures. Weather on Mt Washington is VERY VOLATILE, be prepared! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-3 liters Water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Headlamp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trail Snacks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bug Repellent&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Optional Gear:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hiking Poles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gaiters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunscreen / Sunglasses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Camera / Binoculars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Jeans, Sneakers, or Cotton clothing on the hike!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lodging&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I plan on staying in North Conway, but there are plenty of camping and hotel options in the area. Lets get a discussion going on where people want to stay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AMC sites:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/recreation/tripplanner/plan/washington.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/lodging/lodges/pnvc/pnvc-pnvc.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White Mountain National Forest site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fs.fed.us/r9/forests/white_mountain/links.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fs.fed.us/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Random site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/washington.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://home.earthlink...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>On the front porch of the Visitor Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281439973000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267888598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt.Washington Hike</name><id>12800328</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281184200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/12800328/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/2/a/global_13472858.jpeg</photo_url></item>