<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>545 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350552</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 638-9699 </phone><name>Vlora Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>742937</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075813</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ladies! Celebrate the season of all things red and loved during our 5th Annual Red Shoe Soiree. Put on your beautiful red shoes and show them off during the pink carpet Best-in-Shoe competition. Mingle with other shoe and fashion lovers, enjoy complimentary appetizers and Vlora's famous signature martinis. Event is free to attend. (red shoes are only a suggestion- you can wear what ever you would like!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joining us will be shoe designer and rising star Thom Solo of Thom Solo Shoes. Thom will be showcasing his latest designs with a shoe show. A Boston native and graduate of the School of the Museum of Fine Arts, Thom has designed shoes for a number of celebrity musicians. His shoes are inspired by his fine art background and are truly unique and memorable. Thom is donating a pair of shoes that will be auctioned off during the event for Project Smile!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also joining us to showcase her latest fashions with a fashion show on the pink carpet is designer &lt;a href="http://bondijbyblonddi.tumblr.com/"&gt;Bondij by Blondi.&lt;/a&gt; Boston designer Blond Di started out designing one of a kind custom made clothing, footwear and accessories with an edgy and ornate style. Bondij by Blondi caters to the fashion forward individual who desires one of a kind, edgy and creative designs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://origin.ih.constantcontact.com/fs143/1102207116075/img/28.jpg" alt="A Thom Solo shoe" width="306" height="306" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside the private room. If you have trouble finding us, call 774 232 0000</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360290882000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359402761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ladies Night: Red Shoe Soiree at Vlora</name><id>101824682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360279800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/101824682/</event_url></item>