<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Science of Spirituality Meet Up Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you all know, this winter has been very interesting &amp;#8722; and it’s not over yet. Just when you think it’s beginning to thaw, we get hit again. This is why we don’t schedule programs in the winter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’re planning our spring program schedule now, but before that, we’re going to be doing a couple of classes on the web. Dr. Allan Hughes will be back with “Meditation and the Mind,” on February 18 and “Karma and Reincarnation” sometime in March. The February class is limited to 15, so please register as soon as possible. It’s first come, first serve, however Allan will do this class again. If, when you go to register, the February class is full, please email us and we’ll put you on a waiting list for the next one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meditation and the Mind with Dr. Allan Hughes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have tens of thousands of thoughts every day – or, rather, our thoughts have us. Do we need all those thought? Where would we be if we could control our mind? Everyone agrees we are body plus mind plus spirit. Everyone agrees that the spirit part is the real “me.” But how do we get to it? In meditation, in the stillness of perfect silence and awareness, in the calm of no thought, we discover who we really are. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In this online class, Allan Hughes will talk about the benefits of meditation and the role the mind plays in keeping us from enjoying those benefits. In this engaging presentation, you will learn techniques to keep the mind focused and a simple meditation practice that yields powerful results. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited to 15 people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you in cyberspace,&lt;br /&gt;Mardi and Sandy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This meeting is in cyberspace.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy Glassman</member_name><member_id>6837888</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mardi Hughes</member_name><member_id>6839044</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236902589000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-582</urlname><id>1082356</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2300033569</group_lon><name>The Science of Spirituality Meditation Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234409548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meditation and the Mind</name><id>9725779</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235005200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-582/events/9725779/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/4/global_4303812.jpeg</photo_url></item>