<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02122</zip><lat>42.302894</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Park Street Plaza</name><city>Boston</city><id>1160084</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052645</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>***JOIN THE MOVEMENT***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Protest Arizona's &lt;br /&gt;Anti-Immigrant SB 1070 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and Fox News's Culture of Hate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizations across the country are calling for a National Day of Non-Compliance on July 29th.  This is the day Arizona's anti-immigrant State Bill 1070 goes into effect. This law would encode racial profiling into police policy, terrorize immigrants away from seeking police protection, and expand the threat of deportation over millions of workers. This divide-and-rule tactic is an attack on all working people who must unite for the fight-back that is desperately needed against budget cuts and layoffs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fox News personalities like Glenn Beck, Sean Hannity and Bill O'Reilly have been whipping up anti-immigrant sentiment. It is time to say, loud and clear, to Fox News and the State House: &amp;quot;Working people must be united to stop budget cuts and layoffs! Arizona laws will not spread to Massachusetts! We will not buy into your culture of hate!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, July 29th&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;Park St. T station&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will march through the Boston Common to Fox News headquarters and the State House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored and endorsed by the Boston May Day Coalition, ANSWER Coalition, Student Immigrant Movement (SIM), Brazilian Immigrant Center, Latinos for Social Change, Mass Global Action, Socialist Alternative, Socialist Party of Boston, International Socialist Organization (ISO) and you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The list is growing!  Ask your organization to endorse today!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact the Boston May Day Coalition&lt;br /&gt;617-290-5614 (English / Español)&lt;br /&gt;info@bostonmayday.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP and invite your friends on facebook: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/2chqjbr" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/2c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280504030000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280157870000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Day of Action against AZ's SB1070</name><id>14216096</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280439000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/14216096/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/5/global_16728389.jpeg</photo_url></item>