<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Paine Rd</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02825</zip><lat>41.814670</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Corner of Route 6 and Paine Rd., Foster RI</name><city>Foster</city><id>9361462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.746460</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The dozen who rode with me last wknd loved it.... now I am using new roads, more country roads, more reason to love Foster.... We can ride on Sunday 11/11.   Paine is just before Balcom and opposite side, on the first hill after the only red light in foster(0.5miles past) going up the hill on the right...  We'll take Paine past the apple orchards, to East Killingly Rd.,  left onto it, down several miles to Shippee Schoolhouse Rd , several miles again, which ends at where we cross Rt 6., move down Cucumber Hill Rd(no hills), back onto South Killingly Rd., down a few hills, and into Foster Center, go north on Foster Center Rd/Rt 94, was going to go onto Anthony Rd, but found out in my drive thru the course that a bridge is closed now, so we will follow Rt 94 to the red light at 6 cross it and go down Mt Hygea Rd til we reach East Killingly Rd, take a left up the small hill to where it meets Paine Rd, back down it to our cars.  It measures 17 miles or so.  it is a good ride, some moderate hills, mostly down, tho some up. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;from Prov, take 6W into Foster, down one long hill, up two others.  After redlight, only one in town, go 0.5 miles and take right onto Paine Rd... down a bit and park on side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;from north take either 146S to 295S and to rt 6w in Johnston, or 395s to danielson and 6E a few miles over state line...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick Clark</member_name><member_id>17851281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352677128000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348109478000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike Ride #2 in Foster-really country roads in the Fall</name><id>83221852</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352646000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/83221852/</event_url></item>