<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's try this again and see if the weather is more agreeable to y'all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have planned a section of the Metacomet Trail that we will start in Farmington on route 4 and finish on route 372 in Plainville.  This will be a 6.5 mile adventure that will take us through the Hillsted property, up Rattlesnake Mt. (there are none up there) elevation 750', past Will Warren's Den (a small cave with a story) and past rapper Fitty Cents' house (seriously, Mike Tyson's old place).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a through hike so we will meet at the end point and I will need folks help to get all to the beginning.  At the conclusion, those who drove will need rides back to their cars.  The shuttling should go smooth if we all help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need to meet at the end point (440 New Britain Ave Plainville) at 10:00 a.m. I am figuring this should last no longer than 5 hours.  We should be done by 3:00.  We will be very close to J.Timothy's if folks aren't headed out for a hot date and want to hang out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is still summer-ish so bring plenty of water, snacks, bugspray.  This area has longer grasses and plant growth.  Consider long hiking pants or gators.  As always with me, no dogs or children please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the ending site and where we will meet.  There is a medical building with a large parking lot.  We will park on the right toward the back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Plainville+&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=440+New+Britain+Ave" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is where we will shuttle folks to and start the hike.  We are going to the commuter parking lot across from this road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Farmington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=1+Prattling+Pond+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254277420000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251577953000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the Metacomet Trail/Rattlesnake Mt. Farmington, CT</name><id>11233657</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253368800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11233657/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>