<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/f/7/8/event_141612152.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Although I was a big fan of the original version of this movie with Arnie as the hero and most of the action taking place on Mars, I am caving to pressure from several members of the group to see this version.   Ok ok I am doing it already...Jeez!  :)  Seriously though, it does look interesting and the cast is amazing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Show is at 6:45, I wil be at the theater by 5:45 and we will head in for seats by 6;15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;The movie is showing upstairs so look for me by the tables at the top of the escalator.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They have been advertising this movie very heavily, so I strongly advise buying your tickets in advance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after. We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;$$$$Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after.$$$$$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; August 3, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Columbia Pictures (Sony) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt;Len Wiseman &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt;Kurt Wimmer, Mark Bomback &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt;Colin Farrell, Kate Beckinsale, Jessica Biel, &lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=56016" style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bryan&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Cranston&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, John Cho, Bill Nighy &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Thriller &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt;PG-13 (for intense sequences of sci-fi violence and action, some sexual content, brief nudity, and language) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.totalrecall-movie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;TotalRecall-movie.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Total Recall" is an action thriller about reality and memory, inspired anew by the famous short story “We Can Remember It For You Wholesale” by Philip K. Dick. Welcome to Rekall, the company that can turn your dreams into real memories. For a factory worker named Douglas Quaid (&lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=56016" style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Colin&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Farrell&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), even though he's got a beautiful wife (Kate Beckinsale) who he loves, the mind-trip sounds like the perfect vacation from his frustrating life - real memories of life as a super-spy might be just what he needs. But when the procedure goes horribly wrong, Quaid becomes a hunted man. Finding himself on the run from the police – controlled by Chancellor Cohaagen (Bryan Cranston), the leader of the free world – Quaid teams up with a rebel fighter (Jessica Biel) to find the head of the underground resistance (Bill Nighy) and stop Cohaagen. The line between fantasy and reality gets blurred and the fate of his world hangs in the balance as Quaid discovers his true identity, his true love, and his true fate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344270498000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342998720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Total Recall (6:45PM Show)</name><id>74460152</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344116700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/74460152/</event_url></item>