<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ciao tutti,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Abbiamo cambiato idea.  Invece di incontrarci da Mozzicato, andremo a Real Art Ways Cinema a vedere &amp;quot;Il Divo&amp;quot; - un film italiano sulla vita di Giulio Andreotti, un politco italiano accusato di corruzione e di avere relazioni con la Mafia.  Il film commincia alle 7:00.  Il cinema si trova a 56 Arbor Street, Hartford.  Se non ti piace questo cambiamento, ti prega di lamentarti a Janet e Carlo invece di me - e colpa loro. Ma se tu sei contento, renda merito a me!  Cosi fanno i politici.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Real  Art Ways &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From I-91 North or South &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From either 91 North or South take I-84 West in Hartford and follow directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From I-84 East or West &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From either 84-West or 84-East take Exit 46 - Sisson Avenue. At the end of the long exit ramp, turn left at the light , onto Sisson Avenue. Very quickly you come to another light (Capitol Avenue); turn left. Your third right is Arbor Street (if you pass the UHaul you've gone too far.) Turn right onto Arbor Street; you will immediately see our large sign on the left. Turn into the driveway at the sign, and proceed all the way to the back of the building. You will see lights, windows, an entry way, and people. Park and come in!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>john delnegro</member_name><member_id>4845360</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245886893000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Amici Italiani</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>italian-452</urlname><id>535327</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>Connecticut's Viva Italia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243525136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Serata di Caffe e Conversazione</name><id>10513952</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244674800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-452/events/10513952/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/5/global_5243621.jpeg</photo_url></item>