<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I missed this one the first time around but I heard really good things about the movie.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2008) Director: Darren Aronofsky. Screenplay by Robert D. Siegel. Director of photography, Maryse Alberti. Cast: Mickey Rourke, Marisa Tomei, Evan Rachel Wood. Not since the heyday of 1970s realism have we seen a film as comfortable in its slightly seedy, blue collar setting, of union halls and school gyms, where many Americans might actual live and work. Mickey Rourke's riches-to-dives acting career gets a much-needed boost in a role that shadows his own fall from grace: a has-been wrestler (Randy 'the Ram') tries to find some dignity just by doing what he does best - providing his audiences with the illusion of the fight, all across the small towns of New Jersey. Another outstanding movie from the audacious director Darren Aronofsky, who made Pi, Requiem for a Dream, and The Fountain. &amp;quot;This is the performance of Mickey Rourke's lifetime - one of the year's best films.&amp;quot; Four stars Roger Ebert 105 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, let's grab a bite or a drink somewhere in Hartford or West Hartford.  I'm open to suggestions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anyone who's never been to Cinestudio, I've included directions in the File area of this meetup site.  See you Friday!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby.  The movie starts at 7:30.  Let's meet no later than 7:15.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242063384000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240934385000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Wrestler</name><id>10285453</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241219700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/10285453/</event_url></item>