<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Right now 0 yak is still available, check to see if you have the right one..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT DEPENDS ON WEATHER CONDITIONS BEING &amp;quot;GOOD&amp;quot; Since its a long drive for most and that this area will take a several hours to explore the Fenton River and later the River near the Airport to the south while tarveling through the center of the Reservoir.&lt;br /&gt;After the paddling event is also the Pot Luck Picknick nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain, Winds above 10 mph and cold weather Cancells the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update weather info before the event day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So far its looking like a good weekend..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it dosent look like a good enough paddling day i will substitute a local walk with some kind of Feature on my other site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow Boat Launch:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for GPS use 300 Bassetts Bridge Road Mansfield Center CT, (its close enough)..&lt;br /&gt;mapquest or other...just compare the directions below to what you get..they better be similar..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup map link above looks ok.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-84 heading EAST, take Exit 68 = south on rte 195 through Storrs to Mansfield ctr (about 11 miles from 84)&lt;br /&gt;Go 0.5 mile past rte 89 junction and turn left onto Bassset Bridge Rd at the stoplight, should see Mansfield Hollow Park sign. (licquer store at the intersection too)&lt;br /&gt;Will see a picknick area on left but go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-384 East, bear right onto rte 6 and follow rte 6 to toward Willimantic.&lt;br /&gt;6 and 66 will intersect at a light. Take a left on to 6.&lt;br /&gt;Follow this highway to the second exit, go straight (=rte633 or s. frontage rd.) it is actually a parallel to rte 6 connector to rte 195,&lt;br /&gt;Signs for UCONN should be there somewhere too,&lt;br /&gt;Go North on rte 195 toward UCONN for about 2 miles then turn right at the onto Basset Bridge Rd, Will see a picknick area on left but go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The picknick area you passed will be where we go after the paddling is done.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember and PRINT the directions....LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok bring some food, and other stuff for several hours on the water and the picknick after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Available Kayaks are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have 3 kayaks available but would like a rental doughnation of 15 bucks for each one.&lt;br /&gt;It buys new stuff, repairs, transportation and the like.&lt;br /&gt;Yes i want some more carbon Werners paddles, but the 400 bucks each..maybe one a year..LOL&lt;br /&gt;I have 2  carbon paddles ordered, might be ready for this event..dont know ??&lt;br /&gt;The cobra floor drain is now sealed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please know the kayak type and its quirks before reserving.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on some conditions its ok to try different kayaks given your abilities..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pfd, Paddle and other accessories included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Homeless Bathtub, Recreational Kayak= Pungo 12' with F/R floataion bags installed= IRA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper &amp;amp; Dipper, Sea Kayak= Riot Tourlite 15'= Al-r &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna Snake, Sea Kayak= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = NEIL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Wild Dancer, Sea Kayak= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= DURELLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Flat Boat, Sea Kayak= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= Alex&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there.&lt;br /&gt;AL-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Kayak Trailer and Orange Stryped Cones at boat "CARRY IN" area</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244999572000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243819665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*KAYAK EVENT*  Mansfield Hollow Reservoir Areas</name><id>10539639</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244307600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10539639/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/0/global_5287696.jpeg</photo_url></item>