<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Long Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.359947</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1.877.SEE.WHALE</phone><name>Boston Harbor Cruise</name><city>Boston</city><id>985613</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.049675</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>group fee + cruise/lesson</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Another one of those &amp;quot;I've been meaning to do that!&amp;quot; events...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join SoJust for &lt;b&gt;Salsa Cruise for Justice&lt;/b&gt; and get in one more fiesta before August is over!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A full night of fun kicks off at 6:30pm at &amp;quot;The Landing&amp;quot; at Long Wharf where you can meet up with other SoJusters and enjoy a Signature Fish Bowl Cocktail. The lesson starts at 7pm - and the cruise departs at 8:30. On board there's a cash bar, dinner (buy tickets in advance) and DJs on 2 levels. The cruise returns to dock around 11pm and then there's an optional after-party at Mojito's Lounge** in downtown Boston. Cruise attendees get in for free. Whew! That IS a full night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a crowded cruise so be sure to RSVP&lt;/b&gt; and we'll look for you at &amp;quot;The Landing&amp;quot; before the lesson. &lt;i&gt;Newcomers always welcomed!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purchase tickets on-line ($20 +$2 for optional lesson +$10 for optional dinner) - definitely sign up for the lesson! Best to buy in advance, but tickets are also available at the dock for $25 (+2 for lesson).&lt;br /&gt;Read more about the cruise and purchase Individual tickets at &lt;a href="http://www.salsaboston.com/cruise" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.salsabosto...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Cruise is all ages and &lt;i&gt;sails rain or shine&lt;/i&gt;. Salsa Harbor Cruises is located at Boston Harbor Cruises Terminal, One Long Wharf, Downtown Boston. Recommended to take the T - Blue Line to &amp;quot;Aquarium,&amp;quot; Orange Line to &amp;quot;State&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Haymarket,&amp;quot; Green Line to &amp;quot;Government Center&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Haymarket.&amp;quot; For directions by car (and most importantly where to park for less dineros) visit www.salsaboston.com/cruise/parking/.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**After-party at Mojito's Lounge is 21+. This is an optional event not coordinated by SoJust. It's located at 45 Winter Street near Park Street T stop. Cruise attendees get in free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us if you want to cross-promote your events and campaigns, are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in, or you've been looking for like-minded progressives to hang with in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At SoJust events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;No Program. No Speaker. Just us.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Hey organizers!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers - there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events?&lt;/b&gt; Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the website - just click '&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/"&gt;Messages&lt;/a&gt;'.  The &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/calendar"&gt;SoJust Calendar&lt;/a&gt; is packed with social justice-related events held throughout Greater Boston.  Help us keep it filled - tell us about events you hear about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From our FAQs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;It's not very easy for me to meet new people and I'm not really one for small talk.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hear you. That's why at SoJust events, in addition to traditional name tags, we have &amp;quot;Ask Me About&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Looking For&amp;quot; tags. That way you can slap whatever you're into lately up on your shirt and wait for fellow SoJusters to approach you. These seem to do the trick of moving past the basic &amp;quot;what do you do for work? where do you live?&amp;quot; questions to conversations that lead to more substantial connections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;What actually happens at events?&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll always be greeted by friendly folks who can help get you socializing, introduce you to people, and chat with you about questions or wishes. It's likely a few people will be there promoting their campaigns and issues (&lt;i&gt;yes, SoJust welcomes that sort of behavior&lt;/i&gt;). At our bigger events, there's always a literature table to toss down flyers, postcards, and other paraphenalia about events around town. Most importantly, we can pretty much guarantee there will be someone there you've never met before. As one of our members said, &amp;quot;You are bringing together people who might never get together otherwise - if that ain't a step towards justice I don't know what is.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt;  and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll have a SoJust sign near the entrance to "The Landing" and we'll be the friendly folks with name tags!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253228702000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249263364000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salsa Cruise for Justice</name><id>11018741</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251498600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/11018741/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/9/c/global_10003436.jpeg</photo_url></item>