<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Orange Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.304291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nini's Bistro</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1232766</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.925229</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Saturday, June 26, 2010 at 1:30pm        [b]PURCHASE TICKETS BEFORE EVENT[/b]
Nini's Bistro (40 Orange Street) 
The Wine Thief 
Union League Cafe 

Robin Goldstein 





DURATION 90 minutes
LOCATION New Haven

Admission: $40 

Aficionados of food and drink will delight in exploring New Haven’s food scene through these restaurant explorations and experiences. Meet the chefs, peek into kitchens, watch food and drink demos and taste the specialties of New Haven’s finest restaurants. Foodie Tours will be led by Robin Goldstein, founder of the Fearless Critic series and author of The Wine Trials. He has been a food critic for the New Haven Advocate, written for Fodor's travel guides, and has a certificate in cooking from the French culinary Institute and WSET advanced wine and spirits certificate. 

Please meet outside the first restaurant or designated meeting place 5 minutes before the tour begins. Foodie Tours tend to sell out quickly, so plan to purchase your tickets in advance. 

Tickets on sale now to Members! Become a Member of the Festival today to save on first choice tickets. Join the Festival at the $125 level to receive a variety of great benefits, including the chance to purchase tickets to all Festival events, before they go on sale to the general public on April 6. 

Becoming a Member is easy! Click here to purchase a Festival Membership online, or call the Festival at 203.498.3758. Members enjoy ticket exchange privileges through April 5. 

Click here to purchase tickets online with your Member password. You can also purchase tickets in person at the Shubert Theater Box Office (247 College Street, New Haven), and by phone at 203-562-5666 or 888-736-2663. 

 
Comments
No comments yet.

Leave a comment
Line and paragraph breaks automatic, e-mail address never displayed, HTML allowed: &lt;a href=""&gt;   &lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;a href=""&gt;&lt;b&gt;  &lt;code&gt;  &lt;em&gt; &lt;i&gt;   &lt;strong&gt; 

 Name   

 E-mail 

 URL 

Your Comment 
 

 

0.158 Powered by WordPress
Daisy 
 


 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet up sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277577497000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270006779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Haven Food Festival "Foodie Tour"</name><id>13044779</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277573400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/13044779/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/1/global_4236481.jpeg</photo_url></item>