<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Brian Ditter and Tara McLaughlin invite HAC to a barbecue and
pot luck on Independence Day, Monday, July 4, noon to 4pm at
Crystal Lake Park in Middletown. Please RSVP: Brian Ditter: (860)
704-0439 or Tara McLaughlin: (860) 545-5065 Brian and Tara will
provide burgers/steaks, beverages, chips, and fixings. Please bring
a dish to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From New Haven: take I-91 N to exit 15 for CT-68 toward
Yalesville/Durham. In 0.3 mi turn right onto route 68. In 0.9 mi
route 68 takes a left. Follow 68 for 4.2 mi, when you will turn
left onto route 17/Main St. Take your 2nd right (0.5 mi.) onto
Haddam Quarter Rd. In 1.7 mi.turn left at Arbutus St. In 1.4 mi.
take a slight right onto Livingston Rd. The entrance to the park
will be on your left in 0.6 mi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Hartford: Take I-91 S and take exit 22S on the left to
merge onto CT-9 S toward Middletown. Take exit 11. At the end of
the exit turn left onto route 155 (Randolph Rd.) toward route 17
and Durham. In 0.7 mi. turn left at Millbrook Rd.(there's a traffic
light and a fire station on your left). In 1.4 mi turn right onto
Livingston Rd. and then turn right into the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 84: Take I-691 E toward Meriden and continue onto route 66
(eastbound). In 2.0 miles turn right onto route 147 S. In 2.3 miles
turn right and continue on route 147 and route 157. In 2.5 miles
turn left onto Middlefield Rd. At the end of Middlefield Rd. turn
right and then take your first left onto Haddam Quarter Rd. In 1.7
mi.turn left at Arbutus St. In 1.4 mi. take a slight right onto
Livingston Rd. The entrance to the park will be on your left in 0.6
mi.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the pavilion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>richard.s</member_name><member_id>1140524</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309871633000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307913328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Independence Day Cookout at Crystal Lake, Middletown</name><id>21938791</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309795200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/21938791/</event_url></item>