<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;UPDATES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3/4/10: We are rescheduling for the following week. Please excuse the change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3/3/10: We have a location and time. Please adjust your RSVP accordingly. If you get lost or cannot find the group please feel free to call my cell: 508-510-1136. I am thinking we would spend from 1-2 hours in the woods. Any questions feel free to email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great place to let your dog off-leash.  There are hundreds of acres and all sorts of rock formations.  There are plenty of streams and some really beautiful trails with rhododendron's.  There is one trail that you can see the Boston skyline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note: Date and time are tentative.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all for your feedback. I'm glad to see people taking advantage of the new feature. I would like to schedule an event for this weekend. Please let me know what day and times work best. I will finalize the details according to the feedback I receive in the next 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll find us a map tonight, as well as a parking and meeting area. Please chime in if you know the park, as I do not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks again for taking an active role in this group! Your voices have been heard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Luis&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I am a tall guy with short hair. will be in a green Chevy pickup.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luis </member_name><member_id>6933069</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268665740000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dog-hiking</urlname><id>1123750</id><group_lat>42.2299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8899993896</group_lon><name>Dog hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267557721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whitney and Thayer Woods, Hingham, MA</name><id>12759016</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268492400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dog-hiking/events/12759016/</event_url></item>