<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>As promised, our February read is: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius by David Eggers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;copied from &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio/17-9780375725784-19" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The literary sensation of the year, a book that redefines both family and narrative for the twenty-first century. A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius is the moving memoir of a college senior who, in the space of five weeks, loses both of his parents to cancer and inherits his eight-year-old brother. Here is an exhilarating debut that manages to be simultaneously hilarious and wildly inventive as well as a deeply heartfelt story of the love that holds a family together.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius is an instant classic that will be read in paperback for decades to come. The Vintage edition includes a new appendix by the author.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, I fear I am deserting you, though perhaps if you're nice enough to Allison in January, we can beg her to retain the title of group guru for another month :-) But head on back to our usual Cafe, look for other searching faces with Eggers book clutched in their palms and get to chatting!  As ever, if we are crowded out and you see no familiar Eggers readers, you can always try Au Bon Pain across the street (684 Mass Ave:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will see you next month!&lt;br /&gt;  Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266450983000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260234490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius</name><id>12040137</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265673600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/12040137/</event_url></item>