<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Crescent Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06608</zip><lat>41.184773</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.814.6856</phone><name>off site installation show presented  by The Gallery at Black Rock</name><city>Bridgeport</city><id>1182250</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.184047</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per meetup</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;Come out and join our group and Eileen Walsh, Gallery Director of the Black Rock Gallery and one of our own, who has worked tirelessly to put together this show.&lt;br /&gt;The Gallery at Black Rock presents “Industrial Strength,” a juried show in which artists view the post-industrial landscape. This is an off site show at the address on Crescent Street stated above.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;&lt;b&gt; Industrial Strength&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;3-8pm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;Artists have celebrated landscapes since the first chunks of charcoal were rubbed on a cave walls. Through history artists have tried, with varying degrees of success, to capture the bucolic and stunning views of nature -- mountains, trees, the sky -- that surround them.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;  Today, artists are often confronted with a very different kind of landscape, the post-industrial urban landscape of the 21st century. But inspiration remains the same.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;  In cities like Bridgeport, Connecticut, we are surrounded by the remnants of a once-thriving manufacturing community. All Bridgeporters can resonate in some way to the towering red and white-banded United Illuminating smoke stack, or to the crumbling hulks of once-thriving factory buildings that, in their prime, made Bridgeport one of the Northeast’s greatest industrial cities.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;  It is easy to vilify the industrial landscape as ugly or depressing, but through the eyes of an artist the sights that are so repellant to some, emerge with hidden, sometimes breathtaking, beauty.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;The show will seek to address both points of view on this issue through, painting, sculpture, installation and photography as well as film/projected image. There will be 14 participating artists including: Amber Madia, Jeff Becker, Liz Squillace, Brian Reiley, Ginger Hanrahan, Rachael Haymann, Mark DeRosa, Jessica Materna, Victoria Wyndham, Allen Wittert , Brian Reily, Sean Corbett, Eileen Smith, Janine Brown and Michelle Beaulieau.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;The show will be the Gallery at Black Rocks First off site installation and will take place at the sight of  Camelot development  on 51 Crescent street in the city’s east side. “The location will act as part of the shows vision as it is surrounded by part of the city that was once a thriving industrial site and still holds a neglected beauty.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The sight will be open for viewing on the following  4 consecutive Saturdays from  12 until 4pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music will be provided by Martin C. Early&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions from north:&lt;/b&gt; I-95 S/GOVERNOR JOHN DAVIS LODGE TURNPIKE toward N.Y. CITY. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Take the SEAVIEW AVENUE exit, EXIT 29, toward CT-130/STRATFORD AVENUE. 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn RIGHT onto SEAVIEW AVE. 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn LEFT onto BARNUM AVE. 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn LEFT onto NOBLE AVE. 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn RIGHT onto CRESCENT AVE. 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>will wear my BW scarf with Piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267473888000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265327592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Industrial Strength - Reception</name><id>12522373</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267300800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/12522373/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/b/9/global_12946281.jpeg</photo_url></item>