<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone!&lt;br /&gt;   This Saturday we will having our Conscious Movie Night. (Please note that this is a change from the usual schedule of having it the last Friday of the month.) We will be viewing the fabulously moving film &lt;i&gt;Baraka&lt;/i&gt;. Some would call it an art film, as it has amazing beautiful cinematography. Please see the description below, which contains exerpts from reviews of the movie on Amazon. Speaking of reviews, not one person gave this film less than four stars, and most gave it five. &lt;br /&gt;   We're starting a little earlier this time, so we can have time to talk about the movie afterward. If you are looking for an interesting evening of great film and real conversation with a warm and welcoming bunch of folks, Conscious Movie Night at the Center of Light may be just the thing. I look forward to seeing you all!&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Baraka&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Produced by Mark Magidson and directed and photographed by Ron Fricke, award-winning cinematographer of KOYAANISQATSI&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BARAKA is a profound, moving experience. You will find in it at least a half-dozen moments of pure wonder, and probably many more. You will also see images of things you've never seen before, or even imagined. BARAKA explores natural wonders, religious practices, and humans in harmony and in conflict with nature and themselves. It contains scenes of great beauty, great ugliness, and great humor.&lt;br /&gt;Baraka is powerful... no dialogue. It's a visual documentary of a poetic tour of the globe set to the rhythms of various religious and spiritual rituals, spanning diverse locales as China, Brazil, Kuwait and major US and European sites. The soundtrack will lubricate your mind. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Baraka must be seen, felt and experienced to be understood.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347648000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240501763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night:  Baraka</name><id>10251484</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240700400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/10251484/</event_url></item>