<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>255 Grossman Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.211508</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Border's Books &amp; Cafe</name><city>Braintree</city><id>715069</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.999105</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us as we discuss the Edgar Award Winning novel &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;In the Woods&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; by Tana French. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;As dusk approaches a small Dublin suburb in the summer of 1984, mothers begin to call their children home. But on this warm evening, three children do not return from the dark and silent woods. When the police arrive, they find only one of the children gripping a tree trunk in terror, wearing blood-filled sneakers, and unable to recall a single detail of the previous hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Twenty years later, the found boy, Rob Ryan, is a detective on the Dublin Murder Squad and keeps his past a secret. But when a twelve-year-old girl is found murdered in the same woods, he and Detective Cassie Maddox--his partner and closest friend&amp;amp;--find themselves investigating a case chillingly similar to the previous unsolved mystery. Now, with only snippets of long-buried memories to guide him, Ryan has the chance to uncover both the mystery of the case before him and that of his own shadowy past. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richly atmospheric, stunning in its complexity, and utterly convincing and surprising to the end, In the Woods is sure to enthrall fans of Mystic River and The Lovely Bones.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the cafe area at the front of the bookstore and will place a copy of the book on the table so that new people can find us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See previous books read by this group and future suggestions at our goodreads page here: &lt;a href="http://www.goodreads.com/group/show/1091.South_Shore_Readers" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.goodreads....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the cafe area and will have a copy of the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257382630000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253566392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Shore Readers: In the Woods</name><id>11429733</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256490000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/11429733/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/9/8/global_10834760.jpeg</photo_url></item>