<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 The Riverway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.341718</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wheelock Family Theatre</name><city>Boston</city><id>962723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106381</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Boston ASL!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to this event! Bring your friends and family! All proceeds to benefit the National Theatre of the Deaf, so it's for a good cause as well as being fun and accessible to everyone, hearing or Deaf. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VSA Massachusetts and Wheelock Family Theatre present&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UNIVERSAL SIGNS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday November 11 at 7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Benefit for National Theatre of the Deaf&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: General Admission: $20.; Students/Seniors: $10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the screening there will be a discussion with Director Ann Calamia, Producer Catherine Miller, WFT Producer Susan Kosoff, and NTD Artistic Director Aaron Kubey. VSA Massachusetts will be providing desserts and beverages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy Tickets Now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also call the Box Office at 617-879-2300 or email tickets@wheelock.edu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A groundbreaking &amp;quot;silent&amp;quot; film, presented in mesmerizing American Sign Language (ASL) with English subtitles, Universal Signs touches the hearts and minds of hearing and Deaf audiences alike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the death of his fiancée's daughter while in his care, Andrew (Anthony Natale), a Deaf artist, becomes a prisoner of his own mind. Tormented day and night by memories and self-blame, Andrew falls in a downward spiral of depression and anger that alienates everyone around him. It is only through a serendipitous friendship and new love with Mary (Sabrina Lloyd) that Andrew is able to sense the life around him - forgive himself, rediscover his muse, and experience the transformative power of love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Written and directed by Ann Calamia. Produced by Catherine Miller, Ann Calamia, and Lupe Ontiveros. With Anthony Natale, Sabrina Lloyd, Lupe Ontiveros, Robert Picardo, Ashlyn Sanchez, Troy Kotsur, Deanne Bray, Margot Kidder, Robert Hogan, and Aimee Garcia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional information about the movie please visit UniversalSignsMovie.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erika Wentworth</member_name><member_id>487803</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289607953000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ASL Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonasl</urlname><id>1298565</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston ASL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286407670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Universal Signs Film Screening, A Benefit for National Theatre of the Deaf</name><id>15027654</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289520000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonasl/events/15027654/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/1/global_16399809.jpeg</photo_url></item>