<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hartford CT</address_2><address_1>300 Columbus BLVD</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.765041</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mortenson Park </name><city>Hartford</city><id>550417</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.669594</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thursday, July 12, 5:00 - 10:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Mortensen Riverfront Plaza &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An evening of music featuring some of the best international Latin Jazz and Salsa artists&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RIVERWALK NORTH - Mortensen Riverfront Plaza to Riverside Park?s Greater Hartford Jaycees Community Boathouse, Hartford &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.6 mile loop. Approximate walking time: 30 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceed north from Mortensen Riverfront Plaza following the walkway along the river, pass under a stone arch of the historic Bulkeley Bridge and into Riverside Park to the Greater Hartford Jaycees Community Boathouse. Once you reach the boathouse, simply reverse the directions and return to downtown Hartford. The walkway is paved and lighted its entire length. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mortensen Riverfront Plaza to Great River Park?s Hockanum River, Hartford and East Hartford &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.2 mile loop. Approximate walking time: 60 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceed from the upper level of the Mortensen Riverfront Plaza and head east across the Founders Bridge Promenade into East Hartford. Use the handicapped ramp or descend the stairs to East River Drive and turn left under the highway bridge and then left again up the walkway ramp into the north section of Great River Park. Once you reach the stone arched Bulkeley Bridge (I-84) turn around and follow the path down to the river, under the Founders Bridge and south past the boat ramp and amphitheater. Follow the walkway through the flood plain to the Hockanum River confluence under the Charter Oak Bridge. Once you reach the Hockanum River, simply reverse the directions and return to Mortensen Riverfront Plaza and downtown Hartford. The walkway is paved and lighted its entire length&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARK RULES &amp;amp; REGULATIONS - For park rules and regulations, click here.  Please note: Due to liability and legal restrictions, no outside alcoholic beverages of any kind may be brought into the Riverfront Parks by any party. Riverfront Recapture is the only licensed authority to sell and serve liquor for consumption in the Riverfront Parks. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WIRELESS INTERNET ACCESS - Thanks to an initiative by the City of Hartford, our parks now have wireless internet access.  Click here to sign up for wireless access to the internet in our park from the City of Ha&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;View Larger Map &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Views of Plaza Stairs Entrance from North on Columbus Boulevard&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From North of Hartford, take I-91 South to Exit 31, State St. The pedestrian staircase and elevator to the Plaza are on your left when you reach the end of the exit ramp. To continue to the Morgan Street parking garage, go straight through the intersection and take your first right onto Market St. At the second intersection, turn right onto Talcott St. The entrance to the Morgan Street garage is on your left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From South of Hartford, take I-91 North to Exit 32B, Trumbull St. At the end of the ramp, turn left onto Market St and pass under the elevated highway. Take your second left onto Talcott Street. Parking is available in the Morgan Street garage on your left. To continue to the Plaza, turn right onto Columbus Blvd and the pedestrian staircase and elevator to the Plaza will be on your left at the intersection of Columbus Blvd and State St. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Views of Plaza Stairs Entrance from South on Columbus Boulevard &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From East of Hartford, take I-84 West to Exit 54, Downtown Hartford and the Founders Bridge. The main pedestrian staircase and elevator to the Plaza are on your left at the end of the Founders Bridge. To reach the Morgan Street parking garage, go straight through the intersection and take your first right onto Market St. At the second intersection, turn right onto Talcott St. The entrance to the Morgan Street garage is on your left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From West of Hartford, take I-84 East to Exit 50, Main Street. At the end of Ramp go straight onto Chapel St. and then take your third right onto Market St. Take your first left onto Talcott Street. Parking is available in the Morgan Street garage on your left. To continue to the Plaza, turn right onto Columbus Blvd, and the main pedestrian staircase to the Plaza will be on your left at the intersection of Columbus Blvd and State St. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available at the Morgan Street Garage, Constitution Plaza Garage, and other area garages for a fee. Alternate parking includes on-street parking in Hartford, or you can park in East Hartford and take the short walk over the Founders Bridge Promenade.  Visit the Hartford Parking Authority website for more complete information at &lt;a href="http://www.hartford.gov/parking/map.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hartford.g...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View of the Founders Bridge Promenade entrance which connects East Hartford to Mortensen Riverfront Plaza, Hartford&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HANDICAP ACCESSIBILITY&lt;br /&gt;Views of the handicap elevator entrance on Columbus Boulevard &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mortensen Riverfront Plaza visitors requiring handicap accessibility should use the elevator located on Columbus Boulevard. The entrance to the elevator is to the right of the staircase.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Bring a picnic dinner  or purchase food there.   Let me know wht you want to do in your RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216069866000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Because we are fun.</why><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206073110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RAY GONZALAZ Latin Jazz and Salsa Festival</name><id>7574686</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215896400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/7574686/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/e/global_3074510.jpeg</photo_url></item>