<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's make 2011 a year of all good things by starting off with this movie.  With a cast like this it's many good things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the description.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inspired by the most notorious missing person’s case in New York history, All Good Things is a love story and murder mystery set against the backdrop of a New York real estate dynasty in the 1980s. Produced and directed by Andrew Jarecki (director of the Academy Award-nominated doc Capturing the Friedmans and producer of Catfish), the film was inspired by the story of Robert Durst, scion of the wealthy Durst family. Mr. Durst was suspected but never tried for killing his wife Kathie who disappeared in 1982 and was never found. The film stars Ryan Gosling, Kirsten Dunst and Frank Langella as the powerful patriarch, and captures the emotion and complexion of this real-life unsolved mystery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be out front at around 3:45 and go into the theater to save seats in the middle front at 4:00.  After, we'll go to one of our usual haunts for our usual incomparable discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a feeling that it will be a slightly cloudy Sunday and the movie may be sold out - so get your tickets ahead of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have a wonderful new year until then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shirley&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting near the ticket taker at 3:45 - and then I'll be in the theater itself at 4:00.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294077122000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293653793000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>All Good Things - starts at 4:10 pm at Kendall</name><id>15851246</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294002000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15851246/</event_url></item>