<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I know it's kind of last minute and this is scheduled rather early in the evening, but it's part of the Wesport River Vineyards' Summer Sunset Music series.  Blues Train is a local 4 piece band known to keep your feet moving with some good Rock, Blues &amp;amp; Funk!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at the picturesque Westport River Vineyards for some good music, great wine and and better friends.  It only cost $10 per carload so carpool up in the car/van. Get there as early as you can so we can be together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The series runs through Friday September 7th. From 6pm to 8pm the winery will feature live entertainment as the sun sets over the beautiful vineyard. It's a picnic style event, so either pack in your own food or buy some dinner from Wayne Gibson's South Coast Local (who will be serving up a variety of BBQ, from pulled pork sandwiches to hot dogs for the kids). Don't forget a blanket, chairs, bug spray, glasses or a cork screw.Admission is $10 per carload and beer, wine and SoCo Local food will be served for a fee. The event is weather permitting and NO OUTSIDE ALCOHOL is permitted. They will be selling wine by the glass or by the bottle.  They won't be having wine tastings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the Vineyard's link for the event;&lt;a href="http://www.westportrivers.com/events.html"&gt;http://www.westportrivers.com/events.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is being cross posted with Boston Providence Single Parents and &lt;span&gt;South Shore Hike, Bike and Social Club.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This should be a fun night out, hope you can join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll message attendees the day before with info</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lori </member_name><member_id>9578150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342547319000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341975018000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blues Train at Westport River Vineyards</name><id>72839302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342215000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/72839302/</event_url></item>