<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>11th Floor</address_2><address_1>675 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.365799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-204-2052</phone><name>Emilia Sabatowska</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>879026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104340</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;*** This is a special event. Due to limited space I ask that you pay in order to RSVP.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our Guest Speaker: Linda Marks &lt;br /&gt;www.healingheartpower.com&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linda Marks, MSM, is a body-centered psychotherapist, coach, social architect and author. Through her work with individuals, couples and groups and her personal example, she helps others heal from the soul level up and create new heartful possibilities for their lives. She has been committed to founding organizations that bridge the gap between the individual and the collective for the past twenty -five years. &lt;br /&gt;She holds degrees from Yale and MIT. She is the founder of the Institute for Emotional-Kinesthetic Psychotherapy, the Boston Area Sexuality and Spirituality Network, and HeartPower Press. She is the author of Living With Vision: Reclaiming the Power of the Heart (Knowledge Systems, 1988) and Healing the War Between the Genders: The Power of the Soul-Centered Relationship (HeartPower Press, 2004).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Workshop topic: Keeping a Vital Heart&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our hearts thrive when are lives are &amp;quot;coherent,&amp;quot; meaning we have a sense that life is purposeful, manageable and meaningful. This workshop will give you a chance to listen to and care for your heart, and take steps to follow your heart more closely in your daily life. In a safe, community setting, we will do meditation, and experiential exercises, drawing from EKP body psychotherapy healing work as we nourish and vitalize our hearts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilia</member_name><member_id>1728643</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269970317000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>whole-living-center</urlname><id>1384267</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Whole Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266953752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Keeping a Vital Heart - Special Event with Linda Marks</name><id>12686326</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269709200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/whole-living-center/events/12686326/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/5/global_7333733.jpeg</photo_url></item>