<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I am pleased to announce that at the 4/28/08 meetup several members of the engineering department at &lt;a href="http://tripadvisor.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tripadvisor.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://tripadvisor.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will be leading a discussion about social platform scalability and multiple platform development. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An abstract from department head Andy Gelfond: &lt;br /&gt;TripAdvisor has developed and deployed applications for Facebook, MySpace, Hi5, Orkut, and Friendster. Our &amp;quot;LocalPicks&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Cities I've Visited&amp;quot; Facebook apps have generated millions of downloads and are the most popular travel applications on Facebook. We will discuss how we have addressed social application scalability and multiple platform deployment through the use of a Java based SOA architecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are personal, engaging and everybody is sharing in the topic at hand. Come and share your experience with your peers. Presentations/discussions are held at MIT's EHS Office, 265 Massachusetts Ave, upstairs from the MIT Museum; drinks/food are at the Miracle of Science Bar &amp;amp; Grill, at the corner of Massachusetts Ave and State St, Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.: Thank you to the many members that RSVP (one way or another). This helps your humble organizer to manage the crowd at the venue.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The entrance is a gray door to the right of the main Museum entrance. The number "265" is above the door. Follow the Meetup signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kaj Kandler</member_name><member_id>1142521</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Archambault</member_name><member_id>2399674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209596569000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>IMPORTANT *** I've changed the time to 6:30pm and the venue to the MIT EHS conference Room (thanks John for offering this space *** We still intend to meet up socially after our presentation and discussion.</why><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205798698000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Java April Meeting</name><id>7552695</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209423600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/7552695/</event_url></item>