<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>754 Hopmeadow St, Simsbury</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06070</zip><lat>41.874397</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>860-658-0866</phone><name>Simbsbury's Eno Hall</name><city>Simsbury</city><id>619129</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.801950</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Performing on Tuesday, May 27th at 7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alturas Duo&lt;br /&gt;with&lt;br /&gt;Venezuelan soprano Adriana Balzán and Peruvian baritone José Sacín&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Alturas Duo is recognized as one of the most entertaining ensembles in the chamber music world today. The only group of its kind, the Duo formed with the idea of playing South American and classical music by bringing together the unusual combination of the viola, charango, and guitar, creating fiery programs that move with ease between Johann Sebastian Bach, South American folk rhythms and new music commissioned by the Duo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The name Alturas (Spanish for Heights) is derived from the poem &amp;quot;Alturas de Macchu Picchu&amp;quot; by the Chilean poet, Pablo Neruda. Alturas Duo members are Carlos Boltes (Viola &amp;amp; Charango) of Santiago, Chile and Scott Hill (Guitar) of Ontario, Canada.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adriana Balzan &amp;amp; Jose Sacín:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venezuelan soprano Adriana Balzan ?possesses a vibrant, clear soprano voice with a beautiful dark color, great extension and flexibility.? She is an Opera singer in Colombia, Peru, Costa Rica, Honduras, Spain and the US.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The voice of Peruvian baritone Jose Sacín ?has a velvety nap and nice variety of color? (Washington Post) Sacín has performed as a soloist with the Washington Opera and Baltimore Symphony Orchestra.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After each performance, there is a popular &amp;quot;Meet &amp;amp; Greet the Artists&amp;quot;. Complimentary hors d'oeuvres and a cash bar at a local restaurant (to be announced) make a perfect evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For tickets ($15) or information call: (860) 658-0866&lt;br /&gt;Tickets may be purchased at the door or by mailing an order, including a check payable to:&lt;br /&gt;Simsbury Chamber Music Festival in a self-addressed stamped envelope to:&lt;br /&gt;Simsbury Chamber Music Festival, 1276 Hopmeadow St, Simsbury, CT 06070&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the jean jacket as in my photo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Dworski</member_name><member_id>2589505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212104040000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Leave the confines of CT and experience music from Latin America</why><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211506393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South American Chamber Music - Alturas Duo</name><id>7995548</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211931000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/7995548/</event_url></item>