<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/9/0/event_103354192.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Difficulty: easy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance : 3 Miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duration: 1.5 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Blaze Orange is required. Spring hunting season is in swing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Before signing up for this hike read the entire write up and understand that you (and your guest if applicable) are agreeing to the terms of the liabilty waiver by signing up to participate in this activity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;   Simmons Mill Pond, a little known RI Management Area. There are no blazed trails here, but Simmons Mill offers miles of lanes and old roads, extensive woodlands, some ponds and open fields. Most of the lanes are flanked by stone walls and towering trees. There is plenty of opportunity to explore here with over 450 acres. However we will only be doing a small area of this management area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you following the "Weber" book this is hike #37. This is an easy 3 mile loop. Hunting season is back in play, so wear your blaze oragne. This location can be a bit wet at times. I would suggest boots not sneakers. Make sure you bring snacks, water and tick/ bug repellent. Book time for this walk is 2+ hours, however 1.5 hours should be ample.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: This walk is for the main enterance on Coldbrook Rd. Little Compton RI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;                  Take RI 179 or RI 81 into Adamsville, RI then drive Cold Brook Rd. 1.5 miles SW. to the enterance on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Safety First&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>179 Coldbrook Rd. Little Compton, RI. Take RI 179 or 81 into Adamsville, then drive Coldbrook Rd. about 1.5 miles Southwest to the enterance, on the left. This is the main parking lot. Do not use the John Dyer Rd. lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367806297000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367445462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Simmons Mill Pond, Little Compton (Ken Weber hike #37 )</name><id>117225312</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367764200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/117225312/</event_url></item>