<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I'm going to kick-off [hopefully] a monthly meetup event.  A chance for foodies like me to meet and enjoy good food over friendly conversation.  If you have a restaurant you want to try (or a particular cuisine), let me know! I'm going to keep the group size small every month 8-12 with a waiting list so try to RSVP early to get a spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vlora Mediterranean Restaurant &amp;amp; Wine Bar&lt;br /&gt;545 Boylston Street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the heart of Boston's Back Bay (Boylston Street and Clarendon Street), Vlora Mediterranean Restaurant &amp;amp; Wine Bar focuses on truly authentic Mediterranean cuisine that is characterized by only the use of olive oil, a minimalist approach to cooking with an emphasis on taste and the use of the freshest ingredients. Owned and operated by husband and wife team Aldo Velaj and Cindy Tsai, the restaurant is named after Aldo's home town - Vlora, Albania. Vlora's menu stems largely from Aldo's experiences traveling and eating through the Northern Mediterranean region of Southern Italy, Greece and Albania. The Restaurant's subterranean location and cozy atmosphere mimic the supper clubs and lounges prevalent all throughout Europe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transit: Vlora Mediterranean Restaurant &amp;amp; Wine Bar is accessible by T. We are located within five minutes walk of both the Green Line (Copley Square and Arlington ) and the Orange Line (Back Bay). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vloraboston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vlorabosto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservations under Monica Rouse, my cell 773-290-7859</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1245521361000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242410247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>For the Foodies: Mediterranean Brunch</name><id>10419778</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244998800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/10419778/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/d/global_8634877.jpeg</photo_url></item>