<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Organizer Michael Blair @ (978) 808-1932&lt;/b&gt;             &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the AMC in celebrating National Public Lands Day on September 25, 2010 in Crawford Notch, NH. We will be doing a variety of trail work projects on the trails in Crawford Notch. Projects will rage from trailhead trash clean up, brushing out overgrown trail, clearing trail drainage, and rock or wood trail structure construction. All projects will be led by trained AMC leaders. Beginners and families are welcome. We will meet at AMC's Highland Center at 9:00am for registration and a brief orientation and then head out to work on the various projects. We will all meet back at the Highland Center for free BBQ at 4:00pm and raffle at the end of the work projects. AMC will provide all leadership, tools, and appropriate safety equipment for the planned projects. Participants must wear boots and long pants and gloves for all trail work projects. Participants must also bring weather appropriate clothing as we will be working on the trails rain or shine. Participants are responsible for their own water (at least 2 quarts), snacks and lunch for the day. The free BBQ at 4:00pm and raffle is for individuals that have volunteered in the full day event. Pre-registration is required. Please contact the AMC Trails Volunteer Programs Office: Alex DeLucia - adelucia@outdoors.org Or Call: 603-466-2721 Alex DeLucia - x8128 Lesley Heyl - x8156 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE 08/31/2010:&lt;/b&gt; Neither Monica nor I will be able to participate in this great event - we will be competing in our 5th straight Greenway Challenge, an adventure relay race that promotes the recreational activities within the Blackstone River Valley and supports clean water campaigns along with the creation and upkeep of hiking and biking trails. I will still coordinate the National Public Lands Day Work Party but you will be responsible for getting yourself there and getting involved.&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Much like the National Trails Day event held in June, the AMC is planning a day of trail maintenance to coincide with National Public Lands Day.  NPLD is the nation's largest hands-on volunteer effort to improve and enhance the public lands Americans enjoy.  In 2009, more than 150,000 volunteers built trails and bridges, removed trash and invasive plants, planted trees and restored our water resources.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NPLD 2010 celebrates service and recreation on public lands while educating volunteers about the effects of climate change on our parks.  It engages a diverse audience of adult and youth volunteers to get to outdoors and improve their lands, whether at the grandest national park or at an urban park in their neighborhood.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NPLD inspires a new generation of volunteers committed to service on public lands. The event also encourages volunteers to explore and enjoy America's natural wonders through outdoor recreation. After working hard, volunteers can take a hike, a swim, a bicycle ride and get healthy in America's backyard.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last September, volunteers....   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Removed an estimated 900,000 lbs of trash    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collected an estimated 20,000 lbs of invasive plants   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Built and maintained an estimated 1,320 miles of trails   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Planted an estimated 100,000 trees, shrubs and other native plants   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contributed an estimated $14 million to improve public lands across the country   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members of the Random Group participated in the AMC's National Trails Day on June 6, 2010 - &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/305/calendar/13225048/"&gt;click here to read more about what we did.&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;            &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285708302000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275951054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC National Public Lands Day Work Party</name><id>13729705</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285419600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/13729705/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/7/global_15580391.jpeg</photo_url></item>