<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research and Development Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1534447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you would like to help sponsor this month's food for the meetup, please contact us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will have giveaways!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Session 1: (for beginners)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How To Secure Intellectual Property Rights Created Through Your WordPress Website By William A.M. Mansfield (@&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/PatentMansfield"&gt;PatentMansfield&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;As a U.S. Registered Patent Attorney through the United States Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO), Attorney William A.M. Mansfield helps entrepreneurs, startups, early stage companies, and enterprise clients “protect their passion”with corporate law, intellectual property (IP) law, patents, including IP portfolio strategies, trademarks, trade dress, copyrights, licensing, strategic partnerships, and succession planning.  Attorney Mansfield’s passion for IP began at an early age when he assisted his father, a Harvard Ph.D. graduate and former Harvard professor, with IP work and patents.  Since 2004, Attorney Mansfield has worked on legal matters and has counseled entrepreneurs and startups since 2009 through The Law Offices of William A.M.Mansfield.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;Attorney Mansfield has worked on legal issues faced by entrepreneurs and startups on national and international levels, including company formation, contracts (employment, contractor, non-compete, non-disclosure, non-solicitation, and non-hire agreements), founder representation, and negotiation of term sheets, with a focus on IP protection and the prosecution of both provisional patents and nonprovisional patents, especially business method, business process, electrical, mechanical, telecommunications, and e-commerce patents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;Attorney Mansfield is registered to practice patent law throughout the United States by the USPTO and admitted to practice law in Massachusetts and New York, with high bar exam scores allowing him to waive into the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit (D.C. Circuit). Attorney Mansfield was the recipient of The CALI Excellence for the Future Award before graduating with a J.D. from Western New England University School of Law, and he holds a B.A. from Trinity College.  He also completed Internet, technology, and IP law courses through The Franklin Pierce Law Center and The Harvard University Extension School.  Attorney Mansfield stays current with IP issues through the American Intellectual Property Law Association, Boston Patent Law Association, International Trademark Association, American Bar Association, Massachusetts Bar Association, and Boston Bar Association.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Session 2: (for developers)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Minimum Viable Products and Wordpress&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Andy Cook (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/AndyGCook/"&gt;@andygcook&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this presentation I'll share with you the ins-and-outs of quickly building a minimum viable product with Wordpress to test your assumptions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll also share some of the lessons I've learned while using Wordpress to build my startup, &lt;a href="http://www.rentabilities.com/"&gt;Rentabilities&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;Andy is a Cofounder at Rentabilities where he does a little bit of everything. 5 years of Wordpress experience.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Eng</member_name><member_id>9694496</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Bishop</member_name><member_id>13435843</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348536172000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>100</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343666164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BWPM Aug2012: WordCamp Aftermath</name><id>75537902</id><headcount>80</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346108400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/75537902/</event_url></item>