<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>54 Merrimac St*</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.812047</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>866-984-9283</phone><name>9th Wave Sailing charters</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>996926</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.873037</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ok everyone, here is a repeat event from last year....We all had such an awesome time on this last year we are doing it again only this time you get free Beer!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience the comfort and excitement of sailing aboard the river's only commercial sailing catamaran. Take the helm if you wish! The Ninth Wave sails out of the Merrimack River. We are docked at the far west end of the Newburyport waterfront boardwalk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ipswich Ale Beer Tasting:&lt;br /&gt;The Beer tasting will take place on the Dock, starting at 2PM.  So even if you are not a beer drinker come on down and sample some Ale and have some appetizers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our voyage:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 2:30pm we will board the Catamaran...............&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of the 9th Wave tours include a cruise of the Newburyport waterfront after which we will leave the harbor and raise sails in the open ocean, heading north or south along the coast as the wind dictates. We encourage our passengers to take an active role in the handling of the boat: raise the main, trim the sails or take the helm under the tutelage of our experienced captain and crew, while learning about the region's colorful past and looking at the natural history of our rich marine environment. Please understand that sail times are approximate because we cannot control the conditions and sailing is not an exact science.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket cost is: **$31.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things you need to know about this meetup:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;___Please call right away and reserve your ticket, there are only 48 available tickets and because of the Beer tasting these will sell out fast&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----When calling in your reservation, tell them you are reserving a spot on &amp;quot;Donna meetup&amp;quot;. Once all reservations are made a discount MAYl be applied depending on how many we have in our group.  This is not guaranteed due to the added Beer Tasting but if we get enough people to call in their reservations in advance we maybe able to talk the owner into a discount&lt;br /&gt;----Lunch or Snacks can be brought on the boat, but please be careful not to bring anything that will fly off the boat. NO ALCOHOLIC BEVERAGES CAN BE BROUGHT ON THE BOAT, there will be a Cash Bar available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---Phone # to call to make your reservation is: 866-984-9283&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Call in your reservation with a Credit Card, charges will not be applied until the Friday before and the discount will be applied at that time, if there is one. If this event gets cancelled by the 9th Wave, money will be refunded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So gather up your Friends and Family and join us on this Cruise...The more attendees we have the better the chances are that we can get a discount, but remember reserve now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids are welcome to attend, kids under 3 are Free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sailing time is 2:30pm-5:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Please Note: As the boat is in the water there is no official address, I have posted the closest address which is the Black Cow Restaurant, there is a parking lot in front of the Black Cow and the 9th Wave is on the west end of the dock. We will update the site as it gets closer for Parking options.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>On the Dock by the Ticket booth</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283258233000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280193986000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9th Wave Catamaran Ride</name><id>14223373</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283104800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/14223373/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/6/global_16744630.jpeg</photo_url></item>