<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On Saturday, October 31st from 4pm until 1am the &lt;a href="http://www.cambridgebrewingcompany.com" target="_blank"&gt;Cambridge Brewing Company&lt;/a&gt; will be hosting their 2nd annual Great Pumpkin Festival, featuring six CBC pumpkin beers, a whole patch of guest pumpkin beers from breweries like Elysian, Iron Hill, the Alchemist, Dogfish Head, Southern Tier, Allagash, and a 150 pound giant pumpkin filled with “cask” pumpkin beer, tapped sacrificially by robed monks and offered to the crowds.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, the menu for the evening will feature pumpkin inspired cuisine including pork tenderloin schnitzel with pumpkin spaetzle, pumpkin ravioli with pumpkin seed pesto cream and pumpkin pizza. Additionally, there will be a grill station on the patio serving true 'oktoberfest' style foods like three different kinds of wurst, grilled flat bread and autumn vegetable skewers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh, and for those of you lacking tastebuds, there will be several non-pumpkin offerings available as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is $10 and includes a limited edition festival glass. No Reservations are available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will email my cell number to all &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; RSVPs the morning of the event.  Being a true addict of all things pumpkin, I will likely get there early, but if you can't find us there, you can call or text me.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257209410000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256246877000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Great Pumpkin, festival, that is</name><id>11689119</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257021000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/11689119/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/1/global_11357793.jpeg</photo_url></item>