<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A forum where developers can showcase their work and their knowledge and engage an interested group of fellow developers, partners, and potential clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not to mention do a little showing off...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you or someone you know is working on a unique or particularly interesting project within Wordpress, come to this event and share your awesomeness with the group!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To offer a presentation topic or for general questions feel welcome to contact me directly at jboyce@gaiaworldwide.com or 617-312-3866.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still TBD. Please offer your ideas and suggestions for a suitable venue. I'm down in Mass. so its a bit harder for me to research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location could be anything from a room in a library to a restaurant or bar with a private room, or potentially (and perhaps ideally) someone's office. Of course, the place really needs to be connected and we have to be able to access the network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;projector&lt;/strong&gt; would be a very big plus as we'll need a big screen for optimum &lt;em&gt;showings off&lt;/em&gt;. I can bring one as a last resort, but I don't think the facility managers here will appreciate my "borrowing" equipment to take off site.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OK, so...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send me your topics, projects or subject you want to expound to our group members.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;and...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tell me about a great place we can meet for this thing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Joe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS: My contact info again for those who are eager to offer ideas and/or have questions - but don't feel like scrolling back to the top of this message:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;jboyce@gaiaworldwide.com or 617-312-3866.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Location TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Boyce</member_name><member_id>11913749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326933980000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WordPressDevNH</urlname><id>1488811</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Manchester, NH WordPress Developers and Users</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326224397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wordpress Developer Talent Showcase</name><id>47535752</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326929400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WordPressDevNH/events/47535752/</event_url></item>