<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>9.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Downward Doggin' on Sunday's -&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hey yoga lovers, both Newbies and advanced levels welcome. Have you ever wanted to try a yoga class? &amp;nbsp;Or, a yoga class...Outside? &amp;nbsp;Let us celebrate the warmer days and beautiful New England landscape by practicing yoga near the water in June!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;B. Y. O. M. (Bring your own mat) - we do have a few extras for you to borrow, but let us know beforehand.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;The class will run for three Sunday mornings at Webb Memorial State Park off Route 3A in North Weymouth (there is a parking lot). &amp;nbsp;It is scheduled to start on Sunday, June 5th from 10 am to 11:15 am. &amp;nbsp;The class will start at 10 am - 11:15 am, so please arrive a few minutes early to set your mat up and sign up. &amp;nbsp;All the yoga sessions will be on the first three Sundays in June (June 5th, June 12th, and June 19th) &amp;nbsp;June 26th is open for an unforeseen rain make up class.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;The certified yoga instructor, Lee, has been teaching for 6 years and remains an active teacher in corporate wellness centers, YMCA, area fitness centers,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;among other destination tropical locations. &amp;nbsp;She enjoys making all yoga levels feel welcome and also challenges the advanced yogi.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;All levels welcome, and the price for drop in class is $9. &amp;nbsp;Please bring cash, and sign yourself in on the class attendance list. &amp;nbsp;(The exception is the people that paid for the 3-pack class).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you may want to bring with you... Yoga Mat, Water, towel, and wear comfy clothes preferably layers of clothing so if you get hot, you will be comfortable. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;If it rains, a make up session will be the last Sunday in June...and will be posted or sent through email a few hours beforehand.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The event will close at 8 am every Sunday morning, so please RSVP for each Sunday before 8 am on each Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, and see you there!&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/7/event_30481031.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Webb Memorial Park is located on Neck Street, which turns into River (on 3A in Weymouth - across from Dunkin Donuts) - follow past the beach and drive all the way to the end.  We will be waiting next to the entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>1471217</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308574649000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306896635000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Downward Doggin' on Sundays</name><id>pmwmsypjbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308492000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/20817271/</event_url></item>