<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Old River Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.692941</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-975-3600</phone><name>Wyndham Hotel </name><city>Andover</city><id>809493</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.204044</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;February 9th for this fun and relevant topic! &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sugar Blues Workshop&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Are you constantly craving sweets and want to understand why? Do you want to gain control without deprivation? It is important to recognize that our relationship with sugar has little to do with willpower and discipline. A craving is actually the solution to the problem at hand, by understanding what your body is searching for you can reduce these cravings naturally.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; During this class we will discuss the primary causes of sugar cravings as well as the necessary tools to permanently change your relationship with sugar. &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alicia Joy Moskal&lt;/strong&gt;, Holistic Health Counselor studied at the Institute for Integrative Nutrition in New York City. Having studied all the major dietary theories, she understands there is no one way of eating that works for everyone, so instead she focuses on building the right lifestyle for the individual to ensure long-term success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;Her passion is working with pregnant and nursing moms who are tired, hungry, and overwhelmed with how to meet all the nutritional needs of their growing baby. Alicia is honored to work with these women to help them reconnect to their maternal instincts, to ensure they feel confident, empowered, and healthy throughout their pregnancy and well into motherhood.&amp;nbsp; It is her mission to support women during their magical journey into motherhood, creating happy healthy moms who create happy healthy babies. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen Campaiola</member_name><member_id>6037081</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298418250000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><why>Great Women's Only Networking Luncheon meets the second Wednesday of the month and includes open networking, business card exchange, personal introductions and guest speaker.  Join us!</why><group><who>Daring Women!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup</urlname><id>1412014</id><group_lat>42.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Dare To Be Phenomenal's Success Minded Women's Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281553462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DARE Networking Luncheon</name><id>dqzfpypdbmb</id><headcount>34</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297269000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup/events/16110760/</event_url></item>