<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Morse Auditorium</address_2><address_1>Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.351343</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston University</name><city>Boston</city><id>902463</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118426</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From Boston 9/11 Truth's website (Boston911Truth.org):&lt;br /&gt;====================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Theologian and 9/11 researcher David Ray Griffin will speak at Boston University's Morse Auditorium, 602 Commonwealth Ave, at 7pm on Saturday, April 11, 2009. $5 donation (students/seniors free). The event is co-sponsored by the Boston University School of Theology and the Boston 9/11 Truth Committee. The title of Dr. Griffin's presentation will be, &amp;quot;9/11: Time to take a Second Look.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Ray Griffin is Professor of Philosophy of Religion and Theology, Emeritus, Claremont School of Theology and Claremont Graduate University in Claremont, California, where he remains a co-director of the Center for Process Studies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has published (as author or editor) 34 books, primarily in theology, philosophy, and philosophy of religion, with special emphases on the problem of evil and the relation between science and religion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seven of his books deal with 9/11: The New Pearl Harbor: Disturbing Questions about the Bush Administration and 9/11 (2004), The 9/11 Commission Report: Omissions and Distortions (2005), Christian Faith and the Truth about 9/11: A Call to Reflection and Action (2006), 9/11 and American Empire: Intellectuals Speak Out (2006, co-edited with Peter Dale Scott), Debunking 9/11 Debunking: An Answer to Popular Mechanics and Other Defenders of the Official Conspiracy Theory (2007), and 9/11 Contradictions: An Open Letter to Congress and the Press, and The New Pearl Harbor Revisited: 9/11, the Cover-Up, and the Exposé (2008).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His 9/11 books have been endorsed by Michael Chossudovsky, William Sloane Coffin, Harvey Cox, Richard Falk, Catherine Austin Fitts, David Griscom, Jim Hightower, British MP Michael Meacher, Mark Crispin Miller, Rosemary Ruether, Marcus Raskin, Paul Craig Roberts, Peter Dale Scott, Gerry Spence, Lorie Van Auken, Howard Zinn, and former CIA officials Robert Baer, Bill Christison, and Ray McGovern.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Four of these books have been given special recognition: The New Pearl Harbor and The 9/11 Commission Report: Omissions and Distortion received the 2006 Helios Foundation Award for 2006. Debunking 9/11 Debunking was a Bronze Medal Winner in the 2008 Independent Publisher Book Awards. The New Pearl Harbor Revisited was named a Pick of the Week in 2008 by Publishers Weekly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His essays and interviews about 9/11 have appeared in such disparate publications as Zions Herald, Hustler Magazine, Global Outlook, LA Times Magazine, Conversations in Religion and Theology, Penthouse Netherlands, Whole Earth Times, Tikkun, and Le Monde Diplomatique.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has also been featured on The Richard &amp;amp; Judy Show (London), C-Span (twice), ABC News Radio, Tucker on MSNBC, CBC (Canadian Broadcast Corporation), the BBCs Heaven and Earth, and over 400 radio talk-shows, including Democracy Now! Many videos of his talks and interviews are available on the Internet.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239751770000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232388985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>David Ray Griffin at Boston University - 9/11: Time for a Second Look</name><id>9556528</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239489000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/9556528/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/8/global_6998040.jpeg</photo_url></item>