<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>850 Hillside Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.210381</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Hills at Houghton Pond</name><city>Milton</city><id>1412612</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096436</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We had such a great hike last Sunday, I hope to do it again this Saturday and Sunday! Tell all your friends! This will be a moderately strenuous and brisk hike to Elliot Tower starting at the South side of the Skyline Trail, taking the Red Dot Trail, then back down to the Headquarters on the North Side of the Skyline Trail. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 According to one website, "The classic here is the Skyline Trail (blue blazes), from Quincy going West via Houghton's Pond to the summit of Great Blue Hill, and back to Houghton's Pond. This is about nine miles long, with an elevation gain (my calculations, people disagree about the numbers) of 2,500 feet." - &lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/%7Eellozy/strenuous.html%3Cbr%20/%3E"&gt;http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/strenuous...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 START TIME/LOCATION: Starting promptly at 10:30 - Houghton's Pond, Milton, Ma, address listed is for the Headquarters which is a 100 feet from the Houghton's Pond parking. There is more parking available at the Houghton's Pond parking area (I will be parked here). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ADDITIONAL INFORMATION: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue.htm%3Cbr%20/%3E"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/b...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 RECOMMENDED GEAR: Water, snacks, food, gloves, proper shoes for hiking, proper clothing for weather conditions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Debra's Cell # - 508-237-4454 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;

 GPS Coordinates - 42.2141 N, 71.1200W &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Address - 695 Hillside St, Milton, MA 02186 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Take Route 93 to Exit 3, Houghton's Pond. Turn right at the stop sign onto Hillside Street. Houghton's Pond is located approximately 1/4 miles on the right; continue onto the Houghton Pond entrance on the right. Or you can take Exit 5 MA 28 Randolph Milton, keep on Randolph St. until you get to set of lights, take left at lights onto Chickatawabut Rd, then left onto Hillside St near the State Police, continue onto the Houghton Pond entrance on the left. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Peaks: Great Blue Hill (635 feet). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Difficulty Level: Moderately Strenuous. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Distance: Will have to find this out. If anyone has a pedometer, bring it along. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Elevation Gain: 2,500 feet - will have to verify this. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Time: 3 hours (Skyline Trail to Red Dot trail and back down Skyline Trail). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunrise: 7:11 am &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunset: 4:16 pm &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Weather Forecast:as of Tuesday, 38degrees and partly cloudy. &lt;a href="http://www.weather.com/weather/today/Milton+MA+USMA0260%3Cbr%20/%3E"&gt;http://www.weather.com/weather/today/Milton...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 CANCELLATION POLICY: Inclement weather (mainly Rain) may cancel the hike. If cancelled, it will be rescheduled a few weeks later. I will not have the time to call everyone, so you'll need access to your email to see if the hike is canceled. I will try to post it 4 hours before the hike. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 CODE OF CONDUCT AND DISCLAIMER: In order to participate in this activity, you acknowledge and agree that this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You assume all risk associated with this activity. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at hikesafe.com. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group on the hike and others in the group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * Weather can change quickly. Weather conditions which normally do not appear problematic can be when the body is stressed by hard exercise. You can develop hypothermia or hyperthermia very easily at any outside temperature. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * You agree to hike as a group, with the slowest member of the group. If you are late to the meetup, you may try to catch up with the group. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Details to follow!!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debra </member_name><member_id>12483780</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324774229000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324384014000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sat before Holiday Hike - Blue Hills</name><id>45004122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324740600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/45004122/</event_url></item>