<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next month's Boston Maltese Meet will occur on September 10th (NOT the 3rd, which is part of the Labor Day weekend!), from 2pm to 5 pm.  Kate Horgan-Burke's Maltese training class will run from 1 pm to 2 pm.  RSVP me about each event separately, please:  (questions, write me at laptopmaltese@aol.com).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am looking for a veterinarian to speak at this meeting at 3 pm.  If you've already given me suggestions, I will be calling them.  If you have new suggestions, please write me and send me the vet's phone number as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone that wants to bring food, please let me know!(laptopmaltese@aol.com). Several people brought food last time, a wonderful addition to the event.  Judy Ryan, Joan Labrie, Barbara and Joe Murphy, Fran and Rick Cashell.  Lovely food and beautifully presented.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to all of you that  brought food!  If I forgot someone, many apologies and please let me know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We again used the agility training equipment, but brought it out one piece at a time, so as not to crowd the dogs and owners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate Horgan-Burke's training lesson will run from 1 pm-2pm.  PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS MEANS THAT OUR REGULAR MALTESE MEET WILL START AT 2 PM, an hour later than we usually start.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate' training lesson was lots of fun.  We worked on teaching our dogs boundaries in various ways.  Suggestions for next time's lesson?  Email them to me.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's all for now! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy August.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159918411000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1154887582000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Maltese September Meetup</name><id>5063995</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1157911200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/5063995/</event_url></item>