<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>943 Namquid Drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02888</zip><lat>41.741898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-572-3390</phone><name>Game On!</name><city>Warwick</city><id>1111698</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405803</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>DALE 1-6 Dalelands Regional Adventure by Mickey Tan, for characters of levels 11 to 14. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A trade consortium is being formed. All the players have been selected. Now if they could just agree to meet and finalize the trade pact. Why can’t they all just get along? A Living Forgotten Realms adventure set in the Dalelands for characters levels 11-14.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:  This is a paragon adventure for characters levels 11-14.  Under the new rules for Living Forgotten Realms, you can make a character at level 11.  However, I strongly encourage anyone who is thinking of coming but is uncomfortable with the idea of playing at Paragon to contact me before hand with your concerns.  If it's a rules question, those can be sorted out easily enough.  However, paragon is a vastly different beast from the low heroic adventures we've been running so far.  This event is intended as a way to &amp;quot;test the waters&amp;quot; to see if those of us on here would like to play at a higher tier, with greater challenges and greater rewards to match.  This is NOT an event for players new to fourth edition.  I can not stress that enough, and while I don't like turning people away, if you show up at the table and don't already have a working knowledge of 4th edition (you don't have to have the PHB memorized, but you do need to know your character) I'm going to ask you to come back on Wednesday for Encounters.  Thanks everyone.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanios</member_name><member_id>4187193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287854347000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287708704000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paragon Living Forgotten Realms:  The Vesperin Initiative</name><id>15189247</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287849600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/15189247/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/f/global_6578223.jpeg</photo_url></item>