<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Event Organizer: Joe Ciarcia - 415-480-4335&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please only RSVP if you are attending. If you do not plan to attend, an RSVP is not required (simply do nothing :-) ).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's the first Sunday of Spring but with the recent snowfall it probably won't feel like it! The plan is to climb two of the 4,000 foot summits in NH. Passaconaway (#42 @ 4,043'), the easternmost 4,000 footer of the Sandwich Range Wilderness, shares a prominent ridge with Whiteface (#45 @ 4,020'). A lookout ledge just below Passaconaway’s wooded summit offers great views of the Tripyramid massif to the west and South Hancock and Carrigain to the north. We will use the Blueberry Ledge Trail to climb Whiteface and then the Rollins Trail reach Passaconaway. From there we will use Dicey's Mill Trail to return to our cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike given the current conditions. This may be revised as we get closer to the date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; trip we will hike about &lt;strong&gt;11.7 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and climb about &lt;strong&gt;4,359 feet&lt;/strong&gt; - Book time is 8 hours. This does not account for snack breaks and winter conditions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click for the &lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=43.93628735575264&amp;amp;lon=-71.40744209289551&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; (noaa.gov)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need things like warm layers, wind protection, goggles, snow shoes, and traction. I will update everyone if weather conditions dictate that we bring more than what is described here. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click for a &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a winter day hike&lt;/a&gt; (Appalachian Mountain Club)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current conditions require mountaineering snowshoes, as well as Microspikes or Hillsounds.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. &lt;strong&gt;If you don't have the required items you put yourself and everyone else at risk.&lt;/strong&gt; You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be meeting in the parking lot on the east side of Ferncroft Road near Wonalancet, NH. According to Google Maps this spot is about 133 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 32 minutes to drive there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For driving directions, &lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?daddr=43.914150,-71.364632(Dicey's+Mill+Trailhead)&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=16"&gt;click here and enter your starting address&lt;/a&gt; (google.com)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;daddr=43.914150,-71.364632(Dicey's+Mill+Trailhead)&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;ll=43.91415,-71.364632&amp;amp;spn=0.006295,0.008739&amp;amp;source=embed" style="color : #0000ff ; text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ciarcia</member_name><member_id>40840452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364160022000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362495364000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Whiteface and Passaconway  (Intermediate/Advanced)</name><id>107709752</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>32400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364126400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/107709752/</event_url></item>