<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/a/f/event_7377007.jpeg" width="274" height="190" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Lucid Dreams are dreams in which the dreamer becomes aware that he or she is dreaming. Sometimes this allows the dreamer to act with intention in the dream, such as walking, flying, speaking, or moving something hands-free with mind energy. Sometimes it allows the dreamer to control the content of the dream, such as a change of scene or making someone appear or disappear. In this Meetup we will explore these and other lucid dream experiences. In addition we will share techniques to intentionally dream lucidly. Through guided meditation we will practice the art of lucid dreaming. Bring your lucid dreams and other unusual dreams, to share, or just bring your curiosity. Come with us on these amazing and wonderful journeys! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This Meetup is facilitated by Deerheart, dream guide and experienced explorer of the dream realms. He has been studying dreams for over 25 years, including  dreamwork, shamanism, psychology, empowerment, and healing. For more information about him, visit his website, &lt;a href="http://www.visionarydreamguide.com/"&gt;Visionary Dream Guide&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left through angel doorway, into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342640322000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337129423000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lucid Dreaming</name><id>64964652</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340146800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/64964652/</event_url></item>