<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Kilton Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03110</zip><lat>42.955345</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>228-4794</phone><name>CR Sparks</name><city>Bedford</city><id>847807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.481353</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Note:  This event requires a reservation and it may or may not require a deposit by the organizer so all cancellations within 48 hours of the event requires a reason.  Please do not sign up unless you are sure that you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The membership has voted! The January Restaurant of the month is C.R. Sparks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This elaborate 220-seat restaurant featuring an open, exhibition-style kitchen was designed for owner Charles Rolecek by renowned restaurant designer Peter A. Niemitz of Niemitz Design Group, Inc. of Boston. Niemitz, designer of restaurants in Euro Disney and throughout the US, helped Rolecek realize his goal to offer NH diners a casual, yet sophisticated atmosphere for enjoying fine, gourmet food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conveniently located just off I-293 and South River Road, across from the Bedford Mall, this upscale restaurant and bar serves creative, gourmet food in a casual, relaxed atmosphere for lunch and dinner. Reservations are encouraged and welcomed. The restaurant serves traditional favorites: steak, fish, chicken, pasta and vegetables, with a creative gourmet twist. Rotisserie-cooked meats, flame-grilled specialties and brick-oven pizzas have captured the attention of area diners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;C.R. Sparks' decor features warm woods, Italian slate, brick, and art and artifacts from New England and around the world, with comfortable booths, tables and a beautiful bar. The open-concept and exhibition-style kitchen is the centerpiece of the entire restaurant. With two-tiered mezzanine seating, the restaurant can serve 350 for lunch or dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, C.R. Sparks offers private dining in the Maple or Cherry Room. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crsparks.com/index.php/menus" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crsparks.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crsparks.com/index.php/hours_and_directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crsparks.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1235846536000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232297089000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Restaurant of the Month</name><id>9549126</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235262600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9549126/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/a/global_7304042.jpeg</photo_url></item>