<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Coolidge Corner Theatre has been selected to Exhibit NT LIVE, a series of four plays transmitted in High Definition from the UK’s National Theatre (supported by Travelex). The series kicked off with two &lt;b&gt;sold-out&lt;/b&gt; screenings of PHÈDRE (directed by Nicholas Hytner, starring Helen Mirren).  &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Please get your tickets ahead of time as this event should sell out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 regular/$17 for seniors and Coolidge Members/$10 ages 15 and under.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;NATION&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;based on a novel by Terry Pratchett&lt;br /&gt;adapted by Mark Ravenhill&lt;br /&gt;2h25m with one 20-minute intermission&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live Date: Saturday, January 30, 2010 at 2pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John will be across the street at Panera Bread at 1:15 in order to meetup with those who wish to sit together.  We will plan to go to the Theater at 1::30 in order to secure good seats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A parallel world, 1860. Two teenagers are thrown together by a tsunami that has destroyed Mau’s village and left Daphne shipwrecked on his South Pacific island, thousands of miles from her aristocratic home in Victorian England. Neither speaks the other’s language; somehow they must learn to survive. Daphne delivers a baby, milks a pig, and does battle with a mutineer. Mau fights cannibal Raiders, discovers the world is round, and questions the reality of his tribe’s fiercely patriarchal gods. Together they come of age as they discard old doctrine to forge a new Nation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live music, thrilling dance and dazzling puppetry combine to bring to life the surprising and spectacular world of Terry Pratchett's Nation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following His Dark Materials, Coram Boy and War Horse, the National stages Mark Ravenhill’s exhilarating adaptation of Terry Pratchett’s latest witty and challenging adventure story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suitable for ages 10 years and up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;World Premiere&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Terry Pratchett&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terry Pratchett is an award-winning author with an international following. Best known for his fantasy fiction, he has written over 70 books, including the hugely popular Discworld novels. His novels have been translated into more than 36 languages. Pratchett has won numerous literary awards, was appointed an Officer of the Order of the British Empire (OBE) in 1998, and has received four honorary doctorates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the performance, John will lead the group to a discussion at &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Pho Lemongrass&lt;/span&gt;.  Please indicate in your RSVP whether you can stay for discussion so that we can make an accurate reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be at Panera Bread starting at 1:15, then will hold a beautifuly constructed Meetup Sign following the performance in order to lead International/Arthouse Nation to Pho Lemongrass for a phonemenal discussion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263161433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Theatre Live: NATION</name><id>12279972</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264878000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12279972/</event_url></item>