<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earlier, AccuWeather radar wouldn't load, but it's the same as Channel 5. Shows pop-up storms around Boston, otherwise clear. NWS says chance of Thunderstorms 30%.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Around here, it's the same...some smaller clouds, some more billowy, but not any more than before.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THIS MEETUP IS ON, BUT PLEASE WEAR STURDY SHOES AND BRING RAIN PONCHO. I DO *NOT* GUARANTEE WE HIKE IF CONDITIONS CHANGE AT 7pm, OR THAT WE WON'T LEAVE EARLY. Please make your decision accordingly. DON'T FORGET FLASHLIGHT/HEADLAMP!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch Fireworks All Over from Mount Watatic!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/e/event_130560542.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking lot was in a rural area, on the west-bound side of Rt. 119. There is a sign, though the dirt lot itself is hidden in the woods, and this is popular on the 4th! &lt;em&gt;If the parking lot gets full, you can park on the side of the road, no problem.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Bring headlamps/flashlights, bug repellent, snacks and drinks! (And in summer, be prepared for rain showers.)** &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copied this event from last year...it was great! Lovely views, no cars or lights, just people and a few ATVs. Great view of fireworks in Boston, MA, Hampton Beach, NH, and Nashua NH. Plus assorted private fireworks all around, and town fireworks from here to Boston. Many western towns' fireworks were still going off as we hiked down at night!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lots of fun, short hike! Has kind-of-steep sections, but it's not bad, especially since tree roots and smaller rocks provide natural "steps" along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; We'll hike back down the mountain afterwards pretty much the way we come up.&lt;/em&gt; There are 2 or 3 people attending who have hiked down this trail at night before, and assured me it's very easy to follow. With such a large group, this is the ideal thing to do. &lt;em&gt;I'm also going to cap the attendance at 25.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Linda will still be available to lead some people down the carriage road and drive them back to the parking lot if some want to do that. (However many they can fit in the back of the pickup!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341691355000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335257405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Night Hike up Watatic to watch area FireWorks!</name><id>61888752</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341442800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/61888752/</event_url></item>