<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Harvard Book Store hosts cultural critic and classics scholar DANIEL MENDELSOHN for a discussion of his recent translations of poetry by C.P. Cavafy, both Collected Poems and The Unfinished Poems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No modern poet brought so vividly to life the history and culture of Mediterranean antiquity; no writer dared break, with such taut energy, the early-twentieth-century taboos surrounding homoerotic desire; no poet before or since has so gracefully melded elegy and irony as the Alexandrian Greek poet Constantine Cavafy (1863–1933). Now, after more than a decade of work and study, and with the cooperation of the Cavafy Archive in Athens, Daniel Mendelsohn—a classics scholar who alone among Cavafy’s translators shares the poet’s deep intimacy with the ancient world—is uniquely positioned to give readers full access to Cavafy’s genius. And we hear for the first time the remarkable music of his poetry: the sensuous rhymes, rich assonances, and strong rhythms of the original Greek that have eluded previous translators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;C.P. Cavafy: Collected Poems brings together more than 250 works collected in this volume, comprising all of the Published, Repudiated, and Unpublished poems and covering the vast sweep of Hellenic civilization, from the Trojan War through Cavafy’s own lifetime. C.P. Cavafy: The Unfinished Poems offers a first translation of the drafts of thirty poems Cavafy left among his papers at his death in 1933—some of them masterly, nearly completed verses, others less finished texts, all accompanied by notes and variants that offer tantalizing glimpses of the poet’s sometimes years-long method of rewriting and revision. The two volumes together comprise the definitive English version of the modern poet’s canon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The explanatory essays [Mendelsohn] has attached to almost every poem can contain every bit as much passion and humanity as the poet’s own work. Mendelsohn is such a felicitous interpreter of Cavafy because the poet himself was a kind of scholar: complex allusions to distant figures and events at the margins of Mediterranean history are as essential to his art as his evocations of ardent erotic encounters. And our distance from these places, peoples, and ages makes Cavafy’s achievement all the more impressive: he brings a ‘Political Reformer’ in a Greek colony in 200 B.C., a hero of the Trojan wars, or a young man bathing at Alexandria in 1908 into a palpable and immediate presence.” —Harper’s Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Mendelsohn is a cultural critic whose reviews and essays on literary and cultural subjects appear regularly in numerous publications, including The New Yorker and The New York Review of Books. His previous books include the collection of critical essays How Beautiful It Is and How Easily It Can Be Broken, the memoir The Elusive Embrace, a New York Times Notable Book of the Year and a Los Angeles Times Best Book of the Year, and the international bestseller The Lost: A Search for Six of Six Million, which won the National Book Critics Circle Award, the Prix Médicis, and many other honors. Mr. Mendelsohn is also the recipient of a Guggenheim Fellowship, the National Book Critics Circle Citation for Excellence in Reviewing and the George Jean Nathan Award for Dramatic Criticism. He teaches at Bard College. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271459889000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271188629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mendelsohn on Cavafy at Harvard Book Store</name><id>13172844</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271286000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/13172844/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/d/global_14360269.jpeg</photo_url></item>