<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Mugford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01945</zip><lat>42.505650</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Me &amp; Thee Coffee House</name><city>Marblehead</city><id>11247302</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.851173</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The me&amp;amp;thee coffeehouse hosts the North Shore’s original acoustic music series at the Unitarian Universalist Church of Marblehead. We are located off Rt. 114 at 28 Mugford Street in Marblehead.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meandthee.org/Directions.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;» Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patty Larkin is part of the urban-folk/pop music phenomenon that spun off of the singer/songwriter explosion of the seventies, reinterpreting traditional folk melodies, rock, pop, bossa nova, drawing on anything from Dylan (Bob) to Dylan (Thomas).  A self described “guitar driven songwriter,” Larkin has wound her way through soundscapes of evocative vocals, inventive guitar wizardry and imaginative lyrics.  Her songs run from impressionistic poetry to witty wordplay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pattylarkin.com/bio/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.pattylarkin.com/bio/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets cost $24 approx. YOu have to buy your own ticket at Brown paper tickets website - HURRY AS THEY WILL PROBABLY SELL OUT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/e/262826" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.brownpapertickets.com/e/262826&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please pay me $1 when you get there to help cover Meetup fees. Thank you. I don't usually ask for this, but I'd be grateful if you'd just remember to make this payment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can get there in time, we can meet for an early dinner at the Landing in Marblehead. Park close to the Coffeehouse venue and walk down Front Street to the waterfront to find the restaurant. If you can't make it in time, we will meet you at the Me and Thee (UU Church) at 7. 45 PM. They are usually kind enough to reserve a pew for us for the concert if there are going to be a few of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in foyer OR if you can get there, meet at the Landing Restaurant for pre-concert dinner at 6.15PM</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360382772000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358603429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patty Larkin at the Me and Thee in Marblehead CANCELLED</name><id>100364782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360371600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/100364782/</event_url></item>