<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>**Sunday is the first day of standard time. Set your clocks back one hour before you go to bed Saturday night**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's climb the newest addition to the 52 with a view list, Mt Roberts, which was promoted earlier this year in favor of Mt Wolf. Roberts is 2582' high and the hike has a vertical climb of approx 1900' over 8 miles (4 miles out and back via the Shannon Brook and Roberts Trails).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Given the time of year, traction is required** Microspikes are best. I have some spare equipment but you must clear this with me before the hike. Otherwise I expect all participants to have this essential gear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hike to start at 8 am - carpooling hopefully an option to discuss with those that sign up, Let me know if you have any questions. Andrew B&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a gear list is based on Michael Blair's excellent list (thanks) - and is to be considered the MINIMUM amount of things to bring on this trip. Don't expect someone else will have extras of anything: you need to carry all the stuff you will need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Footwear: Hiking boots or trail shoes. Light traction is mandatory (microspikes strongly recommended, yaktracks or stabilicers will probably suffice).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater - ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain jacket with hood, rain pants, hat, gloves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and at least three quarts of water (electrolyte drink recommended - cut it in half or third with water as they have too much sugar for all-day activity).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Insect repellent. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional Items: Waterproof gaiters. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While I will bring a group first aid kit that contains basic items I am not certified or trained in wilderness first aid. You will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew B</member_name><member_id>4803051</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289350221000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288559410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Roberts (52 with a view) Intermediate Hike</name><id>15288680</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289136600000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15288680/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/0/2/global_18977890.jpeg</photo_url></item>