<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>299 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.343120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 738-1909</phone><name>Panera</name><city>Brookline</city><id>591193</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122190</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll discuss &lt;i&gt;Two Weeks Since my Last Confession&lt;/i&gt; by Kate Genovese from 4 to 4:30. The author, Kate, will join us at 4:30 to answer questions about her novel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description of the book (paperback, $16.19): When Molly O'Brien comes into the world in 1951, she never imagines that her life will turn out the way it does. Born into a wealthy family in which her father is a senator and her mother a devout Catholic, Molly receives a good upbringing and has all the reason in the world to be happy. Yet somehow, at the age of thirty, she is addicted to heroin and hasn't been employed for years. Her father believes that the corrupting influences of society are at fault, while her mother is convinced it's Molly's own depravity that has caused her ruin and her failure to stay in the Catholic Church. Her older brother Sean, however, knows who is really to blame. He holds the family secrets that have caused all of his sister's problems and are leading her down the harrowing road to drug addiction. And ultimately he knows that he and his parents are the only ones who can lead her out. A dramatically written family saga, Two Weeks Since My Last Confession is the story of one woman's survival in the face of serious childhood abuse and addiction. More than this, it is a tale which chronicles the triumph of the human spirit over its enemies - not only external enemies but also the ones we find within ourselves.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll bring the book and a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charis</member_name><member_id>3696786</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264377265000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221048260000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Local author Kate Genovese visits our discussion of her book </name><id>8728417</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225051200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/8728417/</event_url></item>