<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you sometimes wish you could be that person who lights up a room when you walk in?  Do you find yourself admiring other people who seem to have that special magic that endears people to them?  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you've ever wanted to have the kind of personality that people find magnetic and enjoyable to be around, then you're going to love this month's meeting.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;We're going to cover:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;4 big mistakes people make that cause others want to avoid them, and how to easily correct each one of them (I guarantee you're making at least one of these).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A simple technique for remembering people's names.  Learn this technique once, use it forever.  Also, what to do when you forget someone's name, but are too embarrassed to bring it up.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 simple ways to start conversations with people that work almost every time.  I've used hundreds of times in the real world, and they absolutely work.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 simple secrets for keeping a conversation going and getting people to open up to you.  You won't have to worry about awkward silences again once you know these two techniques.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 ways to end a conversation that will leave people feeling good about you.  If you've ever wanted to end a conversation with someone, but were worried about offending or upsetting them, then this is perfect for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;And that's only the first half of the meeting.  During the second half, you'll have an opportunity to practice everything you learned in the lesson.  We'll do fun, interactive exercises and drills to ensure that these concepts and techniques become automatic.  That way they will be there for you in the real world when you really need them.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The meeting is limited to 15 due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings almost always sell out within days, and we end up with a waiting list, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Monday, November 10th available.  The meeting runs from 8pm to 10pm and is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 3 minutes walk from the red line.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that night free, go ahead and RSVP for this meeting right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $10, which helps pay the cost of running this group, classroom rental, and printed materials.  All you need to bring is:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$10 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems.  My cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're in the 1st classroom on left inside the building.  It's easy to find.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1228783799000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227052343000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Skills Meeting - How To Develop Confidence And Charisma</name><id>9188583</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227574800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/9188583/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/b/global_4864315.jpeg</photo_url></item>