<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This is the deadline reminder to submit photos to this contest- it has been updated to Oct 10th. Please see the info below on how to submit. When you come to the judging you will be asked to fill out a form with your info - Please spread the word about the contest! I hope you'll all participate!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Art in the Park Photo Contest!&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the Worcester Cultural Commission and the Worcester Photography Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Worcester Cultural Commission and the Worcester Photography Center are getting together to bring you the “Art in the Park Photo Contest.” There are many events and happenings surrounding this years Art in the Park and we are hoping you‘ll all want to help capture these fun events and then share the images with the Cultural Commission. There are some very impressive pieces in the park this year and having you all show them off with your photographic creativity is a perfect challenge for a photo contest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the contests categories?&lt;br /&gt;The subject matter is the Art Work in Elm Park, but these are the categories to submit your images into for the contest:&lt;br /&gt;·       The Art Itself: Images of the art visibly identified within the context of Elm Park&lt;br /&gt;·       Interaction: Public’s reaction to or interaction with the sculptures&lt;br /&gt;·       Daily Life: Sculpture as a backdrop to daily life in Elm Park&lt;br /&gt;·       The Events:&lt;br /&gt;• Art in the Park Opening Ceremony, August 6th&lt;br /&gt;• ART in the PARKing Lot, August 9th&lt;br /&gt;• Art that Hangs Around, August 13th&lt;br /&gt;• Creative Laundry, August 14th&lt;br /&gt;• Fresh Floral Art, August 15th&lt;br /&gt;Each Category Winner will receive a prize and there will be a Grand Prize awarded for the best overall image.&lt;br /&gt;Each entrant may submit entries in any Category he/she wishes and may submit entries at different times during the entry period, but no entrant may submit in total more than six (6) entries. Images Must be Submitted by Oct 5stth 2009 Midnight&lt;br /&gt;For more information, rules, to learn about the Judges and the prizes: please visit the Worcester Photography Center Web Site at &lt;a href="http://worcesterphotographycenter.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://worcesterphoto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you accept photos shot with a digital camera, or digitally manipulated?&lt;br /&gt;Yes. In fact - We are only accepting digital images to be uploaded to the Meetup Web Site. Digitally manipulated photos are also acceptable, and certainly encouraged. Photographs must be in digital format. Only online entries will be eligible. No print or film submissions will be accepted for entry into this Contest. The photograph need not be taken with a digital camera; scans of negatives, transparencies, or photographic prints are acceptable. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the image specifications?&lt;br /&gt;• Image Size: Image should have a long dimension of at least 1000 pixels and no more than 3000 pixels_&lt;br /&gt;• Save file as (JPG) with maximum quality.&lt;br /&gt;• Color Space: Adobe1998 or sRGB &lt;br /&gt;• File Size: The file should be no more than 8x10 at 300 DPI.&lt;br /&gt;• You MUST label you photo with your name and what category it is being submitted for. Example: DonnaDufault_Events1.jpg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where do I submit my Photos?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/groups/artparkphotocontest09/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.flickr.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You MUST label you photo with your name and what category it is being submitted for. Example: DonnaDufault_Events1.jpg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who are the judges?&lt;br /&gt;To determine the grand Prize and Category Winners and Honorable Mentions, we are employing a panel of 5 judges, all from the Worcester Cultural Arena. The Judging will take place at the Worcester Art Museum on October 18th 2009- 2pm and is open to the Public. All Folks who enter the contest are invited to come see the images judged, hear feed back and comments about their entries, and view all the submissions! Awards will be given at the end of the evening. &lt;br /&gt;They are:&lt;br /&gt;Deb McNamara, Chair Worcester Cultural Commission&lt;br /&gt;Helen Beaumont, Marketing and Business Advisor&lt;br /&gt;Dante Comparetto, Worcester Cultural Commission&lt;br /&gt;Cyrus Lipsitt, Art in the Park Committee Member&lt;br /&gt;Claire Forgues, Local Business Owner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who can enter the Contest?&lt;br /&gt;The Art in the Park Photo Contest is open to all photographers, both students and non-students, amateurs and professionals - anyone that is a member of the Worcester Photography Center. Joining the Worcester Photography Center is free and you can sign up and RSVP at &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/22"&gt;http://photo.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to enter:&lt;br /&gt;Please complete an entry form with the required information, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, and photo caption; and submit along with your photograph.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contest Prizes&lt;br /&gt;The first-place Winner in each Category will each receive a small gift basket containing but not limited to: 2 Passes to the Worcester Art Museum, Awards Certificate, and Photography Swag.&lt;br /&gt;Grand Prize Winner will receive a Photo Gift Basket-  2 Passes to the Worcester Art Museum, Awards Certificate, free photo walk class with Scott Erb, and Photography Swag. (We are still gathering prizes from area businesses…)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What about copyright?&lt;br /&gt;Copyright(s) remain with photographer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By entering this contest you are giving permission to the Cultural Commission to use your images for Publicity of the Art in the Park events. Basically it is a Publicity Release and License in which the entrant warrants that he/she is the owner of the photograph and grants to WCC and its licensees the irrevocable perpetual, nonexclusive license to reproduce, distribute, display, and create derivative works of the entry (along with a name credit) in connection with the Contest and promotion of the Contest and Worcester Cultural Commission without additional compensation.  No prize transfer, assignment, or substitution by winners permitted. If a prize (or part of a prize) is unavailable, the Sponsor, in its discretion, reserves the right to substitute the original prize (or that part of the prize) with an alternative prize to the equal monetary value and/or specification, unless to do so would be prohibited by law. NONCOMPLIANCE OR RETURN OF PRIZE NOTIFICATION AS UNDELIVERABLE, WHETHER BY REGULAR MAIL OR BY EMAIL, MAY RESULT IN DISQUALIFICATION AND SELECTION OF AN ALTERNATE POTENTIAL WINNER. Any of the above can change at anytime!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You to the Park and Take Photos- Submit photos to Flickr Group!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255817040000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250089951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art in the Park Photo Contest- Worcester's Elm Park</name><id>11094717</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255215600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11094717/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/b/global_10161499.jpeg</photo_url></item>