<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>971 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.761684</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Barcelona Wine Bar</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>664545</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742653</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Barcelona Restaurant and Wine Bar is an award-winning Spanish tapas restaurant group located throughout Connecticut from the greater New York region to West Hartford and New Haven. Barcelona was begun in 1995 by Sasa Mahr-Batuz, based on his memories of years of living in Spain and Portugal, and Andy Pforzheimer, based on his 20 years as a chef at world-famous restaurants in France, California and New York.  Beginning with a tiny, 38-seat wine bar they set out to recreate the feel and the look of an evening on the Ramblas.  They worked hard and made no compromises to achieve their aims: sophisticated décor that evoked Milan, SoHo, or Rio de Janeiro. Simple, flavor-filled dishes redolent with olive oil, lemon, smoky paprika. A comprehensive list of wines by the glass from around the world, with an emphasis on the lesser-known regions of Spain and Portugal. They were guided not by any places that existed at the time, but only by what they liked, and the way they liked it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Twelve years later, there are five Barcelonas, and each one is still run the way the original was ? talented chefs with the freedom to create new dishes every day, wines that change whenever something great comes along, and staff that really appreciates your business, and shows it. Barcelona is listed in Zagat?s ?America?s Top Restaurants,? and regularly wins in the Appetizers and Wine categories in Connecticut Magazine?s annual ?Best Of? competition.  The wine list, now run by a full time Wine Director, is a Wine Spectator Award winner, and features 40 different wines by the glass and vintage rarities like Vega Sicilia and Janus. Barcelona runs seasonal wine dinners throughout the year, puts together Food and Wine trips to Spain, and this year helps to host New Haven?s Pilot Pen Invitational tennis tournament.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through all of the growth, we remain dedicated to tasty, simple food, good wine, and friendly people, without the price or fuss of a formal dining experience.  We believe that life should be a party, and we try to be the perfect host.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the "Meet Up" sign on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stuart</member_name><member_id>4565209</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 6596915</member_name><member_id>6596915</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230166572000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>You'll love it because we're a great bunch!</why><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-2183</urlname><id>1179521</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Connecticut Jewish Singles:  35+ Social Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212680674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flamenco Thursday at Barcelona</name><id>8085465</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214517600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-2183/events/8085465/</event_url></item>