<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/calendar/9278546/"&gt;Last Saturday&lt;/a&gt;, six SeaLs including David “Smiley” Montenegro protested Dover P.D.’s pattern of abuse of power. For the first time since David started his campaign, the police did not make an appearance; four people did visit to tell their stories of negative encountered with Dover’s “finest,” many horns were honked, and many thumbs were raised. (Only a very small number of other fingers were raised.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Saturday, it’s back to the primary mission: educating people about Dover P.D.’s pattern of behavior and collecting more stories and contact information. The table will be back—not obstructing traffic, of course. Extra hands are always welcome. It’s this Saturday from 11 am to 1 pm. As before, the intent is to be at the corner of Central and 1st; if you don’t see the big red sign there, look up and down Central from Washington to Broadway, and then check the Dover police station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress warmly. In case of rain or snow, the event will be canceled (note that this is a change from previous events).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/sealpac"&gt;the SEAL PAC site&lt;/a&gt; for more information, or call the SEAL PAC hotline at +1.516.345.1072.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Maden</member_name><member_id>793501</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229357640000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228762210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raise awareness about Dover Police abuse with SEAL PAC</name><id>9302438</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229184000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/9302438/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>