<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>With our membership approaching 1,000 freethinkers, and so much going on in the local and national secular community, it is high time to bring some new energy into the Boston Atheists steering committee, and see if we can't kindle the fires again. If you are a new or recently active due-paying member of the Boston Atheists; and would like to have an active role in the future of our community organization, by planning events, developing social and educational programs, collaborating with allied groups, and the like; and are available for a casual meeting this Sunday, March 4th, at 4 PM in the Porter Square neighborhood, Please let me know by email (zbos, at atheists.org) or phone (617.935.4951). I'll let you know directly where we'll be meeting, and how you can contribute to the agenda. We'll be taking minutes of the meeting, and will be glad to share them with any member who does intend to be involved in the steering committee or one of the other group committees (Service, PR, Mutual Aid, Activism, Membership, and Culture) -- just let me know if you want to be in the loop. Members who were involved in the earlier iterations of the steering committee are more than welcome to attend, of course.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330899569000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330722660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Steering Committee Mtg: Meet-and-Greet to relaunch the Cmte</name><id>54710122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330894800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/54710122/</event_url></item>