<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1211 South Mammoth Rd.</address_2><address_1>The Yard Restaurant</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03109</zip><lat>42.963290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)703-8444</phone><name>Midnight Rodeo Bar</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1140687</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.400250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey y'all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join in on some country-western dancing (the kind you saw in the old John Travolta movie &amp;quot;Urban Cowboy&amp;quot;).  It's alright if you're a beginner because at 7:30, the lessons start.  Usually, 2 or 3 line dances are taught during this 1 hour lesson.  Just the excitement of watch'n the band and skilled dancers is worth the trip!  Plus, it feels like you're at a huge house party...A place where eveyone knows your name.  We will meet at 7:30 to get a table.  Come later if you want.  Check out the details and all the photos on their website (midnightrodeobar.com).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:    Midnight Rodeo Bar at The Yard in Manchester, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:     Saturday, January 30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrance:  From parking lot, you'll see the plexiglass cold-weather canopy.  Enter there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once inside:  Put your coat at the table directly to the right of the wall-mounted TV and join us on the dance floor.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn line and couples dances:   2-step, Waltz, El Paso, Carolina Stroll, 3-Step, 16-Step, Tush Push, Trashy Women, Shadow, 1-Step, Boot-Scoot-&amp;amp;-boogey, Cotton-eyed Joe, etc., etc. (not all in one night!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cover charge $10.00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dance Lessons 7:30 - 8:30pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gale Country band  9:00pm-12:30am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;`Gale County` is New England`s hottest country band. It is comprised of former members of some of the area`s finest acts. Rob and Rick Gale are both former members of the well known band `Gale Force` and have been performing in the area for well over 25 years, with a song repertoire of over 200 songs, many of which are currently being played on your local country stations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since your feet slide on the dance floor somewhat when doing this kind of dance, sneakers won't work too well.  Leather soles or just slippery soles (even if they're slippery sneakers) work best.  I will gladly instruct/lead some of the couples dances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rich&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tall guy with glasses</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266280422000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265419625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live country music and dance - Midnight Rodeo Bar at The Yard in Manchester, NH</name><id>12532503</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266107400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/12532503/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/c/f/global_7601071.jpeg</photo_url></item>