<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1090 Silas Deane Hwy</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06109</zip><lat>41.692345</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Starbucks</name><city>Wethersfield</city><id>426453</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.656250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Serata di Café e Conversazione - In addition to the Italian cultural events, I would like to suggest that those who are so inclined get together on a regular basis simply to practice, improve, or perfect their Italian language skills at whatever level.  My thought is that we meet at a local coffee shop some evening during the week.  That way we do not interfere with the cultural programs that are more likely to be scheduled on a weekend. We could meet every 2 or 3 weeks and maybe alternate locations between north and south (although based upon the residence of members, a location in Bristol may be better).  Let?s see who is interested before fixing a permanent location(s).  To get things started, I have reserved a couple of tables at Starbuck?s in Wethersfield at 7:00 p.m. on Wednesday, November 28 ? 1090 Silas Deane Highway between CVS and Walgreen, easy access from Route 91.  Please RSVP as any more than 10 attendees will necessitate another call to Starbucks.  All levels are welcome, but you will probably need some basic vocabulary to benefit, as the goal would be to keep the conversation in Italian to the maximum extent possible.  However, as long as you can tell us your name, where you live, where you work, etc., in Italian, I think you will benefit from the experience.  There is an Italian expression that is the rough equivalent of the English proverb &amp;quot;practice makes perfect&amp;quot; but is perhaps more accurate - sbagliando s'impara - which if I am not mistaken is more closely translated as &amp;quot;making mistakes one learns.&amp;quot;  It would be nice if a few of those members who are already either advanced or fluent in Italian would attend, as they could help correct some of those mistakes.  I recently joined a couple of Italian language groups in Rhode Island and the meet-ups have been entertaining and instructive.  Perche no?  Gli italiani e le persone chi amano la lingua italiana sono molto simpatici. Spero d?incontrarci il 28.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to contact me directly use jdelnegro@hotmail.com.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Del Negro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lorenzo</member_name><member_id>4408109</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196467731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Amici Italiani</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>italian-452</urlname><id>535327</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>Connecticut's Viva Italia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194716873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Serata di Cafe e Conversazione</name><id>6715882</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196294400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-452/events/6715882/</event_url></item>