<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1074 South Colony Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.431205</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zandri's Stillwood Inn</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>1448657</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.833602</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;UPDATE: GET THERE EARLIE
resaon:
---Al 
this is cathy about the dance tomorrow night.
the person from ctcontacts just called me they are
booked solid for tomorrow nights dance.
if we dont fill two tables tomorrow night by 8 opm we
lose one table. &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; READ THAT
can you put update for the ad for it. be there by 8
pm.. &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;if you show up later, you sit with the rotten potatoes..thats it...

thanks alot. want this to go off with no problems here 

It wont, im going to be there earlie and all the rest of you better be there early too..see ya there...al-r...



Do the Monster Mash..
Scare your dance partner..
Put hungry ANTS down someones pants..and watch em really dance...
Give Goolish Eyes..
Wet Drippy Kisses...
Shake your BOOOOty
Tricks ...ahh no...treats ok..LOL

We will be a small safe group among a large amount of people.
This is an advantage because there is a safety buffer from the mass of the room and all the people that my bug you, i will look for an area that is farthest from the speakers to allow for conversation, (no gorentees, others do the same thing for the same reason. i found earplugs cut the noise but you still can hear voice, its not that loud like those youngins or deaf old folks bars...but you might want to talk to your just met Bride of Frankenstein there..or your Frankenstien..). That will put a new definition to your "better half " especially if made with your old parts..LOL


OK READ THIS:
I  ALWAYS put  two,  MEETUP    signs on the table in easy view..they are balck and white from the laser printer...people have complaind they dont see them...why i dont know at all ???? (well maybe quit looking at the Booty..look for the sighns first) ...so dont be a stupid rotting butt and complaine you cant find us..if you do..go sit with the De-Composers...in-stead, strut around and look at the tables individually...better smile now...scowlers sit with the howlers...


I will get there about 7:30 as best as i can.


Anyway...see people that dress up specificaly on this night in costumes to look like people that go to the Glastonbury Gallery as regulars..
(actually the Gallery isnt that bad..but this is fright night..so anything goes even pick on whatever but enjoy the costumes and new looks)

YOU DONT HaVE TO WEAR A COSTUME&gt;&gt; IM NOT..im gonna show off my finely formed firm ass-ettes as they are without the Flame-Boyant Em-bullish-ment..LOL

The Parents Without Partners Group will also be there.
Who Knows, maybe some New Haven Meetup Group too.

Directions to ZANDRI'S STILLWOOD INN 

For GPS or Mapquest directions from your specific area use:

1074 S. Colony  Rd., (Rte. 5), Wallingford, CT

 

From I-91 N or S:  Exit 13. Right at light at end of ramp (north) onto S. Colony Rd. (Rte. 5).  Stillwood Inn is 800 ft. on right, just past Vinny"s Garden Center. 

 

From Merritt Pkwy Northbound:  Exit 63. Turn right off exit onto Rte. 22 E.  Left at 2nd light onto Washington Ave. (Rte. 5N). Follow for 3 miles.  Stillwood Inn is on right, just past Vinny?s Garden Center.
1074 S. Colony Rd. (Route 5), WALLINGFORD, CT
Huge Ballroom Accommodates 400+ Singles

  Connecticut"s Largest Dance Floor
Dancing to DJ":s Top 40/Soft Rock

Dinner Buffet 8-9:30 , Coffee/Dessert at 11:30.. Go Home at about 12"30

Dress to Impress/No Jeans (ahhh and i love tight jeans on ladies, oh well..oh Costume dress up like a Ho..that might work LOL) , $20 Admission
Fri., Oct. 26   8 pm.. 

Special Note;
Sorry, i cant reserve seating for "maybe" people. IF YOU ARE A MAYBE  you get to sit with the  POLTER GHOSTS...clank you chain, move chairs around, bang on the pots and pans..we dont care..because you are really not there...</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193616618000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192116314000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shake the BOOOty HowL o Wine Singles Dance At The Zandri Stillwood Inn</name><id>6530212</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193443200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6530212/</event_url></item>