<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>196 Crown Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305317</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kelly House Apartments</name><city>New Haven</city><id>6073752</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928070</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dave's moving out of his place and holding one last Bash on St. Patricks Parade Day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details below from Dave: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

" So what's better than one party you ask?? Simple answer...TWO PARTIES!! Yup, this years annual saint patricks day parade party will be a combo moving out party as well. So come on by and wipe out any food and booze&amp;nbsp;I have&amp;nbsp;left. All are welcome, bring friends. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

What can you expect? A good time and plenty of toasts made possible from a case of the cheapest scotch known to man that MUST BE FINISHED before the day is done. Oh, and most important of all on parade day...a working bathroom with no line! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

What can you not expect? Uhhh, well, furniture since I've pretty much sold my entire life away on craigslist this week...but I can probably still scrounge up a folding chair or two. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Remember this sunday is daylight savings so set your clock! Also if you're driving into new haven check for street closings. Anyone is welcome who just wants to stay over the night before or crash the night of (again, see citation about lack of furniture). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For those that have been here before you know the drill. For those who haven't it's the kelly house apartments, corner of temple and crown, entrance on temple behind bus stop and next to kellys cobbler. Unit 402 on 4th floor (code 103 on door buzzer for entrance). Make sure you bring my phone number if you have trouble. 203-499-7777 "&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Front door Buzzer Code 103 - Apartment 402, or Call Dave if you have problems: 203-499-7777</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>dave</member_name><member_id>12623808</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331562209000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331166308000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>St. Patricks Parade and Moving Out Party at Dave's</name><id>55429212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331474400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/55429212/</event_url></item>