<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ladies and Gentlemen,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After several false starts, we really are going to have the first Boston-area Startup Marketing Group meeting on June 16th in sunny, historic Waltham MA. And unlike the previous shots at having meetings, we actually have a venue this time! Depending on the turnout we have two options...if there are 25 people coming we can have the meetup at my office here at Aprigo world headquarters at 460 Totten Pond Road. If we have an even better turnout, we have a sponsor that is willing to hook us up with a bigger space. Depending on the turnout, I'll send venue information when the date approaches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6:30-7:00- Networking-&lt;/b&gt; Come on in, introduce yourself to other startup marketers, trade business cards, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;7:00-7:25- Getting Your Startup Noticed Online&lt;/b&gt;- Nathan Burke (the guy writing this who has now switched to the third person) will give a presentation on getting your startup noticed online. This will be a blend of his Podcamp Boston presentation on &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://blogstring.com/2008/07/20/podcamp-3-boston-panel-discovery-how-people-find-blogs-video-and-podcasts-they-love-what-that-means-to-you/" target="_blank"&gt;Discovery: How People Find Blogs, Video and Podcasts They Love &amp;amp; What That Means To You&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; and his posts on MarketingStartups.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;7:30-8:30- Open Forum&lt;/b&gt;- Hey, it's our first meeting, so let's talk about the issues you're facing as a startup marketer and how we can help as a group. We can talk about future meeting topics, future speakers, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, I will send out more details when the date approaches. If you have any questions, feel free to email me at nathan at aprigo dot com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nathan Burke</member_name><member_id>1770271</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248305053000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Sustainability Partners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>green-business-allies</urlname><id>1366456</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Green Business Allies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243001531000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The First Boston Area Startup Marketing Group Meeting</name><id>10470260</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245191400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/green-business-allies/events/10470260/</event_url></item>