<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>140 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.177994</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 429 1500</phone><name>The Meadows</name><city>Holliston</city><id>959576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.442941</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Members,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since our sugested December meetup falls right smack in the middle of the busiest week for The Meadows, I am going to skip December and schedule our next meet for January 8th, from 2-4 pm, at the Meadows.&amp;nbsp; In the meanwhile, if there is another warm day forecast for a Sunday, I might have a short notice &amp;nbsp;outdoor meet in Newton at the beautiful conservation area that we met in September.&amp;nbsp; I will do this whenever I can because I know so many of you have requested outdoor meets.&amp;nbsp; But in the meanwhile, we will continue meeting at the Meadows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I am reinstating the no-charge policy we had a year ago since so many of us have been hit hard by the problems of the US economy.&amp;nbsp; But I will continue to ask everyone who can do so to bring a folding chair to the meetups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I apologize for not attending this past Sunday's meetup.&amp;nbsp; I am experiencing back spasms from having worked on moving 10 rooms worth of furniture, possessions etc. a couple of weeks ago, with the help of friends.&amp;nbsp; I guess I overdid it, thinking that i am still 25 years old, which is not true!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Small dog hugs,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask someone where I am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326054159000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321928285000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BOSTON MALTESE &amp; TINY DOG MEET SUNDAY Jan. 8th, Sunday, 2-4pm</name><id>42001262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326049200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/42001262/</event_url></item>