<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Sherman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.390476</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Danehy Park</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>359085</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132736</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Danehy new field for us (aside from occasional emergency use) so here are some detailed directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First a &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=&amp;amp;daddr=42.38816,-71.134779&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;mra=mi&amp;amp;mrsp=0&amp;amp;sz=18&amp;amp;sll=42.38894,-71.135155&amp;amp;sspn=0.003938,0.007746&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=18" target="_blank"&gt;map.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The map centers around the baseball fields, where we will likely meet up. We haven't really used these fields before, so we might be playing on a different part of the park, so keep your eyes peeled for flying frisbees on other parts of the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are driving, the easiest place to park is probably in Fresh Pond Mall, which is off to the west of the park or in the Danehy lots behind the mall. There is also a small parking lot on the Sherman Street side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By T:&lt;br /&gt;Red Line to Alewife stop. First walk across Rt 2 (a huge road), then walk east on Rt 2 uphill over a bridge to Fresh Pond Shopping Center. Go to the left of the Shopping Center buildings and to the right of the Fresh Pond Cinema (behind stores) and out the gate. Follow the path into the park. The baseball fields are up the hill and to the right of the path.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PROTIP: If you are taking the T, get off the train and go up the exit that is NOT the one you go up for Russell Field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cleats are ALLOWED on Danehy Field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the game plan:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;1:00 - Toss the disc around, meet folks, be merry &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;1:15 - Overview of the rules, safety, etc - then divide into teams&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;1:30- Play!!!!!! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif' border='0' alt='love struck' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;3:00 - Conclude the meetup with snacks and socializing &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what we humbly ask of you (works great as a checklist): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Arrive on time to be guaranteed a spot in a game (RSVP is optional - but helpful for others who want to know if people they played with in a previous game are going to be there &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring &lt;b&gt;LOTS OF WATER&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you are a regular, please consider bringing a buck for the Frisbee Fund&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, we will supply the frisbees, cones, lanyards, first aid supplies (hopefully will never be used) and our pretty smiles. As we periodically mention, all these supplies are paid out-of-pocket by your loving Frisbee organizers and everyone has been so generous with their donations to-date. Thank you and let's keep the dream alive!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oliver, Cara, and Cameron&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find the Frisbees! Probably by the baseball fields.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Oliver K</member_name><member_id>6144635</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cara</member_name><member_id>7321267</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cameron</member_name><member_id>10452415</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271784034000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271266679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Day-time Ultimate @ Danehy Field</name><id>13182045</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271610000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/13182045/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/1/global_8447601.jpeg</photo_url></item>