<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3710 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Java Jo's</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>189386</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110001</lon></venue><fee><label>Suggested donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking to hang out and knit with like-minded progressives in Boston? Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns over a little &amp;quot;knit one, purl one&amp;quot;? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in and folks who can teach you how to &amp;quot;cast off&amp;quot;? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions AND finishing a scarf?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Socializing for Justice at Java Jo's for Knitting for Justice!  (Java Jo's is directly across from the Forest Hills T stop on the Orange line)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program. No speaker. &lt;br /&gt;Just bring your knitting projects and enjoy yourself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NEW TO KNITTING?&lt;br /&gt;There will be SoJusters on hand to teach.  So if you are new to knitting, don't be intimidated.  It's never too late to learn!  If you've got extra yarn lying around that you feel like sharing, be sure to bring it.  As well as a little cash for Java Jo's yummy snacks and hot drinks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP yes, maybe or no.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Socializing for Justice (SoJust) is for feminists, people working against racism, queer pioneers, genderbenders, environmental agitators, class activists, lefty artists and all people across Greater Boston working for justice in our neighborhoods, in our nation and beyond. But it's not work! Instead, we're building a strong cross-issue network through fun social events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the Socializing for Justice Meetup Board and you'll be able to view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, print &amp;amp; on-line resources - and you'll be able to suggest/coordinate future SoJust events like this one!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1163527735000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1161787182000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Knitting for Justice</name><id>5221797</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1163354400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5221797/</event_url></item>