<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>See the beautiful pink, white &amp;amp; fuchsia flowers bursting in full bloom for more than a mile while the spectacular views for 80 miles takes your breath away!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our group will meet on the porch of P.N.V.C. at 8:45 and hit the Tuckerman Ravine Trail at 9am. We'll take the gentle summer route of Lion Head to the Alpine Garden Trail. These alpine flowers, such as diapensia, rosebay, and azalea, usually seen in Labrador, are found on the Alpine Garden Trail and many of the higher elevations in the Whites. The Nelson Crag Trail will be our next route to summit the 6288' Mt Washington, far easier to reach than the numbers indicate with nice footing on these trails.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The round trip is 8.9 miles with 4050' of elevation in a book time of 7.5 hours not including stops for the fantastic views, photo opportunities, the Cog R.R., the Tip Top House, a gift shop, rest rooms, museum, post office, a ton of tourists, and a stop in the cafeteria for lunch! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Directions from the South: &lt;br /&gt;The most direct &amp;amp; quickest route is 1-93 (or take Rte 95 to Rte 16), take exit 23. Turn right on to Rte 104 east to Rte 25 to Rte 16 north. Pinkham Notch Visitors Center, which provides food, lodging, and showers to the public, is 20 miles north of Conway and .8 mi north of Glen Ellis Falls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is &amp;quot;weather permitting&amp;quot;. Organizers will change or postpone this hike in case of weather advisories. We welcome expereinced hikers to help with trail support.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the Disclaimer and things you must know. Read What to wear on a hike and pack water and food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If time allows, we can stop after the hike just south of the trailhead for supper/drinks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Gold Honda CRV  ph. 603-477-5116. Carpool from Claremont, NH to trailhead- call if you want to share a ride</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212502428000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205874411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Washington &amp; the Beautiful Alpine Gardens! 6/1</name><id>7558207</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212324300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7558207/</event_url></item>