<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Likely easy, but unknown distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration:&lt;/strong&gt; This hike, including breaks, &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; be 3 hours or more...it depends...please see description.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: I do not work this day, so I can change the time if needed. Please make comments below...I don't check my email all the time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Below: Ridges around Quabbin Reservoir were created by glaciers, which scarred this rock on the trail from Enfield Overlook to Hank's Meadow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/3/6/event_100752342.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HIKE DESCRIPTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll explore a trail from the rotary which may go somewhere; possibly a hidden ridge beyond the woods (in the direction of the boat cove), which supposedly has a reservoir view. Depending how that works and how long it is, we may repeat the Enfield Overlook-to-Hank's Meadow hike (the beautiful trail that follows the shore all the way).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enough water for several hours. It will be warm and sunny this weekend!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food/snacks. We'll picnic maybe at Enfield Overlook, maybe at Hank's Meadow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dress cool...it will be warm...but I strongly recommend long slacks because Quabbin has a high deer tick population.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Deep-woods" type (more DEET) insect repellant, or repellant with Pemethrin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera highly recommended!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quabbin Reservoir Rules:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Carry-in, carry-out." Take your trash with you when you go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals. Quabbin Reservoir is a public drinking water supply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove things from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Quabbin Map calls the park road "Administration Road" but Google maps calls it "Old Ware-Enfield Rd."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From East (Worcester):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take Route 9 West (about 45 minutes from the Worcester/Leicester line). You will pass through Spencer, the Brookfields and Ware. After downtown Ware, the road goes up and down two long, steep hills with "climbing lanes." At the bottom of the 2nd hill, look for a pull-off with wood gate on the right. Go past that. After a curve in the road, the &lt;strong&gt;East Entrance&lt;/strong&gt; is on your &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt;. Drive through the park until you see parking spots in front of a scenic overlook on your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From West (Amherst/Springfield):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take Route 9 East through Amherst and Belchertown. The West Entrance is about 2 miles after the intersection of Routes 202 and 9. Pass the West Entrance and take the Middle one a couple miles further...you &lt;strong&gt;cannot&lt;/strong&gt; get to the main park road from the West Entrance! Drive until you have gone through a rotary, and Enfield Overlook will be downhill on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From South of Route 9:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take the nearest route North to Route 9, then follow directions for East or West, above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Mass (Fitchburg/Leominster):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take Route 31 south to 56 north to 122 north. Then take 32A south to Route 9 west. Follow directions as at the top from Ware, MA onward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Western Mass:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take Route 2 to 202 south to Route 9 east. Follow directions as from Amherst, above.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337800757000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337488732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exploratory hike (RESCHEDULED): Meet at Enfield Overlook</name><id>65536142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337781600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/65536142/</event_url></item>