<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-973-5200</phone><name>New England Aquarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1260294</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Taste of the North End (&lt;a href="http://www.tasteofthenorthend.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tasteofthe...&lt;/a&gt;) will give us the chance to sample food from about 25 different restaurants and cafes. And 6 wine distributors will make sure we have something to wash it down with. We'll gather from 6:45-7:00 just outside the entrance to the Aquarium and enter at 7:00. If you arrive late, you should be able to find us in the food lines. We'll sample from the food and wine vendors inside the Aquarium, while also being able to view exhibits such as the penguins. At about 9:00, we'll head for the tent, set up in back of the Aquarium. That large tent will be ringed with desserts, coffees and liqueurs. Meanwhile, a live band will be playing for our listening and dancing pleasure until about midnight. The Aquarium is located on the harbor, just around the corner from the Aquarium subway station. The tickets are all inclusive and cost $99. The price is comparable to other Taste Of's, which don't have the after-party, and can be charged at the website above. Tickets will probably be available at the Aquarium on the night of the event, but I can't guarantee it. All proceeds will go to North End non-profits, headed by the North End Community Health Center. It will be a great time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: Please access our 'About' tab for further event guidelines.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be standing to the right of the check-in tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim S.</member_name><member_id>4216983</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274120617000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM</urlname><id>1397251</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>North End Eating Meetup (NEEM)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272659902000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Aquarium-Taste of the North End</name><id>13343238</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273878000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM/events/13343238/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/7/a/global_7834474.jpeg</photo_url></item>