<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grab our seats!&lt;/strong&gt; 6:45pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Showtime:&lt;/strong&gt; 7pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I strongly suggest getting your ticket early. Theaters are usually crowded on holidays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think 7pm is the best showtime; plenty of time to drive there, but not stay out too late. However, if many comment (soon) that you'd prefer a later showing, there is a 7:30 as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from the North:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take I-190 south to Exit 3. At the end of the ramp, turn left onto West Mountain Street. Go downhill and turn right onto Brooks Street at the light. If you pass Stop &amp;amp; Shop Supermarket, you went too far. On Brooks St, turn right into the huge parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from the South:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take I-290 east to I-190 North. Immediately get off at Exit 1. Continue straight on West Boylston Street for 2 miles, through several lights and past Quinsigamond Community College. A little ways after Wendy's, turn left at the light onto West Mountain Street. Pass Stop &amp;amp; Shop Supermarket. There's a couple lights close together. Turn left at the 2nd light onto Brooks Street. (If you can't see the street sign, you can see the cinemas up the road.) On Brooks St, turn right into the huge parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby! We'll seat ourselves @ 6:45pm</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324954857000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324440560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sherlock Holmes: Game of Shadows @ Showcase North</name><id>45094682</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324856700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/45094682/</event_url></item>