<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_2><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 141</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1346807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091419</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Please Note - to confirm your attendance at this event, you must register at the MIT Enterprise Forum of Cambridge website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Underpinnings for the Internet of Things&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; insights, innovation and industry consolidation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Is it possible &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;to achieve comprehensive visibility&amp;nbsp;...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;... of all of the things that matter to you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;RFID tags are affordable, BUT&amp;nbsp;how about readers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not just about tags! It&amp;rsquo;s about the tag-to-reader interaction, and then how you manage and exploit the data being collected.&amp;nbsp;The decisions you make&amp;nbsp;in architecting&amp;nbsp;your reader&amp;nbsp;infrastructure has profound implications in meeting performance requirements and&amp;nbsp;the cost of implementing visibility solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Years ago we heard about self-healing readers, software radios and much more. In RFID today there are a mind boggling array of choices widely varying in price, performance, packaging and the fit in meeting customer requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The days of the simple reader appliance for portal entry are long gone. Instead there are embedded readers for printers, handhelds, pickup trucks&amp;nbsp;and much more. New to the scene are wide area reader solutions that&amp;nbsp;promise to&amp;nbsp;provide a&amp;nbsp;disruptive leap forward&amp;nbsp;to end users, greatly broadening the&amp;nbsp;visibility footprint for battery less RFID solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve recently hit an inflection point of dramatically greater adoption of passive RFID solutions for retail apparel, asset management and more. How do we effectively scale these solutions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recent M&amp;amp;A activity&lt;/strong&gt; - Just last year two of the companies presenting at this event were involved in significant acquisitions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thingmagic.com/press-room/27-press-releases/318-trimbleacquiresthingmagicrfidtechnology-%20class=latestnews"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trimble Acquires ThingMagic RFID Technology &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.odinrfid.com/news/97-odin-rfid-acquires-reva-systems"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ODIN Acquires Reva Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RFID enabled Global Monitoring System from Universal Postal Union (UN agency)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;xobject width="470" height="264"&gt;
&lt;/xobject&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;Please join us!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MODERATOR: Tom Coyle, AVERY DENNISON&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vice President of&amp;nbsp;Global Market Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPEAKERS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joe Leone, SAIC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mr. Leone has 26 years&amp;nbsp;of detailed&amp;nbsp;system design, development and integration experience, including &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;nearly two decades designing and implementing RFID solutions for DoD and Fortune &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;500&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; companies, including &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wal*Mart, &lt;span&gt;Target&lt;/span&gt;, Coca-Cola, Delta Airlines, &lt;span&gt;Hasbro&lt;/span&gt;, Boeing Corp, Verizon, GSA, DLA, TRANSCOM, the U.S. DoD PMJAIT, and many, many others&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;He has&amp;nbsp;led&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; and managed organizations from Corporate Technology&amp;nbsp;and Direction to &lt;span&gt;Engineering&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span&gt;Professional Services&lt;/span&gt; for RFID Global Solution Inc, &lt;span&gt;Savi Technology&lt;/span&gt;, Matrics Inc, &lt;span&gt;Symbol Technologies&lt;/span&gt;, and SAIC.&amp;nbsp; His scope of responsibilities has spanned driving products and solutions as Chief Technology Officer, Project and Personnel Management, Software Development, System Engineering and product requirements development. He Joe has&amp;nbsp;five patents (pending) under his name.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Pattabhiraman Krishna, ODIN Technologies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.odinrfid.com/images/Leadership/pkrishna_bw.png" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Krishna joins the leadership team of ODIN through the acquisition of Reva Systems where he was a founding team member. During his tenure at Reva, he acted as the chief architect, subject matter expert, and made key contributions to the development of Reva&amp;rsquo;s award-winning products. As the head of solutions and technology group, he aligned Reva&amp;rsquo;s technology and product strategy with the needs and requirements of global customers planning to deploy RFID and RTLS solutions. He led the solution engineering team and managed solutions development teams in China and US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is the editor of Low Level Reader Protocol (LLRP), a global standard for interfacing with RFID readers. He brings over 15 years of experience in the computer networking field having led architecture and design teams at both emerging and established companies including Coriolis Networks and Digital Equipment Corporation. He has published over 20 papers, given several talks and taught courses, and holds 15 patents, with several more pending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Krishna&amp;rsquo;s achievements include the GS1/EPCglobal&amp;rsquo;s Software Action Group Person of the Year award in 2007 for his significant contributions to worldwide RFID standards development. Dr. Krishna holds a Ph.D. in Computer Science from Texas A&amp;amp;M University and a Bachelor of Technology (Honors) from National Institute of Technology, Rourkela, India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ravi Pappu, VP Advanced Development Group (ADG), Founder, ThingMagic &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.thingmagic.com/images/ravi.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Ravi currently runs the Advanced Development Group, which is tasked with developing cutting-edge systems based on our portfolio of RFID products and solving challenging RFID system optimization problems for our customers. Most recently, he led the design and implementation of the Tool Link system in collaboration with Ford Motor Company and DeWalt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He received his Ph.D. from MIT for the invention of physical one-way functions. While at MIT, he co-created the first dynamic holographic video system with haptic interaction. He has published 25 papers, including a recent one titled "RFID Privacy Without Killing", and is a named inventor on 12 US and international patents. Ravi has been honored as one of Technology Review's top 100 innovators under the age of 35. He received the Carl T. Humphrey Memorial Award for Contributions to the Engineering Profession from Villanova University and was named a Fellow of the World Technology Network in 2006.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ravi co-conceived and implemented Asha For Education's "Work an Hour For Education" campaign in 1998. This event, now held annually, has raised approximately $1M for education in India. He is also one of the founders of Design That Matters, a non-profit that harnesses university students to solve challenging technical problems in the developing world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Juan Pons, Former General Manager, AIDA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/4/b/6/highres_21102166.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Started and grow AIDA Center, an RFID system integrator, becoming a high-growth technology start-up, with a leading global position in the RFID industry. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Defined and managed the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy, maximizing its market value and revenue in the mid and long term, generating a high-value IP portfolio, fostering the company culture needed to reach the strategic goals, and establishing and managing the relationship with the stakeholders. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Raised $1,500,000 from VCs and strategic partners, and awarded and successfully executed one of the largest RFID projects in the world, with presence in more than 45 countries, for the Universal Postal Union (UPU), a department of the United Nations (UN)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;, coordinating worldwide postal services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience creating significant grow in technology based large corporations like the &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;European Aeronautic &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Defence and Space &lt;/span&gt;(EADS) where as project manager lead and managed talented competitive and innovative cross-functional teams, in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Soil Moisture and Ocean Salinity Satellite (SMOS) an European Space Agency (ESA) project, which objectives are to provide global observations of two crucial variables for modelling the weather and climate, Soil Moisture and Ocean Salinity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ning An</member_name><member_id>10728354</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298993317000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294682819000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Global Underpinnings for the Internet of Things</name><id>15994683</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298934000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/15994683/</event_url></item>