<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Glastonbury Boulevard</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06033</zip><lat>41.721841</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 659-9300</phone><name>ANGELICO'S ON THE BOULEVARD   </name><city>Glastonbury </city><id>1227594</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.616748</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>MARK YOUR SOCIAL CALENDAR; UPDATE YOUR BLACKBERRY, IPHONE, AND CALENDER SECTION WITH THE DATE BELOW.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ANOTHER SPECTACULAR HAPPY HOUR   WITH                                   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE IRA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;         APRIL FOOL’S DAY HAPPY HOUR EVENT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN:  April 1 2010, (When else would it be?)  Thursday. 5:00P.M. &lt;br /&gt;WHERE:  ANGELICO'S ON THE BOULEVARD   40 Glastonbury Boulevard&lt;br /&gt;Glastonbury, CT 06033.  &lt;a href="http://angelicosotb.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://angelicosotb.c...&lt;/a&gt; (860) 659-9300.    &lt;br /&gt;(Very easy to find, so please do not panic) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                               DETAILS/SMALL PRINT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How should I describe Angelico’s on the Boulevard?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There words: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pairing global cuisine with a uniquely elegant dining atmosphere. Our food is savory, approachable and made with only the finest and freshest ingredients including high-quality meats, seafood and vegetables. Classic menu favorites include roast prime rib of beef, steak frites, bouillabaisse, and cassoulet as well as an outstanding wine list with an ever-changing international selection. Stop by and experience our uniquely designed menu, exquisite food, and polished service in a warm and intimate setting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My Words:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AWESOME, FRIENDLY, FUNKY, GREAT FOOD AND AND MOUTHWATERING COCKTAILS. HAPPY HOUR SPECIALS ROCK THE HOUSE!!!!  (And it is not EXPENSIVE)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL IMPORTANT DRINK SPECIALS&lt;br /&gt;There is always a glass of red wine and a glass of white wine for $5, a special martini for $7 and a draft beer for $3.  Its TBD every week (starting Monday) so I do not have what they will be but it will be posted on the chalk board in the bar for everyone to see.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;ALL IMPORTANT HAPPY HOUR FOOD BAR SPECIALS:&lt;br /&gt;(How very Yummy and Devine for sure) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buffalo Chicken Dip  Chicken, Jack cheese, ranch sauce &amp;amp; chips  - $3 &lt;br /&gt;Clams Fire roasted barbeque clams or  raw on half shell with cocktail sauce - $1 ea &lt;br /&gt;Brochette Duet  Tomato, basil, goat cheese &amp;amp; Broccoli rabe, chorizo, garlic &amp;amp; gorgonzola  - $3 &lt;br /&gt;Quesadilla Chicken Quesadilla with sour cream jalapeño - $3   &lt;br /&gt;Pesto Tart Pesto, oven roasted tomatoes, &amp;amp; fresh mozzarella - $3 &lt;br /&gt;Mussels Mussels in sake ginger, garlic, &amp;amp; scallions - $3 &lt;br /&gt;Calamari Calamari, barbeque sauce, avocado aioli - $3 &lt;br /&gt;Tempura Vegetables  - $3 &lt;br /&gt;Roasted Poblano Pepper Stuffed with creamy polenta  - $3 &lt;br /&gt;Sweet Potato Fries  - $3 &lt;br /&gt;French Fries  - $2 &lt;br /&gt;Home Made Kettle Chips  - $3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Above Specials are till 7:00PM. We will have our own area in the Funky Bar Reserved for The Ira’s Singles Group.  We can stay as late as we want!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, personal introductions to all, name tags, and a nice warm and inviting venue for an easy way to meet new people, and to come alone, but, not feel alone!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;R.S.V.P:  Please let me know if you are joining on or before Wednesday, March 31 9: 00 P.M. so I may keep the Restaurant informed how many Happy Hour Playful folks are joining. If you say yes, please do come, if you change your mind, please let me know. This is only fair to me and the Restaurant. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;R.S.V.P:  Mistrchrming@aol.com. Subject Line, April fool’s Happy Hour. Questions:  Ira- 860-604-5792. (A $200.00 suggested donation- April Fools!!  (2.00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WANT TO SEE PICS OF PREVIOUS HAPPY HOURS?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click and Paste: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/photos/825014/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;  want to see more?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/photos/861418/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT IS THE ORIGIN OF APRILS FOOLS?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most popular theory about the origin of April fool’s Day involves the French calendar reform of the sixteenth century. &lt;br /&gt;The theory goes like this: In 1564 France reformed its calendar, moving the start of the year from the end of March to January 1. Those who failed to keep up with the change, who stubbornly clung to the old calendar system and continued to celebrate the New Year during the week that fell between March 25th and April 1st, had jokes played on them. Pranksters would surreptitiously stick paper fish to their backs. The victims of this prank were thus called Poisson d’Avril, &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Large Group of Singles Having Fun. Signs  will be posted . </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270776787000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267733615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira- April Fool's Day Happy Hour Event. April 1. NEW LOCATION </name><id>12784633</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270155600000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/12784633/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/f/global_13620239.jpeg</photo_url></item>