<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>notloB Concerts’ acoustic folk/roots/Celtic/blues/bluegrass events are 100% volunteer run and not for profit.  After production expenses, all patron donations go to the artists. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joy Kills Sorrow&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.joykillssorrow.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.joykillsso...&lt;/a&gt;, www.myspace.com/joykillssorrowmusic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emma Beaton - vocals&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Jolliff - mandolin&lt;br /&gt;Matt Arcara - guitar&lt;br /&gt;Wes Corbett - banjo &lt;br /&gt;Bridget Kearney - bass&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joy Kills Sorrow is a prodigiously tasteful pop-grass ensemble emerging from the bubbling frenzy of young folk talent in Boston, MA. The five band members--each already respected practitioners on their instruments--share a deep knowledge and respect for the bluegrass tradition and have virtuosity to spare, but as an ensemble hold above all else a commitment to playing great songs well, and forging a new brand of folk music at once innovative and beautiful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JKS was formed in 2005 and released their self-titled debut in 2007, which prompted Sing Out to call the band &amp;quot;'poster children' for the burgeoning Americana format.&amp;quot; Also in 2007 JKS won first prize in The Podunk Bluegrass Festival Band Contest, and was invited to perform on the festival's main stage the following year. JKS has performed at theaters, listening rooms and festivals from coast to coast and has been featured on nationally syndicated radio shows. Since their inception, the band has continued to evolve and change. Their newest and freshest line-up is proud to be working on an increasingly polished sound and lots of new material composed by the band members. The band is excited to begin touring and will head to the studio this winter to record their follow up release.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members of Joy Kills Sorrow include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Arcara (guitar) - 2006 winner of Winfield's National Flat-picking Contest;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emma Beaton (vocals) - 2008 winner of the Canadian Folk Music Awards' Young Performer of the Year;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wes Corbett (banjo) - has toured with The Bee Eaters, Crooked Still and The Biscuit Burners;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Jolliff (mandolin) - grew up performing with his father, renowned banjo player Bill Jolliff and also has shared the stage with David Grisman and Mike Marshall;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bridget Kearney (bass) - 2006 Grand Prize Winner in The John Lennon Songwriting Contest, a graduate of The New England Conservatory and accomplished freelance bassist in bluegrass, folk, rock and jazz.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Boys&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/bostonboysmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric Robertson - mandolin&lt;br /&gt;Nate Leath - fiddle&lt;br /&gt;Stash Wyslouch - guitar&lt;br /&gt;Sam Grisman - bass&lt;br /&gt;Nick Falk - drums&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Boys is a new band of musicians emerging from the hotbed of talented young players in the hip Boston music scene.  Featuring Eric Robertson, Nate Leath, Sam Grisman, Stash Wyslouch, and Nick Falk, all band members are either students at or Alumni of the prestigious Berklee School of Music. The Boston Boys sound is contemporary roots rock, blending reverence for the Beatles and the energy of the Avett Brothers with hints of Appalachian string band music. Be on the lookout for the release of Eric Robertson's debut album, &amp;quot;I'm at Home&amp;quot;, and stay tuned to find out where you can see the Boston Boys live!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner and a show!  Eat dinner at Jade Garden Chinese Restaurant, 1360 Massachusetts Ave. (down Park, just around the Mass Ave corner to the left).   Call ahead for reservations ~ 781-648-8882 ~ then present either your ticket (purchased at the Music Emporium) or printed email reservation receipt and get 10% your party’s food tab.  Details at the website, then click on Restaurants near the venue &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And desert!  Members of the Park Avenue Congregational Church will be baking Saturday afternoon and selling their whole wares to take home and slices to consume during these concerts (as well as coffee, tea, water, etc.).  So save room for desert!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information about the concert series can be found at the notloB website:  &lt;a href="http://notlobmusic.googlepages.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://notlobmusic.go...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mailing list &amp;amp; street team: &lt;a href="http://www.reverbnation.com/notlob" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.reverbnati...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARTIST WEBSITES:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.joykillssorrow.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.joykillsso...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.myspace.com/joykillssorrowmusic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/bostonboysmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION / PARKING / ACCESS: &lt;a href="http://notlobmusic.googlepages.com/directions" target="_blank"&gt;http://notlobmusic.go...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested minimum donation is $15.00 at the door &amp;amp; $10 for seniors and students with ID.   Regular patron admission is $12.50 if a reservation emailed to notlobreservations (at) concast.net is made at least 24 hours prior to the concert.  Advance tickets are available at Music Emporium, located at 165 Massachusetts Ave., Lexington, MA 02420.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask any volunteer.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242514711000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240411953000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joy Kills Sorrow &amp; The Boston Boys</name><id>10242228</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241913600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/10242228/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/a/global_8287834.jpeg</photo_url></item>