<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Yes another social event is back for its pleasant atmosphere of talking, excersizing, and enjoying a mixture of snacks and beverages while sitting atop the mountains and watching the sun as it is setting.. &lt;br /&gt;You can bring what you want, i like bringing cheeze and a bottle of white sinfidel (Castro's Favourite Brand) and other snacks to share. &lt;br /&gt;Those who dont drink can bring sparkling anything..&lt;br /&gt;Its not a getting drunk party..although its either the wine, people, or place that makes it pleasant &lt;br /&gt;Ok enough of the subliminal enticement to get you to a nice location.. &lt;br /&gt;It is a relatively short walk of light hiking to the top of the little hill... &lt;br /&gt;Im not going to tell you what your visual reward is going to be a top ..ya just have to go to see it....so there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yeh you have to work a bit for your reward....its worth it.. &lt;br /&gt;we take our time...no hurry... &lt;br /&gt;besides its all down hill on the way out....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a Back up plan due to rain or bad weather..we can have pizza/dinner at C&amp;amp;E Pizza..&lt;br /&gt;I dont think MackDonalds will let us have wine and burgers inside....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford take Interstate 84, take Exit 60 (Manchester-East Hartford). take a left ...The route is 44 Burnside Ave heading to East Hartford..The park begins about 500 feet west of the exit but DO NoT use the gate. &lt;br /&gt;WE WILL MEET on the side of the road (Vernon Road) between the MARCO POLO RESTARUANT and the &amp;quot;hill&amp;quot;... about 3/4 miles down from the exit, just past the hill. you will see a citgo station and mack donalds to the left and marco polo on the right...&lt;br /&gt;The park &amp;quot;hill&amp;quot; will be in view from there,,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Vernon/Rockville&lt;br /&gt;Im not sure exactly what exit number but as best i know of its the one that goes to the mall but its the one 3 miles before rte 44...Please look at your maps first...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vernon Street, East hartford is the destination..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179009567000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178647832000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Social at Wickham Park, East Hartford Side</name><id>5755992</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178836200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5755992/</event_url></item>