<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>605 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.563324</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-347-4957</phone><name>Buttonwood Tree Performing Arts and Cultural Center </name><city>Middletown</city><id>1118583</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.651543</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;LOVE THAT GYPSY JAZZ!!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Occidental Gypsy Jazz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$10.00 admission&lt;br /&gt;OCCIDENTAL GYPSY JAZZ QUARTET are a refreshing extension of European café music, better known as Jazz Manouche, or gypsy swing. Their well rehearsed and lightning fast swing make Occidental Gypsy Jazz Quartet “ the Archetype of authenticity” and “ the Best Acoustic Gypsy Jazz Band in New England” (Emmanuel Vincent).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;Brett Feldman(Gypsy guitar soloist)&lt;br /&gt;Scott Külman (Gypsy Vocalist and Guitar Rhythmist)&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Feldman(Bass Guitar)&lt;br /&gt;Joel Beauchemin( Violin, Trumpet)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;The OGJQ is over the moon about it’s latest member Scott Kulman (pronounced Koolman for a good reason). Scott is a graduate of the Berkley School of Music with a vast repetoire of skills. He is a composer, an accomplished muscian and a crooner of the first class. His voice is elegant, smooth and perfectly in pitch, while still exuding a masculine confidence reminiscent of John Mayer and Michael Buble.&lt;br /&gt;Joel Beauchemin( Violin, Trumpet) Began playing violin at the age of four. Subsequently, he studied classical music and performed in the R.I. Philharmonic Youth Orchestra. At age 13 Joel began playing trumpet and jazz in high school. He wrote his first jazz composition when at the age of sixteen.&lt;br /&gt;Brett's aptitude and talent with the guitar awarded him the attention of and tutelage under some of New York's finest musicians. In 2007 Brett travelled to Holland where he obtained a Nympheas Selmer copy by World Renowned Luthier Leo Eimers. Leo was so impressed with Brett’s playing and authenticity of his gypsy style he brought Brett to meet Stochelo Rosenberg and The Rosenberg Trio at a performance in Breda, Holland.&lt;br /&gt;Jeff offers the bottom to the acoustic band with warmth and a delicate approach.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;www.occidentalgypsy.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>ask for us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273963428000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269622956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Occidental Gypsy Jazz Quartet</name><id>13000335</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273881600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13000335/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/1/global_13910993.jpeg</photo_url></item>