<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>436 Silver Lake Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03049</zip><lat>42.796299</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hollis Flea Market</name><city>Hollis</city><id>6473442</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.596962</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Flea Market &amp;amp; an Easy Hike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday Nov. 4th., 11 am. to 1:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hollis Flea Market&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;436 Silver Lake rd., Hollis, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hollisflea.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hollisflea.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is canceled if it rains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join Steve Ob1 and friends at anytime for a later morning early afternoon of shopping cheap. This is one of the largest Flea Market in NH. and is the last one to still be open.  My plan is to meet at 11 am. in front of the food stand. Get something to eat there. Then shop and until around 1:30pm.. Then we will head to Nashua. Where we will meet more people doing the hike on the Mines Falls trials, for about an hour or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Easy Hike Mine Falls&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday Nov. 3rd. 2 pm. to 4 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mine Falls Coliseum Ave. Nashua, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962 &lt;br /&gt;

 RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can't join us at the Hollis Flea Market first at 11 am.? Than meet us for the hike after.  Weather permitting, I think it would be enjoyable to go hike the trails at Mine Falls Park in Nashua. Please know this is not a race. My intent is to enjoy the views of the area, and to chat along the way. This event is meant more to have fun than to get a workout. I thought that we would enjoy nature for about two or three hours, with a few breaks/stops along the trail. This park is just full of beautiful views, so come and enjoy some fresh air, beautiful views, and all this while in good company of new and old friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 2:00 pm in the lot at the end of Coliseum Ave, which is off of Rte 130 in Nashua.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS: Take exit 6 from Route 3 (Route 130) and go west towards Brookline, take the second entrance to the shopping center area (Colliseum Ave), go all the way to the end of the road for the parking lot. Look for the meetup sign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring plenty of fluids and to dress in layers so that you will be comfortable the whole time we are out on the trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone cares to, we can then go grab a bite to eat or enjoy a hot chocolate, at a nearby restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is at no cost. I hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; - AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or tex Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352075661000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351553230000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flea Market &amp; an Easy Hike.</name><id>89108462</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352044800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/89108462/</event_url></item>