<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Canal St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02830</zip><lat>42.012260</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waterfire</name><city>Providence</city><id>704910</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.532028</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE IRA'S SINGLES EVENTS  PRESENTS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; WaterFire &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(www.waterfire.org)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is WaterFire?   It is a mix of fire on the river, dramatic music, lots of people and entertainers. There is even live dancing and jazz on some nights. At sundown, 100 braziers are ignited on vessels that travel down the river. The fragrant mixture of pine, oak and cedar creates an intoxicating smoky perfume that wafts delicately off the water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many spectators have noted that WaterFire turns the Providence waterfront into an Italian piazza, where people sit, stroll, walk and talk and watch others doing the same.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WaterFire has been known to inspire romance. (How Sweet) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s hauntingly beautiful and it’s free. (Words to my ears- Free) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this magical summer evening.  We’ll arrive in Providence in enough time to walk around the city, have dinner and then enjoy WaterFire. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also take a gondola ride on the river during WaterFire, but reservations must be made well in advance. Call La Gondola, 401-421-8877.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, August 28 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark you calendar for a summer evening that will engage all of your senses!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Beautiful Bus Ride to Providence. Leave the driving to Mr. Peter. Peter Pan that is…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Our gorgeous bus accommodates 52 Fun- Loving Folks.  Relax and enjoy the fun ride on comfy seats, with WIFI, DVD, and almost a bathroom, highlighted with Gold and Marble inlay flooring and faucets. (OK, maybe you have to use your imagination). Think no pit stops at crowded rest areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PICK UP LOCATIONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Don’t Be Late, or we leave without you!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Windsor Commuter Lot:  2:30 p.m. 91 North. Exit 38. &lt;br /&gt;Springfield, MA:  Basketball Hall of Fame, South side, 3 p.m .Exit 1a from 91South.  Side Basketball Hall of Fame. 1000 W. Columbus AveSpringfield, MA 01105-2518&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the Bus, A Singles Game that will have you meet all on the Bus. Isn’t this what a Singles Function should do?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate arrival in Providence: 5 p.m, ( We will be dropped off in a area that will offer an array of Restaurant Choices) We recommend making dinner reservations in advance, as WaterFire attracts large crowds. Visit www.waterfire.org to learn more and for a list of restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Say good bye to Providence with great memories at 10 p.m. (Don’t be late, or we will leave with out you!!_&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Say Hello to  Springfield: 12:02 a.m.ish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Say Hello to Windsor- 12:30 a.m. ish ( Okay- It is a tad late/ Just close your eyes and take a nappy on the Bus) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Big Print Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited to a total of 52 fun-loving folks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Please share with friends so we can fill the bus for a fabulous, adventure-filled fall day trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost/RSVP Info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; $30.00 if payment is received on or before August 1.   After August 1 , if room is available, payment is : $35.00 till August 15. After August 15, till the day of the event: $40:00  ( You get the idea- Book early and save!! Also, Less Expensive than driving, No Parking Fees, and you get to Hang with the Best Singles Group Folks Ever!!!)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment:  Preferred Method is Pay Pal. Please send me your email, and I will send you Pay Pay Information.   Mistrchrming@aol.com  Subject Line: WaterFire/Providence &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD OPTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dine Out/ Reservations recommend for “upscale restaurants”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simply walk the area to find an eatery that excites your taste buds&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your own Picnic Basket&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t’ Eat at All &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See: &lt;a href="http://www.goprovidence.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.goproviden...&lt;/a&gt; for restaurant information &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancelation Policy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  If venue cancels due to inclement weather, a full refund.  Also, if we are unable to fill the bus to 52 Fun Loving Singles!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A largre Peter Pan Bus will arrive at PickUp Locations</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283249479000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275917816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira-  WaterFire/ Providence Bus Trip Extravaganza!!</name><id>13723080</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283020200000</time><rsvp_limit>52</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/13723080/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/5/a/global_15575722.jpeg</photo_url></item>