<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>31 Wakefield St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.305164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rochester Opera House</name><city>Rochester</city><id>425892</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.976074</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Halloween parties are fun, but let's try something different during the weekend before Halloween.  The Rochester Opera House is putting on a production of the play &amp;quot;Dracula&amp;quot;.  The Rochester Opera House is a beautifully restored theatre located in the City Hall building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show begins at 8 pm but the doors close 10 minutes prior so let's meet there at 7:40.  Tickets can be ordered online at &lt;a href="http://rochesteroperahouse.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://rochesteropera...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've already bought 4 tickets that are all spoken for.  We'll be in Row D (3rd row), seats 101 to 104.  When you order your ticket online you can opt to select your seats rather than just taking &amp;quot;best available&amp;quot; and try to sit next to us.  If you'd like to do this I'd recommend ordering ASAP.  Tickets in this section are $22.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those interested, we're also doing an optional dinner prior to the show at Slim's Tex Mex at 5:30 pm (hey, no Transylvanian cuisine in Rochester, but oooh, the Empanadas &amp;amp; 'Rita's!).   Slim's is located at 45 North Main St. in Rochester.  (603) 330-3300.  &lt;a href="http://slimstexmex.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://slimstexmex.co...&lt;/a&gt;.  It's just a short walk from Slim's to the Opera House.  &lt;b&gt;Please&lt;/b&gt; mention in your RSVP if you're planning to attend dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;          &lt;b&gt;DRACULA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;b&gt;  A Thrillingly Terrifying Tale&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A stage adaptation by Ted Tiller from the Bram Stoker novel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A mysterious nobleman, at times suave and charming but always menacing, moves into a remote neighborhood, nearby Dr. Seward's sanatorium, in the North of London. The Doctor's sister, Sybil, invites the new neighbor to join them for a bite...and soon the beautiful Mina falls gravely ill with an unknown malady. Dr. Van Helsing, rare disease specialist from Amsterdam, is called in to get to the root of the evil. Will the villainous vampire be unveiled in time to save the lovely Mina?&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Sharon Asher Arsenault&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Inside Opera House/City Hall lobby--near "Will Call" window</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288029255000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286334549000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dracula at the Rochester Opera House &amp; Transylvanian Dinner</name><id>15017405</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287878400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/15017405/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/global_18528275.jpeg</photo_url></item>