<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>14 JFK  Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373096</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 576-0101</phone><name>Z Square Cafe Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>460146</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Last year, we had such a wonderful final year brunch experience at Z Square, let's go back for some good food (delicious crepes, waffles, and tasty apple bacon), and great conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://www.z-square.com/PDF/1132138397.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Z Square Menu&lt;/a&gt; for breakfast and lunch items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested post brunch options:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:15 PM Godfather Double feature at &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/081228.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brattle Theatre&lt;/a&gt; 40 Brattle Street (617) 876 6837&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:00 PM Free Preshow Talk of &lt;a href="http://www.revels.org/the-christmas-revels/" target="_blank"&gt;The Christmas Revels&lt;/a&gt; at Sanders Theatre 45 Quincy Street (617) 496 2222&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch the Patriots final regular season football game in the Z-Square bar?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route. Less than five (5) minute walk from Harvard subway station on the Red Line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your driving route&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;Very limited parking at meters on Dunster and JFK Streets as well as Massachusetts Avenue. Check out &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Square Public Parking&lt;/a&gt; for garages and lots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BEST PARKING DEAL: Validation at University Place  124 Mt. Auburn Street   617-491-0801 for $8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tonya added these MEMBER GUIDELINES so our events run smoothly.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with comment about your circumstances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP. *If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change your RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's which are staffed based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call me on my cell (617) 445-7549&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to me, Tonya explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the bar downstairs. Ask for the Christos and Meetup reservation.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christos Kyriakis</member_name><member_id>3456882</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231690892000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229971336000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Z Square Last Sunday Brunch of 2008</name><id>9376272</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230489000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/9376272/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/0/global_6721312.jpeg</photo_url></item>