<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>59 Jfk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.491.9851</phone><name>Redline</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692091</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120694</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Special Darwin Day event: A Toast to Darwin &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because February 12 is Darwin's birthday, our regular Allies meeting at Redline has been pre-empted by a celebration of science and Darwin.  This of course is completely consistent with naturalism (its basis in fact), so I hope you'll join us for the festivities. There will be free appetizers and cake, and of course food and drink at regular prices.  Here's the scoop: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Toast to Darwin &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raise a glass to celebrate science on the occasion of Charles Darwin?s birthday.  Join us Monday February 12, starting at 7 pm, as the Center for Naturalism, the Humanist Association of Massachusetts, and the Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard host a Toast to Darwin at Redline, 59 JFK St. in Harvard Square.  Free appetizers and birthday cake, plus food and drink at regular prices.  Featuring toasts, rhymes, readings, stories, songs and whatever else spontaneously arises as we honor the man who put us in our rightful, natural place.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Science?  It's a piece of cake! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.darwinday.org/englishL/home/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.darwinday....&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1171498183000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1168304491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Allies of Naturalism February Meetup</name><id>5376970</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171324800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/5376970/</event_url></item>