<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Market St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02885</zip><lat>41.730804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>40`-247-4200</phone><name>2nd Story Theater</name><city>Warren</city><id>777424</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.281755</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For this Meet-up we will return to the 2nd Story Theater in Warren, RI for Neil Simon's "The Good Doctor". Here is the description on 2nd Story's website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Ireland to Russia, a mid-season trade; the Playboy is out, The Good Doctor gets played.&amp;nbsp; It's Chekhov, a heck of a writer, it's true; Neil Simon's concocted this comic ragout.&amp;nbsp; So make way for laughter and maybe a tear; with Chekhov and Simon and Shea in high gear. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $27. Seating is General Admission.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8B0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Each person is responsible for purchasing their own ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For reservations, please call the 2nd Story Theater at 401-247-4200.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8B0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note that Friday nights at 2nd Story do sell out early.  Please do not wait to order your tickets! I strongly recommend that you order your tickets now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Cafe is no longer open.  I received an e-mail stating that they are permanently closed for dinner.  We're going to try someplace new for dinner this time.  Tyler Point Grille, was recommended and is fairly close to the theater.  Here is their website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tylerpointgrille.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tylerpointgrille.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that will be attending dinner, reservations will be made under "RI Theater Group" for 6:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost of dinner will be handled as follows:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drinks will be consigned to a separate check from the meal.  Each person will add 30% to the price of their drink to cover the 8% RI Tax plus a 20% tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meal will be on one check.  A 20% tip will be added to the total and meal check will be divided evenly by the number of people attending the dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will send an e-mail including my cell phone number to all who RSVP "yes". If you will not make it to the restaurant by 6:00 PM please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner is optional and is not included in the price of the ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a fairly large parking lot located next to the theater between Market Street and Route 114 in Warren. A sign for Second Story Theater is on Route 114, although it's somewhat hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be in the lobby at 7:30 and will be holding a small MEET-UP sign. Seating is first-come;first-served, so please be prompt so we can all sit together. When you RSVP, I will provide my cell phone number in case you're running late or get lost.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302388672000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296430240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Good Doctor</name><id>16374227</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300491000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/16374227/</event_url></item>