<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Plainville</address_2><address_1>56 E Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06062</zip><lat>41.672012</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-793-1450</phone><name>Plainvile Public Library</name><city>Plainville</city><id>377901</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.864967</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: burlywood"&gt;An energy exchange meeting will take place at the Plainville Library.  Let's share a healing technique with the group and then have the group practice it on each other!  I have scheduled 2 hours for this program so we will get through as many techniques as possible.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If many members enjoy this session and we do not get to share all of our healing techniques, I will set up another meeting.  I feel it is very important for us to heal each other and share some techniques that we use so that others can learn about them and use them on others if they choose to do so.  I reserved the larger room at the library so that we will have plenty of room to spread out.  The floor is carpeted but being winter, I am not sure how clean it is.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like, I advise you to bring a towel you can lie on.  I also can bring my reiki table that we can share if it is needed.  You are invited to bring whatever healing instrument that you use.  If you heal with singing bowls, please bring that and teach the rest of the group how you heal with it.  I feel we have so much to share with each other and we all could use some healing at the same time.  If you don't have a healing method to share, come anyway and hopefully you will leave the meeting with one!  If this is a popular meetup, I would like to schedule them monthly if enough people are interested.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk down the spiral staircase.  Take a right through the doors.  The large meeting room is straight ahead.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jo-Ann Blanchette-Silverio</member_name><member_id>9921229</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1267466892000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264389340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healing and Energy Exchange</name><id>12413330</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267293600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/12413330/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/0/global_1140976.jpeg</photo_url></item>