<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The polls have spoken--by a small but consistent margin, Friday May 6th is the most popular day for a Scrabble potluck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The word games fun will start around 7:30, but you are welcome to come even if you can't make it until later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a dish to pass, appetizer, dessert, snack or beverage, and (optionally) your favorite word game!&amp;nbsp; I'll have three Scrabble boards and several other word-related games: Bananagrams, Snatch, Quiddler, Upwords. I will also provide some vegetarian appetizers and drinks to go with whatever others are bringing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you RSVP, let us know what you'll be bringing. Take a look at what others are bringing when you decide what to bring yourself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably the most people my apartment can fit is in the neighborhood of 20, so I'm going to limit the RSVPs to that number for now. If it's a nice night we can expand to the outdoors. There will be a waitlist--please do RSVP even if you'll be on the waitlist, as it is likely that everyone will be able to attend. If we're just a little over I'll open it up. Directions will be sent out during the week before the event to folks who are planning to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My apartment is about 5 minutes from the Alewife stop on the Red Line or a shorter walk from the 77 bus. There is plenty of resident-only parking and some parking open to everyone just a block or two away.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>By T to Alewife Station, near intersection of MA 2A / MA 16 (directions and address will be sent closer to RSVP date)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Quinten</member_name><member_id>9980941</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304967837000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>By popular demand!</why><group><who>Word Freaks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scrabble-Enthusiasts-of-Boston</urlname><id>1385528</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Scrabble Enthusiasts of (Greater) Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302877684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scrabble &amp; Word Games Potluck Part Deux</name><id>17315757</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304724600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scrabble-Enthusiasts-of-Boston/events/17315757/</event_url></item>