<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Thompson St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06033</zip><lat>41.680211</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Udderly Woolly Acres Farm</name><city>Glastonbury</city><id>1267263</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.513992</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please Note this month's healing will be held at Udderly Woolly Acres in Glastonbury - located at 851 Thompson Street! In the event of rain we will meet the the Growing Green Co-op!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us before the healing for a Wild Weed Walk with helpful gardener Scott Reill and Roots founder Lindsay Roepelle as they co-lead a wild weed walk around the soon to be Alchemy Acres farm located at 581 Thompson Street in Glastonbury from 4-6 pm on Sunday, June 6th. Learn about nutrient dense real food, the power of wild edibles our plans to turn the farm into a community educational center. The walk will be followed by a full body gong healing with the CONDUIT @ 6pm. Come experience the power of vibrational healing! (www.gongtheplent.com). $25 donation to go towards the purchase of the farm! For more information about the farm, nutrient dense food or the co-op, go to www.alchemyacres.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vibrational healing through sound can be traced back to ancient civilizations and is used all over the world. This Sunday (and every first Sunday of the month), The Conduit performs a sound healing meditation which incorporates the use of planetary gongs &amp;amp; Tibetan singing bowls. Feeling the synergistic nature of vibration can open our minds to higher possibilities and states of harmony, ultimately resulting in self-healing. Shifting the themes each month keep us in touch with the energies of the world and life around us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gathering people together for sharing a harmonic musical experience can be powerful. Something uplifting happens when we come together to create a sense of community through sound healing. Join us as we reconnect our hearts and bring love to our planet through the transformational power of vibration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Using sound as a healing modality, a Conduit sound healing session clears and aligns the energy centers to promote deep relaxation &amp;amp; renewal. In meditation, we will unify with our essence, our original self, by hearing vibratory sounds that produce a quieting influence on the mind and body.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join &lt;a href="http://www.gongtheplanet.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Conduit&lt;/a&gt; and others as we meditate and connect with the sacredness of the universe through sound and vibration. A $20 donation goes to support the work of The Conduit and the Growing Green Co-op's healing arts space. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about The Conduit, please see &lt;a href="http://www.gongtheplanet.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.GongThePlanet.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.theconduitcenter.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.TheConduitCenter.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Owen James</member_name><member_id>10503612</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275867750000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274672718000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Guided Transformational Meditation Concert</name><id>rklgnynjbjb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275863400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/13574395/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/6/global_12748038.jpeg</photo_url></item>