<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Amherst Street (Building E51)  </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wong Auditorium, MIT, </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>12097812</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084457</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come to a magical evening of Jazz with the honey-voiced Neha and friends !!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After graduating from Northwestern University with a degree in Economics. Neha took a job working for Google in San Francisco. She spent as much of her free time hitting the San Francisco jazz scene, performing and learning as much as she could. After four years of working in the bay area, Neha made a career changing decision to finally pursue what she had wholeheartedly always wanted to music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shortly thereafter, Neha was accepted into the prestigious New England Conservatory's Masters program for jazz voice study, a feat she only thought could have become a reality in her dreams. Under the tutelage of amazing and gifted teachers and students, Neha continues to hone her craft. "It really has been a dream come true to be invited to study at New England Conservatory amongst such rich musical forces. I learn something new everyday and feel so blessed to be given the opportunity to study here," says Neha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A gifted singer, composer &amp;amp; pianist, Neha's style can be characterized as a smorgasbord of musical personalities. While definitely rooted in jazz, elements of folk, blues and pop also play a huge role in her music. Echoes of her mother's classical Indian musical training and influence can also be heard in her music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I just write," says Neha. "I try not to think about what box I'm fitting into, because what is most music these days anyway? It's a product of many different stylistic influences."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A young siren with magnetic stage presence, Neha brings an intriguing uniqueness to her music that will leave you wanting more. Her vocal lines boast embellishments that will whisk you away to the jazz world of the 1940s. A young woman who's only at the beginning of her career, Neha works the audience with an intimate finesse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.nehamusic.com/#_"&gt;http://www.nehamusic.com/#_&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In North America, Students for Bhopal and ICJB is a network of students, professionals, activists, and partners working in solidarity with the survivors of the Bhopal disaster in their struggle for justice. We use education, grassroots organizing and non-violent direct action to pressure Dow Chemical and the Indian Government to uphold the Bhopalis' demand for justice, and their fundamental human right to live free of chemical poison. SfB/ICJB work directly to improve the condition of Bhopal's survivors. Our role is to empower and train leaders in the worldwide movement to end this crime against humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all live in Bhopal and we will not rest without justice in Bhopal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn More about ICJB at&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://studentsforbhopal.org/"&gt;http://studentsforbhopal.org/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 www.bhopal.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can buy tickets for &lt;br /&gt;

 $15 General Seating &lt;br /&gt;

 $10 Students with Valid ID &lt;br /&gt;

 at &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/343774"&gt;http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/343774&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;facebook: &lt;a class="linkified" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/550666534968093/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/550666534968093/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364780364000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonjazz</urlname><id>87187</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Jazz Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362540250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jazz for Bhopal with Neha and Friends</name><id>107842812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364767200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonjazz/events/107842812/</event_url></item>