<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Hunt Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.836670</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Amesbury Sports Park</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1486796</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.945374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE note I have changed the time for this meetup to 2:30 if you still want to come but are not able to attend at that time, put the time that you plan on attending and call the Meetup phone when you get there, or look around for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To purchase your entrance ticket ahead of time:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amesburysportspark.net/brew%20fest%20tickets.html"&gt;http://www.amesburysportspark.net/brew%20fest%20tickets.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Brew Fest attracted tons of people over the last 5years let's go join in on the fun this year.  If you don't like crowds this event may not be for you, please consider that when RSVPing  Once we get in you can either stay with the group or go explore on your own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aside from beer, BBQ and bands, the Brew Fest will feature OGO rides and summer tubing. The OGO (Outdoor Gravity Orb) is an 11 foot inflatable transparent sphere with another inflated sphere suspended inside it. Riders enter the orb and strap themselves into a harness, or enter the H2OGO with up to 3 people and 5 gallons of water and are pushed over the edge of an 800 foot grassy slope!  As more information is announced I will update this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests must be 21 or older unless accompanied by parent or legal guardian. You MUST have your ID on you whether you are drinking or NOT.  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE: Everyone WILL get carded.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So come on out to the Amesbury Sports Park and join us for the Brew Fest!!  We have the option to sample 100 Beers and meet the master brewers, listen to 6 bands on an outdoor stage, enjoy tasty BBQ, have fun with some fun people and more people watching.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buying a ticket for the event:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will update this as the date gets closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 They have a pretty big parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Please remember that we will only wait 15 minutes to head out to this event (get some beer) if you are running late, get stuck in traffic or get lost, please call the meetup phone at 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Rain may cancel this event! Check back before you head out to see if there are any updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be on the stairs as you are heading into the front of the building. (The front is facing the road)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348365064000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343332040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>6th Annual Brew Fest</name><id>75036142</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348338600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/75036142/</event_url></item>