<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sunset Ln</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.327626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Maria College</name><city>Paxton</city><id>725813</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.918336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Starfest 2011 is the annual free public event sponsored by the Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. which offers a whole host of speakers, activities, demonstrations and displays for adults and kids to have fun while exploring our Universe!&amp;nbsp;( 6 to 10PM on the campus of Anna Maria College in Paxton, MA ) &amp;nbsp;The theme this year will cover the successful completion of the Space Shuttle Program after 30 years plus offer great talks about meteorites, Mars exploration, Exoplanets, the Space Shuttle along with rocket launching outdoors and solar observing! We also offer great chances at spacey door prizes plus a raffle for a&amp;nbsp;small telescope &amp;nbsp;to raise funds for a future Aldrich handicap accessible observatory and learning center!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the details on the Aldrich website at 
&lt;a href="http://www.aldrichastro.org"&gt;www.aldrichastro.org&lt;/a&gt; and click on Starfest 2011 to let us know if you plan to attend and how many will be coming with you! This event is scheduled indoors with outdoor observing planned if the weather cooperates! It is very well attended and offers a chance to hear about the latest breaking news about major findings in the world of astronomy and space exploration!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also hear about some great science done by students from Monty Tech whose experiment was accepted on board the last Space Shuttle flight of Atlantis which ended the era of American human spaceflight into low Earth orbit! Plan to attend - plenty of munchies and beverages along with great handouts and teacher resource packs if you need material for your classroom, home school environment or scout troop!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The quarter Moon, Saturn,&amp;nbsp;Albireo, Alcor and Mizar&amp;nbsp;and the great M13 globular cluster will be prime targets for Aldrich telescopes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---Jim J. Zebrowski&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be signs for the event parking at Foundress Hall  stop by the entrance tables to pick up your list of speakers!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312672671000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312234867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Starfest 2011</name><id>27861721</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312668000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/27861721/</event_url></item>