<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trinity College</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.748314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio</name><city>Hartford</city><id>291370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Want to see this before it leaves..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.thedoubleho"&gt;www.thedoubleho&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#8203;ur.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.samu/"&gt;www.samu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#8203;elgoldwynfilms.&amp;#8203;com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Italy, 2011) Directed by Giuseppe Capotondi. Written by Alessandro Fabbri, Ludovica Rampoldi and Stefano Sardo. Cast: Ksenia Rappoport, Filippo Timi, Antonia Truppo, Gaetano Bruno. The best mystery to come out of Europe since Tell No One is a twist-filled thriller that won Best Actor and Best Actress Awards at the Venice Film Festival for its two stars, Fillippo Timi and Ksenia Rappoport. The Double Hour takes its title from those times of the day like 10:10 (or, since it&amp;rsquo;s set in Italy, 23:23), when you can make a wish and it will come true. Which may or may not be accurate, like much of the narrative puzzle that kicks off when the brand new love affair between an ex-cop and a Slovakian hotel chambermaid in Turin plunges into (what may be) murder. &amp;ldquo;A beautiful, head-spinning mystery that requires keen attention - and rewards it with a tricky and poetic payoff.&amp;rdquo; Steven Rea, Philadelphia Inquirer. 95 min (Italy, 2011)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A sly, triple twist of a film, this Italian intrigue is almost never what it seems, although everything ends up making perfect sense eventually. Along the way, though, it&amp;rsquo;s slippery stuff.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : right"&gt;- Tom Long, Detroit News&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the fabulously acted Italian thriller &amp;ldquo;The Double Hour&amp;rdquo; twice now, and for all its intricate manipulations, it stays with me for a very simple reason: The love story at its bittersweet heart is played for keeps.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : right"&gt;- Michael Phillips, Chicago Tribune&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311647358000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311439892000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>the Doublehour @Cinestudios</name><id>26770061</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311635700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/26770061/</event_url></item>