<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The show starts at 7:30 so let's meet at the theater at 7:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to keep your RSVP current or call me (508/308-4897) if you need to change it after 5:00 the day of or if you get lost or will be late (so we can wait for you).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;This ain't no April Fool's joke: This group seriously needs a silly comedy. Having just loved Forgetting Sarah Marshall, I thought &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810022085/info" target="_blank"&gt;I Love You, Man&lt;/a&gt; would be a good choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Peter Klaven is a successful real estate agent who, upon getting engaged to the woman of his dreams, Zooey, discovers, to his dismay and chagrin, that he has no male friend close enough to serve as his Best Man. Peter immediately sets out to rectify the situation, embarking on a series of bizarre and awkward &amp;quot;man-dates,&amp;quot; before meeting Sydney Fife, a charming, opinionated man with whom he instantly bonds. But the closer the two men get, the more Peter's relationship with Zooey suffers, ultimately forcing him to choose between his fiancee and his new found &amp;quot;bro,&amp;quot; in a story that comically explores what it truly means to be a &amp;quot;friend.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The usual stuff:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet inside the theater doors (or outside if it's nice out) and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.50 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers eacg for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are always welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for I Love You, Man!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239321690000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237914021000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>I Love You, Man</name><id>10024686</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238626800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10024686/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>