<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>See Gloria's Walk Along the Windsor Locks Canal, in the hartford hike section....She is having a good light walk along the canal a few miles  from this paddle at 3 pm.&lt;br /&gt;Since this paddle location is right on my way to the hike..and on the way home....might as well stop and fit in a short paddle..either upstream for a while or downstream to the CT river. Dont matter to me..&lt;br /&gt;If someone is interested after the hike and some dinner...can do a sunset trip here too... Bring some Pine Wooden Steak Bug Spray...Vampire Mosquetoes&lt;br /&gt;come out at night&lt;br /&gt;This part of the river is usually slow, and sometimes a little faster depending on the upstream dam release...&lt;br /&gt;anyone can paddle upstream even during the release for a good long ways...&lt;br /&gt;..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;From north or south..&lt;br /&gt; Take I 91 exit 37 in Windsore, go EAST on rte 305= Bloomfield ave for apx 1 mile where it ends and runs into rte 75=Poquonock ave. Take a right onto rte 75 for a short distance and then a left onto rte 159=Palasido ave. Go under the train bridge then take the first left turn=Pleasant ST.&lt;br /&gt;Look right for the first buildings one of them is BARTS&lt;br /&gt;Go a bit past the front and head to the back lot.&lt;br /&gt;The boat launch is down from there to the river.&lt;br /&gt;I have the blue toyota avalon and trailer with 2 yaks on it. if there is not enough room i unhook the trailer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1153768617000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle before or after Gloria's Hike</name><id>5039657</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1154187900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5039657/</event_url></item>