<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>245 Whiting Farms Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.175727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Holiday Inn at Ingleside</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>906244</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.641467</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This February, our breakfast meeting will step outside of our normal routine.&amp;nbsp; Instead of having one expert speaker, we will be having five!&amp;nbsp; In this round table format, you will be moving from table to table to learn from our speakers in small groups in mini-sessions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Experts and their topics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carleen E. Fischer Hoffman &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;Putting an End to Clutter&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clutter seems to be a problem most people face in their homes and offices.&amp;nbsp; Although it often becomes obvious that the clutter is causing stress, most people are too overwhelmed to know where to begin to get organized.&amp;nbsp; Carleen Eve Fischer Hoffman, owner and founder of The Clutter Doctor, Inc., will help you explore ways to create order in your life through simple organizing techniques you can begin using as soon as you leave the roundtable!&amp;nbsp; Leave feeling inspired, excited, and motivated to start your project!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Carleen Eve Fischer Hoffman has been featured in several radio shows, newspaper and magazine articles, and television interviews.&amp;nbsp; She also has been awarded the prestigious Golden Circle Award from the National Association of Professional Organizers.&amp;nbsp; Ms. Hoffman has taught classes on conquering clutter at Springfield Technical Community College and produced a local TV show entitled &amp;ldquo;Clearing the Clutter&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suzanne McElroy &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;Authoritative or Bitchy: Challenges of Women Leading Women&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Suzanne will explore some of the challenges of working with women who are subordinates or subcontractors, and balancing a pleasant work environment with being an effective manager / boss.&amp;nbsp; Included will be some tips, tricks, and &amp;ldquo;golden nuggets&amp;rdquo; of truth learned through experience and good coaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Suzanne opened the Springfield, MA branch of Home Instead Senior Care in 2005 after spending several years caring for her grandmother and great-aunt, and realizing that this was, indeed, a calling for her.&amp;nbsp; She brings with her the clinical skills she gained as a mental health therapist with a concentration on geriatric psychology.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Christine Burns &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;Finding the Balance&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Being a woman in business means balancing your family life with your career, while dealing with the challenges of being successful and keeping it all together. Hear from a woman who has found a way to make it work while getting the bills paid, taking the dog to the vet, picking up the kids from school, showing up at networking events, and staying sane through it all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Christine is the owner of Clowntique, a family entertainment company based out of Holyoke, MA for the past 12 years.&amp;nbsp; Clowntique offers clowns, jugglers, magicians, balloon artists, professional games coordinators, face painters, animated and holiday characters.&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amy Woolf &lt;br /&gt;"Working with Color - Effective Choices for the Business Environment&lt;/strong&gt;" &lt;br /&gt;Learn how choosing the right color for your work environment can increase your productivity. &amp;nbsp;Discover how color can shift the way your clients feel about you when visiting your office or business. &amp;nbsp;Amy will also discuss the top five misconceptions about selecting color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Amy Woolf has been working as an Architectural Color Consultant since 2006, assisting clients both locally and long-distance with color strategies that are beautiful as well as functional.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Janine Fondon &lt;br /&gt;"Front Page PR Gets You VISIBILITY"&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Join Janine for a brief PR assessment to highlight opportunities for improving your outreach, PR and marketing. Remember, you are a reflection of your PR efforts, so let&amp;rsquo;s take a look in the mirror! Learn the basics from a professional with a proven record of success. Here&amp;rsquo;s the first tip: Your success is re-ignited with every new meeting, interaction or press release, so let&amp;rsquo;s get busy on Feb. 17. The front page is waiting for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Janine Fondon is one of the region&amp;rsquo;s leading firms specializing in Front Page PR, cause-related branding, marketing for bottom line success, multicultural outreach and diversity news distribution.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298071208000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296759490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Breakfast Meeting- Expert Roundtable</name><id>16429992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297946700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/16429992/</event_url></item>