<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>77520</zip><lat>29.716753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>From Your Home</name><city>Anytown</city><id>4152372</id><country>us</country><lon>-94.994980</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Keeping in mind what happened to &lt;strong&gt;Susette Kelo and her Fort Trumbull neighbors&lt;/strong&gt; in that eminent domain scandal &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;[Kelo vs. New London],&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; it would be nice to remind the mainstream of the Institute for Justice and the type of work that they do. This public interest law firm takes on un-Constitutional&amp;nbsp;attacks against&amp;nbsp;free enterprise, school choice and other matters --- not just the abuse of eminent domain for private gain. Here is their website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.IJ.org"&gt;www.IJ.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Institute for Justice&lt;/strong&gt; defended Susette Kelo and the other residents. Even though they lost the case, this sent a shot around the country on the issue of private property rights. 13 or more state quickly enacted laws to &lt;strong&gt;forbid the use of eminent domain for private interests&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;merely to increase a town's tax revenue&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the organizers think this is a great idea for a Meetup, please spread the word to other Connecticut Ron Paul groups. Heck, spread the word to as many Ron Paul groups as possible. If we do it, however, it will have to be a target date far in advance to allow as many people as possible to take part. Time will be needed to spread the word.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322688329000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319606179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Is anyone open to a money bomb for the Institute for Justice?</name><id>38752352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322683200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/38752352/</event_url></item>