<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Loomis St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.487458</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MINUTE MAN BIKE TRAIL</name><city>Bedford</city><id>791380</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.274444</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Minuteman Bikeway passes through the historic area where the American Revolution began in April 1775.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, the Minuteman Bikeway is one of the most popular and successful rail-trails in the United States, enjoyed for both healthy recreation and transportation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bikeway has become a new type of “Main Street” where neighbors and strangers alike come together while riding, walking, or skating on the path.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2008, Rails-to-Trails Conservancy inducted the Minuteman Bikeway into the national Rail-Trail Hall of Fame.&lt;br /&gt;Built by the Commonwealth of Massachusetts on an inactive railroad, the Minuteman Bikeway has become a treasured regional resource, used by local residents and visitors from near and far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connecting to the Alewife “T” Station in Cambridge, the bikeway provides an easy way for bicyclists and pedestrians to travel to subway and bus lines, serving to reduce automobile traffic in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bikeway is collectively managed and maintained by the four communities it passes through: Bedford, Lexington, Arlington, and Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet in the parking lot of The Bikeway Source located on Loomis St. Bedford in a large red barn. There are bike rentals available there or bring your own.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can ride for a few hours and have lunch at a local restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain Cancels &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're running late or have to cancel at last minute please call me at 617-775-0045&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225645258000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224259904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHESTNUT HILL WALKING MEETUP BIKE RIDE</name><id>8979968</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225033200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/8979968/</event_url></item>