<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>66 Thunder Mountain Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01339</zip><lat>42.623013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Berkshire East Canopy Tours</name><city>Charlemont</city><id>1629020</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.878899</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;So, here's the deal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is being changed to Bershire East in Charlemont, MA.&amp;nbsp; There is a  Buy With Me for $45.00 for the Mountain Top Tour. It's available at  &lt;a href="http://www.buywithme.com/boston/deals/6276-berkshire-east-canopy-tours" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.buywithme.com/boston/deals/6276-berkshire-east-canopy-tours&lt;/a&gt;. This  is 1/2 the usual price!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are doing the Mountain Top Tour, but you  can also have the option of doing the Valley Jump instead at the same time.  According to the people at Berkshire East, this is "more extreme".&amp;nbsp;  There is a Buy With Me deal for that as well, but the price is higher.  The Mountain Top Tour is for kids 8 and up, weighing at least 70 lbs.  (they said they are very strict on the weight requirement). &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately they only take out 10 people at a time, so they've added a 3:00  slot as well.&amp;nbsp; Some people can go at 2:30, and another group can go at 3:00.&amp;nbsp; We'll meetup before and after.&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;They can't hold any slots for us without  either the Buy With Me voucher number, or a payment.&amp;nbsp; So, you pretty  much need to get your voucher and reserve your spot asap for us to go as  a group. You can't do this online, so be sure to call Berkshire East  (413-339-6617) to reserve your spot, and have your Buy With Me voucher  number ready. Or, if you prefer, pay full price with a credit card. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you want to do the more extreme Valley Jump, the  info. is on Berkshire East's website, and the Buy With Me for that is  $85.00, but includes a lift ticket in the winter for the ski resort.&amp;nbsp;  Kids need to be 12 and up and weigh at least 100 lb. for that one. Feel  free to call them with any questions about the options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Berkshire East's website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.berkshirezip.com/zip_home" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.berkshirezip.com/zip_home&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Berkshire East's phone: &lt;br /&gt;413-339-6617&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please update your RSVP after you've gotten confirmed that you have a slot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the parking lot, or registering. Details will be firmed up when we figure out who is going when.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307385241000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Officially a Meetup !</why><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294783660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zip Lining in Western MA - Kid Friendly</name><id>16304720</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305396000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/16304720/</event_url></item>