<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass, Framingham, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301254</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Framingham 15 AMC Theater</name><city>Framingham</city><id>597341</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390236</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show we're going to see is at 2:15 this coming Saturday. We'll meet outside between 1:45 and 2:00 and try to head in around 2 so we can sit together. Please RSVP if you haven't already!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part 2 in The Chronicles of Narnia series, &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809244324/info" target="_blank"&gt;Prince Caspian&lt;/a&gt;, promises lots of fantasy wonderment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't seen the first movie in the series (or don't know the story), read up on &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Chronicles_of_Narnia:_The_Lion%2C_the_Witch_and_the_Wardrobe" target="_blank"&gt;The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I picked a Saturday afternoon about a week after opening night for this movie because I was trying to get away from the crowd pinnacle that is opening weekend. I'll choose a time around 2 p.m. when the showtimes for 5/24 come out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring your kids, neighbors, friends, neighbors' kids, etc. Just include them in your RSVP so I know how many people to expect. I may be bringing a few people myself (maybe the hubby and the stepkids).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you think that another time/date would work better for the vast majority of people interested in this movie, please include a suggestion in your RSVP. I'm trying to arrange these blockbuster outings so the most people can come, so input is much appreciated!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at this movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll fill this bit in later... I may be outside, I may be inside. It depends on whether or not I have a multi-ticket discount card (take the poll to find out more about how you can save money on each of our outings).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211917642000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Because we have fun! We can go out afterwards to talk about the movie.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210362337000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Chronicles of Narnia: Prince Caspian</name><id>7907572</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211652000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/7907572/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>