<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><fee><label>Guest Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us as guest speaker Paul Esajian of A&amp;amp;E's &amp;quot;Flip This House&amp;quot; hosts the February Monthly Meeting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00 - Networking, Deals &amp;amp; Meet our Vendors&lt;br /&gt;6:15 - Networking&lt;br /&gt;6:45 - Bring your deals&lt;br /&gt;6:55 - Announcements&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - Guest Speaker Paul Esajian&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Are you looking to jumpstart your real estate investing career and want to learn from one of the nation?s most successful investors?  &lt;br /&gt;Are you interested in learning how systems can make your business run itself ... without your constant attention?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If so then you will not want to miss the Feb 18th monthly meeting and the Saturday Feb.23, workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * How to evaluate a house in disrepair and figure a total repair cost in 15 minutes&lt;br /&gt;    * The 6 critical documents you need to get signed when working with contractors&lt;br /&gt;    * How to organize and manage a project so you don't have to be on the jobsite 24 hours a day&lt;br /&gt;    * How to rehab homes so they sell before you finish hammering the last nail&lt;br /&gt;    * How to limit your liability when working with contractors&lt;br /&gt;    * How to interview and pre-screen contractors so you never get burned&lt;br /&gt;    * How to control your rehab costs, so you never go over budget&lt;br /&gt;    * Where to find best deals on construction materials&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't miss the February Monthly Meeting with Paul Esajian.  Register today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who is Paul Esajian?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Esajian, CFO of CT Homes, LLC and Co-Founder of FortuneBuilders Inc. is one of nation's premier young real estate investors and speakers.  His ideas for building a business have been used to develop CT Homes into the premier real estate solutions company in Connecticut and the New England area.  Paul is an experienced project manager who specializes in personnel management and incentive based motivation for his contractors.  Currently, Paul manages over 25 development projects with five teams of over 35 contractors in nine different cities and three different states.  Although Paul's expertise is in managing larger rehabs and multi-unit rehabs of over $50,000 dollars, he has also been responsible for the accounting and companies' financial details since the beginning. Throughout his investing career, Paul has been continuously developing unique accounting systems custom to our specific home buying business, as well as contractor systems that have been developed to meticulously manage the numerous contractors and projects.  This range of duties has given Paul a wide breadth of knowledge about running an efficient, productive company, from the accounting books in the office to the foundation of a house on site.  In addition, Paul has contributed in developing and now managing two branch offices in Fresno, CA and New London, CT that are currently run by students of his company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; In addition to the contribution Paul has had on the community of New Haven through his diligent efforts to re-construct formerly ugly houses into beautiful ones, Paul has also been instrumental in sustaining business for minority contractors within the cities of New Haven and Waterbury, among others.  His ability to manage and motivate people has led to more work for contractors, thus further sustaining income for previously slow businesses.  There are countless number of people Paul has worked with who have produced their best work as a result of his attention to detail, dedication and persistence to get the job done the right way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Esajian is originally from California, where he graduated from the University of California at Davis with a focus in accounting.  Paul also wrestled for the University while earning his degree.  With a work ethic seldom can match, Paul continues to grow his business while keeping in mind this important thought: as long as there is no work left to be done, then everything has been done right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our monthly meetings are the premier event of CT REIA every month. Imagine being in a room with hundreds of real estate investors and professionals. They range in experience from brand new to over 30 years of experience. At the monthly meetings, you can:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network with companies who provide services specifically for real estate investors, like mortgage companies, contractors, insurance companies, etc&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network with other investors!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Find your next rehab deal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Find someone who wants to buy your wholesale deals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Get advice on a challenging situation you are dealing with&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Get motivated to take your career to the next level&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hear about success stories from other members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Remind yourself to get off your couch and get into action&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Re-focus on your goals for financial wealth and freedom!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;and much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We usually have around 300-400 people at our monthly meetings, so finding where you need to be is never a problem.  When you arrive, please visit the check-in table and one of our volunteers will get you checked in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203547273000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>If you're serious about investing in real estate, the Connecticut Real Estate Investors Association is the group for you!</why><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201983191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Meeting with "Flip This House" Star Paul Esajian</name><id>7249416</id><headcount>200</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203373800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/7249416/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/0/global_3120816.jpeg</photo_url></item>