<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will meet at the Parmacheenee road on rt 16 at 10:30 am on Sunday morning. There is excellent parking area .3 miles in for people who want to head home straight from the trail on Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the day hike event of the Bullwinkle Weekend On Pristine Lake Aziscohos. Your welcome to join us camp and cabin, just RSVP on the Saturday event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Magalloway summit is at 3360 feet and requires only a short hour hike. (&lt;a href="http://www.firelookou..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.firelookou...&lt;/a&gt;) It has a maintained fire tower which can be scaled to near top, even when the ranger is out. GreyJays are plentiful and will pluck apple cores from platform. Garfield Falls is a historic logging legacy and the stony scape is breathtaking and inviting. In spring flood it must be deafening and fierce. Another nearby falls could be added as the group wishes, called Hellgate Falls. In the logging days loggers where lowered on ropes to cut up logjams, or to place dynamite. Many loggers died in the attempt and the name seems therefore appropriate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to Magalloway Mountain&lt;/b&gt;  and Garfield Falls from the Bosebuck (Parmechenee Rd) on other side of Aziscoos Lake.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At about ¼ mile in you can pull off to left to park extra cars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.6- take fork toward Bosebuck (sign says Bosebuck)&lt;br /&gt;6.0 – there is a fork which you don’t take&lt;br /&gt;6.3- take a left turn where you’ll see the GATE ( it was unlocked)&lt;br /&gt;7.4- Magallowey Rd and it says mile (14)&lt;br /&gt;8.5- stay left&lt;br /&gt;9.6- you’ll come to triangle that is made by roads to your right- just stay on the Magallowey Rd-so you will not go on the triangle&lt;br /&gt;10.5- you’ll go on a bridge and you will see another gate&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222255617000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220913865000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>52 With A View!  Mt. Magalloway Lite hike</name><id>8716952</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222007400000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8716952/</event_url></item>