<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361406</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857.453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft N.E.R.D. Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1210878</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081282</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Come learn about a new PHP Framework that some are touting as a potential game changer for PHP. If you are using any of the popular PHP frameworks like CakePHP, Symfony, Zend, or CodeIgniter - then you owe it to yourself to check out what Lithium has to offer...  &lt;a href="http://lithify.me/" target="_blank"&gt;Lithium&lt;/a&gt; is a framework for PHP 5.3+ that is focused on quality, speed, and flexibility. It's a set of no-nonsense philosophies and tools that enable you to build better applications, in less time, without sacrificing quality or extensibility.  Lithium understands distributed storage and caching, queuing systems, micro-dispatch frameworks, with integrated support for document oriented databases like CouchDB and MongoDB, alongside relational databases like MySQL and PostgreSQL. Lithium's architecture allows you to get your application up and running quickly, and still allows you to take control of the framework to support the requirements of your application.  This presentation will be presented by &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/members/2341437/"&gt;Nate Abele&lt;/a&gt; who is the co-founder of Lithium framework. Prior to this, he was the lead developer of the very popular &lt;a href="http://cakephp.org/"&gt;Cake PHP framework&lt;/a&gt;. Nate has been a member of Boston PHP for a long time, and we are really excited to have him come talk about Lithium.  &lt;b&gt;Huh? - What is a PHP Framework?&lt;/b&gt; A PHP Framework is a basic platform that allows you to develop web applications really quickly. In other words, it provides structure. By using a PHP Framework, you will end up saving loads of time, stopping the need to produce repetitive code, and you'll be able to build applications rapidly (RAD). Without a PHP Framework in place, it gets much more difficult to produce applications since you'll have to repeatedly code a lot of PHP. You'll also have to execute the connection between your database and whatever application you develop from scratch.  Here is a &lt;a href="http://www.onextrapixel.com/2010/05/24/an-overview-of-php-framework-guides-for-developers/"&gt;great article on frameworks&lt;/a&gt; if your new to concept.  &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda:&lt;/b&gt;  6:00 - 7:00 : Doors open, socializing, BoothCamp  7:00 - 7:15 : Announcements  7:15 - 8:45 : Presentation  8:45 - 9:00 : Questions  9:00 - ???? : Beers somewhere?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>1ST Floor. Look here for parking: http://bit.ly/adRzem</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Abele</member_name><member_id>2341437</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308405944000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>170</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290680541000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introducing the Lithium PHP Framework</name><id>15553713</id><headcount>170</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307570400000</time><rsvp_limit>380</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/15553713/</event_url></item>