<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Rain Advisory! Mount Washington Via Ammo &amp;amp; Jewel trails.&lt;br /&gt;This event has been officially canceled due to the hurricane messing with our weekend weather. If you still hike, it is advised that you stay below the tree line due to thunder storms, poor visibility and wind gusts. The ledges on the Ammo trail will be slippery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This incredible hike features two beautiful waterfalls, two mighty mountains, a world of fantastic views, and a large A.M.C. hut to rest in! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ammonoosuc Ravine Trail is the &amp;quot;easiest&amp;quot; way up to Mt Washington. This is a moderate rated hike for conditioned hikers.   Stop at Gem Pool to see a wonderful waterfall pour into the emerald pool. A quarter mile more sees two spectacular cascades drop more than 500' into the foot of a gorge. Very impressive views, a favorite trail that you will return to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At only 3.1 miles to the Lakes of the Clouds, the hut &amp;amp; crew welcome hikers to eat, rest, get some shade and spend the night at the foot of Mount Monroe. Here the group will take a break and double check the weather for the summit conditions. If conditions are not favorable, this is a good place to start a descend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt Monroe Option:  It is just .3 of a mile, 20 minutes to summit Mount Monroe (5372') and only 1.5 miles in 90 minutes on Crawford Path, cut in 1819, to summit Mount Washington (6288') from the hut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jewel Trail option: from The Mt Washington Summit the group can chose to descend via Jewel trail. Some feel that this is an easier descend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://inlinethumb10.webshots.com/5577/1467583229079256950S500x500Q85.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part way up Mt Washington looking back at Monroe, lower lake, &amp;amp; the hut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This full day round trip is a moderate, yet spectacular 9.0 miles, 3800' of elevation gain in a hiking book time of 6 hours 30 minutes ( allow more time for a group hike and extra stops.) Watch your time on the summit! there is much to see and it is easy to spend too much time in the hut and snack bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group will average at latest a 1pm turn around time. If trail or hiker conditions slow the group, you need to understand that the goal for the day can change and we must start back to end the hike safely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even though this is a summer hike, The summit can have a chill to it. Pack a fleece, windbreaker and ski hat. You can refill your water supply at the hut and Summit. Bring cash for snacks and souvenirs. I got my summit patch at the gift shop.  Carry your headlamp, just in case you run late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury. Review the trail maps and itinerary available in the White Mountain Guidebook. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members. Annual Parking pass or day fee of $3 is needed at the trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Hike is offically canceled- if your still hiking, contact each other for an alternate location</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251116318000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248134394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rain Advisory: Mount Washington Via Ammo &amp; Jewel trails</name><id>10919478</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250943300000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10919478/</event_url></item>