<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 West Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.346043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>530-736-9189</phone><name>Marlborough Public Library</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>966581</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.554450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Organizing Your Papers and Fighting Junk Mail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you struggle with junk mail, paying your bills on time, or dealing with paperwork that you never file or take action on?  In this 60-minute seminar you will understand how to stop unnecessary papers from coming through your door, as well as learning how to manage, file, and take action on the documents that need your attention.  You will discover how to set up a system that organizes your paperwork and leaves you with more time and energy for other things in your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring about an inch of paper to get help from Lorena in organizing it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Biography&lt;br /&gt;Lorena Prime, Owner of Clearly Organized, specializes in time management, overcoming procrastination, and teaching people how to be more efficient by organizing their tasks, spaces, and things.  In her career she has worked for several Fortune 500 companies, but left corporate America last year to start her own company.  Now she focuses on her true love – efficiency and organization!  She helps businesses and individuals streamline their tasks and their lives - helping them achieve a peaceful balance between work and home.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're downstairs, feel free to ask about us at the desk</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dayanna Moreno</member_name><member_id>8672243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254437573000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Procrastinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers</urlname><id>1357989</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>Metrowest Procrastinators and Clutterers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245692190000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Organizing Your Papers and Fighting Junk Mail</name><id>10708344</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249596000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers/events/10708344/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/a/global_6942970.jpeg</photo_url></item>