<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;I saw Keane a couple of years ago and have been waiting for it to screen again in the area. I was very happy to see it listed on the Harvard Film Archive calendar and having the director,Lodge Kerrigan, present for a Q &amp;amp; A session  is a great bonus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Damian Lewis portrays an unstable man of little means desperately searching the streets of New York for his abducted daughter. He finds some comfort via a relationship with his neighbor (Ryan) and her young daughter (Breslin) who triggers memories of his own missing child. Anchored by a tour-de-force performance from Lewis, Kerrigan?s gritty, puzzling work defies expectations with a bracing immediacy  HFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Somewhere between a thriller and a clinical study in schizophrenia, &amp;quot;Keane&amp;quot; is a movie that puts you so far into someone else's head you may have forgotten your own name by the time it's over. It's also the story of one of those marginal people on the periphery of urban life, so familiar to most of us, so willfully invisible to most of us. Washington Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lodge Kerrigan is one of the great, though largely unheralded, filmmakers of our time, and with Keane, his third feature, he finally shows himself to be in full command of his uncompromising talent. Austin Chronicle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;amp;id=8191" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is a week-day night we'll have a brief (but what should to prove engrossing meetup discussion) at a local restaurant afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the Q &amp;amp; A session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193871848000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191878325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Keane- Another Character Study- Director Present</name><id>6513321</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193698800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6513321/</event_url></item>