<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Film description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danny McBride and James Franco team up for an epic comedy adventure set  in a fantastical world&amp;mdash;Your Highness.Thadeous (McBride) has spent his  life watching his perfect older brother Fabious (Franco) embark upon  valiant journeys and win the hearts &lt;span&gt; of his people. But when Fabious&amp;rsquo; bride-to-be, Belladonna (Zooey  Deschanel), gets kidnapped by the evil wizard Leezar (Justin Theroux),  the king gives his deadbeat son an ultimatum: Man up and help rescue her  or get cut off.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Half-assedly embarking upon his first quest, Thadeous joins Fabious to  trek across the perilous outlands and free the princess.  Joined by  Isabel (Natalie Portman)&amp;mdash;an elusive warrior with a dangerous agenda of  her own&amp;mdash;the brothers must vanquish horrific creatures and knights before  they can reach Belladonna. If Thadeous can find his inner hero, he can  help his brother prevent the destruction of his land.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby at 7:00 p.m. for the 7:30 p.m. show, off to the right as you come in.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302826239000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>The movie starts at 7:35, so meet in the lobby at 7.  

I've been sick and so I've changed this to a NoOrg. I'll make it if I can.

Please note: I don't have movie passes everyone will be buying tickets themselves (retail is $10.50 each).</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300914416000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Your Highness</name><id>17031175</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302822000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/17031175/</event_url></item>