<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Higginson Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02865</zip><lat>41.887131</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.727.1704</phone><name>Rock Spot Climbing</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>721392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! I'm scheduling a reoccurring event on Mondays at Rock Spot Climbing's Lincoln, RI location (formerly RI Rock Gym). I set it at 6:30pm, but of course since the gym is open until midnight if you come a little later you'll probably still find someone to climb with. Lately, most of us have been arriving around 7/7:30. &lt;strong&gt;Please post the time you expect to arrive so we don't miss each other.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that I can climb again I will try to make it every week, but please also use the mailing list to get in touch with other members if you need a carpool or want to make sure you'll have a belay partner. If you don't know how to belay yet, please call RSC Lincoln 401-727-1704 and let them know you're coming and will need a lesson. It'll take about 45 minutes. If you've never climbed at RSC but already know how to belay, you'll need to take a quick belay test, no need to call ahead for that. Special Meetup Prices: Mention that you're there for the Meetup and you'll pay $15 if you need gear and/or a lesson, and just $10 if you have your own gear! It's also hospitality night so if you're bringing a friend who's not in the meetup group but they work at a restaurant or hotel tell them to bring proof of employment and they'll get the same discount prices as you. What a deal! Climb on! ~Kat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.rockspotclimbing.com for more info on the gym.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Mention Meetup at the front desk</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kat Waterhouse</member_name><member_id>8778978</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366076627000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Clmbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Rock-Climbers</urlname><id>1497941</id><group_lat>41.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Rock Climbers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287419681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Nights at Rock Spot Lincoln</name><id>wdkrpyrgbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366065000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Rock-Climbers/events/113553452/</event_url></item>