<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>building no.3 room 133</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.369549</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT</name><city>cambridge</city><id>6364162</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114937</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This has a potential of being a really great event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rather than individually attending it may be if people are interested we can all meet at the mass ave entrance of MIT and sit together. If there is interest we can also go grab a bite to eat afterwards in Centra sq.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a brief description of the author and what she will be talking about&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bio: Alpa Shah is a social anthropologist at Goldsmiths, University of London. She is interested in inequality and efforts to address it. She has drawn on more than a decade of field research in India to explore how marginalised people experience indigenous rights activism and Adivasi politics; poverty, the developmental state and corruption; seasonal casual labour migration and transformations in the agrarian economy; the state, education and positive action policies; and the radical left and emancipatory politics, notably the Maoist movement. She is the author of In the Shadows of the State: Indigenous Politics, Environmentalism and Insurgency in Jharkhand, India. Durham and London: Duke University Press, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>vaibhav</member_name><member_id>10494016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333320440000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332711583000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Go to....Forest Notes on the Maoists..in India</name><id>57817272</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333310400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/57817272/</event_url></item>