<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Cabot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01850</zip><lat>42.650002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Brewery Exchange</name><city>Lowell</city><id>297917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.309998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dinner reservations have been increased to 12 people but I am sure we can add others if you want to join us at 6. Tickets to the Spread Eagles are sold at the Brewery that night and are first come first serve. I called to confirm that there ARE tickets available but they couldn't confirm how many, so plan accordingly. It looks like about 24 for the concert...WOW, should be a fun time! See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPREAD EAGLE - A Tribute To The Eagles!&lt;br /&gt;The Second Best Eagles Show You'll Ever See...&lt;br /&gt;The Brewery Exchange (Playloft Upstairs) 201 Cabot St Lowell MA &lt;br /&gt;$10 &lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 8pm - show begins at 9, cash bar is available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spread Eagle: Tribute To The Eagles is a six-piece Eagles Tribute Band based out of north-central Massachusetts. They formed as a direct result of passion for the music of The Eagles, and they share a yearning to perpetuate that timeless music and sweet vocal harmony.  The Eagles have given us 30 years of musical artistry both, as a group, and as individual artists. Spread Eagle: Tribute To The Eagles covers their old, their new, their ballads, and those socially and politically provocative hits everybody has come to love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to a great evening...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185882877000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183407985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>After the Lowell Folk Fest</name><id>5965449</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185660000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/5965449/</event_url></item>