<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>258 Andover St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01833</zip><lat>42.718019</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-352-7926</phone><name>Black Swan Country Club</name><city>Georgetown</city><id>1419196</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.012106</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Break out your stonewashed jeans, neon and sunglasses for Back to the 80&amp;#8242;s Night!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's go dance the night away to 80's music featuring all our favorite 80&amp;#8242;s music by NUIMAGE Entertainment, Light Snacks &amp;amp; Desserts, Cash Bar and prizes for the best 80&amp;#8242;s outfit (optional 80&amp;#8242;s dress). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are only $10.00 per person and can be purchased by calling 978-352-7926 x205 ask for Carol, tell her you are with the &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Donna Meetup&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; group, give her your credit card # and she will charge your card for the ticket(s), or you can send her a check.  You are responsible for calling and paying for your own ticket(s). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where to meet in the room where the dance is, look for the meetup tables they will be holding 2 for us and if there is enough interest we will call for more tables.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to update your RSVP when you have call in for your ticket so we know to be looking for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nov/Dec:  November 1-Dec 11 we will be collecting donations for the Lazarus House in Lawrence.  If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Most of all don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank You&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the Meetup table(s).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290292907000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288749889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go back to the 80's and dance, baby dance!</name><id>15319402</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290214800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15319402/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/d/c/global_19354572.jpeg</photo_url></item>