<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Danforth St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.317614</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>202-213-9267</phone><name>Spontaneous Celebrations</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>796278</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105601</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>www.handreach.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Join us Tuesdays beginning November 2 from 7:00pm to 9:00pm at Spontaneous Celebrations! Spontaneous Celebrations is located at 45 Danforth St. Jamaica Plain MA, 02130. Stony Brook is the closest MBTA stop.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The HandReach Beat Brigade is a program that seeks to empower local youth through healing modalities such as drumming, rehabilitation therapy, and leadership development through assisting child trauma survivors locally and abroad. The Beat Brigade's purpose is to offer training and experience for local youth to travel internationally to train teams in developing countries who work with pediatric trauma patients, particularly those with major burn injuries and amputations.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Drum therapy is an ancient approach that uses rhythm to promote healing and self-expression. Ample research indicates that drumming accelerates physical healing, boosts the immune system, produces feelings of well-being and a release of emotional trauma, and promotes reintegration of self.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Studies have demonstrated the calming, focusing, and healing effects of drumming on trauma patients, autistic children, emotionally disturbed teens, recovering addicts, Alzheimer's patients, and prison and homeless populations. Study results demonstrate that drumming is a valuable treatment for stress, fatigue, anxiety, hypertension, asthma, chronic pain, arthritis, mental illness, migraines, cancer, multiple sclerosis, Parkinson's disease, stroke, paralysis, emotional disorders, and a wide range of physical disabilities. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Martin Isaac</member_name><member_id>5687062</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288743427000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Rhythm Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-drum-circle</urlname><id>617617</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288725510000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HandReach Beat Brigade: empowering local youth- meeting in JP Nov. 2</name><id>15313849</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288738800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-drum-circle/events/15313849/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/1/global_8679361.jpeg</photo_url></item>