<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>280 Argilla Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.681907</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Castle Hill</name><city>Ipswich </city><id>1062213</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.777473</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Greening of the Great House Holiday Open House.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12/4 UPDATE: To save on the parking cost let's meetup at Bruni's marketplace were we can pile in a couple of cars and split the  cost of parking.  We will be at the Market on Route 133.  We will be there at 12:15, and I will be on the right hand side of the parking lot, in front of my Silver Corolla.  We will leave there promptly at 12:45 to meet everyone else at the event.  If you plan on car pooling into Castle Hill please be @ Bruni's so we can go together or we will see you at Castle Hill. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrate the magic of the holidays at the Crane Estate Holiday Open House, featuring self-guided tours of the Great House festively decorated by area florists and designers. Family craft and “I Spy” available for younger visitors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A national treasure, this magnificent mansion offers an opulent glimpse of the Crane family’s life in the roaring 20’s. Tours feature beautifully appointed rooms with ornate woodcarvings, luxurious Italian marble, sterling silver fixtures, and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A little History about Castle Hill on the Crane Estate:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes Castle Hill a special place?&lt;br /&gt;Centuries before becoming a grand summer estate owned by one of America’s wealthiest families, Castle Hill was well known by Native Americans, who called the area Agawam, referring to its rich fishery. John Winthrop, Jr., son of the first governor of the Massachusetts Bay Colony, laid claim to Castle Hill in 1637. For more than two centuries, a succession of owners farmed the land. Beginning in the 1880s, J. B. Brown transformed Castle Hill Farm from an agricultural holding into a gentleman’s farm, improving roadways and plantings and renovating his modest farmhouse into a rambling, shingle-style cottage that is now &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cost: members Adult $8, Child $5.   Nonmembers: Adult $12, Child $8 &lt;br /&gt;Phone: 978.356.4351 x4015 &lt;br /&gt;E-mail: neregion@ttor.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children are welcome at this event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260465433000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252632943000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Open house at Castle Hill.</name><id>11343493</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260122400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11343493/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/5/global_10638389.jpeg</photo_url></item>