<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>711 Atlantic Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-861-4940</phone><name>WorkBar Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>1138289</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056473</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;07:00 - 07:30 Fast networking, exchange business cards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;07:30 - 08:00 Building a Killer Content Strategy - Discovering Your Inner Expert&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;08:00 - 08:30 Live Case Study - Building a Content Strategy - we will choose a member to help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content Strategy - Are you creating content that attracts your customers? Are you building credibility with the right audience? Creating unique and valuable content for your customers online is one of the single most important parts of your marketing efforts. A well written article with the right marketing efforts can drive hundreds and sometimes thousands of potential customers a day to your site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you leverage this? By creating a simple and sound strategy for creating, distributing, and measuring the results of your content. In this presentation, we will cover: 1. How to identify the "right" content for your business 2. How to create and schedule your content 3. Where to distribute your content to drive prospective customers 4. How to measure your results Rinse. and Repeat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presenter: Keith Griffis - SimpleMediaMarketing &amp;amp; IsItIndie.com As the new organizer, I am interested in meeting everyone and start bringing the activity back to this group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in presenting on a topic, suggest it or email me Keith.Griffis@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bio: I am a social media and online marketing mentor specializing in making web technology simple. I help small to mid-size business maximize their online marketing activities in a simple and sustainable way. My background is in engineering and marketing. I am an engineer and MBA with 12+ years in web development and internet marketing. I have worked in marketing with businesses ranging from $300K to $250M.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, I have developed websites for artists, small businesses, and online magazines. This will follow in the successful format of the past meetups of this group. I am in the lookout for a permanent location, but have reached out to workbar and the Microsoft NERD center. I would prefer to host this at a member's business location to provide exposure for the business owner and to cultivate the community.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Keith</member_name><member_id>6153796</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329436242000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Marketing Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising</urlname><id>984032</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Internet Marketing and Advertising  Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316887025000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Building a Killer Content Strategy</name><id>34801362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320969600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising/events/34801362/</event_url></item>