<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In October (how did it get to be October already?!) we're reading &lt;em&gt;Gone Girl&lt;/em&gt; by Gillian Flynn, a psychological thriller perfect for Halloween! &lt;em&gt;So&lt;/em&gt; much in this book to talk about. Also, of course October at Chaibo means pumpkin lattes and whoopie pies. Yum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of the book from Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On the day of their fifth wedding anniversary, Nick's wife Amy disappears. There are signs of struggle in the house and Nick quickly becomes the prime suspect. It doesn't help that Nick hasn't been completely honest with the police and, as Amy's case drags out for weeks, more and more vilifying evidence appears against him. Nick, however, maintains his innocence. Told from alternating points of view between Nick and Amy, Gillian Flynn creates an untrustworthy world that changes chapter-to-chapter. Calling&lt;/em&gt; Gone Girl &lt;em&gt;a psychological thriller is an understatement. As revelation after revelation unfolds, it becomes clear that the truth does not exist in the middle of Nick and Amy's points of view; in fact, the truth is far more dark, more twisted, and more creepy than you can imagine.&lt;/em&gt; Gone Girl &lt;em&gt;is masterfully plotted from start to finish and the suspense doesn't waver for one page. It's one of those books you will feel the need to discuss immediately after finishing because the ending doesn't just come; it punches you in the gut.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/c/8/event_19784744.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351261525000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349724670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Gone Girl by Gillian Flynn</name><id>86079732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351206000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/86079732/</event_url></item>