<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>640 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.348854</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Auditorium (Room 101), College of Communication, Boston University</name><city>Boston</city><id>4063352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Liberty at Boston University welcomes Dr. Tom G. Palmer &amp;#147;Adventures in International Freedom&amp;#148; Wednesday, October 26, 2011, 5:30 p.m. Auditorium (Room 101), College of Communication, Boston University 640 Commonwealth Avenue Boston, Massachusetts Did you know there are freedom movements in Afghanistan, Pakistan, Malaysia, China, Russia, Slovakia, and Nigeria? Tom Palmer travels the globe to help create and nurture organizations committed to advancing human freedom, helping champions of freedom create a better world. Dr. Palmer is Executive Vice President for International Programs of the Atlas Economic Research Foundation. Atlas supports an international network of more than 400 free-market organizations in over 80 countries. To learn about its mission, see its website and video, &amp;#147;Atlas Network: Champions of Freedom.&amp;#148; Dr. Palmer is also a Senior Fellow at the Cato Institute and Director of Cato University, the Institute&amp;#146;s educational arm. He is the author of Realizing Freedom: The Theory, History, and Practice of Liberty. He received his BA from St. Johns College, MD, his MA in philosophy from The Catholic University of America, and his doctorate from Oxford University. Please join us for this exciting event. It is guaranteed to give you a new perspective on the world! Reception to follow: Please join us after the event for refreshments and conversation with our guest. Price: $0.00 Register here: &lt;a href="http://www.libertybu.com/?page_id=145&amp;amp;regevent_action=register&amp;amp;event_id=4&amp;amp;name_of_event=Adventures%20in%20International%20Freedom%20with%20Dr.%20Tom%20Palmer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.libertybu....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319668931000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319067613000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Adventures in International Freedom with Dr. Tom Palmer </name><id>38029002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319664600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/38029002/</event_url></item>