<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>65 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.398327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 591-2100</phone><name>Orleans Bar &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669349</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123787</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets kick this season off right with the Warren Miller Movie and some pre-drinks and food at Orleans Restaurant in Davis Sq Somerville.  This years movie is called &amp;quot;Wintervention&amp;quot; and looks like a great movie - check out the trailer. &lt;a href="http://www.skinet.com/warrenmiller/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.skinet.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm Early arrivals at Orleans  - come early if you want to order food.&lt;br /&gt;6:40pm Somerville Theatre - We will sit in the center of balcony &lt;br /&gt;9:30pm When movie lets out we will be back at Orleans for a larger celebration&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warren Miller movies are the gold standard for all ski/snowboard movies. Every Fall for 50 years the Warren Miller team has toured the country to show off its latest creation. It is not just a movie, its an event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ticket price ($20) may seem like a lot for a movie BUT you get several 2 for 1 lift tickets and other give-aways. You will make back your admission price - some years i go twice just to get the deals :).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7pm but we will meet at a bar for drinks and snacks before the show and go over as a group. If people want to meet early we can get dinner. We can also have a few post-movie beers as well. This will be a great way to meet members of this meet up and make some connections before the snow starts falling. The Somerville Theatre is in the middle of Davis Sq, about a 50 ft walk from the RedLine station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy your tickets on your own as soon as possible, it will sell out - Somerville Theatre&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://feitheatres.com/somerville-theatre/events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://feitheatres.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;also check out the Warren Miller web site&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skinet.com/warrenmiller/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.skinet.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>look for us just past the entrance to Orleans!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288910791000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287949789000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Warren Miller Ski Movie + pre-meetup</name><id>15212916</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288906200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/15212916/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/8/global_14726280.jpeg</photo_url></item>