<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1555 Asylum Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06117</zip><lat>41.777724</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-231-9443</phone><name>Elizabeth Park Rose Garden</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>688473</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.717725</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will meet up with Al-rs Group  &lt;br /&gt;THE BAND &lt;br /&gt;Formed in 1986, the Floyd Patterson Band has been regarded by many over the years to be a Pioneer Valley favorite. With material ranging from the 1950s to present, the group always brings home their own style of quality performance .Whether &amp;quot;old school&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;new school&amp;quot; music , state fairs or private situations, the Floyd Patterson Band never fails to keep their audiences satisfied. As evidenced by the awards they've received in past years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Park: &lt;br /&gt;Its also good to make food right there on site, and i usually bring the grillo to this spot for some cooking &lt;br /&gt;something. Iits available for others in the group too.. &lt;br /&gt;I do what i can to keep people from complaining by having the grill in our immediate area and away from the crowd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your chairs, blankets, bug spray, food and your own favourite bug juice, a lot of us share our stuff with the others so offer some to your fellow attendees too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancels the *MEETUP* event, (The performers usually play inside if it rains) since i dont like the indoors things, you can go, i like the event &amp;quot;outside&amp;quot; so we can socialize and get to meet each other and move around freely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Think of it this way, ITS THE SOCIALIZATION AND INTERACTION BETWEEN THE PEOPLE THAT MAKES THE EVENT, NOT necessarily THE MUSIC, THE MUSIC IS THE BACKGROUND ! but we pick music most would enjoy and if you want to go up to the front also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I update as the weather approaches on the day &lt;br /&gt;i try to get there before 5:30 but that depends on traffic..etc..so its an apx time. &lt;br /&gt;If you get there early, check out the gardens..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Park is located at the corner of Prospect Avenue and Asylum Avenue on the Hartford / West Hartford line. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-84 West bound to Exit 48 (Asylum Street).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay to the Right on Asylum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow for approximately 1.8 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn left into the park (1555 Asylum Avenue, West Hartford). 06117&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park where you see it, its not that bad. but you may have to look a bit if you are late..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-84 East bound to Exit 44 (Prospect Ave)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Straight thru stop sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Left at light onto Prospect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow approximately 1.8 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrance on Left (915 Prospect, Hartford)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park where you find a place.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the back by the Gazebo</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215208369000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214768770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Floyd Paterson Band</name><id>8240791</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215035100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/8240791/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/5/global_2981797.jpeg</photo_url></item>