<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>If you are passionate about Integral Theory, Evolutionary Philosophy or Eastern Spiritual Approaches you are probably a Romantic. In this talk, Jeff Carreira will outline the exciting story of a view of reality that is probably central to your own thinking even if you don’t realize it. In the 18th century German Idealists and English Romantic Poets became convinced that the universe is not a mechanism like a clock, but is actually a dynamic evolving organic whole system. This explosive idea came to American and formed the foundations of the American Transcendentalism of the 18th century, the American Pragmatism of the 19th Century, and the Beat Movement, 1960’s Counter Culture and East/West Spirituality of the 20th Century. Please join us for this fascinating tour through the historical development of your own mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the story of American Romanticism unfolds you will find answers to questions you didn’t even know you had. Sometimes our interest in alternative ideas seems out of step with the rest of our culture, When seen in a historical context these ideas become part of a rich and valuable tradition of American thought. &lt;b&gt;Seeing this context will strengthen your understanding, conviction and confidence in the ideas and attitudes that you are already passionate about.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;As Director of Education at EnlightenNext, Jeff Carreira oversees the education and membership programs which support a growing global network of individuals committed to guiding humanity through an evolutionary leap in consciousness. Over the past 16 years he has become one of the leading representatives of EnlightenNext founder Andrew Cohen and his teaching of Evolutionary Enlightenment. Carreira gives talks and seminars around the world and also trains and supervises other teachers and seminar leaders. Prior to his involvement with EnlightenNext, Carreira spent five years working as a research engineer before obtaining a Master's degree in Education and spent the following twelve years in teaching and educational management.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270942166000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268429695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Are You A Romantic?: Exploring the Roots of Alternative Spirituality in America</name><id>12861914</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270768500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/12861914/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/f/global_7098607.jpeg</photo_url></item>