<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-245-1525</phone><name>Harrington's Pub</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>733190</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;***Please Update your RSVPs and indicate approximate ETA.&amp;nbsp;Arrive Early if you can to avoid any lines. A&amp;nbsp;bunch of people should be there mid to late afternoon.&amp;nbsp;The place will be packed after 5pm.&amp;nbsp;E Mail others who are attending to coordinate. If you plan to be there a while and need to eat I strongly sugggest putting&amp;nbsp;your name in for a table.***&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one is for the suburban folks. We are returning after last years madness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives &lt;a href="http://www.RedSoxNatives.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;are inviting any available Boston Happy Hour members to celebrate St Patricks Day at Harrington's Food and Spirits in downtown Wakefield. Harrington's is a cozy Irish Restaurant and Pub with two floors. We have been there before. The food is great too. &lt;a href="http://www.harringtonspub.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harrington's is all Irish, all day, all night, on both floors. There is live entertainment all day at Harrington's with Sligo Road, Outside Madra, Casterbridge Union, Dave O'Sobol and Traditional Irish Seisiun. There is $10.00 cover after 2 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear your green and be there at 5:00 pm or afterward. Please RSVP and let us know if and at approximately what time you will join us. Many of us will be having dinner during the course of the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking in downtown Wakefield in the public lot across from Harrington's and along Water and Main Streets. The location is T accessible by the 136 and 137 Bus from the Orange Line in Malden Center And Commuter Rail accessible from North Station by the Reading and Haverhill Trains stopping at Wakefield with a less than 10 minute walk up Albion to Main to Water Street. &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own bar tab or pay in cash as you order or maintain your bar tab and settle with your server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be there until at least 10pm. Last year a few of us closed the place and had to walk home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask Dan or the Hostess for the Red Sox Natives Meetup, Last year we were on the second floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300497849000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>A large group of us went last year and we had a blast...and stuff happened.</why><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297534919000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>St Patrick's Day  with the Red Sox Natives at Harrington's Pub</name><id>16541061</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300395600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/16541061/</event_url></item>