<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In September we're celebrating the cooler weather and change of seasons with a fondue night book discussion! We'll get our chocolate on as we enjoy Chaibo's famous fondue while discussing &lt;em&gt;Charlie and the Chocolate Factory&lt;/em&gt; by Roald Dahl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of Chaibo's chocolate fondue, from their &lt;a href="http://www.chaibo.com/menu.html"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;, along with a description of the book from an Amazon reviewer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to expect with a &lt;br /&gt;

Chaibo Fondue Creation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You will be presented with a Fondue Pot containing an ample amount of warm melted chocolate. The chocolate is ready and waiting for you to gently dip&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;(or if you prefer to ram in and smother)&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;the following delectable treats:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Strawberries • Banana Chunks • Marshmallows Brownies • Cheesecake • Rice Krispy Treats&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last time we ordered one pot of milk chocolate and one pot of white chocolate fondue, and all dug in. YUM!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Charlie and the Chocolate Factory&lt;/span&gt; by Roald Dahl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Along with his other classic,&lt;/em&gt; James and the Giant Peach&lt;em&gt;, Roald Dahl's&lt;/em&gt; Charlie and the Chocolate Factory &lt;em&gt;stands at the top of the heap when it comes to children's books. This is a pure classic of imagination, storytelling and magic. Far superior to the film (where Willy Wonka becomes the title character), the book tells the story from Charlie Bucket's point of view. Charlie, who lives with his four ancient grandparents and his mother in a one-room house, is the kind of child who can only dream about his future, since his family has barely enough money to survive. When the Wonka chocolatier announces that five golden tickets to visit the aged factory have been carefully tucked inside chocolate bars the world over, Charlie's dreams are suddenly wide open. He stumbles on some money in the street, purchases a chocolate bar and is thrust into the limelight beccoming one of the five lucky vistors. The rest of the tale is one of scrumptous folly and nerve-wracking sentiment, highlighted by magical workers (the one and only Oompa Loompas), the etheral Willy Wonka, a host of loony characters - both adults and kids - and a thrill ride in a factory where time stands still and also rocks forwards, backwards, sideways and then some! It's a classic tale of the triumph of good over evil, generosity over greed and family over fair-weathered friends. Sure to be enjoyed by children of all ages, adults included, this is the best children's book ever written.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348798697000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344627820000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion and Fondue Night-Charlie and the Chocolate Factory by Roald Dahl</name><id>77211362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348786800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/77211362/</event_url></item>