<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A walk through Brookline's Larz Anderson Park, a former country estate that includes lovely gardens and a pond. The 'carriage house' mansion is now the home of the Liz Anderson Auto Museum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original owner of the land now known as Larz Anderson Park was&lt;br /&gt;Isabel Anderson?s maternal grandfather, William Fletcher Weld. Isabel?s cousin,&lt;br /&gt;also named William Fletcher Weld, later inherited it. In 1899, shortly after their&lt;br /&gt;marriage, Larz and Isabel Anderson purchased the 64 acres of land in Brookline.&lt;br /&gt;When the Andersons acquired the property, there were few major landscape&lt;br /&gt;features in place. They quickly set about designing the land to suit their needs as&lt;br /&gt;a summer estate. They began by naming the estate Weld after Isabel?s&lt;br /&gt;grandfather.&lt;br /&gt;The Andersons had a keen sense of their important place in history and&lt;br /&gt;knew that they could benefit others by leaving this as their legacy. Upon her&lt;br /&gt;death in 1948, Isabel left Weld to the Town of Brookline to be used for public&lt;br /&gt;recreation, charitable purposes, or public education.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mot.org/Museum/tour.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mot.org/Mu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour includes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Carriage House K Italian Garden&lt;br /&gt;B Putterham School L Deer Park&lt;br /&gt;C Rond Point M Allée&lt;br /&gt;D Water Garden N Goddard Ave. Houses&lt;br /&gt;E Chinese Garden O Polo Field&lt;br /&gt;F Entrance to Greenhouse Complex P Tenement&lt;br /&gt;G Tennis Court Q Washington House&lt;br /&gt;H Anderson Residence R Coachman?s Cottage&lt;br /&gt;I Japanese Garden S Gardener?s Cottage&lt;br /&gt;J Bowling Green&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200921515000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196338543000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Larz Anderson Park walk</name><id>6824196</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200528000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6824196/</event_url></item>