<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Wellesley St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02493</zip><lat>42.360115</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 893-1162 </phone><name>Land's Sake Farm</name><city>Weston</city><id>958104</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.292066</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Biochar: Old Technology and New Solutions&lt;br /&gt;Date: Saturday, October 16th, 2010; 9:00am-2:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Location: Land's Sake Farm, 90 Wellesley Street&lt;br /&gt;Presenters: Bob Wells and Peter Hirst&lt;br /&gt;Fee: $25 for Landsake members, $35 for non-members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special this month: I'll reimburse $10 off the fee for each of the first 5 attendees to sign up.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To attend this workshop, please RSVP to this meetup page AND to the &lt;a href="http://landssake.org/education/workshop/registration" target="_blank"&gt;Landsake.org page&lt;/a&gt;.  They ask registrants to mail payment to their office at 27 Crescent St. in Weston MA.  Checks may be made out to Land's Sake. In the memo line, include &amp;quot;Biochar Workshop&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Biochar is an emerging technology based on centuries old techniques and principles for producing charcoal. Biochar is the byproduct when biomass is burned or heated with a minimum of oxygen. It is primarily used to enhance soil fertility and helps improve the health of plants, increases yields, reduces costs and improves food’s nutritional quality/density. Making biochar by pyrolysis also produces energy. When this energy is captured biochar can be turned into electricity, space heat or diesel (this workshop will focus on the soil fertility aspects and touch upon these other uses.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info about the workshop, see the &lt;a href="http://landssake.org/education/adult_workshops" target="_blank"&gt;Adult &amp;amp; Family Education page in the Landssake website&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, a great website to learn more about biochar is &lt;a href="http://www.biochar-international.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.biochar-international.org/&lt;/a&gt;.  Here's a sample from Bill McKibben:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We can, literally, start sucking some of the carbon that our predecessors have poured into the atmosphere down through our weeds and stalks and stick it back in the ground. We can run the movie backward. We can unmine some of the coal, undrill some of the oil. We can take at least pieces of the Earth and – this is something we haven’t done for quite a while – leave them Better Than We Found Them.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Dobbelaar</member_name><member_id>2225625</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287411642000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Alternative Energy Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>AltEnergyBoston</urlname><id>219161</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Area Alternative Energy Supporters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284006876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Meetup: Biochar Workshop</name><id>14707922</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287234000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/AltEnergyBoston/events/14707922/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/f/6/global_17820758.jpeg</photo_url></item>