<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>cambridge</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366810</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Central square, cambridge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8949932</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106010</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;1984 to Now: The Ongoing Disaster in Bhopal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Often referred to as the world's worst industrial disaster, Bhopal still remains a global symbol of corporate negligence. Bhopal didn't start on the night of the tragedy; Bhopal still has not ended. This tragedy of multinational proportions continues in the abandoned factory's corpse, as it leaks its poisons into the community drinking water. It continues in Indian and American court rooms, as Union Carbide and Dow attempt to deny their responsibilities. It continues in the generations of affected Bhopalis, as they face a wide range of health issues. Bhopal lives on in the hearts and in the minds of thousands of activists worldwide, as they tirelessly fight for justice that should have come 27 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ironically, Dow chemicals , which has responsibilities now to clean up Bhopal, and has left several million people disabled around the world ( because of Bhopal, and Agent Orange in Vietnam, and other toxic wastes in Midland Michigan and Nicaragua), is the main sponsor of the Paralympics 2012 in London .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us in a peaceful candle-light vigil to protest this hypocrisy of Dow chemicals and urge them to own up to their responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today: Tuesday Aug 28th, 8pm &lt;br /&gt;

at: Central square&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346209940000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346175327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Candle-light vigil to protest Dow's partnership with the paralympics</name><id>79749962</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346198400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/79749962/</event_url></item>