<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Star Room on 4th Floor</address_2><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.361753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 577-8812</phone><name>MIT Stata Center - Star Room</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>588318</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091419</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;**********************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Agenda&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**********************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;State-of-the-art In Semantic Interpretation of Health Care Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Your clinical records have long been recorded either on paper, in monolithic medical record systems like EPIC, or in short-lived tools which never see sufficient development time to have interfaces with other systems. Initiatives like the Affordable Care Act in the US and Electronic Health Records for Clinical Research in Europe seek to get more use out of your clinical data for drug research, machine-assisted medication interaction and adverse event detection, efficacy evaluation, and even simple patient portability. Recent work by HL7 effectively defines the RDF representation for the clinical data exchange format (CCDA) mandated by the US government. Joint industry and academic projects in Europe also express clinical data in RDF for drug research and translational medicine. From SMART Platforms's commoditized smart-phone apps to revolutions in clinical trial submissions, semantic representation of clinical data stands to change our health efficiency and outcomes for the better.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/c/c/event_185178892.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eric Prud'hommeaux is a sanitation engineer employed by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at MIT. While at W3C, he has edited and participated in the development of many specifications, extending open source tools like libwww, Apache, Mozilla, MySQL and SWObjects to implement and test new protocols. His past standards work includes HTTP 1.1, PEP, SOAP, SAWSDL, RDF, SPARQL and SQL Direct Mapping. The latter work aims to connect existing relational data via the Semantic Web without performance penalty. The Semantic Web and relational database work formed the backbone of several projects in W3C's Semantic Web in Health Care and Life Sciences Interest Group. This group has established a large corpus of biological and chemical data to connect to clinical data for research and health care support. Accompanying work on FHIR and C-CDA provides researchers and patients with "meaningful use" of health records and biological knowledge.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Rm 32-D463, 4th floor, Star Conference Room, Stata Center, MIT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kingsley Idehen</member_name><member_id>3320828</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lee Feigenbaum</member_name><member_id>8546101</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted Slater</member_name><member_id>9149630</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Booth</member_name><member_id>47371092</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1371048156000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Semantic Web Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1336198</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge Semantic Web</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304603588000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Semantic Web Monthly Meetup</name><id>fjrzqyrjbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370988000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group/events/111641712/</event_url></item>