<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rt. 302 Crawford Notch</address_2><address_1>Willey House Site</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03812</zip><lat>44.090000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kedron Flume Trailhead</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>368990</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.279999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Willey Range Traverse - featuring Mt. Tom, Mt. Field &amp;amp; Mt. Willey&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;A perfect hike to assist you in your New Hampshire 48 quest!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rising sharply to the west of Crawford Notch, the Willey Range is topped by Mounts Tom, Willey &amp;amp; Field. These peaks are close together, and the classic way to bag them is to do all three of them in one trip.  On a clear day they afford spectacular views of the Presidential Range, the Pemigewasset Wilderness, the Hancocks and Cardigan.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our Route:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will make our way to the summit of Mt. Tom via the Avalon, A-Z &amp;amp; Mt. Tom Spur trails. From the summit of Mt. Tom we will take the Willey Range Trail to the summit of Mt. Field &amp;amp; on to the summit of Mt. Willey. Our descent will be via the Kedron Flume Trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Total Distance:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;8.55 miles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;7 hours, 22 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meetup Time &amp;amp; Car Spot:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 8:45 am at the Kedron Flume Trailhead, located at the Willey House site. We will spot a car here and then take a short drive to the Avalon Trailhead located at the Crawford Station Depot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trip Notes:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt. Tom&lt;/b&gt;, 4,051, is the northern most peak of the Willey Range. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mount Field&lt;/b&gt; is named after Darby Field, who in 1642 made the first known ascent of Mount Washington. At 4,340 feet, Mount Field is the highest peak of the Willey Range. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mount Willey&lt;/b&gt; is named after Samuel Willey, Jr. and his family, who in 1825 moved into a house in Crawford Notch. Tragically the family was killed a year later in August 1826 during a landslide.  At 4,285 feet, Mount Willey is the southernmost and second highest in the Wiley Range. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a Meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup a success. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that your late or lost.  Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that you are qualified to join us on this White Mountain hiking adventure &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please send your email and cell number when you rsvp to my direct email: &lt;br /&gt;tourbusiness@altazone.com &lt;br /&gt;I will email you a detailed Trip Report outlining our route. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Check out photos from a past Meetup to Tom, Field &amp;amp; Willey at:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/photos/228951/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the NEHAAG disclaimer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215890291000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214939480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Willey Range Traverse - featuring Mt. Tom, Mt. Field &amp; Mt. Willey </name><id>8255964</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215261900000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8255964/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/7/a/global_4651402.jpeg</photo_url></item>