<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What does the REAL Christmas Story have to do with Advanced Energy Healing?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The same group who preserved the COMPLETE records of Jesus' birth, also saved all the info about the REAL purpose he came. He was MUCH MORE that a singular spiritual being as is currently believed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He was called &amp;quot;Jeshua 12&amp;quot; and his mission included bringing self-help energy healing techniques to humanity, as necessary to spiritually survive severely disruptive energetic changes known for eons to arrive here Dec 21, 2012.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since all other records have since been twisted and perverted, we can now understand why the original records were hidden and cloistered so they could be brought back now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this Meetup, a recording will be played telling the soulful story of Jeshua's arrival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These records were preserved by the Melchizedek Cloister Emerald Order (MCEO), described on this link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.azuritepress.com/melchizedek_cloister.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.azuritepre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As it turns out, the group who preserved these records also preserved WAY more information, which is vital for us to know at this time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To view a description of &amp;quot;The Real Christmas Story&amp;quot; which will be played and discussed this time, click on the link below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.azuritepress.com/products_us/chr_hb.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.azuritepre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Meetup adjourns at 9:00 PM. Please bring your own refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Get on I-93 from wherever you are. We are approx. half an hour north of Concord, NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get off on exit 22. At the end of the ramp go North on Rt. 127 (toward Gaza). In approx. 1.5 miles you will come to a stop sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn left, going North on Rt 132. Watch for mailbox number 298 on the right side of the road, approx. 1.5 mi. up. A tan building with semi-circular window is across the street, on the left side. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go up the first driveway into the property, which has a Meetup sign at the end. Do NOT go up the second driveway which has a sign &amp;quot;ULCS Clinic&amp;quot;. No parking is allowed there, so if you get that far, turn around in that driveway and go back and up the first driveway. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enter through the front door, where you will see another Meetup sign. No need to knock. Just go on in and down the stairs and have a seat in the classroom. If you are arriving early for a private appointment, have a seat in the waiting room instead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293071798000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Awakening Indigoes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>IndigoInsights</urlname><id>1319438</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Indigo Insights: Awakening to our Full Potential</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289188513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The REAL Christmas Story (from Cloistered Records)</name><id>15374838</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293058800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/IndigoInsights/events/15374838/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/1/global_18743441.jpeg</photo_url></item>