<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Nahant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01945</zip><lat>42.503437</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Corinthian Yacht Club</name><city>Marblehead</city><id>6960012</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.835091</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/6/7/2/event_115310802.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The 2012 11th Women's Sailing Conference sponsored by BoatUS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming ... the 11th Women's Sailing Conference sponsored by BoatUS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;June 2, 2012 at the Corinthian Yacht Club, Marblehead MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The registration form is now available! CLICK for a printable copy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be sure to print out the Waiver, Release and Assumption of Risk Form and return it with your Registration Form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.womensailing.org/Registration_2012.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.womensailing.org/Registration_2012.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.womensailing.org/NWSAWSFwaiver.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.womensailing.org/NWSAWSFwaiver.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, June 2, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

8:00am until 7:00pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Corinthian Yacht Club, Marblehead MA, 1 Nahant St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

A full day of workshops, demonstrations, on land and on-the-water; dinner and a speaker included. Ladies, this annual event is NOT to be missed! &lt;br /&gt;

On June 4, 2011 the Corinthian Yacht Club hosted the 10th annual Women’s Sailing Conference. The weather was picture perfect ...– warm day, lots of sun and morning strong breeze died down to provide a gorgeous afternoon. The women came from 14 different stats including California, Florida and West Virginia to learn, network and get inspired. They were not disappointed. &lt;br /&gt;

The conference, whose primary sponsor is BoatU.S., featured a full day of classes and workshops, giving the novice to expert women sailors a terrific opportunity to network with other women while learning new skills or brushing up on old one. Some women were timid and came away fully engaged in the sport. &lt;br /&gt;

"Thank you for the wonderful first time experience at the Women's Sailing Conference. The conference was so organized and professionally executed. I learned a lot and met many wonderful women sailors." &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.womensailing.org/index.php/98-2011-news-archive" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.womensailing.org/index.php/98-2011-news-archive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ladies, this date &amp;amp; event is creeping up on you. You do NOT want to miss this event by forgetting to register or registering too late to get the seminars you prefer or being left out because it is FULL! Tomorrow is May 1st so June 2nd is only 30 days away! If you are having any difficulty finding the application or understanding how to register, post a message here and ask. Also, a LOT of you will be commuting alone or getting rides, consider car pooling with another woman sailor!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://www.corinthianyc.org/Club/Scripts/section/section.asp?ns=homep</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>BillS</member_name><member_id>2822960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340158089000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335805185000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 2012 11th Women's Sailing Conference sponsored by BoatUS</name><id>62768262</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338638400000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/62768262/</event_url></item>