<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Easy Hike, Saddleback Mountain, Northwood, NH &amp;amp; Mega Yardsale&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;organized and hosted by Meetup Member Judy&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;for more info, phone or email Judy directly&lt;br /&gt;603-568-6856 or judyabarker@hotmail.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mega Moving Yard Sale&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hours: 9:00 am to 3:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Location: Momenta, 442 First New Hampshire Turnpike (old Route 4), Northwood, New Hampshire&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is for anyone who wants to sell off stuff and meet other  Meetup people. (I want company!) I am taking off for the Peace Corps late August and hope to unload some things.  Items for sale include factory equipment, furniture, scrapbook supplies and misc. household items.  The yard sale will take place at my business Momenta in Northwood.  This high traffic location has a large parking lot and field and makes an ideal venue.  No cost to participate.  To reserve a selling space please RSVP at your earliest opportunity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Easy Hike, Saddleback Mountain, Northwood Meadows State Park, Northwood, New Hampshire&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Time: 3:00 pm (hike will take 1 1/2 to 2 hours)&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Location: Momenta, 442 First New Hampshire Turnpike (old Route 4), Northwood, New Hampshire&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the close of the yard sale we will head down the road a mile to Northwood Meadows State Park. Spanning 674.5 acres in a beautiful wilderness setting, this wooded park has a vast wetlands area and is ideal for nature walks and picnicking. A lovely 2 1/2 mile gravel road circles around fishing ponds. There are also several single track trails through the woods. We will follow the mile long, grassy path (400 feet elevation gain) beyond the park to Saddlebacks 1,057 foot summit. This is a beautiful spot to snack while capturing views of nearby lakes and mountains. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After the hike, which should last about 1 1/2  to 2 hours, we will head to Johnsons Dairy bar for delicious ice cream.  If it is a hot day bring your bathing suit.  Refreshing Jenness Pond is nearby and is great for swimming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join this fun event.  Feel free to just come for the hike or just the yardsale or hopefully both.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to contact me with any questions and to reserve a space to sell at the yardsale.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raindate: July 20th&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216684669000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214363393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Hike, Saddleback Mountain, Northwood, NH &amp; Mega Yardsale</name><id>8209832</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216494000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8209832/</event_url></item>