<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britian Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Growing Green Co-Op</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1504658</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>150.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As women living in a man&amp;rsquo;s world we&amp;rsquo;re told who we are, how to live and love, and how to heal according a predominantly masculine world view from the moment we&amp;rsquo;re conceived. Whatever our gender, we all have masculine and feminine within us, and it&amp;rsquo;s only by harmonizing both sides that we become whole. In this sacred circle of women we&amp;rsquo;ll honor the wisdom of women&amp;rsquo;s strengths and vulnerabilities, heal the past wounding that keep us from fully showing up for ourselves and our loved ones, and celebrate ourselves as the magnificent and divine beings we truly are. Open to women of all ages, whatever your sexual or relational orientation. There will be no nudity or direct sexual contact at this event. This experiential workshop uses breath, movement, energy, and communication to support you to &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Learn new ways to release genital armor and expand your sexual experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Create a harmonious relationship among all four genders within you &amp;ndash; an alchemical&amp;nbsp; template for love&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Learn how to navigate the transitions from maiden to mother to crone. Creating a graceful menopause starts NOW whatever your age&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Resolve dysfunctional generational patterns, and free yourself from both conformity withand rebellion against forms of relating which no longer serve you &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cost: $150 includes delicious and nutritious lunch &lt;br /&gt;PLUS optional evening puja circle for women and men ($20 separately) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Deborah Taj Anapol, Ph.D. in Clinical Psychology is the author of Polyamory in the 21st Century, The Seven Natural Laws of Love and Love Without Limits, and has led seminars internationally on conscious relating, tantra and sexual healing for over two decades.&amp;nbsp; She now offers seminars, training, and relationship coaching for couples &amp;amp; singles worldwide in person and via phone, Skype. She is intimately familiar with trifold aspects of maiden, mother, and crone. Visit her at www.lovewithoutlimits.com.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>email Imani@themamlution.com with any questions</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306595920000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>rare opportunity to gather in a woman only environment to heal and expand our sexual selves.....</why><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301720420000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sexual Healing ~ for women only</name><id>17151794</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306591200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/17151794/</event_url></item>