<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Presented as part of Sundance USA, the Coolidge will be hosting a special premiere screening of &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;MY &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;IDIOT BROTHER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; on Thursday evening, January 27. &lt;b&gt;Filmmaker Jesse Peretz&lt;/b&gt; will be IN PERSON to introduce the film and answer questions afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TICKET INFORMATION&lt;br /&gt;* All tickets are $15&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Coolidge member tickets go on sale on Friday, January 7th at 1pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* A &lt;b&gt;limited&lt;/b&gt; number of tickets will be available to the general public on Monday, January 10 at 1pm&lt;br /&gt;* Tickets will be available online and at our box office.&lt;br /&gt;* For more information about Coolidge membership, please visit our Membership page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be sure to act fast — this event sold out quickly last year!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/benefits" target="_blank"&gt;To become a member of the Coolidge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT THE FILM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director: Jesse Peretz; Screenwriters: Evgenia Peretz and David Schisgall&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Paul Rudd, Elizabeth Banks, Zooey Deschanel, Emily Mortimer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite looking for the good in every situation and the best in every person, Ned (Paul Rudd) always seems to find himself holding the short end of the stick—being conned into selling pot to a uniformed cop, being dumped by his girlfriend, and worse yet, losing custody of his beloved dog, Willie Nelson. When he turns to family, he is passed from sister to sister while he gets back on his feet. Ned’s best intentions produce hilariously disastrous results, bringing the family to the cusp of chaos and ultimately the brink of clarity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Jesse Peretz has a keen eye for idiosyncratic human foibles, especially those that make you laugh. My Idiot Brother rolls along with fine-tuned precision by enlisting the talents of Paul Rudd and a talented cast (including Elizabeth Banks, Zooey Deschanel, and Emily Mortimer), who can make uncomfortable moments delightful by infusing characters with the perfect balance of humor and pathos. My Idiot Brother reminds us of something we know already: there is no such thing as a normal family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT SUNDANCE FILM FESTIVAL USA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Coolidge Corner Theatre is delighted to be one of the few theaters selected nationwide to take part in Sundance Film Festival USA, a groundbreaking initiative designed to take the Festival experience to local art house audiences who support independent film throughout the year, and to stimulate conversation about the art of filmmaking. Sundance Film Festival U.S.A is designed to both entertain audiences and to highlight the ability of art, specifically film, to introduce new concepts, challenge ideals and spur debate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On January 27, filmmakers and their films will be dispatched from Park City to cities across America, providing film loving audiences the opportunity to experience screenings direct from the Festival in their home town art houses and to engage in live conversation with Festival artists. In each city an introduction video featuring highlights from the Festival will precede the screenings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year, tickets were sold out before the general public had a chance to get any.  We need to coordinate purchasing tickets on Friday, January 7 with current members.  Please email me before Friday if you are not able to become a member before Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update this Meetup after the show is sold-out to coordinate getting together for anyone that is able to get a ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at the movie.  Last year, exactly none of us were able to get a ticket &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/crying.gif' border='0' alt='crying' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will update the Meetup for those able to get tickets.  Either be a member, become a member, or let me know that you need a member to order a ticket for you.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296259866000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294191715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sundance USA: MY IDIOT BROTHER</name><id>15922015</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296172800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15922015/</event_url></item>