<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>private</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06029</zip><lat>41.943202</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>paul and angela</name><city>west hartford</city><id>1140010</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.463585</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/1/5/event_30898901.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For my money, there is nothing so good or so rare to eat as a fresh, perfectly cooked, poached egg. Getting a truly fresh egg at the market is not that easy and the art of poaching, even when done by someone with knowhow and practice is a tricky process. The white of the egg is soft, pure, just cooked yet retaining a clean delicate texture and taste. The yolk bright, firm, but when your fork cuts smoothly, effortlessly into the egg the yolk &lt;strong&gt;explodes&lt;/strong&gt; out in a river of warm yellow lava that wraps itself sinuously around your taste buds. The taste of a perfect poached egg is not eggy; it is clean, warm, sinuous, and silky. The sexuality of the egg remains present; eggs are fundamentally a sexual product. A little salt, a little pepper, a triangle of buttery, lightly toasted fresh baked bread and you should be moaning your pleasure at breakfast. If you are blessed enough to serve yourself or be served such a delight, take your time to appreciate this amazingly simple, amazingly difficult, perfect little food, savor it, store the memory of it tightly because it will be awhile before you taste it again. Romance is fleeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have all had one at a restaurant, the lava cake. Chocolate cake with a warm chocolate syrup center, often served alamode with vanilla ice cream. I have had more than a few of these; I have had homemade ones and even made them myself. Not one comes close to the experience of eating the chocolate lava cake at one of my favorite restaurants on the riverside in Napa Valley. This desert, which is baked to order, arrives at your table, a semisweet, just out of the oven, tiny chocolate cake with a generous scoop of homemade vanilla bean ice cream melting just to the side of the cake. Your fork or spoon drifts through the warm, light cake to release an &lt;strong&gt;explosion&lt;/strong&gt; of locally crafted chocolates blended with a perfectly matched wine into an unbelievably decadent thick sauce. It rolls onto the plate surrounding the ice cream to create a rising steam just as is found on the shores of the Big Island in Hawaii where the volcano heat meets the cooler Pacific waters. The server has assured that your dinner wine has been finished and that you have your choice of espresso or coffee to compliment the desert. Your dessert wine or cognac will be served after the lava cake, much like one luxuriates after particularly satisfying intercourse. One can stay as long as one wants, holding the experience of a perfect dinner, watching the birds along the river bank, the play of the sun on the water, and clouds as roll along the horizon brushing the tops of the vines on the opposite bank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s your &lt;strong&gt;explosion&lt;/strong&gt; food story?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn&amp;rsquo;t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310331637000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271720908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>s'plosions, oldies but goodies, s'plain yerself Lucy!</name><id>vmbmnypkblb</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310166000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/21561271/</event_url></item>