<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&gt;&gt;&gt; NEW ADDRESS closer to the Rotary Pavilion (near Police and Town Hall area) &lt;&lt;&lt;

&gt;&gt;&gt; NEW INFO: Show starts @ 7:00, so let's try to gather before that @ 6:30-ish!  We had @ 24 at last evenings rainy "Beatles" tribute in Elizabeth Park!  Following the concert we all were invited back to a member's home for a post-show party.  In case this happens tonight in the South Windsor area, IN ADVANCE, in addition to bringing your own food &amp; beverages to the show, please bring with you some snacks &amp; beverages of your choice to contribute to the post-show party, should it materialize - at a private home or we simply hang out in the park on this beautiful evening!  &lt;&lt;&lt;

NOTE: The Single Event's "Thirsty Thursday" group is being invited to join us for this event. During the summer months, we are trying to do more casual, BYO type gatherings, featuring different types of outdoor musical entertainment, moving around to various towns to encourage new folks to join us and make new friends! Typically 8-24 come together each time. These new introductions lead to invitations to each other's events and the opportunity to enjoy varied activities and make even more new friends! 

No one suggested a local "watering hole" alternative in case of rain... luckily, it's a BEAUTIFUL day today!

NOTE: We welcome, and encourage, suggestions for FREE Live Outdoor Music (7 days a week!) and/or Thirsty Thursday MeetUps in the Greater New Haven and Shoreline communities!

&gt;&gt;&gt; Look for me/us by three shiny BLUE STAR-shaped BALLOONS (low to the ground to not block the view of others)! 

&gt;&gt;&gt; BYOB and Picnic dinner, if you'd like. As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly! 

IF RAIN: concert will be postponed to 07/17 - however, we'll more likely go to a bar! 

For specific venue info &amp; other shows: recreation.southwindsor.org - 860-648-6349</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184715685000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182224129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thirsty Thursday: "Eight to the Bar" (Swing) - South Windsors' "Rotary Pavilion"</name><id>5907402</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184279400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5907402/</event_url></item>