<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>36.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>... or fall like a rock?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are you nuts?  Why would you jump out of a perfectly good airplane?  Well, nuts maybe, but there's no airplane involved in this skydiving trip.  This is indoor skydiving at &lt;a href="http://www.skyventurenh.com" target="_blank"&gt;SkyVenture in Nashua&lt;/a&gt;.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now listen up: DON'T THINK! JUST DO IT!  JUST SIGN UP and give it a try!  It'll be a blast.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How safe is this?  They offer it for 3 years old and up!!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RESTRICTIONS:  There are few restrictions on who can &amp;quot;fly&amp;quot;.  Check it out here: &lt;a href="http://www.skyventurenh.com/beginners.html" target="_blank"&gt;Your First Flying Lesson&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Put aside some of that Christmas cash for yourself.  Experience something that will really spice up the conversation at that boring company holiday party!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SHOUT: Thanks to member Maria for mentioning this at a past meetup!  Hope you can make it and show us the ropes!  &lt;br /&gt;============================================  &lt;br /&gt;UPDATE (11-28-07)  &lt;br /&gt;TIME CHANGE:  Sunday 1:30 pm.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;============================================ &lt;br /&gt;UPDATE (11-26-07)&lt;br /&gt;New RSVP's are closed.  Unfortuneately there aren't enough payments to make a full second group.  Anyone that has payed after the 12th person will get their RSVP's changed to MAYBE in case someone can't make it.  After the event, you'll get a full refund via PayPal.  To be fair, I am going by the dates of the PayPal payments.  There was enough interest - we'll likely do this again!&lt;br /&gt;============================================  &lt;br /&gt;UPATE: (11-17-07) &lt;br /&gt;PUT YOUR MONEY WHERE YOUR FLOCK IS: (REFUND POLICY)  &lt;br /&gt;I have pre purchased 2 blocks of time for $850 at my expense.  The $36 is the cost of the block of time divided by 24.  If I get less than 24 payments, the second group will be dropped and their $36 will be refunded. If I get less than 12 payment the entire event will be cancelled and payments will be refunded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REFUND cut off date: Sunday Nov. 25th. After this date, if you paid and don?t show up, YOU are out $36 and WE get more fly time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to the 13 people that have paid so far.&lt;br /&gt;============================================  &lt;br /&gt;UPDATE (11-9-07)  &lt;br /&gt;DATE AND TIME CHANGE:  Sunday 1:45 pm.    &lt;br /&gt;Sorry if that conflicts with any of your prior plans.  :-( &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BIRD FOOD:  Dinner to follow at &lt;a href="http://www.tokyosteakhouse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Tokyo Steakhouse&lt;/a&gt;  This venue was chosen for its large group seating capicity.  We'll fly like a flock and eat like a flock!! This is posted as a separate event so click here to   &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1169/calendar/6711105/"&gt;RSVP for the Dinner at Tokyo Steakhouse in Nashua Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SHOUT: Thanks to member Joel for the dinner suggestion! &lt;br /&gt;============================================&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE (11-1-07)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FLY WITH THE FLOCK?  &lt;br /&gt;That's right. Due to the positive feedback from members and after working with SkyVenture, I've opened up the RSVP to a bonafide FLOCK!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE FLIGHT PLAN:   &lt;br /&gt;We'll have two groups of 12.  The first group with take the lessons, then head to the flight chamber while the second group gets their lessons.  The second group gets to watch the 1st group after the lesson is complete.  At the 1/2 hour mark, the second group swoops into the flight chamber.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;30 Minutes per 12 people  &lt;br /&gt;2.5 minutes per bird of flight time   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't think that's much time? SkyVenture says &amp;quot;Two minutes in the flight chamber is equal to 3 skydives from 13,000 feet! &amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST:   (See the Refund Policy above)&lt;br /&gt;$36 each.  You MUST pay via PayPal in advance to attend this event BEFORE SAT. NOV 17TH. Those who haven't paid will have their RSVP's bumped to NO.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BIRD FOOD:  &lt;br /&gt;Save some cash for a follow up dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SHOUT:  Thanks to member Linda for volunteering to be the Official Event Photographer.    (PS: She's not able to fly with us, so doesn't count as part of the 12)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beantown and Beyond</member_name><member_id>4494456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196793686000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191630448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fly Like A Bird!!</name><id>6497507</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196620200000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/6497507/</event_url></item>