<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>96 Winthrop street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372280</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tommy Doyles</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1114814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This November's Boston Skeptics in the Pub event features &amp;quot;geek musician&amp;quot; &lt;b&gt;Marian Call&lt;/b&gt; performing at Tommy Doyle's in Harvard Square. Care to check her out? Let's grab a table together at Tommy Doyle's at 6:00 pm, order dinner, then wait for the 7:00 pm performance to start. You can check out her music on her official website at &lt;a href="http://www.mariancall.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mariancall...&lt;/a&gt; or her Youtube Channel at &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/mariancall" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Skeptics suggests a $5.00 - $10.00 donation for the artist, and to RSVP on Facebook at &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=6399460578#!/event.php?eid=159880630701778" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting outside Tommy Doyle's from 5:45 pm to 6:00 pm, herding nerds. We can grab a few tables together at 6:00 pm near the stage and order drinks and appetisers, saving spaces for those who end up RSVPing Yes on the day of the event but can't get there until 6:15 pm the latest for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7 with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is TJ&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Boston Skeptics website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonskeptics.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonskeptics...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Join us for a very exciting Skeptics in the Pub event: Marian Call, geek musician extraodinaire!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Marian is in the midst of her 49&amp;gt;50 tour, on which she is touring all 50 states (beginning with the 49th and ending with the 50th). We are lucky enough to be getting a free show the night after she appears at Boston’s W00tstock! Check her out at mariancall.com and youtube.com/mariancall, and don’t miss out–I saw her perform at Dragon*Con and it was an AWESOME show! You don’t often get to see someone play both a typewriter and a rainstick in the same concert…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Please note: there is a $5-10 suggested donation to the artist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;See you at Tommy Doyle’s in Harvard Square (96 Winthrop St.) on Monday, November 1st at 7pm!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Don’t forget to rsvp on facebook: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=6399460578#!/event.php?eid=159880630701778" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Marian Call, according to her site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mariancall.com/press.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mariancall...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Short Bio&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt; Marian Call delivers whimsical Alaskan folk funk for the Coffee Counter-Culture. She sounds a little like Joni Mitchell &amp;amp; Regina Spektor raising the child of Jason Mraz &amp;amp; Erin McKeown. Call's sound is always soulful, honest, and clever, loved by all types -- computer geeks, church ladies, teenage thugs, NPR listeners, and urban hipsters worldwide. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Long Bio&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt; Marian Call is a trained composer and a spunky self-taught singer based out of Anchorage, Alaska. Her songs are eclectic and diverse, funny and light on their feet, powerfully honest, and grounded in the human experience. Call's compositions are half study and calculation, half improvisational instinct, and always full of unexpected musical twists and turns. She has written pieces by commission for film projects and events, and she has been known to write songs on dares or to surprise devoted fans. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Her live shows have been loudly applauded nationwide in homes, quiet coffee shops, noisy bars, churches, radio stations, bookstores, and concert halls, in and out of Alaska. In only eight months she went from a relative unknown to playing the main stage at several of Alaska's summer festivals. Marian released her first two albums plus fourteen singles in only fourteen months during 2007 and 2008. She is nearing completion on a new two-volume project titled &lt;i&gt;Something Fierce&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Boston Skeptics&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonskeptics.com/about/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonskeptics...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Boston Skeptics is a group of critical thinkers who get together to talk, eat, drink, and be skeptical about things like homeopathy, creationism, psychics, aliens, alternative medicine, conspiracy theories, and whatever else catches our attention. This website began as a front for our monthly event Boston Skeptics in the Pub (or 'Skeptics in the Hub' if we were feeling particularly clever), but has grown to includes blogging from our panel and regular outing&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Tommy Doyle's:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/harvard-square/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tommydoyle...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tommy Doyle’s in Harvard Square opened it’s doors in 2005 in the historic Hyde-Taylor house. The building was once the site of the original 'House of Blues.' With historic shoes to fill, we have committed ourselves to providing proper live music, nightly entertainment, and quality food &amp;amp; drink for the Harvard Square community.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Since opening we have become a staple for Harvard student life, and have had a great time doing it! A vibrant and eclectic crowd on any given night, we boast tons of screens with all the games, Pub Trivia on Wednesday, Live Music 5 nights a week, DJ &amp;amp; Dancing Wednesday thru Saturday&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu (in PDF Format):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2010/10/harvard_menu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tommydoyle...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288830770000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287694197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner + Skeptics in the Pub present Marian Call @ Tommy Doyle's, Harvard Square</name><id>15186600</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288648800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15186600/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/2/global_18932658.jpeg</photo_url></item>