<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come and Join us on a bit of a road tour through the backroads of New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During this trip we will be photographing some of the covered bridges here in New Hampshire. A list of bridges as well as a map of travel will be coming soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip will begin in Nashua at Nashua South.(For those interested there are a few wooden bridges located just steps from Nashua Souths parking lot in Mine Falls State Park. There is also a number of small waterfalls located in the park). We will then head up Route 3 to Henniker NH, the site of our first Covered Bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details &lt;br /&gt;New Hampshire Covered Bridge Shoot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Trip will begin at Nashua High School South - Directions - From Mass - Take Rt 3 into Nashua NH. Take Exit 5W. Go through 1 set of lights. At next set take right onto Riverside Dr. Follow Riverside to Nashua High South located on your left. Follow around to back parking lot next to the high school track.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will spend about a hour here shooting Mine Falls wooden bridges and waterfalls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Nashua we head up to the Henniker Bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nh.gov/nhd.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nh.gov/nhd...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From Nashua to Henniker - Route 3 north which will turn into RT 93 north. After we pass through the tolls we will take RT 89 North towards White River Junction Vermont. We will take Exit 5(rt202/rt9 into henniker(the bridge is off of this road).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Henniker to W. Hopkinton - Rowells Bridge - Clement Hill RD(rt 127).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nh.gov/nhd.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nh.gov/nhd...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Henniker - Follow Rt 202 back towards rt 89. Take left onto rt 127 in West Hopkinton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;West Hopkinton to Hopkinton - Railroad Bridge - East of RT 103.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nh.gov/nhd.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nh.gov/nhd...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions - From Rowells Bridge we will continue north on rt 127 into hopkinton where it will meet up with Rt 103 in the village of Contoocook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopkinton to Warner - Waterloo Bridge and the Dalton Bridge in Warner NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nh.gov/nhd.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nh.gov/nhd...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nh.gov/nhd.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nh.gov/nhd...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions - Continue to Follow RT 103 into Warner. Bridges are located just a few miles apart.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205253224000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Great opportunity to meet other photographers from the area!</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202851951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Hampshire Covered Bridge Tour</name><id>7318855</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205067600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/7318855/</event_url></item>