<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's gut check time. Time to get serious. Time to up the miles. To redeem myself for last Saturday's exercise in humiliation (don't ask), I am running 10 miles along the Charles this Saturday starting at 9:00 AM at Panera Bread in Watertown. I may run in the direction of Watertown/Waltham on the path, or I may run toward the city on the path-- I haven't decided. That's just the fly-by-the-seat-of-my-pants kind of gal I am. Regardless of which way I run, I'd prefer not to run alone. (Whining is only truly satisfying when you have an audience.) I run 9.5 minute miles, so we're not going to be burning up the path. Speedy folks who passive-aggressively try to get the group to go faster are not welcome (Just kidding, anyone is welcome, but if you plan to run fast, bring a fast buddy with you, bc I certainly won't be able to keep up with you.) There are multiple turnaround points, so those folks who don't want to do 10 miles, don't have to. Please join me!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Panera Bread at Arsenal on the Charles in Watertown- 321 Arsenal Street</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>heidi</member_name><member_id>8485896</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247490914000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247172378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Morning 10 Miler Along the Charles</name><id>10841313</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247317200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/10841313/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/4/global_2413972.jpeg</photo_url></item>