<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>292 State St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.075680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South Church</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>885171</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757765</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We post this presentation by our sister group over on the Seacoast for your information.&lt;br /&gt;We will arrange carpooling over - we'll post details of that as the date nears at the bottom of this page.&lt;br /&gt;We've uploaded a letter form invitation to architects and engineers to &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/307/files/"&gt;our files section&lt;/a&gt;. You can print this out and take it to local architects' and engineers' offices.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Seacoast 9-11 Questions Group&lt;/b&gt; will present San Francisco Bay Area architect Richard Gage, AIA, member of the American Institute of Architects and Founder of Architects &amp;amp; Engineers for 9/11 Truth, speaking on:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;“9/11:  Blueprint for Truth&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, contact Bill Woodward at &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Gage has gathered data by government reports, videos of the collapses, and eye-witness accounts which have surfaced since 9/11/2001. To fully understand what happened that day, and to prevent this kind of collapse from ever happening again, we must have a full, unbiased, and vigorous examination of all the evidence available. He has come to the conclusion that the official story and investigation have ignored a great deal of evidence and left key questions unanswered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://AE911Truth.org"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Architects &amp;amp; Engineers for 9/11 Truth&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are calling for a new investigation. They signed a petition calling for a new, fully funded, unimpeachable Congressional investigation with subpoena power.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope you’ll join us for this presentation.  Bring your tough questions (there will be Q&amp;amp;A) and your friends.  For most of us, it takes great courage to even consider this evidence, and we applaud you for your willingness to keep an open mind while you evaluate it for yourself.  It would be impossible to overstate the importance of doing so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool details from the Manchester area to follow. Check back here as the date becomes near for the latest plan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Addendum:&lt;br /&gt;Seacoast 9/11 Questions Group announces: Architect Richard Gage &lt;br /&gt;will speak for 2 hrs and answer questions (AE911truth.org). &lt;br /&gt;Bring a friend. Free but donations requested. Expenses over &lt;br /&gt;$1000. Come back for strategy potluck breakfast at 10 a.m. on &lt;br /&gt;Sat. 10/10 at Bill Woodward's home, 76 Madbury Rd., Durham, NH &lt;br /&gt;03824. contact: swampgreenfrog@yahoo.com, 603-866-3254&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255306334000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253380893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9/11: Blueprint for Truth, Richard Gage in Portsmouth</name><id>11413614</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255132800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/11413614/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/5/0/global_3004432.jpeg</photo_url></item>