<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Back by popular demand....wine night at Ralphs house!!! Had so much fun we had to do it again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our gracious member Ralph, will once again open his home for a multi group meetup.(Thanks Ralph!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For wine night, everyone will bring a bottle of wine (no boxed wine please) AND a pot luck dish, finger food or hors d'oeuvres to share.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming by yourself or don't want to go in with someone just bring a bottle of wine that is $15 or more. Couples or groups can go in together on a bottle that is $30 or more, to ensure we have a good assortment of wines to taste.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get some different types of wine so we have a varied taste &lt;br /&gt;testing.. &lt;br /&gt;Reds Malbec, Blends, cab, merlot, shiraz pinot noir, whites - &lt;br /&gt;sav blanc, chards, reisling, &lt;br /&gt;pinot grigio, etc&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just post it so we know who wants to partner and who want to buy one alone so we know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be 3 Meetup groups attending, and RSVP's will be limited to 20 from each group...so sign up quick!! This event was very popular last time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please ensure you show up if you RSVP yes, since we may have a waiting list and you are taking up a persons spot if you do not show up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please note* The address will be sent a few days prior to the event to all the &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVPs, due to this being a private residence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to a great night...and meeting some new faces.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ring the DoorBell !!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rena</member_name><member_id>5082966</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve C</member_name><member_id>6197158</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph</member_name><member_id>8774347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288055164000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286842110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine Tasting</name><id>15077743</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287871200000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/15077743/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/a/e/global_16726014.jpeg</photo_url></item>