<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>63 Foster St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01960</zip><lat>42.523777</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-531-0500</phone><name>Metro Bowl</name><city>Peabody</city><id>509583</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.929130</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Update 1/4/2011:  This event has seemed to become popular, we have 10 from this site and 14 from the Our Circle of Friends site.  We will be calling to reserve the alleys, so please if your plans have changed please kindly change your RSVP.  &lt;br /&gt;The forecast is also calling for snow, but the weather people are not stating how much, so please check back on the site to ensure we have not moved the event to another day.  If a reschedule is needed, the organizers will attempt to post it as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you all at the alleys for a lot fun, laughter and friendly competition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We started this last winter, we try the different bowling in all the different area alleys. First round was Academy Lanes in Bradford, where we had 4 lanes of bowlers with glow bowling. Round 2 was at Pilgrim Lanes in Haverhill, where we had 1 lane of bowlers with standard bowling. This round we will venture down to Peabody for some Cosmic Bowling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will bolwing at Leo's Metro Bowl in Peabody for some Cosmic Bowling. What is the difference between Glow Bowling and Cosmic Bowling? Glow bowling the pins are neon, Cosmic bowling the whole alley is neon under Black lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So lets go out to Leo's grab a pizza or a hotdog and roll our best balls down the Cosmic Lanes. Laughter and fun WILL be allowed and so want a friendly banter between bowlers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the lobby and pick teams dependent on how many bowlers we have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price:  $27.00 per lane per hour, 6 bowlers per lane&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't want to bowl but don't want to miss this fun event? Come on down and be a score keeper and route on your friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember: Its that time of year again, if weather is inclement, this event will be cancelled. Before leaving to attend this event, please check back or if the weather is questionable call the Meetup Cell phone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have to cancel at the last minute, are running late or get lost please call the Meetup Cell phone and let us know. The Cellphone number is 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you all at the alleys&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294622568000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292464534000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Round 3 Cosmic Bowling</name><id>15746458</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294444800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/15746458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/f/global_20283647.jpeg</photo_url></item>