<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building E51, Room 335</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>376848</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TITLE: AN EVENING WITH CHUCK JAFFE by CHUCK JAFFE, SENIOR COLUMNIST, MARKETWATCH.COM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DESCRIPTION: Nationally syndicated financial columnist CHUCK JAFFE - host of Your Money Radio - talks about what's hot and what's not when it comes to investing in the market and mutual funds, and let's you decide the subject matter. JAFFE, a senior columnist for MarketWatch -- whose work appeared in The Boston Globe for a decade and whose columns now run in both The Boston Herald and the Patriot-Ledger in Quincy - will let you drive the night's discussion. So bring your questions and your curiosity for what promises to be a fun, involved evening of financial talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BIO: CHUCK JAFFE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHUCK JAFFE is senior columnist for MarketWatch. His three weekly columns are syndicated nationally to a weekly audience of more than 20 million readers; his &amp;quot;Your Funds&amp;quot; column is the most widely read feature on mutual fund investing in America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upon joining MarketWatch in 2003, CHUCK created the &amp;quot;Stupid Investment of the Week&amp;quot; column, a quirky feature that highlights the flaws that make for bad investments. His stories, and the investments he has attacked, represent an incredible rogues' gallery of dreadful issues, from which he believes investors can learn to do things the right way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHUCK is also the host of &amp;quot;Your Money,&amp;quot; a weekday morning radio talk show on WBIX-AM in Boston; the highlights of his show are also used as daily podcasts on MarketWatch. In addition, CHUCK appears frequently on CNBC, provides regular guest commentary for Nightly Business Report on public television and makes periodic appearances on Fox News, National Public Radio and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHUCK is the author of two books, &amp;quot;The Right Way to Hire Financial Help&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Chuck Jaffe's Lifetime Guide to Mutual Funds.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aside from his work on money and investing, CHUCK is a past president of the Society of American Business Editors and Writers, a group representing more than 3,000 business journalists nationwide. In the 17 years since he first joined SABEW's board, CHUCK has been an outspoken critic of the business media.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to joining MarketWatch, CHUCK spent nine years as personal finance and mutual funds columnist at The Boston Globe. He moved to Boston after six years as business editor and columnist at The Morning Call in Allentown, Pa. His business journalism career includes Florida stops at the St. Petersburg Times and the Bradenton Herald.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Throughout his career, CHUCK has received numerous awards for personal finance journalism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHUCK lives on Boston's South Shore with his wife Susan - who he always describes in print as &amp;quot;the most patient and understanding woman in America&amp;quot; - and two daughters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The agenda for the meetup will be:&lt;br /&gt;6:00 - 6:50 Bob Pod's premeeting will not be held, but come early and we'll discuss and socialize&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 8:00 Meeting Starts with Fred Sears's Q&amp;amp;A, Doug's Market Talk, Stockpicks&lt;br /&gt;8:00 Feature Presentation by Chuck Jaffe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191021050000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>59</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186642155000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors Business Daily September Meetup</name><id>6150426</id><headcount>53</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190847600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/6150426/</event_url></item>