<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a big weekend here and starts their summer. I say we head to the events and stop to smell the daffodils...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; A Three million daffodil Celebration: April's gentle breezes and warming sunshine coax new growth from the island's sandy soil, adorning roadsides and gardens with an astonishing variety of daffodils. Come wear your Daffy Hat, watch the Antique Car Parade, have a tailgate picnic and welcome spring. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can have breakfast and then head to town and see the sights... Might be a good time to also see the Nantucket Whaling Museum.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know the novel Moby Dick was written after a Nantucket whaler named Essex was destoyed in 1882 by a whale? Even caused the crew from ACK to cannabalism... How bout that...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we can go have lunch somewhere on the island too :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nantucketchamber.org/visitor/daffodil.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nantucketc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The big antique car parade is also on Saturday... at noon.... at 12:30, the Daffy Dog Parade starts.. dogs dressed in daffodils... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a fun day trip... Bring the family and let's pack the planes....  RSVP PIC or PAX.&lt;br /&gt; This is why you learned to fly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272285856000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265933775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Natucket  (Stop-and-Smell-the ) Daffodil Weekend</name><id>12584324</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272112200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/12584324/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/4/global_13051844.jpeg</photo_url></item>