<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2950 10 Rod Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02822</zip><lat>41.573997</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Beach Pond</name><city>Exeter</city><id>7622032</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.785690</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before signing up for this event, Please read the entire Write Up and understand and agree to the enclosed Liability Waiver.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Rating: Strenuous&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Distance: 8+ Miles&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Time Duration: 4 Hours&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blaze Orange: REQUIRED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/e/0/event_127351712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pachaug Trail is hike #18 in Ken Weber’s “Weekend Walks in Rhode Island”. It is one of the longest hikes in the book at 8 ½ miles. A five mile section is as strenuous as any trail in the book. It is also an enjoyable and scenic hike as the trail climbs ledges, crosses streams, and passes through ravines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike should take about 4 hours, which includes hiking along the eastern edge of Beach Pond, in Beach Pond State Park in RI. The trail also crosses into CT and Pachaug State Forest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the rocky trails and stream crossings, a pair of hiking boots is strongly suggested. As always bring sufficient water and snacks along for a 4 hour hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The forecast calls for rain, so bring appropriate gear for hiking in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Jo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/4/5/0/event_127353872.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 From Providence: Take I-95 south to exit 5A, (Rt. 102 south). At the merge of Rt. 102 and Rt. 3, take Rt. 3 south. Continue on Rt. 3 south for another mile to the next light (a flashing light) at the intersection of Rt. 3 and Rt. 165. Turn right at the flashing light onto Rt. 165 west. Follow Rt. 165 west for about 7 miles, until you come to Beach Pond. Park in the lot on the right side of the highway, on the RI side of the pond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L&lt;strong&gt;iability Waiver: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety First!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tony Chernasky</member_name><member_id>12464984</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John H.</member_name><member_id>14299089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369585667000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1369266173000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pachaug Trail (Ken Weber Hike #18)</name><id>120754332</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369486800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/120754332/</event_url></item>