<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The more focus you put on something, the more the tendency is to attract it - positive or negative. It makes sense then to focus on what you want much more than what you don't!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll learn, practice and reinforce focusing on what you want with visualization, clear statements, announcing to others what you want, making lists, being receptive and reinforce how to maintain a positive focus throughout the day with an inner and outer smile, breathing techniques, gratitude lists and having fun. We'll also focus on how to manage distressing thoughts and return to what you want&lt;br /&gt;in a positive fashion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's a sliding scale from $20-40. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $20, it helps the presenter and those who might pay less. No one is turned away because of money, so pay what you can honestly afford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcome to bring and share vegetarian food and drink.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce *****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce is a relationship coach and workshop leader. He specializes in working with communication between people but communication with one's self is just as important. He is an expert in the Enneagram Personality Typing System and is the author of the Idiot's Guide to the Enneagram. 781 648 3737, herb@herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;also see his meetup at www.meetup.com/The-Arlington-Singles-Events&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248699989000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Arlington-Singles-Events</urlname><id>1416650</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Arlington Singles Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247500878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Law of Attraction</name><id>10865201</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247526000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Arlington-Singles-Events/events/10865201/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/4/global_7835444.jpeg</photo_url></item>