<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>44 South Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.759493</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-676-9463</phone><name>Flemings steak House</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1072079</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742202</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I am a volunteer at Foodshare, so Caryl is allowing me to post this idea as an official event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event starts at Flemings Prime Steakhouse &amp;amp; Wine Bar, 44 South Main Street, West Hartford, at 5:00pm (or any time until 10:00pm). A donation of $10 gets you an admission sticker and map to other WH eateries participating in the event. Each offers a drink, dinner or appetizer special so you can have a moveable feast and sample new eateries in the name of a good cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The proceeds raised at the Charity Tastes N' Toasts event on August 11th will help support Foodshare's vision of creating a community where hunger is universally unacceptable and where businesses, organizations, and individuals work together to ensure that everyone has access to good, nutritious food.   Foodshare serves as our region’s food bank and distributes 16 tons of food each day to a network of nearly 350 local partners that feed our hungry neighbors. Every $30 that Foodshare receives provides enough food for a hungry person for an entire month and 94% of Foodshare's resources go directly to ending hunger.  More info on their FB page:  &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=128117183897723" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;   There is a page on the Blue Back Square site but it still has the July dates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a weekly event sponsored by the Blue Back Square restaurants.  Each week a different restaurant hosts a different charity.  The host restaurant offers the opportunity to learn about the specific charity benefited by the day's activities through an educational display within the restaurant.  Since I volunteer for Foodshare, I have information about this event and thought it sounds like fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I set the start time as 6:30pm because I don't get out of work in time for the 5:00pm opening.  I'll try to get to Flemings a little before 6:30pm so we can meet and then decide as a group what sounds most interesting:  Moveable feast with appetizer at one location and main course at another?  Or just one restaurant for the evening?&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281648847000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280230476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Night Tastes N' Toasts at Blue Back Square - August 11th</name><id>14226516</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281565800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/14226516/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/5/global_3916629.jpeg</photo_url></item>