<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/c/8/event_193097352.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The trailer for this makes it look like a hoot and how can you not laugh with this cast?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Showtime is at 7.  I will be at the theater by 6 and we will be heading in for seats at 6:30.  Note the movie is playing upstairs so look for the group at the tables by the windows at the top of the escalator. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, I arrive at the theater an hour before the show to start gathering people, and we head in for seats about 30 minutes before the show, so we can sit together. This also allows us to take turns getting snacks, etc., before the previews start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;Because the group usually sees movies opening weekend, it is a good idea to buy your tickets in advance, especially if there is a lot of buzz about the film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after. We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;$$$$Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after.$$$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; March 15, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; New Line Cinema (Warner Bros.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Don Scardino &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; Jonathan Goldstein, John Francis Daley &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Steve Carell, Steve Buscemi, Olivia Wilde, Alan Arkin, James Gandolfini, Jim Carrey, Jay Mohr, Michael Bully Herbig &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Comedy &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; Not Available &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.theincredibleburtwonderstone.com" target="_blank"&gt;TheIncredibleBurtWonderstone.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Superstar magicians Burt Wonderstone (Steve Carell) and Anton Marvelton (Steve Buscemi) have ruled the Las Vegas strip for years, raking in millions with illusions as big as Burt's growing ego. But lately the duo's greatest deception is their public friendship, while secretly they've grown to loathe each other. Facing cutthroat competition from guerilla street magician Steve Gray (Jim Carrey), whose cult following surges with each outrageous stunt, even their show looks stale. But there's still a chance Burt and Anton can save the act—both onstage and off—if Burt can get back in touch with what made him love magic in the first place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366921021000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357419570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Incredible Burt Wonderstone (7PM Show)</name><id>98088732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363471200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/98088732/</event_url></item>