<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Members and Guests of the SSDOMG for our first Appetizer Social in a looong time! Let's start off the new year with a relaxed laid-back fun event where you can come and go when it suits your schedule. We'll be meeting at TGI Friday's which is located next to the Sheraton Hotel across the street from the South Shore Plaza. This is located right off the highway so it is easily accessible for everyone.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TGI Friday's has some great specials available.  Special half-price appetizers are available from 4-7pm. If you buy one entree you get a half-priced appetizer. They have $4 mixed drink specials, $2 domestic pints, and $3 premium pints. &lt;i&gt;Plus, the SSDOMG will buy 3-4 appetizers for the Group depending on how many attendees we have.&lt;/i&gt;  As is our policy, you will still have to pay for your drinks, individually ordered food, any shared appetizers that the SSDOMG does not cover as well as tax and tip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will run for at least a couple of hours from 5:30-7:30pm or later.  With an appetizer social you can join us whenever you can get there, whether it be 5:30, 6 or 6:45.  If you would let us know approximately when to expect you in your RSVP Comments it would be helpful so we can keep an eye out for you.  Over 30% of members who voted in the poll stating how early they could meetup with us said they could be at an event by 5:30pm, with another 30% stating they could arrive by 6pm.  Since the bar fills up around 6pm and tables are few and far between at that time I decided to start the event at 5:30pm but if anyone can meet me closer to 5:15 to help grab a couple of tables together please let us know in your RSVP Comments.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a load off - it's Friday night and time to start the weekend off right! Join us for an Appetizer Social at TGIFriday's in Braintree!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday Night Appetizer Social!&lt;br /&gt;Friday, January 30th @ 5:30-7:30pm or later&lt;br /&gt;37 Forbes Road&lt;br /&gt;Sheraton Hotel&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;781-356-9130&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizer(s)&lt;/i&gt;: Angela &amp;amp; Linda J  (Email Angela by Wednesday if you can help co-org.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Min/Max&lt;/i&gt;: At least 6 Yes RSVP's by 5pm on Thursday, January 29th. No max!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Guests&lt;/i&gt;: Up to 2 per member!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Event Fee&lt;/i&gt;: Org Team and Annual Members - Free, Members and Guests - $2pp; Event Fees will go directly towards 3-4 appetizers that the SSDOMG will pay for tonight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Price Range&lt;/i&gt;: Appetizers, Soups and Salads range from $3 to $15, with entrees ranging from $10 to $24.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/i&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps us to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/i&gt;: Friday, January 30th @ 12NOON&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Please watch this space for more detailed directions to be posted prior to the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us in the bar.  My photo is posted.  We'll have a meetup table card.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234481724000</updated><rating><average>4.44999980927</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232728709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Appetizer Social!!!</name><id>9585814</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233354600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/9585814/</event_url></item>