<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.363068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Innovation Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>5488072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083893</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Java &amp;amp; NewSQL: Merging the Best of the Old World &amp;amp; New World Technologies &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;In recent years, Java, Scala and Clojure developers have jumped through countless hoops to work around the Object-Relational Mapping "impedance mismatch." Akiban Server is a powerful data store that enables developers to work with data both as structured objects *and* as relational tables using SQL. By implementing a feature called Table Grouping in the core storage engine, relational joins have orders of magnitude higher throughput while still providing transactional fault tolerance. Data in Akiban Server is accessible via ORM tools and JDBC as well as a new REST (JSON over HTTP) interface providing direct object-level access, making it a perfect match for e-commerce, game development, social media, CMS, CRM and enterprise applications. Akiban Server itself is written in Java and Open Source is at its core -- the PersistIt B+ tree core storage engine, REST interface and a growing collection of extension modules are freely available on GitHub. You can download Akiban Developer Edition today:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://goo.gl/x9YhX" target="_blank"&gt;http://goo.gl/x9YhX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Ori Herrnstadt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ori Herrnstadt is the founder and CTO of Akiban. He has been involved in developing large scale operational database systems since his days in the Israeli Military. After experiencing similar problems of large-scale operational systems in healthcare, ERP, CRM and modern web applications, he began developing the Orthogonal Architecture. In 2009, he founded Akiban Technologies to accelerate the development of this technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Burc Oral</member_name><member_id>4238999</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350485583000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>69</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347469645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Java &amp; NewSQL: MergingThe Best of the Old World &amp; New World Technologies</name><id>82068322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350426600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/82068322/</event_url></item>