<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Nassuas to Curtis Park</address_1><lat>41.180000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Farmington River .5x18 Mile Section</name><city>Oyokkuduk</city><id>375851</id><country>uz</country><lon>65.209999</lon></venue><fee><label>KAYAK RENTAL fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per AL's KAYAK s</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is an EXPLOR TRIP to see if this section would be a good trip for new paddlers as the leaf color changes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Ok i know most of you wont make it on a 18 mile trip..so its shorter now..&lt;br /&gt;Sycamore tree take out location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THERE WILL BE SHALLOW SPOTS AND PORTAGE NECESSARY&amp;gt;&amp;gt;BRING WATER SHOES&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to all that informed me..and i also seen some really low areas when i was in avon for work projects...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I dont want a big group that blasts off and i have no idea where they are, run out of energy, equipment malfunction, or run into places where assisted PORTAGE may be necessary..or the unthinkable..wet exit, or entangled in tree strainers..then drowning.....but then again you can be the explorer on your own and just meet up at the way points...&lt;br /&gt;let me know thet is your intention and things will work fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I AM MORE INTERESTED IN UNDERSTANDING THIS RIVER, looking at its flows, its scenery, and talking with our members along the way..then having a good synopsys on the trip details for the FALL LEAF EVENT...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I dont want wimps or complainers here..unless you have someone ready at every take out point waiting...&lt;br /&gt;Bring a rope...im not going to tow you but might tie you up if you complaine..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING ASSPERINS, GLOVES..a BUTT pad..FOOD and Liquid..and the other regular paddlinstuffs...the rope is to tie up the kayaks at the stop points if needed...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS IS A CAR MOVING THING...&lt;br /&gt;I have my method picked out...YOU FIGURE OUT YOUR OWN METHOD if you dont like mine....i presented a method before and eveyrone got confused, or thought they drove more than the other..or something like that, i dont want to hear it.....ahhh ..explorers will find this just one of the faciniting challenges to add to the trip to solve...&lt;br /&gt;its all the same distance and drive thing for everyone just at different times..&lt;br /&gt;Suggestion..all meet at put in, unload yaks..1 person stays guard, all go to end.pick a few cars to go back to beginning..(without kayak racks obviously ) then in the end of the trip..give those who gave you a ride back to the begining a ride back to their cars when the trip is over..sound simple enough..good i thought so.. simpler methods work if 2 have roof racks and only one kayak per person....but not practical for those without racks or other carrying configurations..but again you figure it out..if you cant..i will bycycle the length back to retrieve my car and trailer..and never offer this kind of trip again..but limit it to very few trusted individuals only that have this figured out.  sound fair..good i knew you were all inteligent and understanding of this..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you have a phone and a willing retriver you can get out anywhere. just not with my yaks unless you are willing to take em to the end point..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see map data:  &lt;a href="http://www.frwa.org/recreation_area5.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.frwa.org/r...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look at your maps&lt;br /&gt;PUT-IN : Access Point 21, Rt.4 Bridge, Farmington, CT &lt;br /&gt;Directions :from hartford direction..go to Farmington center..Travel .3 mile west on Rt. 4 from jct. Rt. 10/ 4 in center of Farmington. Cross Rt. 4 bridge in Farmington and turn left on to a small paved road leading to a large parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;Thios is just after the bridge but before the sewage plant&lt;br /&gt;GPS mapquest..use. 900 Farmington Ave, farmington ct to get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TAKE-OUT : Enter by the The Big Sycamore tree..intersection of rte 185 and Nod Road, Simsbury..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route..rte 10 north..at intersection of rte 44..go strait on Nod Rd to end..Sycamore tree entrance is straight ahead just a tad to the right and down the dirt road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INTERMITTENT ACCESS POINTS : &lt;br /&gt;Access Point 22, Alsop Meadows (Rt.44 Bridge), Avon, CT From jct. Rt. 44/10 (bottom of Talcott Mountain) go south on Rt. 10 (Waterville Road) for .2 mile. Turn right into Nassau?s and go straight through a gate onto a dirt road. This property is owned by the Town of Avon and the gate may be locked. It is approximately .2 mile to the river from the gate. &lt;br /&gt;Access Point 23, Rt.185 Bridge, Simsbury, CT Travel north 3.1 miles on Rt. 10 from jct. Rt. 44/10 in Avon center. Turn right at Rt. 185. Just over the bridge, there are two access points. Taking an immediate left, you will follow a dirt road down into a pleasant park with the renowned Gifford Pinchot Sycamore Tree. Turning right just after the bridge onto Nod Road, take an immediate right into a parking area along side the river. &lt;br /&gt;Access Point 24, River Road, Simsbury, CT Just north of the jct. Rt. 10/167 in Simsbury, turn right onto Drake Hill Road, cross the river and turn left onto River Road. Go .3 mile to small access area on left. &lt;br /&gt;Access Point 25, River Road, Simsbury, CT From jct. Rt. 10/167 in Simsbury, travel 2.1 miles north on Rt. 10. Turn right onto Rt. 315 and go .5 mile. Park entrance is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; AL-r= Tourlite 15&lt;br /&gt;?= Cobra 18 or Pungo 12&lt;br /&gt;?= Cobra 18 or Pungo 12&lt;br /&gt;Kathy G= Greenlander Pro 18&lt;br /&gt;Janice,= Eddyliner..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190728992000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190123878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DETAILS: Half of the 18 Mile Exploration Kayak Trip on the Farmington  + PICKNIC</name><id>6381369</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190556000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6381369/</event_url></item>