<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>60.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In this all-day workshop, participants will learn techniques to attend to challenges that often arise around this time of year.  These include:  travel, family gatherings, over consumption, economic pressures, increased alcohol intake, children's expectations, and other seasonally related situations that can sometimes create stress and anxiety.  You will learn a combination of breath techniques, guided meditation and mindfulness practices that are geared specifically around this time of year and the build up of &amp;quot;the holidays.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For lunch we will be suggesting a &amp;quot;local foods&amp;quot; pot luck, where participants can bring a food item to share originating from our local community. We will offer tea and light snacks throughout the day. The workshop will conclude at approximately 3:00pm. The fee will be a sliding scale from $40-60 to cover fees and expenses, please offer what you can afford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About our teacher: Lisa Blake, M.A. has taught meditation to hundreds of students as young as three, as wise as ninety and many ages in between. Currently, she teaches meditation to high school students and adults, both through her private practice and as a practitioner at True North Health Center. She is the founder of the Maine Mindfulness Project. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Lisa and her work, see: &lt;a href="http://mainemindfulnessproject.com" target="_blank"&gt;Maine Mindfulness Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>TomC</member_name><member_id>7931343</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259015375000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256916196000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breathing Joy into the Holiday: Meditations for a Thankful Heart &amp; Merry Moments</name><id>11749576</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258812000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/11749576/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/0/global_10129760.jpeg</photo_url></item>