<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Arlington</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.415130</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Minuteman Trail</name><city>Arlington</city><id>583778</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.176620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to all of the new members.  This is the first Meetup schedule for this group in eight months!  I'm new to the group too and next winter I plan on scheduling some ice skating Meetups since it seems a lot of you ice skate also.  This is such a seasonal Meetup group and I don't want people to think it's inactive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm not really sure what day and time people like to go rollerblading or where people like to go.  It seems a lot of you like the Minuteman Trail and I do too.  It's wide, well-paved, mostly flat and not crowded for those unfamiliar with this place.  Thursday is my one free night of the week and it's supposed to be sunny and in the upper 60s so that's why I chose Thursday.  The weather this time of year can be so unpredictable.  Personally, I'm not a fan of rollerblading in temperatures less than 60 degrees.  Also, I'm not sure what condition the trail is in.  It may be too early for them to have cleared it off and there may be sand and downed tree branches from the winter.  If anyone has already been this year, let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All levels are welcome to join.  Since I'm pretty out of shape, I'll probably go at a slow, but steady pace.  If you'd rather go faster, definitely come too, we'll meet up at each street crossing.  I'm good for about an hour and hope to make it at least to the water fountain in Lexington, but open to seeing how the group feels.  If there's time and people are interested, we could get ice cream or something to eat afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't go Thursday, I'd appreciate it if you would respond &amp;quot;No&amp;quot; and also give a reason; date/time not good, location not accessible, etc.  It will help with planning other Meetups.  I was thinking of making the time 6:00 p.m., but not everyone gets out of work at 5:00 p.m. and some people like/need to go home first.  I'd really like to set up a couple of polls to get some feedback.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather prediction changes, i.e. rain or cold, or if there's low interest, I will cancel and schedule something for a weekend in the near future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dee&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There's a Not your Average Joe's at 645 Mass Ave in Arlington.  Next to it is a driveway to the parking lot.  We'll meet on the trail accessible from the parking lot.  There's a big rock near a tree.  I'll be there or on the fence across from it.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214067589000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Weather is supposed to be in the upper 60s and sunny.</why><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208749047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First skate of the season!</name><id>7779010</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209076200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/7779010/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/8/global_1713624.jpeg</photo_url></item>