<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;Yet another film festival in the Boston area : &amp;quot;Salud&amp;quot;  is  about Cuban health care while &amp;quot;I am Andean&amp;quot; depicts American dancers -yes, this is probably our group's first event about Dance, in search of their Peruvian roots. The films are playing back to back, but you will have to buy  separate tickets ($18) if you plan to attend both. When you RSVP please enter in the comments section which film (or both) you will be attending.  The &amp;quot;official&amp;quot; group discussion will take place after &amp;quot;I am Andean&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First up is Salud, at 4:30 - a look at the Cuban Health Care System:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Moore?s Sicko, an incendiary expose of the for-profit health care system in the United States, generated some predictable backlash from right-wing pundits. More than anything else in the film, what tended to get them especially enraged was the role of Cuba in the documentary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After comparing and contrasting the US system with health care in Canada, Britain and France, Moore delivers the coup de grace by taking a number of 9/11 rescue workers to Cuba to get treatment for work-related illnesses that the U.S. system would not cover. These scenes feature friendly Cuban medical professionals providing free, quality care to the sick 9/11 heroes so shamefully neglected by their own government. Contrary to the hysterical claims of Moore?s critics, these acts of generosity were not mere propaganda set-ups; in reality, the provision of free treatment for the 9/11 workers only scratches the surface of Cuba?s exemplary medical internationalism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Connie Field?s Salud!(93 minutes) picks up from Moore?s Sicko with a  documentary that examines Cuba?s long and elaborate history of exporting the gains of socialized medicine. In addition to telling an inspiring story that has received next to no mainstream media coverage in the western world, Salud! also presents an important debate, counterposing two very different philosophies as to what it means to be a physician.  Seven Oaks Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.zmag.org/content/showarticle.cfm?ItemID=13763" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.zmag.org/c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am Andean  (62 minutes)   at 6:30   Two New Yorkers raised in different worlds - an immigrant from the Andes, a modern dancer from Queens - journey to Peru to reconnect with roots and an astonishing world of traditional dance. This screens with If It Doesn't Rain (21 minutes) where the residents of a poor, rural Mexican community grapple with the competition for water between a new trout farm and traditional irrigation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As might be expected, reviews of I am Andean are hard to come by- I just thought it was an interesting topic:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am Andean tells the intersecting stories of two New Yorkers (a modern and hip-hop dance dancer raised in Queens, and a folkloric dancer from the Andes) on a dazzling odyssey through Peru in search of roots and a world of folkloric dance. Soy Andina is an exuberant cross-cultural road trip, bursting with traditional music and dance rarely seen outside the country. But the core story is intimate and universal: a yearning for roots and connection in turbulent times. Southside Film Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after both  movies and will make sure that those who only attend the first movie, Salud, will &amp;quot;meetup&amp;quot; for a discussion at a local restuarant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, please drop me an email-&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192567077000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190425368000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Films from the Boston Latino International Film Festival</name><id>6405823</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192393800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6405823/</event_url></item>