<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>411 Waverley Oaks Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.387184</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 894-7011</phone><name>Wave Sports Pub</name><city>Waltham</city><id>786723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.203256</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's meet at the Wave Sports Pub for their Karaoke Night on Saturday March 15th, 2008. Some folks may want to get together earlier for dinner. More details to follow and we can also organize some carpools! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM BOSTON&lt;br /&gt;Take Storrow Drive West towards Watertown.  After the Harvard Square exit, take the Fresh Pond Parkway exit (Route16).  Go over the Bridge and follow signs for Rte 16 Watertown.  Take a right after the Star Market onto Belmont Street.  This will turn into Trapelo Road.  Stay on Trapelo Road / Belmont Street until you come to your third set of lights.  At lights take a left onto Route 60, which is Waverley Oaks Road.  Less than a ¼ mile down on the left is an industrial park . We are located in building #2.  Look for the brown awing that says THE WAVE SPORTS PUB.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM RTE 128&lt;br /&gt;Take route 128 towards Waltham to the Trapelo Road exit (28). Follow the signs for Belmont.  You will stay on Trapelo Road for approximately 4 ½ miles.  You will come to a set of lights and see a sign for Route 60, Waltham.  Take that right at lights which is Route 60 / Waverley Oaks Road.  Less than a ¼ mile down on the left is an industrial park.  We are located in Building #2.  Look for the brown awning that says THE WAVE SPORTS PUB.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will pick a designated meeting area later!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ellen</member_name><member_id>4148667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213591094000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>We always have a great time together and everyone enjoyed doing karaoke at our last party!</why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>425314</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Jewish Singles 55+  of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203722324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Karaoke at the Wave</name><id>7388826</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205629200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston/events/7388826/</event_url></item>