<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://xtcboston.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;eXtreme Thursday Club Boston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original eXtreme Tuesday Club is a weekly gathering of eXtreme Programming practitioners that has taken place in London for 8 years or so. It has provided a great community for like-minded software developers, managers and coaches to get together in a very informal way to discuss the ups and downs of using XP and other agile Software Development methods on a wide variety of projects in all sorts of organisations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A similar group formed in New York in January 2007, and the Boston group formed in September 2007.  The Boston group has since decided to move its meetings to Thursdays because of conflicts with other things on members' schedules.  We are currently planning to hold meetings on the first Thursday of each month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The schedule is changing to the second Thursday for this month because of a conflict I have for the regular date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to a place in Central Square, Cambridge that I recently saw work very well for a different meetup group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The June meeting will be:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Thursday, June 12 from 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;    * The Tavern in the Square,  730 Mass Ave, Cambridge, MA 02139&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My photo and those of some other regulars are on the blog at http://xtcboston.blogspot.com as well as here at Meetup.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Don Roby</member_name><member_id>5713230</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213483194000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Extreme Programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>xp-28</urlname><id>840210</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>eXtreme Tuesday Club - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209685192000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>eXtreme Thursday Club - Boston June Meeting</name><id>7853754</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213309800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/xp-28/events/7853754/</event_url></item>