<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>538 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.655553</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207 828 5600</phone><name>Space</name><city>Portland</city><id>808535</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.261570</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>My name is jay thompson, I run the Science group l live 20min south of portland and 40min to nh boarder 95 portsmouth and dover.  I have teamed up with Nerd Fun in boston for a few events - and carpooled to them - great fun.  This spring - first year in America 4 Science festivals will be held.  We are lucky to live within 90min drive of the event - It will be heald all over Cambridge MA.  The event is sheduled to take 9 days - so that will be 2 full weekends - I have taken the week off to Make the best of it!  Id like you all to join me.  You can start by comming up to Portland Maine on a Thursday night for 10 or more presentations from average people like me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS IS THE EVENT AS POSTED ON the science group:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pecha Kucha, (which is Japanese for 'the sound of conversation'), was created by Klein Dytham Architecture in Tokyo and has spread to hundreds of cities worldwide, including Portland. It is intended to gather creative individuals, designers, architects and artists to meet, network, and to share and discuss their work in an informal, relaxed environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presenters are allowed 20 images, shown for 20 seconds each—giving 6 minutes &amp;amp; 40 seconds per presentation. This allows the audience to experience a diverse group of speakers in a relatively short space of time. After the presentations, the evening continues with drinks and music. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been to a few of these they are great fun - science meets art! I may try to present - most people would choose death over public speaking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 6:30pm, event starts at 7:20pm, $5, all ages. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do go please - see me - Lets really MEET UP - I'm not going to push it with dinner first but if anyone else is game there are good restaurants nearby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please tell your friends to join - and let me know of any other good ideas for meet ups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;j your science guy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>google jay thompson</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241401366000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232821936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SCIENCE group mash up</name><id>9592324</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235088000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/9592324/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/e/global_1941310.jpeg</photo_url></item>