<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Sorry for the mix-up.  Our event this week was scheduled for the same night as the Revolve Nation Quarterly Party!  I have included the information and link below.  We always have around 150 to 200 people attend these events, with a strong green business presence.  I hope to see you all there.  Also, feel free to sign up at our other meet-up, Revolve Nation, for more notices on these events, other events, seminars and panels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://entrepreneur.meetup.com/674/calendar/9131863/"&gt;http://entrepreneur.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3rd Annual Revolve Nation Holiday Networking Party at The Greatest Bar!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a fun evening of networking, music, food and drinks and meet over a hundred colleagues in entrepreneurship at this great event. Discover new business partners, build rewarding relationships, and network with the largest and most premiere networking organization in Boston, Revolve Nation: Boston Entrepreneurs Group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When; Thursday, November 20th 6pm-9pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: The Greatest Bar &lt;br /&gt;262 Friend Street &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02114&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP as space is limited!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored By: Exemplar Companies, Inc. www.exemplarcompanies.com &lt;br /&gt;Revolve, Inc. www.revolvethis.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the stiff in the suit</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229644809000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>smallbiz-1186</urlname><id>1252936</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation: Boston's Green and Sustainable Business Grp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225407964000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston's Green and Sustainable Business Grp (Revolve Nation) November Meetup</name><id>9063736</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227222000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/smallbiz-1186/events/9063736/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/5/global_5114293.jpeg</photo_url></item>