<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us as we try a new restaurant in Weymouth Landing.  Blue Pointe Bistro serves Contemporary American Cuisine.  Appetizers include salads, crispy calamari and salmon risotti, and range in price from $6-$10.  Entrees include grilled chicken breasts, spring lamb pasta, and grilled hanger steak, and range in price from $15-$20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, May 9th, 2008&lt;br /&gt;7pm&lt;br /&gt;Blue Pointe Bistro&lt;br /&gt;61 Washington Street &lt;br /&gt;Route 53&lt;br /&gt;(On the Corner of Front Street across from Sacred Heart Church)&lt;br /&gt;781-335-7505&lt;br /&gt;www.bluepointebistro.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minimum/Maximum: Attendance is limited to 16 people.  &lt;br /&gt;Guests: Sorry, due to the limited number of attendees as well as the surprise we have in store for attendees, Guests are not allowed.  This is a Members Only event. &lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place:  We'll meet outside if the weather is good.  Otherwise, we will meet inside the Lobby/Bar Area.&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: $2pp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Wednesday, May 7th @ 4pm ~ The Restaurant has asked us to finalize our reservation by Wednesday night.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organized by:  Angela and Kathy&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather:  Event takes place rain or shine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Can be found on the website at www.bluepointebistro.com.  Blue Pointe Bistro is located on Route 53 in Weymouth Landing on the corner of Washington and Front Streets across from Sacred Heart Church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;Commuter Rail: 1/4 mile south of the East Braintree/Weymouth Landing Commuter Rail Station&lt;br /&gt;T: On the Bus Line&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be meeting in the Lobby and then we will go to our table together.  If you arrive after we are seated please ask the host to show you to our table.  The reservation is under "Kathy" and "Meetup Group."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathy</member_name><member_id>339609</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210650265000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>11</count></rating><why>We have a surprise for you all.</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208633225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Dinner!</name><id>7770607</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210374000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7770607/</event_url></item>