<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's ride the very flat, &lt;strong&gt;Minuteman Rail Trail&lt;/strong&gt; (~16 miles round trip). We'll poll the group to see if they would like to lengthen the ride, by going out to Concord.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I should add that I'll set a 10-14 MPH (moving average) pace with plenty of stopping at major points for the group to regroup. We'll try to keep this at a brisk pace, but be on the look out for kids, bladers, runners etc. and road crossings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring bike tire repair kit, energy snacks, water, camera, layers of clothing etc. &lt;strong&gt;A bike helmet is required.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slick road surfaces cancel this ride. &amp;nbsp;My mobile number will be sent out on Friday night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high for Saturday is a sunny 49 degrees, so be advised to wear cold weather biking stuff (leggings, jacket, gloves with fingers,...)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards we will stop at _____________ (a pub) for food and drink and laughter. Please indicate if you're interested in going to the&amp;nbsp;restaurant&amp;nbsp;after the ride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's &lt;strong&gt;meet behind&lt;/strong&gt; the Bank of America / Not Your Average Joes parking lot near the corner of Mystic Ave and Mass Ave (RT 60 &amp;amp; 2A). Here is a google map link&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://g.co/maps/2w7xf" class="linkified"&gt;http://g.co/maps/2w7xf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be wearing a bright yellow jacket and hanging out near my brown MINI cooper on the East side of the parking lot &amp;amp; trail.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>East end of parking lot behind Bank of America and Not Your Average Joes.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Douglas M.</member_name><member_id>9031252</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320633120000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320067154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ride the Minute Man Rail Trail Arlington to Bedford and Beyond?</name><id>39345532</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320516000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/39345532/</event_url></item>