<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>236 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01550</zip><lat>42.074353</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 764 5426</phone><name>Jacob Edwards Library</name><city>Southbridge</city><id>1219568</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.032281</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I thought I'd share this with you all... Scott was asked to have a show of his portraits of the artists from his book at the Library in Southbridge. If you are in the area please stop by and check out the photos!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TWENTY ARTISTS OF WORCESTER: Photographic Portraits of the Artists&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Erb of Erb Photography is hanging his photographs from the book Twenty Artists of Worcester during an exhibiting at the Jacob Edwards Library located at 236 Main Street Southbridge, MA, from April 1st to April 30th. The project, which was partially funded by an individual grant from the Worcester Cultural Commission, highlights 20 of Worcester County’s most talented artists. Including Southbridge’s own talented artist, Antonio Fonseca.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It was hard to believe after meeting so many creative people in the area that there was so little publicity about them,” Erb said.  Taking matters into his own hands, he began his own creative journey to document—through photography and text—20 of the most sought after artists in Worcester County in their personal studios. “I wanted to meet and collaborate with them in order to create interesting images…images that could tell a little bit about them as creative people living and working in the area.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Erb will be able to show off these hidden and not-so-hidden gems in this exhibition. But if you are interested in the book based on this show, you’ll have to order it online; as the book sold out at the opening show last November at the Davis Art Gallery in Worcester MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ordering the book is easy: &lt;a href="http://www.blurb.com/bookstore/detail/384556" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.blurb.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone who would like Scott to sign their book is welcome to bring their copy to the opening of the show on April 1st at 6:30PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Book&lt;br /&gt;Worcester County is teaming with talent, and this book showcases that talent. 20 Artists of Worcester is an amazing array of images showing artists in their work spaces. These artists are international known and collected and there is a very broad array of work to be discovered. Scott Erb, a professional photographer located in central MA, photographed the many types of artists to be found in Worcester. Everyone from traditional oil painters to photographers to sculptors to portrait painters to watercolor artists. This combined with colorful text written by Julie Grady, will give you a unique and inspiring view of Worcester artists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information or to learn more about the project Twenty Artists of Worcester, please contact Scott Erb and Donna Dufault at 774.239.0214 or scott@erbphoto.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270397385000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268772892000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>20 Artists of Worcester Photo Show at the Jacob Edward's Library in Southbridge </name><id>12894111</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270161000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/12894111/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/5/global_5650101.jpeg</photo_url></item>