<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/6/4/event_155464452.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The topic of this event is how to have an effective, comfortable pricing conversation with prospective clients that works with your personality.&lt;/strong&gt; We'll talk about how friendly, relationship-oriented professionals can stand strong on their pricing without losing the sale, sounding desperate or getting on that emotional-roller coaster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Marketing Cafe™ is the online radio show that features simple, yet highly effective ideas&lt;/strong&gt; for solopreneurs and small business owners like you who want to make a good living while making a difference in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Show Access Info here:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://wp.me/P29Qf9-ro"&gt;http://wp.me/P29Qf9-ro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; Thursday, Sept. 27, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 12 noon Eastern Time &lt;br /&gt;

 (&lt;strong&gt;48 hour replay&lt;/strong&gt; available if your schedule doesn't cooperate).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The featured guest speaker is power maven and positive problem-solver Dina Eisenberg, JD.&lt;/strong&gt; She understands the importance of speaking up for yourself in life and business. Dina has been a Senior VP at one of the nation’s largest financial institutions and consulted to leading organizations like Coca Cola, Harvard, Lexmark and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your host is marketing results coach Mark Reinert,&lt;/strong&gt; founder of Authentic Business Growth, LLC and the creator of the Business Growth Dojo™ the definitive business incubator for independent professionals and owners of small service-based businesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Show Access Info here:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://wp.me/P29Qf9-ro"&gt;http://wp.me/P29Qf9-ro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;During this program you will learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to talk about price without sounding desperate&lt;/strong&gt; or getting on that emotional-roller coaster. &lt;br /&gt;

 Understand deeply what's so important about speaking up for yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The important difference&lt;/strong&gt; between setting the right price and saying it powerfully, and comfortably.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How friendly, relationship-oriented professionals can stand strong&lt;/strong&gt; on their pricing without losing the sale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role of your mindset and the dangers of stinking thinking&lt;/strong&gt; about money, value and self-esteem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to say to your spouse about your business.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The key components of a pricing conversation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are naked numbers&lt;/strong&gt; and the clothes your price should wear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What it takes to be fearless.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Show Access Info here:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://wp.me/P29Qf9-ro"&gt;http://wp.me/P29Qf9-ro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Reinert</member_name><member_id>7305695</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348775878000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSmallBusiness</urlname><id>1319989</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Small Business Success Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346707014000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Say Your Price Powerfully!</name><id>80671862</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348761600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSmallBusiness/events/80671862/</event_url></item>