<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sorry for the short notice.  I've just gotten back from the Palm Springs International Film Festival (PSIFF).  This movie is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE ROAD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2009) Directed by John Hillcoat. Screenplay by Joe Penhall, based on the novel by Cormac McCarthy. Director of photography, Javier Aguirresarobe. Cast: Viggo Mortensen, Kodi Smit-McPhee, Charlize Theron, Robert Duvall. &lt;br /&gt;Cormac McCarthy's last novel to hit the screen, No Country For Old Men, may have swept the Oscars, but The Road is a more interesting - and Pulitzer Prize winning - story. Sometime in the future there has been an apocalypse that wipes out life as we know it. As fires rage and roaming thieves prey on the weak, what remains is a father (Viggo Mortensen) with the desperate quest to protect his 11 year old son (Kodi Smit-McPhee) and bring him to the safety and warmth of the ocean. Nick Cave provides the perfect musical backdrop to a future gone terribly wrong. &amp;quot;Haunting...the artistry of Mortensen and Smit-McPhee carries the fire of our shared humanity and lets it burn bright and true.&amp;quot; Peter Travers, Rolling Stone. 111 min. www.theroad-movie.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby on the bench. (Waiting expectantly)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264638504000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264268419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Road</name><id>12401146</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264464900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/12401146/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>