<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Berlin CT</address_2><address_1>151 Webster Square RD</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06037</zip><lat>41.628593</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-828-7721</phone><name>Ultimate Billiards</name><city>Berlin</city><id>523523</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.746000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are joining The Thirsty Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Meetup Group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soul Sound Revue at Ultimate Billiards (Steve's Birthday bash!) Great band&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who should come: Anyone who enjoys night life, dancing, billiards, ping-pong and meeting new people and seeing old friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why: IT'S A GREAT GROUP OF PEOPLE. (Plus it's my birthday!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Description: COME TO ULTIMATE BILLIARDS ON FRIDAY NIGHT! DANCE THE NIGHT AWAY, PLAY POOL, PING-PONG, ETC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soul Sound Revue by far the hottest Motown show this side of Detriot, performs the greatest hits in the true ?Motown Tradition&amp;quot;. Soul Sound Revue recreates the dynamic vocal harmonies and musical stylings of classic Motown groups of the sixties, seventies, and eighties: The Four Tops, The Temptations, Stevie Wonder, The Supremes, and many more. With the popular resurgence of the seventies, eighties, and nineties, Soul Sound Revue currently performs the most popular dance hits spanning four decades. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soul Sound Revue has performed with a variety of Detriot's greats such as, The Temptations, The Marvelettes, The Chi-Lites and Wilson Pickett. The group also shared the stage with The Drifters, Little Anthony and the Imperials, Shirley Austin Reed &amp;amp; The Shirrells, James Cotton and Tower of Power, to name a few. This high energy show performs to full houses from the peaks of Killington, VT. to the dazzling stages of Las Vegas. Soul Sound Revue is currently a steady act at the world class Mohegan Sun Casino and Resort in Uncasville, CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With all the flash and finery reminiscent of a time when dress and show were as important as the players and vocalist's stage presence, Soul Sound Revue's three lead vocalists explode onto the stage with a vibrant six-piece rhythm and multi-horn back-up band that will leave you breathless!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Audiences will &amp;quot;groove&amp;quot; through the sixties and &amp;quot;boogie&amp;quot; through the seventies with Soul Sound Revue. This Band guarantees to make your event the most exciting and fun-filled party ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we  will be the life of the party</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy</member_name><member_id>4345102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213576766000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213268374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>great  music and dancing</name><id>8128469</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213403400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8128469/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>