<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.407211</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>Online</city><id>4355392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.382439</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As you know WAP and the Worcester cultural commission have a unique gallery space in city hall downtown Worcester. It's that time of year where we switch out the current show and put up a new one. But this one is the best one of the year. As we know there will be a ton of events going on downtown for the holiday seasons. We are planning our opening of this show to be the same night as the tree light ceremony at city center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme for this show is "Let there be Light" and is your opportunity to interpret this broad theme any way you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few simple rules - due to this being a public space and one with high traffic, we ask that you use discretion when picking your images. We also ask that you keep things upbeat and in the festive mood of the season. Please pick up to three images, use your names as the file name when submitting them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be juroring them since we only have 25 frames for the space. You must be able to attend the framing party on nov 10th at the library so you can frame your chosen image.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where to submit? There is a photo album in the photo section of this web site labeled Let there be Light. Please submit your photos here: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/photos/11099542/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/photos/11099542/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submissions need to be made on or before 7pm 10/18/12 We will notify you on 10/23/12 if your image is chosen for the show. We will do so by leaving your photo in this gallery. If you do not see your image among the 25 images chosen, then it was not selected this time around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who? A trio of city folks do the jurying it may vary due to deadlines, but typically it is Erin Williams of the Worcester cultural commission, Howard and Anne, who run Worcester windows program throughout the city. What? if your image is included in the show you must print it and get it matted with a white mat that will fit into a 16x24 frame. 16x24 is the frame size your matted print must fit into. That's 16x24.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any questions?&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the photo section of this web site to submit up to 3 images for jury show</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350612491000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349506085000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>City Hall Gallery Show: Let There Be Light</name><id>85761272</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350601200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/85761272/</event_url></item>