<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Herb Pearce continues to teach us about the amazing Enneagram of Personality.  This week the focus will be on learning about the different kinds of Enneagram subtypes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description of the workshop from Herb: “Once you know the Basic 9 Enneagram types, you are just brushing the surface. Learn about Instinctual Subtypes, Subtype Stacking, Wings, Stress and Secure Types, TriTypes, Parental Types. There are plenty of subcategories within each type, as well as ways that you take on qualities of other types. You'll learn more about yourself and others than you ever dreamed possible!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it. Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit of 30 has been set. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** Details from Herb Pearce’s website *****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About the Enneagram **&lt;br /&gt;The star-shaped Enneagram (Greek for &amp;quot;nine&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;drawing&amp;quot;) groups human emotions and behavior—positive and negative –into nine personality types. According to the Enneagram theory, personality develops as a result of a unique combination of genetics, cultural influence, family and childhood experience, and spiritual growth inclination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About Herb Pearce **&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce, M.Ed, has been teaching the Enneagram for 18 years with public workshops, as well as to organizations and companies for team building and sales training. He is a psychotherapist who uses the Enneagram with individuals, couples and families to improve communication, self understanding and psychological and spiritual growth..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240010967000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237782477000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enneagram Subtypes </name><id>10013676</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239750000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/10013676/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/8/global_7203288.jpeg</photo_url></item>