<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>407 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396122</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comicazi</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1498136</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121231</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Good News Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The poll this month was a dead tie! It looks like people want to read both books, so we will be reading one in November and the other for December. For December, why don't we read Redshirts: A Novel with Three Codas, by John Scalzi! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 From Amazon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ensign Andrew Dahl has just been assigned to the Universal Union Capital Ship&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Intrepid&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;, flagship of the Universal Union since the year 2456. It’s a prestige posting, and Andrew is thrilled all the more to be assigned to the ship’s Xenobiology laboratory.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Life couldn't be better…until Andrew begins to pick up on the fact that (1) every Away Mission involves some kind of lethal confrontation with alien forces, (2) the ship’s captain, its chief science officer, and the handsome Lieutenant Kerensky always survive these confrontations, and (3) at least one low-ranked crew member is, sadly, always killed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not surprisingly, a great deal of energy below decks is expedition avoiding, at all costs, being assigned to an Away Mission. Then Andrew stumbles on information that completely transforms his and his colleagues’ understanding of what the starship&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Intrepid&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;really is…and offers them a crazy, high-risk chance to save their own lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be meeting at Comicazi on Highland Ave in Davis Square. There is metered parking all along Highland as well as a public lot on Day Street near Redbones and across the street from Orleans restaurant. There is also T access and bus connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Josh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the back of the store in the action figure section.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Josh</member_name><member_id>9704391</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben S.</member_name><member_id>12781630</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355632968000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350929530000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Book Club</name><id>88078902</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355445000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/88078902/</event_url></item>