<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Canal Plaza</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.656825</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Senate Offices</name><city>Portland</city><id>1118395</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.255533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The following event has been postponed do to difficulty coordinating on such short notice.  I will follow up early next week with new date and time.  We may, im lieu of visiting maine, simply send a delegation with letters.  Please work on letters to Senators Snowe and Collins.  Our comrades in Maine will hand deliver them.  We will plan an event for MA in the coming weeks.  Stay tuned.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Maine, Massachusetts and Rhode Island Tea Party groups as we travel to Portland to meet with aides to Senators Snowe and Collins.  We will meet at Canal Plaza to hold an outdoor rally encouraging a &lt;b&gt;No Vote&lt;/b&gt; on the proposed healthcare bill the Senate will begin debating next week.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt; on a public option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt; on health benefits payroll taxes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt; on Medicare cuts - rationing of care to seniors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt; on mandates to purchase coverage or pay fines and go to jail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt; to $1.2 or $2.4 or whatever the price tag is this week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As citizens of Massachusetts, who are being represented in the Senate by a socialist twit and an unconstitutional seat warmer, we must show our support to our neighboring Senators - if they vote &lt;b&gt;NO on Obamacare&lt;/b&gt;.  If you cannot join us, send me your letters and we will deliver them.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpools are being organized  contact me with your location.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will set up a meeting place and update you.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christen Varley</member_name><member_id>9247789</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258561001000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258034708000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Senate Healthcare Vote Demonstration in Maine Postponed</name><id>11858166</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258387200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/11858166/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/a/4/global_8615540.jpeg</photo_url></item>