<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Main Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02837</zip><lat>41.530945</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-635-2985</phone><name>The Barn</name><city>Adamsville (Little Compton)</city><id>1168712</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.164072</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's get to know each other. This is a social get together (even though I'm the walking events planner, I'm trying something different &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt;). How about a Sunday Brunch at a quaint little breakfast restaurant called The Barn in Adamsville RI?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've heard about this place and I have never been. I know it's last minute, but if you're able to come - please do!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Barn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;15 Main St&lt;br /&gt;Little Compton, RI 02837&lt;br /&gt;(near Adamsville)&lt;br /&gt;(401) 635-2985&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Little Description I found online:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located a stone's throw from what is considered the oldest general store in the entire country (Gray's General Store) and situated in a village that is well over 300 years old, The Barn is literally surround by history. And the restaurant has a little history going for it as well, as it resides in a restored barn that feels like it is nearly as old as some of the structures around it. The charming spot includes an upstairs section that looks down over the main dining area, huge windows that let in an abundance of sunshine, an attractive wide-plank pine floor, exposed wooden beams along the ceiling, and artwork along the walls, including some pieces that are for sale to the public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Barn is all about breakfast, and they certainly seem to do breakfasts well here. Many items on the menu have twists on standard items, with the results often being quite memorable. Take the oatmeal, for instance; unlike what you tend to find at most places, it is baked and mixed with such items as apples, white raisins, and walnuts, making for an incredibly complex--and tremendously tasty--dish that is ordinarily rather basic. The homemade corned beef hash is also done differently, with green peppers and carrots giving the dish a hint of sweetness as well as a pleasant texture. The jonny cakes (a specialty in this part of Rhode Island) are so thin that you can almost see through them, and they have a slightly nutty flavor coming from the cornmeal and a mouthwatering sweetness from the whipped cream and real maple syrup. Some of the items at The Barn reflect the Portuguese heritage of the cities and towns in this part of New England, including the &amp;quot;six gun on a bun&amp;quot; which features eggs, hash, and cheese on Portuguese sweet bread, and the Portuguese omelet that comes with chourico, peppers, onions, and cheddar cheese. Other items on the menu at The Barn include biscuits in sausage gravy, an omelet with lobster meat, and cinnamon raisin French toast. The Barn is open Monday-Friday, 6am-11:30am; and 7am-12:30pm on the weekend. Closed Thanksgiving and Christmas Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hiddenboston.com/TheBarn.html" target="_blank"&gt;Read More &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271169727000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270824235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Sunday Brunch @ The Barn!</name><id>13134387</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270996200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/13134387/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/e/global_14232734.jpeg</photo_url></item>