<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 Brookline Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.343174</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.375.WITS (9487)</phone><name>5wits: The Tomb!</name><city>Boston</city><id>680683</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102789</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;8/25.10 update:  Donna and I will be taking the train, here are all the options to get there:&lt;br /&gt;scroll down&lt;br /&gt;BY SUBWAY&lt;br /&gt;Green Line&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the Green Line to the Fenway stop this requires taking the D-train, all others branch off one stop earlier in Kenmore square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit the T and cross over the tracks into the parking lot of the Landmark Center (you will see a big Bed, Bath &amp;amp; Beyond on your left). Walk around to the front side of the building, which faces Brookline Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5W!TS is directly across the street from the Best Buy and the Regal Fenway 13 movie theater.&lt;br /&gt;TRAVELING BY CAR&lt;br /&gt;From West of Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-90 East (Massachusetts Turnpike) toward Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit at Cambridge tolls and proceed towards Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn right onto Storrow Drive East before crossing the Charles River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Storrow Drive East to the Fenway exit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Fenway exit off Storrow Drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At lights, bear right onto Boylston Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Boylston Street, proceed through another set of lights and continue a couple blocks, past Fenway park on your right, and a Burger King on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will pass a Shaw's on your left. The rear side of 5W!TS is on your right, immediately after the Shaw's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main entrance is around the corner on Brookline Avenue, across the street from the Best Buy and the Regal Fenway 13 movie theater.&lt;br /&gt;From North &amp;amp; South of Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Head North/South into Boston on I-93 to Exit 26 (Storrow Drive).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Storrow Drive West approximately 2.5 miles to the Fenway/Route 1 South exit (on left). The exit ramp forks, stay to your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At lights, bear right onto Boylston Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Boylston Street, proceed through another set of lights and continue a couple blocks, past Fenway park on your right, and a Burger King on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will pass a Shaw's on your left. The rear side of 5W!TS is on your right, immediately after the Shaw's. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at the tomb, remember if your plans have changed, please update your RSVP&lt;br /&gt;Thank you&lt;br /&gt;Janet &amp;amp; Donna&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have the nerve to go head to head with Pharaoh? 5W!TS presents a mind-bending adventure of sights, sounds and action that's sure to get under your skin!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 5wits tomb adventure will be leaving the Boston Area effective Labor Day weekend, lets not miss out on this great adventure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;What is this event?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the heart of Boston, 5W!TS is the company producing TOMB. Participants get to play the role of hero in their own adventure, as they are confronted with puzzles, challenges, twists, and traps to test their bodies and minds. Sharp eyes, good ears, and quick wits will be required for any chance of successfully completing your personal adventure! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;So what exactly does a TOMB explorer do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each group is briefed by the Director, given flashlights, and makes your way to the Tomb entrance to try to discover a way in…Once inside, no one knows quite what will happen, but there are a few things you can be certain of: You’ll be using your mind and body to solve physical and mental challenges, working together as a team to progress through to the pharaoh’s burial chamber. Your choices matter in this hands-on adventure—no one said it would be easy, and there are consequences if you fail! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is TOMB physical?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, you will be walking through TOMB, on your feet, actively manipulating items in the TOMB. However, there is no crawling, climbing or jumping. TOMB is accessible to all.&lt;br /&gt;How long is each adventure?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TOMB is roughly 45 minutes long – the exact time varies depending on the choices your group makes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Current cost is $20.00 per person but if we get enough people to attend we will get a group rate.  All RSVPS must be in by the deadline in order to make a reservation, so please only RSVP if you are definitely coming. there is also a AAA discount available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 2:30pm for a 3Pm adventure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tomb is T accessible and located right near Fenway Park (there is no game at Fenway this day so there will not be alot of foot traffic)   If you have trouble locating us or are running late, please call us on the meetup cell phone @ 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at the tomb&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, look at the calendar for the dinner to follow this event&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the front entrance</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283126873000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280005706000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5WITS Tomb Adventure</name><id>14201755</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283020200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/14201755/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/6/global_16659542.jpeg</photo_url></item>