<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From our member who suggested this, Billie Gregorio: "Let's let them play, run, and chase and get some exercise.&amp;nbsp; A happy dog is a tired one!!&amp;nbsp; This is our second meet-up together.&amp;nbsp; The dogs seem to enjoy a few toys, sticks and tug-a-war rope play.&amp;nbsp; It's a large, safe environment to work on dog socialization, some dog training, and companionship of other bully owners.&amp;nbsp; If you're interested in having some fun and exercise for your furry pet, come meet us and say hi!!!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEBBC Dog/Handler Etiquette - PLEASE REVIEW:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~ Avoid head-on greetings between dogs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Until&lt;/em&gt; you are familiar with individual dogs AND handlers, contact between dogs must be kept to a minimum.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~ Prevent your dog from lunging on leash, whether it is in play or not.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~ Dog(s) must be kept under owner control &lt;em&gt;at all times.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~ Do not allow your dog to surprise, or "sneak up on" other dogs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~&amp;nbsp;A VERY important note: Just because two dogs are friendly, does &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; necessarily mean they are going to be friendly with &lt;em&gt;each other&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Make no assumptions and DO NOT LET YOUR DOG GREET ANOTHER DOG until you have asked and BEEN GIVEN PERMISSION by the owner.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the president &amp;amp; founder of the New England Bully Breed Club: "This meetup is being repeated on a trial basis for the month of March.&amp;nbsp; Dog parks are controversial topics among both bully breed lovers, and their detractors.&amp;nbsp; All town by-laws are always expected to be followed at these events, including at town parks.&amp;nbsp; Always clean up after your pet, and please be conscious of park-goers who may not be using the park as responsibly as you.&amp;nbsp; Leash your dog if a questionable owner/dog comes in; do not allow for an incident to take place.&amp;nbsp; ALWAYS have your eyes on your dog and be aware of their behavior; stop problems before they occur.&amp;nbsp; ALWAYS remember that you are representing your dogs, your breed, AND the NEBBC.&amp;nbsp; Your etiquette needs to indicate this.&amp;nbsp; This is the first time the NEBBC has promoted a repeating dog park event, and in order for this to continue, handlers need to 'keep it classy,' and be exemplary in controlling their dog's behavior as well as their own.&amp;nbsp; Please, no more than two dogs per handler (bring a friend if need be), and keep this very important etiquette in mind."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a great excerpt from an email entailing how these particular very responsible dog owners handled their first meeting at the park:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;"Better safe than sorry...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;We started our meet up with just some chatter amongst owners with the dogs on leashes, letting them get acclimated to each other and such.&amp;nbsp; Brawlick is a very mild mannered pit with fairly good manners.&amp;nbsp; Sophi is a pup, with lots of energy and excitement, and then there was my Missy, which was a little hyper there, as i think she was hoping it was doggie daycare (as that's where she goes).&amp;nbsp; After spending about 10 minutes together, we walked to the play area where everyone got into the empty dog park.&amp;nbsp; We kept the dogs on leash for a little longer, so again, they could get acclimated.&amp;nbsp; I had brought some toys for the dogs to distract them with, and each dog got a squeeky ball to start working with their handlers. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;All dogs were in great space, and interested in playing.&amp;nbsp; We then let them off leash, where the spent a better half of the next hour running and chasing the balls, ropes and sticks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;During the play time, another group of dogs joined in the park, which we introduced ourselves and our pets to.&amp;nbsp; She unfortunately let her dogs off leash quickly... but all 5 dogs got along great.&amp;nbsp; Another set of dogs came in later, and immediately started growling.&amp;nbsp; Our group grabbed our dogs to ensure there would be no issues, and that individual quickly left with her dogs who never got off leash.&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;I am by no means a "professional" when it comes to this stuff.&amp;nbsp; I use some common sense."&lt;/span&gt; This email and the way the meetup was handled are EXTREMELY appreciated.&amp;nbsp; We try not to keep these messages so long, but this is a sensitive topic, and we want this to be successful, happy and most certainly not doing any damage to our already-maligned breeds' images. THANK YOU ALL for your cooperation. &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;This meetup is for socialized, non-aggressive dogs ONLY.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; If these issues are something you need to work on, please contact me directly at justcassie101@gmail for more information.</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Billie Lyn</member_name><member_id>38788962</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332124463000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331525967000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Southern NH - Bully Breed Play Date</name><id>qwvtpcyqfbxb</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332084600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/55981672/</event_url></item>