<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come learn the breathing techniques and body awareness principles that are the foundation to the STOTT PILATES Method of Conditioning. With just a few basic mat pilates movements, you can begin to build core strength, improve your posture, increase circulation, and reduce pain and tension in your muscles. Workshop will be based on matwork, but will also include a demonstration on the Pilates Reformer.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have all the equipment we'll need, but feel free to bring your own yoga mat if you prefer. Come prepared to exercise, but you are also welcome to join us if you just want to watch!  &lt;u&gt;This is a SECOND offering for this very popular class&lt;/u&gt;.  Don't hesitate to RSVP, as spaces are sure to fill up quickly! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Cate Vallone, STOTT PILATES Instructor Trainer and owner of Evolution Pilates, for this FREE introductory workshop. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;------  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Pilates was originally designed for rehab.  I took this introductory class and was very impressed.  I have a hip injury from a severe car accident that I have been working on for a long time now.  Certainly many muscles have gotten quite strong after a total of 6 months of physical therapy and 2 years of the elliptical trainer....but the use of the Pilates Reformer machine helped me to isolate the exact muscles that are still injured so that I can specifically work on them.  You can be sure I'll be back for more!  I'm so excited that I found something that can help me get better and feel less pain!   ~Susanne&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By clicking &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for agreeing to attend this event, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the STEPPIN' OUT...A Social Group! Meetup Group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event and grant the STEPPIN' OUT...A Social Group! Meetup Group the authority to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285295735000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283822533000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Introduction to Pilates: The Basic Principles (9/23/10)</name><id>14678443</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285282800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/14678443/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/2/global_17651250.jpeg</photo_url></item>