<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Wednesday, September 20th, 2006: Four people who hadn't previously known each other met for dinner at Finian's Restaurant in Quincy Center. It was a simple test of a simple idea; a Meetup group centered around dining out. Depending upon any number of variables - timing, personalities, luck - it could have flourished or fallen flat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fast-forward nearly three years. At this writing, there are approximately 90 people in the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group; the group has dined at restaurants all over the South Shore, from Quincy to Stoughton, Scituate, Middleboro, Plymouth and many, if not most of the towns in between. People have learned about new restaurants, tried new foods and made new friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a nutshell, SSDOMG has been a success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're planning to celebrate that success the way that we do pretty much everything: With food, company, conversation and laughter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Thursday, August 27th, we're returning to Quincy for our third anniversary dinner. We'll be sitting where we can look out over the water from the &lt;a href="http://www.innatbaypointe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Inn at Bay Pointe&lt;/a&gt;; a restaurant that several members consider a favorite; which we have been saving for the right occasion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join Angela, Mike and Mindy as we remember three years of food and friendship, and look toward the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Third Anniversary Dinner&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, August 27th @ 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;The Inn At Bay Pointe&lt;br /&gt;64 Washington Court&lt;br /&gt;Quincy, MA 02169&lt;br /&gt;617-472-3200&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.innatbaypointe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.innatbaypo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Organizer(s):&lt;/b&gt; SSDOMG Organizer Team - Angela, Jeanne, Mike and Mindy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; Max of 30 people.  (Increased from 25 to 30 on 8/20 due to the high interest and lengthy Wait List.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Sorry, due to the high interest among Group Members, this event is for Members Only.  Please encourage your potential Guests to join the Group and put themselves on the Wait List.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Most dinner entrees are under $20.00 - The menu starts out on its low end with a vegetable stir fry for $12.95 and tops out at $23.95 for New Zealand Rack of Lamb.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for nearly three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; None for Group Members.  [Guests will be $2 each.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; 12:30pm on Thursday, August 27th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions (Credit to Inn at Bay Pointe website):&lt;/b&gt; The Inn At Bay Pointe is located at the Bay Pointe Marina in Quincy. The Bay Pointe Marina is located at the end of Washington Court, a side street off of Washington St (Route 3A).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3:&lt;/b&gt;  Take Exit 17 (Union St). This is the Union Street Rotary. Exit the rotary by turning onto the Union Street, East Braintree exit, passing the Braintree Police Station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through two traffic lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next major intersection is Weymouth landing, where you will see a 7 Eleven convenience store on your left. At this point you can either bear right, heading into Weymouth Landing, or go straight, which brings you immediately to a traffic light. Go straight, then take a left at the light onto Quincy Avenue, keeping the 7 Eleven and Eastern Bank on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Immediately after you turn left there is another light at the entrance to the new Weymouth Landing MBTA station. Go straight through this light, then straight through the next couple lights, remaining on Quincy Avenue until you come to the traffic light at East Howard Street (at this light, railroad tracks cross the road and the old Fore River Shipyard, now owned by automobile tycoon Dan Quirk and full of cars, is on your right).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn right onto East Howard Street, keeping the former shipyard on your right. Follow East Howard St for a short distance as it skirts the boundaries of the shipyard, then bears right, becoming the last section of South St. (The road forks just after it becomes South St; it's alittle easier to bear right to remain on South St than to bear left onto Cleverly Court, although this route will also bring you to the restaurant).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South Street ends at Washington St (Route 3A). There is a trafic light at this intersection and a Dairy Queen acoss the street. Turn left onto Washington St, then take your next right onto Washington Court. Follow Washington Court all the way down until it ends in the Bay Pointe Marina. The restaurant and its parking area are easily visible once you're on the marina grounds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3A, heading North:&lt;/b&gt; Go over the Fore River Bridge, crossing from Weymouth into Quincy. Take your first right &lt;b&gt;after&lt;/b&gt; the set of lights where Dairy Queen is on your right. You will see the sign for The Inn at Bay Pointe on the corner. It is a blue sign with gold lettering. Follow this road (Washington Court)all the way to the end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3A, heading South:&lt;/b&gt; Washington Court is a left off of Route 3A shortly before Route 3A crosses the Fore River Bridge. This stretch of Route 3A is part of Washington Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Head South on Washington Street. After St. Joseph's Church, take your second left onto Washington Court. You will see the sign for the Inn at Bay Pointe on the corner. It is a blue sign with gold lettering. Follow this road all the way to the end. Note that if you pass a Dairy Queen on your left, you have overshot Washington Court and need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the Front Door.  Late arrivals should ask the host for "Angela."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>714439</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>8014085</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252791533000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248020757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Three's a Charm! Third Anniversary Dinner!</name><id>10909092</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251412200000</time><rsvp_limit>31</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10909092/</event_url></item>