<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at the end of January as we discuss &lt;em&gt;Forever Amber&lt;/em&gt; by Kathleen Winsor. This epic historical fiction set 17th century England is a total page turner, but long (972 pages!) so I'm posting this early to give everyone a chance to finish it! I have a feeling this will be one of our best discussions yet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below are descriptions of the book from GoodReads and an Amazon reviewer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Abandoned pregnant and penniless on the teeming streets of London, 16-year-old Amber St. Clare manages, by using her wits, beauty, and courage, to climb to the highest position a woman could achieve in Restoration England-that of favorite mistress of the Merry Monarch, Charles II. From whores and highwaymen to courtiers and noblemen, from events such as the Great Plague and the Fire of London to the intimate passions of ordinary-and extraordinary-men and women, Amber experiences it all. But throughout her trials and escapades, she remains, in her heart, true to the one man she really loves, the one man she can never have. Frequently compared to Gone with the Wind, Forever Amber is the other great historical romance, outselling every other American novel of the 1940s-despite being banned in Boston for its sheer sexiness. A book to read and reread, this edition brings back to print an unforgettable romance and a timeless masterpiece.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wildly Addictive&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This is NOT a story to be missed! I could not believe that this was written back in 1944...it felt so fresh and not at all old fashioned. I thought that the authors writing style was brilliant. The book is mainly about the life of a girl called Amber St. Clare. The thing about Amber is that she is not easy to like..in fact..I was appalled by her often, but at the same time I found myself admiring her determination, rooting for her, and pitying her as well. The book goes on for 972 pages and at the end of it all I actually wanted MORE. The descriptions were so vivid that I felt like I could see, smell, TASTE London as it was in the 1660s. I am so happy to have experienced this tale. I plan to look for more of Kathleen Winsor's work and I wholeheartedly recommend this book to any lover of historical fiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359910474000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351785854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Forever Amber by Kathleen Winsor</name><id>89479852</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359676800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/89479852/</event_url></item>