<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Watson-Spruce Corner Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01330</zip><lat>42.519289</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South Face Farm</name><city>Ashfield</city><id>1205989</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.853578</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>How fun! It's that time of year when the sap is running and the pancakes are flipping. This fun jaunt will be our first casual event hosted by a member (and several more are coming in the next few weeks). How exciting! &lt;br /&gt;Lou Franco has offered to be the Event Organizer for pancakes at the Southface Farm Sugar House, this Sunday, March 7th. Lou, who is a self-styled sugar house expert definitively states that if you don't get there early, you have to wait an extra hour to get a table, so...this one's for the early birds (or the ones who haven't gone to sleep yet)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's no extra charge for this event, everyone will just pay for themselves at the farm, but please RSVP if you're coming and please show up if you said you would. We're going to make room for 10 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone can meet there or carpool and it will be lots of fun. I'm going to try and make it myself! (we'll see...)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions? Ask Lou: 413-250-6660.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Northampton: Take rte 9W to rte 112N (towards Ashfield) when you get to rte 116N, make a left (towards Plainfield). Make a right on Watson Spruce Corner Rd. Follow the signs, it's on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://southfacefarm.com/sugarhouse.php" target="_blank"&gt;South Face Farm&lt;/a&gt; for further info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From their website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Our cozy dining area is an integral part of our maple producing operation. Our traditional old New England sugarhouse and restaurant is open starting the first weekend in March each year, and stays open to the public for six weekends. We are closed on Easter Sunday. Our hours are 8:30-3:00.You can watch pure maple syrup being made and then just a few steps away, taste the results on a plate of steaming hot blueberry pancakes. See our menu below for a complete list of our selections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We offer a varied menu of traditional New England sugarhouse food, using the best ingredients from local farms and other sources. These include blueberries from Tripp's Blueberries in Heath, farm fresh eggs from Diemand Eggs Farm in Millers Falls, ice cream from Bart's Ice Cream in Greenfield, and milk from local Massachusetts dairies. Our French toast is made from locally baked real French bread, or cinnamon bread. All of our batters are made from scratch using the finest ingredients.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South Face Farm Sugarhouse Menu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(All of our items are served with our own pure maple syrup, and a meal costs about $5 to $6.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pancakes:&lt;br /&gt;Short Stack or Tall Stack, blueberry or regular, whole wheat or white. &lt;br /&gt;Available with bacon or sausage, also available with ice cream. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Waffles:&lt;br /&gt;Three half rounds, available with bacon, sausage, blueberries, or ice cream. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;French Toast:&lt;br /&gt;Short Stack or Tall Stack, homemade French or cinnamon bread. &lt;br /&gt;Available with bacon or sausage, also available with ice cream. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Farm Fresh Eggs:&lt;br /&gt;Available fried or scrambled, available with bacon, sausage and your choice of toast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Corn Fritters:&lt;br /&gt;Deep fried golden brown drizzled with fresh maple syrup. Ummm, they are tasty. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children's Selections:&lt;br /&gt;Any of the above items are available in child sized portions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Side Orders:&lt;br /&gt;Bacon, sausage, toasted homemade bread, maple sugar donuts, pickles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dessert Specialties:&lt;br /&gt;Super premium ice cream. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beverages:&lt;br /&gt;(Hot) Freshly brewed regular, decaf. or hazelnut coffee, assorted teas, and hot chocolate. &lt;br /&gt;(Cold) Milk, maple milk shake, orange juice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will be the ones laughing the loudest</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lou Franco</member_name><member_id>150602</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268273055000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267559614000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sugar House in Ashfield (South Face Farm) informal breakfast EatUp!</name><id>12759491</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267967700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/12759491/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/5/2/global_13423618.jpeg</photo_url></item>