<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Washington Square</address_2><address_1>1665 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.338623</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 277-1752</phone><name>Tamarind Bay Coastal Indian Kitchen</name><city>Brookline</city><id>893336</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.137383</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Restaurant - Tamarind Bay, 1665 Beacon Street in Brookline&lt;br /&gt;Good availability of on-street parking&lt;br /&gt;Buffet lunch - we are hoping for a nice day, and eating outside!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon.com Review&lt;br /&gt;A memorable experience is in store for the reader of David Davidar's The House of Blue Mangoes. In a similar fashion to Vikram Seth's A Suitable Boy, Davidar's ambitious novel set in India relates many stories in one, each ineluctably merging into the other. We are shown three generations of an old family in the oceanside village of Chevathar. The patriarch Solomon strives to maintain equilibrium as caste struggles begin to create harsh conflict in the village, while his sons endure triumph and disaster as India inaugurates its battle for independence and his grandson, who may be the last of the line, undertakes his own bid for independence. All of these characters are drawn with a mercurial vividness, and Davidar has a Tolstoyan sense of the larger canvas--his epic covers the spectrum of heroes and rogues, clans and dynasties, the ugly and the beautiful.&lt;br /&gt;The narrative, alternately measured and hectic, richly weaves together assassinations and passionate affairs, exorcisms and beggars' banquets. Davidar's models are often stories from India's great epics, but the fascination of the everyday is never overlooked, from making a perfect cup of tea to whipping up a flavorsome biryani. Along with the tribulations of the protagonists, we are shown the various strategies Mahatma Gandhi and Winston Churchill used in their battles, and we see how the English memsahibs played their part in the downfall of the Raj. The mangoes of India, a key image in the novel, suggest the heady, ripe taste of this engrossing and thoroughly individual novel. --Barry Forshaw, Amazon.co.uk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284319955000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280071173000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September 2010 - The House of Blue Mangoes, by David Davidar</name><id>14206297</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284220800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/14206297/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_5395668.jpeg</photo_url></item>