<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>778 Broadway</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>12487</zip><lat>41.851524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Headless Horseman</name><city>Ulster Park</city><id>3438882</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.972244</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/6/2/event_54625442.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s that time of the year again - let&amp;rsquo;s get so scared we scream like little girls, run into walls fleeing from monsters, and cover our eyes asking when it will be over. Yep, time for haunted houses and trails - time to get SCARED!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Headless Horseman Hayrides and Haunted House has been voted one of the scariest in the country and the WORLD! &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/4/7/0/event_54625712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;It was even featured on the Travel channel. I went last year and actually ran into people running from a &amp;hellip;. well, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to ruin it for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a 1 mile long hayride, a labyrinth-style corn maze and 6 haunted houses with ghouls and monsters galore! It takes about 3 hours to go through all of the attractions so the $37.95 price is well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They used to do reservations but this place is so popular they now &lt;strong&gt;ONLY sell tickets in advance!&lt;/strong&gt; Please RSVP once you have purchased your ticket for &lt;strong&gt;October 15 @ 730pm&lt;/strong&gt;. If the time slot fills up, select the next one &amp;amp; enter that time in the comments section when you RSVP. Headless Horseman is only estimating when we start the trail, etc&amp;hellip; The sooner you get your tickets for this time, the more likely we will all be able to go together. &lt;strong&gt;They sell out fast, especially a Saturday Night!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.headlesshorseman.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.headlessho...&lt;/a&gt; Check out the website to get your tickets &amp;amp; to see the disclaimers &amp;amp; check out&amp;nbsp; photos of years past&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Mid-October is chilly so please dress to keep warm because we&amp;rsquo;re going to be sitting on the hayride for a while then walking through the other attractions. They also have souvenir shops at the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location to meet for Carpooling:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;New Haven&lt;/strong&gt;: Christian can fit 3&amp;nbsp;more people comfortably /&amp;nbsp;4 if necessary to leave from&amp;nbsp;La Quinta Hotel on Long Wharf, 400 Sargent Dr. &amp;nbsp;New Haven&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;@ 4:00pm sharp &lt;br /&gt;

to meet up with Andi 's carpool in &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Waterbury&lt;/strong&gt; @&amp;nbsp;commuter lot off of I84 West, exit 17 - take right onto&amp;nbsp;Chase Parkway -&amp;nbsp;lot is on the right, near entrance ramp for highway.&amp;nbsp;(mauroon Durango - can fit 6-7 more people)&amp;nbsp; Leaving at 5:00pm sharp. link to map: &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dot/LIB/dot/Documents/dtravelroad/waterbury2.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dot...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

OR &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Meet everyone @ the event @ 7:00pm: line outside ticket booths @ &lt;strong&gt;Headless Horseman&lt;/strong&gt;, 778 Broadway Ulster Park, NY link to directions: &lt;a href="http://www.headlesshorseman.com/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=48&amp;amp;Itemid=62" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.headlessho...&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Accordingto mapquest, it is approximately 2 hours from the Waterbury area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

From Headless Horseman site - Please be aware: Terms of Service Placement of order(s) for ticket(s) indicates your acceptance of all Headless Horseman Hayrides &amp;amp; Haunted Houses conditions, which include, but are not limited to: WEATHER - We are an outdoor attraction. Therefore, we cannot control the weather and in the unlikely event that the weather forces Headless Horseman Hayrides &amp;amp; Haunted Houses to close for the evening, all existing reservations can be used on any other evening for the remainder of our current season. All patrons acknowledge and accept that reservations/tickets must be rescheduled... there are NO REFUNDS! Headless Horseman Hayrides &amp;amp; Haunted Houses reserves the right to declare a specific ride time or entire evening SOLD OUT. All scheduled ride times are approximate - Headless Horseman Hayrides &amp;amp; Haunted Houses will make every effort to ensure that hayrides run as scheduled but some delays are possible due to weather and safety conditions. Tickets obtained from sources other than Headless Horseman Hayrides &amp;amp; Haunted Houses run the risk of being counterfeit and may not be honored. No High Heels or Flip Flop footwear allowed. All patrons acknowledge that they have read, understood and accepted our terms, policies, and disclaimers. We reserve the right to amend such as the need arises, and without prior notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Text/Call Andi 203-805-8279 - see below for CARPOOL/MEETUP times</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andi</member_name><member_id>14218596</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318773156000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315703069000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Headless Horseman Haunted Hayride &amp; Houses</name><id>33053432</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318719600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/33053432/</event_url></item>