<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 E Main St</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>01344</zip><lat>42.599693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Box Car Restaurant</name><city>Erving</city><id>4886302</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.396866</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Brush Mountain (Northfield) Brush Mountain is traversed by section 16 of the M&amp;amp;M Trail (now the New England National Scenic Trail) and includes the Crag Mountain outlook. Mount Grace protected 46 acres at the trailhead in 2005 and an additional 188 acres beside the Northfield sections of the trail in 2011. Brush Mountain is traversed by section 16 of the M&amp;amp;M Trail (now the New England National Scenic Trail) and includes the Crag Mountain outlook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Mount Grace protected 46 acres at the trailhead in 2005 and an additional 188 acres beside the Northfield sections of the trail in 2011. Brush Mountain Trail MapThe 1.7 mile (one-way) walk on Brush Mountain to the summit of Crag Mountain can be accessed from Gulf Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Follow the trail south on an easy ascent along the ridge of Brush Mountain. You will pass a black gum tree swamp and then follow a beautiful path through a hemlock forest along the ridge of Brush Mountain to Crag Mountain&amp;rsquo;s open ledges, making sure to continue a few feet beyond the ledges to the view of Mount Grace and Mount Monadnock. The rocky ledges of 1,503-foot Crag Mountain feature excellent views of northeast Franklin County and southern New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Because most of the elevation is gained driving up the mountain, the trails are easy walking, and the most direct route can be done in 15&amp;ndash;20 minutes. The New England National Scenic Trail, which winds nearly 120 miles from the Connecticut border to Mount Monadnock&amp;rsquo;s summit, passes over Brush and Crag Mountains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Since parking is limited at the Trail head for this hike, we will meet at the Box Car restaurant parking lot (route 2 in Erving) at 1pm to assemble for carpooling for this hike. It's also a nice lunch spot if anyone cares to grab some lunch before the hike. Meeting at 11:45 for anyone joining us for lunch at the Boxcar Restaurant before the hike.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325689064000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324695274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brush and Crag Mountain Hike</name><id>45364012</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325613600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/45364012/</event_url></item>