<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/4/a/event_153921322.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Join us for the next in the series of Science in the News Fall Lectures, as they discuss their latest scientific findings about clean energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you not familiar with SITN's lecture format, lectures are free, accessible, and open to the public. All lectures are given entirely by graduate students at Harvard and focus on hot topics in science research and news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All lectures are on Wednesdays starting at 7 PM at the Armenise Amphitheater at Harvard Medical School. They are 2 hours in length, with a 10 minute break in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They will have light refreshments before the lecture (coffee, tea, cookies, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2012 Fall Schedule is as Follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September 19:  Broken Genes: The Role of DNA Repair in Preventing Cancer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September 26:  Big Love: Monogamy and Promiscuity in the Animal Kingdom&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;October 3: How Evolution Generates "Endless Forms Most Beautiful"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;October 10: Biotechnology and the Emergence of New Therapeutics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;October 17: Living Foods: The Microbiology of Food and Drink&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;October 24: The Universe is a (Pretty Big) Box: From Cells to Galaxies using Supercomputers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November 7: Clean Energy of the Future: Solar cells, Biofuels and Fuel Cell Catalysts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;November 14: Thinking about Thinking: the Science of Decision Making from an Economics and Neurobiology Perspective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;November 28:  What's in Your Genes: Whole Genome Sequencing and its Impact on Personalized Medicine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best way to get there is by T.  The closest Green Line stops are the E train at Longwood Medical Area, and the D train at Longwood.  The Harvard Medical School Quadrangle is on Longwood Avenue, across from the half traffic circle at Avenue Louis Pasteur.  The Armenise Amphitheater is the first building on the left (facing into the quadrangle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is parking at the Masco Garage at 375 Longwood.  Evening rate is $7&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/images/maps/quadmap.jpg"&gt;HMS Quadrangle Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/images/maps/LMAmap.jpg"&gt;Longwood Medical Area Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;msid=101729904914405135624.000439a3efaa5a627500c&amp;amp;om=1&amp;amp;ll=42.338832,-71.10549&amp;amp;spn=0.011579,0.020921&amp;amp;source=embed"&gt;Interactive Google Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.masco.org/directions/lma-public-parking"&gt;Masco Parking Garage Info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll gather on the benches outside the main entrance of the Courtyard Cafe (or in the lobby if it's wet out). We'll hang out there until about 6:45, then go in to get seats and refreshments before the lecture.  Afterwards, they usually have lab tours, or if anyone's up for more food, drinks, and socializing in the 9:00 hour or so, there's a Bertucci's down the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll gather on the benches outside the main entrance of the Courtyard Cafe (or in the lobby if it's wet out). Both John and Doreen will be wearing meetup pins.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>14</waitlist_count><updated>1352397019000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>71</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346275021000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SITN Lecture - Clean Energy of the Future:  Solar cells, Biofuels and Fuel Cell</name><id>79963102</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352331000000</time><rsvp_limit>80</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/79963102/</event_url></item>