<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>306 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.348064</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-888-HARPOON</phone><name>Harpoon Brewery</name><city>Boston</city><id>669000</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.037100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;After taking countless Brewery tours from around the world, we decided to focus our tours on what we feel is the best part of any brewery tour - the sampling. That being said, we offer the Harpoon Tastings at the Brewery. Our Tasting takes place in our Tasting Room and includes in-depth information about Harpoon and the great beers we brew. This information is narrated by our knowledgable staff and includes complimentary samples of our delicious beer. That Tasting lasts about 1 hour which includes access the the Brewhouse Platform. Because of our small size, we do not have the ability to allow people to walk through the brewery.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harpoonbrewery.com/index.cfm?pid=28487" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harpoonbre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you like the taste of beer, this will be fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour itself should be done within 2 hours, then we will head down to the Barking Crab, which is just next door, for some clam chowder and shrimp scampi.  After a snack we will then head over to the Middle East for the Hoodoo Gurus gig.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm not too familiar with the layout of the brewery so let's just aim to meet at the front door at 3:45pm.  Tour starts at 4pm.  Don't be late or all the beer might be gone when you arrive.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>3466832</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189453689000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Larrikins</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aussie-145</urlname><id>222356</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Aussie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187737634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harpoon Brewery tour</name><id>6220661</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189280700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aussie-145/events/6220661/</event_url></item>