<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Palisado Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.876385</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Windsor Center Trail</name><city>Windsor</city><id>12313222</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.626228</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Another after work walk...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Windsor Center River Trail is a one-mile paved loop, part of which runs beside the Farmington River.  We may make two laps if we're feeling energetic.  This will be a slow, socially placed walk and a good chance to unwind after a day at work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kids and leashed dogs are welcome. For the kids, or the young at heart, this trail is all paved and can be done on roller blades!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking lot is located across the street from Bart's restaurant on Palisado Avenue in Windsor. If the trailhead lot fills up, park in the boat launch lot behind Bart's. (Please don't park in front of Bart's as those spaces are for customers!)  Parking lot is not that large, so attendance is limited accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Address for Bart's for your GPS is 55 Palisado Avenue, Windsor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hot dog aficionados may wish to go to Bart's for a bite after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information about the trail and directions can be found here &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dot/lib/dot/documents/dbikes/126.pdf"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dot/lib/dot/documents/dbikes/126.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note about dogs:  While this is a dog-friendly hike, the dog owners need to be responsible.  Park rules require leashes.  If you choose to break that rule and let your dog off the leash, please be sure it is okay with the other hikers (some of whom may not be dog people) and be sure you can control your dog when off leash.  Finally, please be prepared and clean up after your dog when needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me in the parking lot with my dogs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364264947000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363554935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Windsor Center River Trail Walk</name><id>109716802</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364247000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/109716802/</event_url></item>