<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>882 Ocean Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02050</zip><lat>42.105701</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fieldston Restaurant</name><city>Marshfield</city><id>1707931</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.664757</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;And now for something completely different!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, ok, maybe not &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; different: We're still going out to eat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a little different is that we don't often do so on Sunday night, yet Mike finds that early-evening events on Sundays should work well with his current schedule. So, an experiment: Mike is planning to host an occasional Sunday evening event and see what kind of response he draws. Call it Mike's Sunday Supper Series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're starting this month with The Fieldston in Marshfield; a South Shore restaurant that has long been known for imaginative and well prepared American cuisine (the South Shore's obligatory Italian influence manifests here in the inclusion of a few pasta dishes).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike has enjoyed The Fieldston in the past and recent reviews online seem to indicate that chef-owner Jan Perrin is still on his game. So let's bring &lt;em&gt;our&lt;/em&gt; game to Marshfield on a Sunday night as we head down Route 139 and stop just before we get to the Atlantic. The atmosphere will be casually elegant and the food, we're confident, will make you glad that you came out to join us and sit at The Fieldston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Fieldston Restaurant&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;882 Ocean St (Route 139)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Marshfiled, MA 02050 &lt;br /&gt; (781) 834-2909&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.thefieldston.com/home.htm"&gt;The Fieldston Restaurant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer:&lt;/strong&gt; Mike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. Two per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact Mike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price Range:&lt;/strong&gt; The &lt;a href="http://www.thefieldston.com/menu.htm"&gt;online menu&lt;/a&gt; is definitely worth a look: Nothing listed is over $16.95, but the dishes described do not sound like a budget menu. In addition, on Sundays the restaurant offers "Clean out the kitchen" specials for $9.95.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; Current Annual Members - None, Group Members - $2.00, Guests - $2.00; $12 to become a 2011 Annual Member&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over four years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Saturday, May 21st @ 3:00 pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer. Changes to "No" after the deadline will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us Pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; The Fieldston is located on Ocean Street (Route 139) in Marshfield, just across from Fieldstone Marine. If you're heading East on Routh 139, this is just BEFORE you'll start to see the ocean on your left. The distance from Exit 12 off Route 3 to the restaurant is approximately 6 miles.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308847574000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305250722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Supper Series: The Fieldston</name><id>18202731</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306101600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/18202731/</event_url></item>