<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our speaker for this evening will be Mindy Popp, who is an expert on the college admissions process.  Mindy herself went to Tufts and Harvard (grad school of education) and is an active member of many professional educational organizations.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, if if you are looking for colleges for your children (or thinking of returning yourself!) come meet Mindy!  I KNOW that you'll be impressed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's her web page:  &lt;a href="http://www.poppandassociates.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.poppandass...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALSO, Elise Miller will be there with Beijo bags!  If you're not familiar with these handbags, they're beautiful, functional, and affordable!  ($75 to $105)  Beijo was started by a  single mother who wanted to help other women find balance in their lives -- and the company just keeps growing! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elise has kindly donated our raffle prize for the evening, which will be a gift certificate to be used for the purchase of a Beijo bag.  If you want to simply purchase one (and you WILL, once you see them!) Elise accepts cash and checks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, the meeting is FREE and light snacks will be provided.  Remember to bring your business card for the raffle!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll see you there!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers, Karen&lt;br /&gt;617-650-8716 (cell)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture on the site</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen K.</member_name><member_id>3407018</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221770168000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Professional Women</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Women-in-Business-Network</urlname><id>997886</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Women in Business Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220380957000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What Colleges Value Most!</name><id>8671993</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221174000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-in-Business-Network/events/8671993/</event_url></item>