<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Intersection of Rt 1 and 128</address_2><address_1>950 Providence Hwy</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02026</zip><lat>42.232470</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-232-8900</phone><name>Legacy Place</name><city>Dedham</city><id>1028960</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.179692</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Legacy Place in Dedham is hosting a charity event under the stars with food and entertainment. Proceeds benefit the Italian Home for Children. Every restaurant and food-related business in the center is offering a 'taste".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'd love to meet a group of Boston Couples there to enjoy the night together!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy tickets in advance! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.italianhome.org/site/PageServer?pagename=TasteofLegacyPlace" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.italianhome.org/site/PageServer?pagename=TasteofLegacyPlace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebrate the beginning of summer at Taste of Legacy Place Under the Stars for an outdoor fundraiser on the roof top parking deck of Legacy Place Parking Garage in Dedham to benefit the Italian Home for Children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests will be able to enjoy an eclectic array of music while tasting unbelievable servings from Legacy Place’s top restaurants. A sampling of food will include cheeses from Whole Foods Market, cotton candy from Sugar Heaven, chicken parmigiana from Studio 3, ice cream from J. P. Licks and much more! You will be able to partake in the Legacy Raffle, and try your chance to win gift cards from the businesses and restaurants of Legacy Place. Also, there will be fantastic items in our Legacy Place Experience Live Auction. There are a limited number of tickets available! Tickets are $30 per person in advance and $35 at the door.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stacy Goodman</member_name><member_id>3216337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340713603000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339008427000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taste of Legacy Place Under the Stars</name><id>68029732</id><headcount>4</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340317800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/68029732/</event_url></item>