<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come learn how to still your mind, and altar your consciousness in (2) ancient ways that witches have always known to help guide them on their spiritual path. This (4) hour class will run from 1:00- 5:00 pm. It will begin with a lecture on Channeling, What it is, and the steps on how to do it, to enable one to channel messages from their Spirit Guides, Ascended Masters, and one's higher self. Each participant will also have their pineal and pituitary glands activated for increased channeling abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then there will be a break with snacks, before continuing on to the 2nd half: Which is Meditation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a lecture on the four types of meditation, What the differences are, and how to do them and then everyone will participate in a guided meditation, and then a deep concentrated meditation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please wear comfortable clothing and bring a cushion, pillow or comfortable chair to meditate in. Some cushions will be available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class is $24.00 per person, please bring cash or check, and paypal is available upon request at talawitch@charter.net &lt;br /&gt;

Please park next door at the Copper Stallion, and come in the front door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class was a great hit last year,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and will be even better this year!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park next door at the Copper Stallion and come in the front door! :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359265397000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pagans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pagan-1307</urlname><id>1221723</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pagan Learning Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356890296000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Art of Meditation &amp; Channeling (Sturbridge)</name><id>97081092</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358100000000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pagan-1307/events/97081092/</event_url></item>