<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>295 Daniel Webster Hwy</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.704552</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 888-4904</phone><name>Sun Plaza Bar &amp; Grill</name><city>Nashua</city><id>1155072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.441261</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ok, folks felt bad karaoke didn't work out on Wed with the 'snow that never came'! ;-)  So they wanted another chance this Friday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris, the KJ (like DJ) @Smokey Bones (ex-KJ @Killarney's), is the KJ at the new &lt;b&gt;Sun Plaza Bar &amp;amp; Grill&lt;/b&gt; in Nashua!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its in the Sun Plaza across the road from the Pheasant Lane Mall, but more directly across from Barmakians Jewlery and U-Haul.  Its where Quiznos and before that, D'Angelos were.  We have a great time with Chris, whether its at Killarneys, Smokey Bones or wherever, and if you can't make a middle of the week sing, here's a weekend opportunity.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small place, but a more homey grill experience than say Applebees or Fridays and with a bar and takeout area.  Homemade American fare, like steaks, prime rib, seafood and sandwiches, yet some fancier fare like New England Seafood Corn Chowder, Panko Herb Crusted Seafood Cake with Roasted Red Pepper Remoulade, Sea Scallops wrapped in Bacon with VT Maple Syrup, Grilled Farm Raised Salmon ($8!), Italian Trio (chicken, eggplant, &amp;amp; veal parmesan with penne), and Half Roasted Duck.  A little fancier than we're used to at Killarneys or Smokey Bones! ;-)  Yet a very homey place.  I got chicken fingers, yet they turned out to be chicken breasts! ($7!)  All draft beers are $2 and 1/2 price on mixed drinks for women!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Karaoke will start at 9 and go until 1!  Guess we'll do our usual and show up an hour earlier, at &lt;b&gt;8&lt;/b&gt; for some food and talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its right on Daniel Webster Highway, the road going past the Pheasant Lane Mall, coming south, past Market Basket, Chilis and Newbury Comics, just turn right right in, BEFORE Costco.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming north, from the Mall or Mass, you have to go past it and do a U-turn at the light in between Market Basket and Chilis.  Or you can go around behind Borders to the secret back entrance. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had a great time last time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom D'A 603-521-7610 before, c603-682-2412 during&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom D'A</member_name><member_id>5016514</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266195788000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265965484000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Karaoke/Dancing/Food, Sun Plaza Bar &amp; Grill, Nashua</name><id>12587669</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266022800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/12587669/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/6/global_12810790.jpeg</photo_url></item>