<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, Oct 30 from 2 to 4 PM we will have a high intermediate level meetup at the Cambridge Recreational Center in Cambridge. This game is for Yankee C- and above level only. Players are required to know how to play a 6-2 and 5-1 formation; players who sign up for this event but do not know how to play these formations will not be allowed to play. When you RSVP, please answer the questions about 6-2 position preference. If you do not then you may be removed from the RSVP list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a strict cap at 12 players to make sure everyone gets lots of playing time. The cost of the meetup will be $5. Please pay the organizer when you arrive before the meetup starts. The money goes to cover the cost of the court rental. The entrance to the gym is on Cambridge Street opposite Harvard Market. The nearest intersection to the entrance is Cambridge Street and Roberts Road. The nearest T stop is Harvard Square. The gym is about a ten minute walk from the T stop. Parking near the school on Sundays is generally easy to find, as meters and residential parking rules are generally not enforced on Sundays (parking signs should say "EX SUNDAY" or similar).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wing</member_name><member_id>3198724</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>10</waitlist_count><updated>1320609426000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319404423000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge High Intermediate (Yankee C/C-) Indoor Volleyball</name><id>38427402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319997600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/38427402/</event_url></item>