<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Front Street at Derby Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.520490</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Old Town Hall</name><city>Salem</city><id>897637</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.894720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For those interested in food, wine, and beer sampling from local and more distant entrepreneurs, the Salem Spring Fling is certainly not to be missed.  Check out this description copied verbatim from: &lt;a href="http://www.pmousse.com/springfling.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pmousse.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;On March 21st, Salem Massachusetts will host the second annual SPRING FLING: A GARDEN OF EARTHLY DELIGHTS sponsored by Magic Hat at Old Town Hall in the center of this beautiful, historic seaport. The Festival, which is fashioned after the Bacchanalia - a religious festival in honor of the wine god Dionysus or, as the Romans called him, Bacchus - will kick New Englanders out of a long hibernation and jumpstart Spring by indulging in the finest wines, craft beers and mouth watering food from North Shore restauranteurs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Historically, the Bacchanalia was held in mid-March and priests and priestesses adorned with garlands of ivy would carry wine, honey, and cakes throughout Rome, celebrating and expressing themselves freely through music and pleasure.  This modern day version - Spring Fling - will feature a tasting of over 50 fine wines and international and domestic craft beers from Magic Hat, Ipswich, Cape Ann, and Harpoon. Wine professionals will be on hand with an assortment of vino from the US, Europe, South Africa, South America and Down Under. Truly a party fit for Bacchus!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Salem Restaurants such as The Old Spot, Finz, Sixty2 on Wharf, Rockafellas, The Lobster Shanty, AJ King Artisan Bakers, Cafe Grazziani, The Upper Crust Pizzeria, Gulu Gulu and more will tickle and tantalize your palate with delectable culinary delights! North Shore Artists will be offering an eclectic variety of art to please your eye and warm your home! Local favorite, Machine 475 will be performing live. Free chair massages provided by Living Well.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Meet familiar characters from myth and legend and enjoy the goddesses and nymphs that wander the &amp;quot;Garden of Earthly Delights.&amp;quot; Seek out The Oracle of Delphi to hear your fortune. Roman attire is encouraged! Experience the intoxicating power of this celebration on March 21st from 1 - 4pm at Old Town Hall on the Pedestrian Mall in Salem, MA.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;ECONOMIC CRISIS? CALL DIONYSUS! Tickets are $20 in advance, $25 at the door and are available at&lt;/span&gt; www.pmousse.com, localwineevents.com &lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;or by calling 978-745-2900.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note, you are responsible for acquiring tickets on your own!!  I  have no idea the rate at which they sell out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is always an issue, so check out other alternatives including the commuter rail at: &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/schedules_and_maps/rail/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As this is not really the setting for en masse maneuvering, we won't be doing our typical meet and take the venue by storm :-).  If you're interested in going, RSVP away, and I'll provide my cell number so we can find everyone, and then divide and conquer the different, well, &amp;quot;Earthly Delights&amp;quot;.  Heh, for those enthusiasts, I apologize in advance for my lack of Roman attire:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email Lisa with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will provide my cell # to those that RSVP yes and maybe</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238107215000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236610902000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salem Spring Fling</name><id>9914641</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237654800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/9914641/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>