<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076322</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rusty Hammer</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1023192</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/6/8/event_101320552.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Our book selection for the month of April is Let The Great World Spin by&amp;nbsp;Colum McCann. &amp;nbsp;Here is the book description from Amazon.com:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the dawning light of a late-summer morning, the people of lower Manhattan stand hushed, staring up in disbelief at the Twin Towers. It is August 1974, and a mysterious tightrope walker is running, dancing, leaping between the towers, suspended a quarter mile above the ground. In the streets below, a slew of ordinary lives become extraordinary in bestselling novelist Colum McCann&amp;rsquo;s stunningly intricate portrait of a city and its people.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Let the Great World Spin&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is the critically acclaimed author&amp;rsquo;s most ambitious novel yet: a dazzlingly rich vision of the pain, loveliness, mystery, and promise of New York City in the 1970s.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Corrigan, a radical young Irish monk, struggles with his own demons as he lives among the prostitutes in the middle of the burning Bronx. A group of mothers gather in a Park Avenue apartment to mourn their sons who died in Vietnam, only to discover just how much divides them even in grief. A young artist finds herself at the scene of a hit-and-run that sends her own life careening sideways. Tillie, a thirty-eight-year-old grandmother, turns tricks alongside her teenage daughter, determined not only to take care of her family but to prove her own worth.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Elegantly weaving together these and other seemingly disparate lives, McCann&amp;rsquo;s powerful allegory comes alive in the unforgettable voices of the city&amp;rsquo;s people, unexpectedly drawn together by hope, beauty, and the &amp;ldquo;artistic crime of the century.&amp;rdquo; A sweeping and radical social novel,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Let the Great World Spin&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;captures the spirit of America in a time of transition, extraordinary promise, and, in hindsight, heartbreaking innocence. Hailed as a &amp;ldquo;fiercely original talent&amp;rdquo; (San Francisco Chronicle), award-winning novelist McCann has delivered a triumphantly American masterpiece that awakens in us a sense of what the novel can achieve, confront, and even heal.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;And here is a short review from Publisher's Weekly:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt;McCann's sweeping new novel hinges on Philippe Petit's illicit 1974 high-wire walk between the twin towers. It is the aftermath, in which Petit appears in the courtroom of Judge Solomon Soderberg, that sets events into motion. Solomon, anxious to get to Petit, quickly dispenses with a petty larceny involving mother/daughter hookers Tillie and Jazzlyn Henderson. Jazzlyn is let go, but is killed on the way home in a traffic accident. Also killed is John Corrigan, a priest who was giving her a ride. The other driver, an artist named Blaine, drives away, and the next day his wife, Lara, feeling guilty, tries to check on the victims, leading her to meet John's brother, with whom she'll form an enduring bond. Meanwhile, Solomon's wife, Claire, meets with a group of mothers who have lost sons in Vietnam. One of them, Gloria, lives in the same building where John lived, which is how Claire, taking Gloria home, witnesses a small salvation. McCann's dogged, DeLillo-like ambition to show American magic and dread sometimes comes unfocused-John Corrigan in particular never seems real-but he succeeds in giving us a high-wire performance of style and heart.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334160191000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331690619000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club April Meetup - Let The Great World Spin</name><id>dpskncyqgbnb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334098800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/56263972/</event_url></item>