<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>580 Mountain Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03452</zip><lat>42.830054</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-532-6711 - MIKE/DIRECTOR</phone><name>The Grand View Inn &amp; Resort</name><city>Jaffrey</city><id>843115</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.098855</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The all free, only true, 1st amendment event in U.S., 4th Annual Live Free Or Die Rally '09 will be held on August 21,22,23, 2009 at &lt;a href="http://THEGRANDVIEWINN.com" target="_blank"&gt;THEGRANDVIEWINN.com&lt;/a&gt;, a fabulous 300 acre estate at the base of Mt. Monadnock in Jaffrey, New Hampshire.  Location has rooms at Inn, Cottages, Bar, 100+ acre events field, 200 acres of trails &amp;amp; more. Rooms &amp;amp; Bar are not free, but, available to participants &amp;amp; do not allow pets/smoking inside. Rooms are limited so book ASAP. Event, camping, booth spots are free, will allow pets, &amp;amp; smoking. So far, event will feature 20+ Bands, Revolutionary War Reenactment 10+ Cannons battles, Farm aid benefit Motorcycle Show, Camping, Pig Roast, Lazer screen &amp;amp; show, Vendors, Speakers, National Advocacy Organizations &amp;amp; much more. Many to all of the 800+ participants, Organizations &amp;amp; vendors from the 3rd annual will be participating in the 4th annual. New features being added to '09 event will be announced. Many of the topics from the 3rd annual or still in legislation will be carried over to the 4th annual. To make reservations for booth or camping spots should be e-mailed to caacp01@aol.com , send message to &lt;a href="http://myspace.com/caacp" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://myspace.com/caacp" target="_blank"&gt;http://myspace.com/ca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or call 603-532-6711.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To request booking to speak on a topic, please submit group name, if available, speaker name, title &amp;amp; topic.  It takes us hundred of hours all year to organize event &amp;amp; the hardest part is recruiting volunteers for the weekend of the event. So, PLEASE register to volunteer. The many costs (over items donated) to put on the event that require cash payment (approx.$10,000) are paid out of very few of ours blue collar pockets to keep event all free &amp;amp; true first amendment. Any pledges would be a huge help where event doubles in size every year. We can't pay for the event alone again this year, so please pledge. Please read Rally Constitution blog at &lt;a href="http://myspace.com/caacp" target="_blank"&gt;myspace.com/caacp&lt;/a&gt;. With luck, hopefully we'll see you next year!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jean&amp;quot;Mike&amp;quot;Coutu, Chairman, caacp01@aol.com, myspace.com/caacp&lt;br /&gt;POB 736,Jaffrey,N.H. 03452, 603-532-6711&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251112374000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231082585000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4th Annual New Hampshire Live Free Or Die Rally</name><id>9440041</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250938800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/9440041/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/9/6/global_3841686.jpeg</photo_url></item>