<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>800 BOYLSTON ST.</address_2><address_1>PPRUDENTIAL TOWER</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02199</zip><lat>42.347161</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 536 1775</phone><name>TOP OF THE HUB</name><city>Boston</city><id>941863</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082522</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Top of the Hub is a great place to wind down on a Friday evening, with a few sundowners and some awesome live jazz.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The view from one of the tallest buildings in town is spectacular (unless it's foggy!!), you really feel like you are on top of the world. Bring a camera if you're into urban sunset scenes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;lounge&amp;quot; food menu is very good and reasonably priced. Most appetizers are close to meal-size.They do have a minimum spend requirement after 8pm (when the jazz band starts) of $24 per head - but that's not much when you consider that a cocktail/mixed drink is close to $10, or more than $10 when you do the fancy cocktails. . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're meeting at 7pm, well before the minimum spend requirement starts, so will probably have already achieved it by then!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.topofthehub.net/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top of the Hub&lt;/a&gt; for directions and more info including list of who's playing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**** VERY IMPORTANT ****&lt;br /&gt;There is virtually zero cellphone reception at Top of the Hub, due to all the reinforced concrete of the structure!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will do our best to let the hostess know where we are in case people ask where our group is, but that is not always 100% reliable. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So as far as finding the group goes, you may well have to walk thru the lounge until you spot a face or faces that you recognize. We're joining another Boston social group for this event, so we should be a group of close to 20 people, possibly more, so it shouldn't be too difficult to find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI: The Prudential Center garage has validated parking for Top of the Hub. Get the hostess to stamp your parking ticket.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the lounge area to the right of the bar.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn L</member_name><member_id>3649230</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243543206000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Tall Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostontallsingles</urlname><id>1235066</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Tall Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241610218000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Sundowners, Jazz and more @ Top of the Hub</name><id>10349888</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241823600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostontallsingles/events/10349888/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/4/global_8510884.jpeg</photo_url></item>