<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bound by Tremont, Beacon, Charles, Park and Boylston Streets </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.316933</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common's Parkman Bandstand </name><city>Boston </city><id>8352572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

We invite everyone from every political and ideological persuasion to join with us to take back control of our monetary and banking systems. This is an issue that affects EVERYONE. A mini-audit was done from 2007 - 2010 that exposed Trillions of (taxpayer backed) Dollars being used to not only prop up the "Too Big to Fail" institutions in the US, but also Trillions in extremely low-interest loans being given to foreign institutions like Deutsche Bank, Credit Suisse, and Arab Banking Corp. We've also learned that sitting members of the Regional Boards of the Fed have given their own companies low interest loans, which can only be described as a supreme conflict of interest, and we've also seen well-connected individuals taking loans from the Fed personally. It seems like everyone is getting bailed out by the Federal Reserve while we are still dealing with economic hardships on Main St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This must stop now! We will gather at Boston Common's Parkman Bandstand for a walk to the Federal Reserve (where we will be making stops to spread our message to the general shopping public and disperse literature and mail-in petititions to US Senators). We will end with a rally at the Fed, to continue promoting the message to the public, and to build a regional network to press all of our Senators (from Rhode Island to Maine) into supporting S 202.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone who wants to get involved but can't walk with us is welcome to meet us at the Bandstand and then take the subway to South Station to leaflet at the Fed Reserve while the walkers wind through the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So join us in Boston, and at every Federal Reserve branch, to demand that the Federal Reserve be Audited, and then held accountable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Justin Roy will be performing at 12 noon while we gather at the Boston Commons &amp;amp; prepare for our march. Bring signs, flags, bullhorns, &amp;amp; the most important thing, your voices. We will be handing out information along the way to spread our message to the public.* Other performances/speakers TBA&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353880860000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350855056000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>End the Fed / End the Wars Rally</name><id>87960052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353776400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/87960052/</event_url></item>