<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>132 Water St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06854</zip><lat>41.094959</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Norwalk Oyster Festival</name><city>Norwalk</city><id>683388</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.414040</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's that time of year again! The Norwalk Oyster Festival is back!!! Join us on Sunday, Sept. 13 for the Beatlemania Now show!!!!!!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 32nd annual celebration of fun for all ages will feature international headliners and popular regional entertainers, seaport circus, hundreds of arts and crafts booths, environmental displays, children's activities and rides, International Food Court , oystering exhibits, vintage vessels, harbor cruises, helicopter rides, and other attractions! AND ALL OF US!!!! Buy your tickets in advance for just $10 ($12 at the gate) or buy an entire weekend pack for just $25! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The BEATLEMANIA SHOW will start at 6 p.m. but we can meet earlier at 3:30 which will give us time to walk around and take in all the sights before the show. Please keep in mind that this will be a Multi-Group Meetup so expect more people to be there than what is listed. We will post a meeting place and a way to keep in touch, as the date gets closer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;BEATLEMANIA NOW!&amp;quot;...formed from members of the original Tony-award winning Broadway musical, has toured worldwide, performing to countless audiences since 1984. Meticulously faithful to the original music, Beatlemania Now's four member cast recreate, note for note, over 30 classic songs in an extravaganza that retraces the entire care HEAR IT, SEE IT, BELIEVE IT!... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Beatlemania Now” , the multimedia musical stage show, is the ultimate celebration of the 60's and the group that helped shape them… “The Beatles”! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through nine scenes and eight costume changes, the Show's cast performs live-on-stage, against a backdrop of stunning images spanning the most exciting and turbulent decade of modern times. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recapture the excitement, mood and frantic intensity of the 1960's as you revisit historic moments in the lives and deaths of John F. Kennedy, Robert F. Kennedy and Martin Luther King Jr., the politics of Richard M. Nixon, the raging war in Vietnam, protests in the streets, “Flower Power”, “Peace and Love”, Space Exploration and see film footage and TV commercials of the times, as the cast meticulously performs more than 30 Beatles' classics, including songs the Beatles themselves never performed live! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Beatlemania Now” … the music transcends time and generations… a “must see and hear” experience for all ages! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check the website below for directions and parking instructions. You'll need to park in the surrounding areas but the site lists shuttle bus service pick up points. The event is very well attended and so worth it! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WEBSITE LINK &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE HOPE YOU WILL JOIN US!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Fairfield singles will be there with meetup signs and red &amp; white Balloons.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367845777000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249259164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Norwalk Oyster Festival</name><id>11018152</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252870200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/11018152/</event_url></item>