<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Faneuil Hall</address_2><address_1>148 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359501</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 227-5100</phone><name>McFadden's</name><city>Boston</city><id>753501</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join me for STUMP! Trivia at McFadden's on Wednesday, Jan 12th.  Trivia starts at 6:30pm.  (Website says 8pm, they LIE.)  The wonderful Mimi is the trivia jockey here.  Not sure of the prizes for winning but McFadden's boasts $1 sliders and 10CENT wings (40 different flavors).  I have yet to try this particular trivia room but if I can get a regular team together, we can do this on a regular basis! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://mbta.com...&lt;/a&gt; ... or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hopstop.co...&lt;/a&gt; ... to create your route by public transit. Aquarium (blue line), Haymarket (green &amp;amp; orange lines), State (orange &amp;amp; blue lines), Government Center (blue &amp;amp; green lines), and South Station (red line &amp;amp; commuter rail). These subway stations are no more than a ten (10) minute walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mcfaddensboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;McFadden's Web Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Put the insignificant information in your head to use in the trivia contest, which begins at 6:30 and ends at about 8:30-9pm. Intriguing questions, fairly run, at a good pace and great interlude music. Some previous categories have been Science, Music, History, Geography, Literature, Sports, TV, Art, Business, &amp;amp; Movies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stump! Trivia rules:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) To be eligible for prizes, teams are limited to six players. Be aware, teams with less than six players and have one of the top three scores, win first or second place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) The trivia jockey (TJ) provides Stump! sheets, on which to keep your team score. Write the categories as the TJ reads them, and keep track of the points you've wagered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) When the TJ asks a question, you have one song to write your team name, your answer, and your wager on an answer ticket and hand it in. You can wager 1, 3, 5, or 7 points in the first two quarters, and 2, 4, 6, or 8 points in the last two quarters. You can only use each value ONCE per quarter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) There are three bonus rounds where you can earn lots of extra points! Your TJ will explain how they work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) No shouting out answers, and absolutely no using cellphones or other devices to look up answers!&lt;br /&gt;Teams breaking this rule are disqualified.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6) Have fun and good luck.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294877344000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294332905000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stump! Trivia at McFadden's near Faneuil Hall **CANCELLED**</name><id>15944169</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294873200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/15944169/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/8/global_6854760.jpeg</photo_url></item>