<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Old North Dana Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01355</zip><lat>42.506814</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quabbin Reservoir Gate 35</name><city>New Salem</city><id>907353</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.270399</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/6/d/event_50717261.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Easy (as long as you can walk 4-5 miles)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Shoreline Hike @ North Quabbin!&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Gate 35 we can hike right along the Quabbin shoreline! Since this is the far north end of the Quabbin, near the islands and in view of the water, we stand a greater chance of seeing bald eagles. (Granted, sightings are hit-or-miss; you can see eagles anywhere around the reservoir if they're fishing and you're lucky!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How far we hike depends on the group that attends, though I would like to hike a couple miles down shore before the trail turns into the woods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's plan on round-trip 5 miles. In the woods at a "group pace" I estimate 2+ hours, plus a lunch break. *IF* we got lucky enough to see bald eagles, and *IF* they hovered around longer to "pose" for pictures, it could take longer. (In fact, I will definitely want to *revisit* this hike in late spring or early summer, when young eagles are becoming good fliers.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the *rare* circumstance bald eagles hang around for a while (and if you don't want to) it is easy for you to continue onward or return to your car on your own. This "trail" is an old road and a baby could follow it. (Most eagle sightings are minutes or seconds, but I was very lucky to watch *6* of them for an hour this May!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Important Regulations:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* No swimming or wading. (Public drinking water supply.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* No animals. (Same reason.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* "Carry in, carry out." (Take your trash with you when you leave; no trash cans.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* Do not remove items from the reservation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* Do not block gates. (Park on either side of the road. *First person* to park, park *25 feet away* from the gate...the road is too narrow to pull very far to the side.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the East, take 122 North, or from the South, take 37 or 37A North onto 122 North. "Old N Dana Rd" is several miles further on the left. (You can see "S Athol Rd" further on, on the right.) If you pass between North and South Spectacle ponds (water on both sides of the road, some marsh grasses on the south side), you have gone too far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the West or North, take 202 to 122 South. After you pass between North and South Spectacle ponds, look for "S Athol Rd" on your left. Slow down, because "Old N Dana Rd" is coming up on the right!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gate 35 is at the end of Old Dana Rd. Do not park directly in front of the gate. Whoever gets there first, park 25 feet back because the road is narrow and you cannot pull too far to the side.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We park on either side of the road, approching the gate (at the end of the road).</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315766932000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314151532000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Hike: Quabbin Reservoir from Gate 35 (shoreline)</name><id>30659311</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315576800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/30659311/</event_url></item>