<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>February's selection will be  The Road by Cormac McCarthy in anticipation of the theatrical release :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The Road by Cormac McCarthy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.bookbrowse.com/reviews/index.cfm?book_number=1964" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bookbrowse...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A father and his son walk alone through burned America. Nothing moves in the ravaged landscape save the ash on the wind. It is cold enough to crack stones, and when the snow falls it is gray. The sky is dark. Their destination is the coast, although they don’t know what, if anything, awaits them there. They have nothing; just a pistol to defend themselves against the lawless bands that stalk the road, the clothes they are wearing, a cart of scavenged food—and each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Road is the profoundly moving story of a journey. It boldly imagines a future in which no hope remains, but in which the father and his son, “each the other’s world entire,” are sustained by love. Awesome in the totality of its vision, it is an unflinching meditation on the worst and the best that we are capable of: ultimate destructiveness, desperate tenacity, and the tenderness that keeps two people alive in the face of total devastation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will, as ever plan to meet at the Clear Conscience Cafe, but if the place is too crowded and you don't see us, head across the street to Au Bon Pain, 1100 Mass Ave (cross Prospect and Mass Ave and look for the yellow awning)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will admit to being out of town for this one, so if anyone is able to serve as the point person for converging, send me a note&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236640029000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228823399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> The Road by Cormac McCarthy</name><id>9307068</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234224000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/9307068/</event_url></item>