<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Highland Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389535</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center of Arts at the Armory</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1046137</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106069</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;THE FIRST AND LAST WORD POETRY SERIES &lt;br /&gt;

Hosted by Harris Gardner and Gloria Mindock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TUESDAY, DECEMBER 18, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

7:00 PM/ADMISSION: $4.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the readers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kathleen Aguero's poetry collections include Investigations: The Mystery of the Girl Sleuth, Daughter Of, The Real Weather and Thirsty Day. She has also co-edited three volumes of multi-cultural literature for the University of Georgia Press and is a poetry editor of Solstice Literary Magazine. She teaches at Pine Manor College in both the undergraduate and low-residency M.F.A. programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michelle Blake has published poetry and essays in Ploughshares, Southern Review, Seneca Review, More, The New York Times and a number of other publications. She is also the author of three novels-The Tentmaker, Earth Has No Sorrow and The Book of Light. Blake has taught writing at Tufts University, Stanford University, Warren Wilson College and Goddard College. She received a MTS from Harvard Divinity School and a MFA from Goddard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Hoffman is author of the poetry collections, Without Paradise, Gold Star Road, winner of the 2006 Barrow Street Press Poetry Prize and the 2008 Sheila Motton Award from the New England Poetry Club, and Emblem. He is also author of the memoir Half the House, and the short story collection, Interference and Other Stories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An open mic will follow the reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Center for the Arts is located between Davis Square and Union Square at 191 Highland Avenue. Parking is located behind the armory at the rear of the building. Arts at the Armory is approximately a 15 minute walk from Davis Square which is on the MTBA Red Line. You can also find us by using either the MBTA RT 88 and RT 90 bus that can be caught either at Lechmere (Green Line) or Davis Square (Red Line). Get off at the Highland Avenue and Lowell Street stop. You can also get to us from Sullivan Square (Orange Line) by using the MBTA RT 90 bus. Get off at the Highland Avenue and Benton Road stop.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355886651000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355500609000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Aguero, Blake, and Hoffman at the Armory</name><id>95346542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355875200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/95346542/</event_url></item>