<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Delorean is a Spanish band that has been getting quite a bit of buzz on the indie blogosphere. Ever since I heard &amp;quot;Deli&amp;quot; off of their first EP I was hooked.  Recently, they released a new LP titled &amp;quot;Subiza&amp;quot; and it's practically always on in my car.  The perfect soundtrack to summer.  This is sure to be a good show, probably quite a dance party.  Mystery Roar is opening.  A good local band to start things off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great Scott&lt;br /&gt;$12&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/delorean" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mysteryroar.com/#" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mysteryroa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From wikipedia:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Delorean are a Spanish alternative dance band formed in 2000 in Zarautz, a Basque town. Vocalist and bassist Ekhi Lopetegi, guitarist Tomas Palomo, keyboardist Unai Lazcano, and drummer Igor Escudeo wanted to explore their mutual interests, from the local punk rock scene to electronic music. The quartet released an EP and two studio albums between 2004 and 2006 to little mainstream success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2007, Palomo left the band and was replaced by Guillermo Astrain. Delorean subsequently relocated to Barcelona, veering towards more computer-based composition and production. Tiring of the relative low quality of the local dance music scene, the band members created their own eclectic club night, Desperrame, in which they continued the evolution of their music. Remixes for the likes of The xx, Cold Cave, and Franz Ferdinand gave Delorean exposure in the music press.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ayrton Senna EP was released in 2009 to positive reviews from critics. The band subsequently toured with Swedish groups jj and Miike Snow. In 2010, Delorean released their third album, Subiza, and secured a worldwide distribution deal with New York label True Panther Sounds.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278984154000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274458826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Delorean </name><id>13553335</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278979200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/13553335/</event_url></item>