<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Route 123)</address_2><address_1>14 Pond Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02061</zip><lat>42.174060</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-878-7878</phone><name>Strawberry Fair Restaurant</name><city>Norwell</city><id>201047</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.884870</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person donation</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for our FIFTH South Shore Dining Out Meetup and FIRST LUNCH Meetup!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be dining out for lunch at The Strawberry Fair Restaurant in Norwell on Saturday, December 9th.  Located on Route 123, a few yards from Route 53 and less than a mile from Route 3 at Queen Anne's Corner, the Restaurant has grown from a store into a quaint 3-room restaurant appropriately decorated with strawberries.  Strawberry Fair Restaurant offers a wide variety of food sure to please everyone's palate.  Lunch entrees range from $5-$10.  For more information about The Strawberry Fair Restaurant please visit the website at www.thestrawberryfair.com.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy.  This will also be a great time to plan our next Dining Out event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, at this event, if you would like to make a monetary donation towards the Braintree Community Food Pantry's Holiday Adopt-A-Child Program which provides toys for underpriveleged children in the Braintree area, Angela will be taking collections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash.  You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items.  Please plan to arrive a few minutes early to sign-in so we may be seated on time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our &amp;quot;About&amp;quot; page for full details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela and Jen&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165862873000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1164664282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group December Meetup #1: Lunch</name><id>5293104</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165687200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5293104/</event_url></item>