<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Ann St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.768109</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Russian Lady</name><city>Hartford</city><id>4202592</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.677906</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CTMatch.com SPEED Match Dating * UPCOMING EVENTS  * MEET SOMEONE SPECIAL IN 2012* &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.CTMatch.com"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/0/0/event_95778432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;If you have not tried SPEED Match Dating – you are missing out on the most popular way to meet other singles – all in a safe setting and all in one evening. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Meet and chat with more people in one evening than at any other event, and find your match. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;___________________________________________________________________&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TUESDAY April 24 SPEED Match Dating &amp;amp; AFTERPARTY -Ages 21-41 at 7pm &lt;br /&gt;

 at The Russian Lady, 191 Ann Uccello Street, Hartford, CT 06103 &lt;br /&gt;

 on Second Floor -across from XL Center &lt;br /&gt;

 * Includes FREE Appetizers &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;* Visit &lt;a href="http://www.ctmatch.com/"&gt;http://www.CTMatch.com&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 236-3343&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;♥♥♥♥♥ MEET SOMEONE SPECIAL IN 2012♥♥♥♥♥&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CTMatch.com Hosts The BIGGEST Speed Dating Events in Connecticut – So You Meet More People For The Same Price As A Smaller Speed Dating Event&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet More People FACE to FACE at the Largest Speed Dating Events in Connecticut – And Then Pick Your Matches&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPEED Match Dating lets you Meet MORE Local Singles and Potential Matches In One Exciting Evening at Connecticut’s BIGGEST Speed Dating Events - Meet Someone Special and Party with CTMatch.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPEED Match Dating is inexpensive and fun way for busy people looking to meet other local singles. It gives you instant mini dates to help you find that special someone that you will enjoy spending time with and share common interests.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instead of boring and frustrating dates with people you have little in common with, find someone who matches up with you, your interests and lifestyle, and then build a great relationship!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Match results will be emailed to you after the event&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All your information is confidential – we only exchange email address with the people you choose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you tired of Internet dating, fake profiles, and disappointing meetings? Try SPEED Match Dating and meet people face to face to see if you share the chemistry for a great relationship&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* WHO WILL YOU MEET AT SPEED MATCH DATING? Registration and Appetizers start at 6:30 pm - SPEED Match Dating starts at 7 pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All your information is confidential - your Matches will be emailed to you exchanging email addresses only for added privacy and safety.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CTMatch.com SPEED Match Dating is the only Speed Dating Event to double-verify your Speed Dating Matches professionally. We do this to ensure the accuracy of your Matches and to make sure that you receive the all your correct matches&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- and that you don't receive unwanted false matches.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your matches are professional calculated and reviewed AFTER the event, and then emailed to you within a few days to guarantee accuracy, confidentiality, and privacy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tickets Are $40 and include Appetizers, SPEED Match Dating, and AFTERPARTY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

ADVANCE TICKET DISCOUNT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 $30 Online only at &lt;a href="http://www.CTMatch.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.CTMatch.com&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 236-3343&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be on the second floor at the Russian Lady</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>CT Match</member_name><member_id>13123961</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335569320000</updated><rating><average>2.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Classy CT Match Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Match-Singles-Events</urlname><id>357950</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>CTMatch Singles Events Music Dance Speed Dating Golf Comedy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333043789000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TUES April 24 SPEED Match Dating &amp; AFTERPARTY *Ages 21-41 *7pm *The Russian Lady</name><id>58403972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335308400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Match-Singles-Events/events/58403972/</event_url></item>