<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>ESPLANADE ON MEMORIAL DRIVE IN BOSTON</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.353558</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BOSTON HATCH SHELL</name><city>BOSTON</city><id>11028922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122940</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;ALLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLL breeds welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ONCE AGAIN MAYOR MENINO AND HIS HENCHMAN COUNCILMAN ROBERT CONSALVES are attempting to reverse the new Animal Control Bill that went into effect on november 1, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christina White and i thought it would be fantastic if all responsible pittie owners meet together and take a walk at the esplanade/charles river area in boston. it would be a bully walk not a parade so we don't have go through the city to okay the walk. friends of greyhound hold a similar walk every year - this year over 100 people attended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the sooner we meet and walk the better - since the mayor is speaking out again, he might want the police to pay more attention to pitties. so i think it's best if we 'strike while the iron is hot'. mayor menino needs to see responsible owners and well-behaved pittiess&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so, Christina and I are meeting on Sunday, January 20. we will meet at the hatch shell in boston at 11am. we can walk to the mass ave bridge and back to the hatch shell OR if people are interested in a longer walk we can start at the hatch shell, walk over the longfellow bridge and back to the hatch shell again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you decide to walk with us, please make sure your dog is not dog aggressive or human aggressive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that this isn't a parade, it's just a bully walk like the one we have on Saturday at the Milford Rail Trail and the one that just started up at blue hills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;thanks, nancy and frankie and roxie (his new sister!!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THIS IS THE NEBBC'S ETIQUETTE &amp;amp; IT MUST BE STRICTLY ADHERED TO:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just a friendly reminder regarding etiquette at NEBBC-hosted/sponsored events, but nevertheless needs to be taken very seriously and is expected to be followed, especially considering the size of the club and all the newbies! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Dog/Handler Etiquette: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ NO flexi-leashes. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Avoid head-on greetings between dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ &lt;em&gt;Until&lt;/em&gt; you are familiar with individual dogs AND handlers, contact between dogs must be kept to a minimum. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Prevent your dog from lunging on leash, whether it is in play or not. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Dog(s) must be kept under owner control &lt;em&gt;at all times.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Do not allow your dog to surprise, or "sneak up on" other dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ A VERY important note: Just because two dogs are friendly, does &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; necessarily mean they are going to be friendly with &lt;em&gt;each other&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Make no assumptions and DO NOT LET YOUR DOG GREET ANOTHER DOG until you have asked and BEEN GIVEN PERMISSION by the owner.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Dog must be wearing a securely fitting collar/harness or combo thereof with NO chance of slipping it.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359060774000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357595753000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BULLY WALK IN BOSTON ON SUNDAY, JAN. 20TH</name><id>98437592</id><headcount>1000</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358697600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/98437592/</event_url></item>