<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5450 Fitch Ave</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04011</zip><lat>43.899780</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207.406.2081</phone><name>Brunswick Executive Airport   (KBXM)</name><city>Brunswick</city><id>1597235</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.923973</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our depart times may be changed once we find out the details. &lt;a href="http://www.mrra.us/flyin2012.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mrra.us/fl...&lt;/a&gt; "...Calling all pilots and aviation enthusiasts! Join us for the Second Annual Brunswick International Fly-In June 2 and 3, 2012 at the Brunswick Executive Airport (BXM)! Since last year's inaugural fly-in was a wonderful success, we decided to make it a two-day event this year! As the unofficial start to summer, the Brunswick International Fly-In has an action packed line up of activities, such as: Business Aviation Expo Safety seminars Bi-plane rides Airplanes on display Overnight camping Local Maine food vendors Entertainment, and more! The Brunswick International Fly-In is free and open to the public. Fly in, drive in or bike in! There's something for the whole family!  Sponsors Interested in becoming a sponsor? Click Here! There are several sponsorship levels available to meet your needs. Business Aviation Expo The Business Aviation Expo is a two-day aviation industry focused expo held in conjunction with the Second Annual Brunswick International Fly-In.  Click here to learn more about the Business Aviation Expo..."&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338718987000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335299788000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunswick Airport 2nd Annual Fly In</name><id>61959012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338640200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/61959012/</event_url></item>