<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>551 Peacedale Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06010</zip><lat>41.700393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>8605858649</phone><name>Chippens Middle School</name><city>Bristol</city><id>827263</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.967446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>8th Annual Shamrock Run &amp;amp; Walk &lt;br /&gt;March 20, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;551 Peacedale Street &lt;br /&gt;Bristol, CT &lt;br /&gt;________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 Mile Run, 2 Mile Fitness Walk, 5 Mile Run &amp;amp; Kids Fun Run&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Event starts at 9:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$22.00 Registration Fee except for kids fun run $5.00, Fee changes to $25.00 after 3/10/2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lots of stuff being given away for everyone registered ! Craziest Costume Contest- WIN A Sports Version Wii&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each year the after party gets better and better- Hamburgers &amp;amp; Hot dogs, Fruit and much more....We have AWESOME race bags filled with GREAT useful stuff !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking- Get to the race area early- there is plenty of parking but its scattered around the welcome center/school area. Please park on James P. Casey adjacent to the school grounds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Name and Contact Information: Patrick Collins 860.585.8649 or PCIRISHC5@AOL.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last years 7th Annual Shamrock Run &amp;amp; Walk was a huge success which was evidenced by the committee presenting a check for $10,500 to the shelter and hosting over 1500 athletes. Not only was it a great fundraising event for the shelter it helped raise awareness within the community of the good work being done for those less fortunate. Since the race inception in 2003 the event has raised over $80,000 for the shelter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An Irish Blessing &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May you be poor in misfortune, &lt;br /&gt;rich in blessings, &lt;br /&gt;slow to make enemies, &lt;br /&gt;quick to make friends, &lt;br /&gt;but rich or poor, &lt;br /&gt;quick or slow, &lt;br /&gt;may you know nothing but happiness &lt;br /&gt;from this day forward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For registration:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bristolct.net/roadraces/shamrockrun.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://bristolct.net/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi, this is SAM Z. I did this event last year with my social group and it was a fantastic event. Great food, Irish Music, exhibits, booths, family environment, etc. We can go out for some lunch afterwards. I also anticipate bringing at least 25 people between my school and the other social groups. Lots of non-runners also. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anyone who wants to carpool: There is the huge parking lot at Target, 475 Hartford Road, New Britain, CT 06053. Take exit 39A off Route 9 South. Then a quick right &amp;amp; Target is on your left. We can meet there 8:20 AM (email me).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sam</member_name><member_id>4195296</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269272011000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>5K-Runners-Meetup</urlname><id>1354697</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>5K Runners Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260158904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>8th Annual Shamrock Run &amp; Walk - Bristol, CT</name><id>12033631</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269090000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/5K-Runners-Meetup/events/12033631/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/e/a/global_12130586.jpeg</photo_url></item>