<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It seems that more and more people are turning to yoga these days as a path to spiritual enlightenment. Yet, despite yoga's popularity, there are those who remain skeptical about its effects. One of those people is journalist Nick Rosen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Enlighten Up!, filmmaker Kate Churchill follows Rosen through a six month yoga journey, convinced that he will undergo a transformative experience. Yet, Nick remains skeptical that the act of contorting your body into different poses can lead to any kind of spiritual enlightenment, getting in the way of Kate's original plan to document a yogic journey toward enlightenment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is one of the first area screenings of the film (before a two week long stint at the Kendall), the director (who happens to be from Boston) and the subjects of the film will be present at the screenings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is a new release without a lot of distribution, I couldn't find many reviews of the film, but here is a trailer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kKQw0-IlJiY" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film, we'll head off to Boston Shwarma for lunch and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: If you can't make this screening, there will be special events at the Kendall on the 19th and the 24th, which will be sponsored by Whole Foods and REI. Free yoga classes will be offered at those Kendall events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a meetup sign after the Q&amp;A.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220735374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Englighten Up!: A Skeptics Journey into the World of Yoga - Director Present</name><id>8703854</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221402600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8703854/</event_url></item>