<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The HFA is running a mini-retrospective of the films of Ritwik Ghatak. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ghatak is generally considered one of the greatest Indian directors of the second half of the twentieth century, and his significance is often compared to Satyajit Ray`s, India most famous and beloved director. However, contrary to Ray, whose work is widely shown and acknowledged outside of India, Ghatak`s movies remain largely unseen, even today, 30 years after his death. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ghatak`s relative obscurity is mainly due to the way he made movies: In fact, whereas Ray`s work is characterized by a deeply universal humanism, serene elegance, and many parallels with established currents in world cinema (Jean Renoir, Italian neo-realism, etc) which give his masterpieces a sense of immediate familiarity, Ghatak`s movies are more explicitly personal, even autobiographic, and very deeply rooted in Indian history.  His whole work is centered on the key historical event of his generation: the disastrous aftermath of the partition of Bengal. A viewer who is not well versed in Bengali history is likely to feel lost and confused in some parts of his movies, but Ghatak`s intense and passionate preoccupation with his people`s condition still shines through, and makes the experience more than worthwhile.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I`ve only seen one Ghatak movie, &lt;i&gt;The Cloud-Capped Star&lt;/i&gt; (which will also be playing at the HFA), a melodrama centering on a displaced middle class family falling into poverty in a refugee village in Calcutta. It`s a great movie, inventive and powerful, made in a very distinctive style (original use of naturalistic sound, deep-focus, close-ups, aggressive editing which brings Eisenstein to mind). Reading about the movie after watching it, I realized that I had missed many plot details referring to specific aspects of Bengali society at the time, but that did not stop me from really enjoying it. Ghatak has the talent of elevating melodrama into high-art, a skill shared by very few. But beyond the technical prowess and the impressive style, what really gripped me about &lt;i&gt;The Cloud-Capped Star&lt;/i&gt; is the feeling of intense compassion that pervades every single frame of the movie: you can feel how much Ghatak is moved to his very core by the plights and hopes of his characters. His passion is infectious; it overwhelms the screen, and eventually the viewer. I don`t think I`ve had that feeling in a movie before, and if I have, it is very rare. I sound pretty vague, I know, but you should come and see for yourselves. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway, here`s a synopsis of &lt;i&gt;E-Flat&lt;/i&gt; taken from the HFA website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;This tale of two rival theater groups struggling to collaborate is at once a backstage drama and an allegory about the partitioning of Bengal. The dictatorial stance of the director Bhrigu led to some of his troupe splitting off to go their own way. Now young actress Anasuya tries to reunite the two groups for a production of the classic play Shakuntala. As Anasuya and Bhrigu draw closer, their personal and professional relations are complicated by the jealousy of Shanta, Bhrigu's former actress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a really rare opportunity to catch a glimpse of the work of one of India's most brilliant and criminally underrated artists.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201967427000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>E-Flat - A Film by Ritwik Ghatak</name><id>7247621</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203796800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7247621/</event_url></item>