<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>245 Whiting Farms Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.175727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Holiday Inn at Ingleside</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>906244</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.641467</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Translating Your Business Strategy into Execution&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iraida Delgado&lt;br /&gt;Business Account Representative&lt;br /&gt;Workplace &amp;amp; Business Solutions&lt;br /&gt;At Holyoke Community College&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of today’s organizations face similar business issues:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * surviving in a changing economy and marketplace&lt;br /&gt;    * operating at more profitable levels&lt;br /&gt;    * delivering premier customer service&lt;br /&gt;    * meeting the demands of owners, stakeholders, and workforce&lt;br /&gt;    * maintaining quality control&lt;br /&gt;    * capturing and leveraging organizational expertise through better knowledge management&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting these challenges requires building and retaining a skilled and motivated team of employees and managers and communicating clearly with your customer.  The answer to these challenges depends on how well you can translate your business strategy into execution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn how your business strategy enables you to create unique value propositions for your customers and thus separates yourself from other competitors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iraida Delgado has over 15 years experience as an educator and consultant in workforce development initiatives.  Her areas of expertise include business strategy alignment, organizational development and instructional design concepts and applications.  She is an active leader engaged in the development of business and community through service and change management roles.  Her professional and educational backgrounds blend the creative and business aspects of result oriented solutions in her position as a business account representative and faculty member for The Kittredge Center for Business and Workforce Development at Holyoke Community College.  Iraida provides community support through her present role as the president of the board of directors for Girls Inc., of Holyoke.   She holds an MBA and her areas of research interests are intercultural communication, entrepreneurship and creative leadership within organizations.  She is a seasoned presenter and instructor of extemporaneous presentation skills.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256385312000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253231750000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Breakfast Meeting</name><id>11401087</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256211900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/11401087/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/global_10758349.jpeg</photo_url></item>