<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;Its not really us kayaking, its most likely raining Thursday ??? dont know, too soon for any weather prediction to be accurate enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is something to do on a Thursday night and promote a healthier diet and see a presentation..&lt;br /&gt;Sounds good to me.. Im going, may meet new members if not its ok too..etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh i know the info says to bring enough for 6- 8 ..but we all know from our own pot lucks there will be way too much food waste.&lt;br /&gt;I say bring enough what you eat and some more ? (you choose) , it has always worked out on every single one of our events in general.&lt;br /&gt;This being somewhat more of a healthier thinking bunch, i would say bring fruits of some kind..ya dont have to prepare em, ya just eat what is there.. ya take home whats not eaten for the next day..etc....and its healthy all around.. again you choose..&lt;br /&gt;Im getting something from ALDI's what ever looks good , dont know yet..&lt;br /&gt;Mmmm Almond Stollen... maybe Banannas, blue berries.. &lt;br /&gt;Plastic cheez wiz ?? isnt this that silly string stuff ??&lt;br /&gt;Na will bring something good...LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the info i got from Dianne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What Dianne wrote:&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Hello there!&lt;br /&gt;You and your members might like to come to this wonderful event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday June 10th- Sierra Club Hartford chapter&lt;br /&gt;Potluck supper and slide show. Westmoor Park, Flagg Road , West &lt;br /&gt;Hartford&lt;br /&gt;The potluck (we eat outside if it isn't raining) is surrounded &lt;br /&gt;by the gorgeous perennial gardens in full bloom. It is a &lt;br /&gt;beautiful spot.&lt;br /&gt;We will have a leisurely dinner and then have a great &lt;br /&gt;presentation on your next vacation destination- Greenland!? I &lt;br /&gt;saw in a magazine that they are farming a lot of cabbage there! &lt;br /&gt;There will also be doorprizes.&lt;br /&gt;Please bring some food (try to keep it &amp;quot;green&amp;quot;- low on the food &lt;br /&gt;chain) to share with other outdoor-loving friends.&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 6:00. Dinner from 6:30-7:30, meeting and program &lt;br /&gt;starts at 7:30.&lt;br /&gt;Bring a dish (entree, salad, dessert) to serve 6-8. Plus own &lt;br /&gt;place setting(s) and mug if you can---- Beverages provided.&lt;br /&gt;Our presentation is on sea kayaking in western Greenland, where &lt;br /&gt;3000-foot-tall mountains plunge straight down into icy waters &lt;br /&gt;and huge icebergs can ground out in 700 feet of water. Bruce &lt;br /&gt;Hooke, professional photographer and kayak trip leader from RI, &lt;br /&gt;will be showing photographs from two kayaking trips he made in &lt;br /&gt;these waters.&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info: 860-573-3501&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;Use your GPS or map program since there is so many ways here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are located on Flagg Road in West Hartford, hidden between the bustle of Bishops Corner shops, Mountain Road, and Route 44.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;119 Flagg Road&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;West Hartford, CT 06119&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(860)561-8260&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a ORANGE Something, not sure yet..cant wear a hunting vest or hat..maybe my PFD ??</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276265269000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276019780000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greenland Kayaking Presentation and Pot Luck Dinner by The Sierra Club</name><id>13738069</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276208100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/13738069/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/1/global_13936689.jpeg</photo_url></item>