<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Laning Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06489</zip><lat>41.631957</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Holiday Inn Express</name><city>Southington</city><id>1156759</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.870907</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;ARTICLES OF FREEDOM FROM CONTINENTAL CONGRESS 2009  SATURDAY, FEBRUARY 6&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us at the Holiday Inn Express in Southington at noon on Saturday, Feb. 6 for an overview presentation of Continental Congress 2009 and the Articles of Freedom it produced.  You'll learn about the remedial instructions to Congress designed to take us back to our Constitutional foundation, and the recommended civic actions for the people of the United States, designed to compel our servant government to abide by the will of We the People.  Our delegates will be there to answer your questions and give you insight into the deliberations of the historic Continental Congress 2009.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This gathering will be held in the same meeting place as the Rob Simmons forum later that afternoon, designed so you can have time for lunch in between the two events. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all there so we can start spreading the word across CT that we hold this truth to be self-evident: that any action, by any branch of the government, that is repugnant to the Constitution, is null and void.  Let's rise up and restore the Constitution for the United States of America!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Day:   Saturday, February 6, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Time:  12-1 PM&lt;br /&gt;Place:   Holiday Inn Express, 120 Laning Street, Southington (off of Queen Street)&lt;br /&gt;Contact:    Estelle B. Stevenson (203)518-0948&lt;br /&gt;We the People CT State Coordinator&lt;br /&gt;Estelle B. Stevenson&lt;br /&gt;Prudential Ct Realty&lt;br /&gt;504 B Bridgeport Avenue, Shelton, CT  06484&lt;br /&gt;phone:  (203)924-1000 ext. 108&lt;br /&gt;fax:  (203)924-8143&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANDIDATE FORUM - ROB SIMMONS - SATURDAY, FEBRUARY 6&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the first of a series of candidate forums that we will be sponsoring, along with our coalition members, to help you get informed.  Come and meet Rob Simmons, Republican candidate for U.S. Senator, and decide if he will get your vote!  Rob Simmons is a former U.S. Representative who served the 2nd Congressional District from 2001 - 2007.  He is also a U.S. Army Veteran with 37 years of active and reserve duty, and a former CIA officer with 10 years of service.  Most recently he worked for Governor Rell as a Business Advocate focusing on small business issues.  After a brief introduction, Mr. Simmons will answer our questions, and yours!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will also have the opportunity to meet Rusty Haig, who is running for State Representative in the 81st District of Southington.  Rusty is a long-time Southington resident, who has served in the U.S. Air Force, is retired after working over 40 years in the elevator industry, and is a recently-published writer.  He is a conservative and wants to represent you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DAY:  Saturday, February 6&lt;br /&gt;TIME:  2 PM to 4 PM&lt;br /&gt;PLACE:  Holiday Inn Express, Southington&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT:  Joe Markley  at joe@joemarkley.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265648944000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265296975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Continental Congress Presentation, then Tea Party Rob Simmons Interview</name><id>12517642</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265475600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/12517642/</event_url></item>