<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.407504</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-643-1377</phone><name>Dodgeball of Boston</name><city>Arlington</city><id>1339998</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134852</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for another Meet Up Dodgeball night! The last one was a blast! All athletic abilities are welcome to play. We will be playing against each other and having a fun time. We will be playing on a padded floor, wearing socks. The arena is air conditioned and is smaller than a typical dodgeball court. Dodgeball is a lot of fun, so be sure to join us. It doesn't matter if you haven't played since you were a kid, everyone is welcome to participate and have fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members are asked to donate between $5-10 at the door (cash only) to support the Not Me charity which provides self defense classes for Boston youth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please look for Catherine inside the entrance or on the dodgeball court, if you need help finding us, please call 774 232 0000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a joint event with other meet up groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dodgeball, we will head for drinks/appetizers at nearby Joe Sent Me, 2388 Mass Ave, Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Please be sure to bring socks with you in order to play!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dodgeball of Boston is located at Together in Motion, 1 Broadway in Arlington, at the intersection of Rte 16 and Broadway on the Arlington/Somerville line.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please look for Catherine inside the entrance or on the dodgeball court, if you need help finding us, please call 774 232 0000.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327969222000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>74</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324352165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fun Dodgeball Night at Dodgeball of Boston! All levels welcome!</name><id>44982192</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327709700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/44982192/</event_url></item>