<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>680 Admiral Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02908</zip><lat>41.849205</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jamra</name><city>Providence</city><id>1549685</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.439346</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jamra is a Lebanese (Mediterranean) restaurant and hookah bar. They recently opened up directly next door to the Abbey pub over on Admiral street near PC (across from LaSalle bakery - corner of River Ave and Admiral St). I stopped in this weekend and much to my surprise it has a very cool lounge, as from the street it looks like a bright sports bar. Tucked in the back is morrocan and lebanese style decor, lit with lanterns and cozy cushion seating. They don't have a liquor license yet (only coffee/tea &amp;amp; virgin drinks), but the food was tasty. They have hearty appetizers, salads, and wraps. Let's go before the liquor license as it may eventually turn into a cheesy or packed college bar as word gets out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have not begun to promote the place yet, so we can invade and maybe have it all to ourselves. The chef (owner?) was nice and will be happy to accommodate our group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on how many people show up and how conversations are going, I may stay til 9pm or even a little later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's a parking lot adjacent and plenty of street parking on Admiral or interior neighborhood streets.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the back lounge area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299884110000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Hi everyone. I realize that there are lots of meetups this week, but I thought I'd open up a visit to a new venue anyway for a mellow night.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299426478000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>mellow night @ Jamra - new lebanese place near the Abbey</name><id>16817185</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299801600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/16817185/</event_url></item>