<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Fenway Park</address_2><address_1>82A Lansdowne Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.347164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 262-2424</phone><name>The Bleacher Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>735764</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097854</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;***Please Update your RSVP. On-line donations made before March 24&amp;nbsp;are tax deductible. Raffle tickets will also be sold at the event.&amp;nbsp;Prizes are wine and a pair of Yankees Red Sox tickets. Drawing will take place around 8pm. Boston Happy Hour members will also be there. This is your last chance to play Trivingo at the Bleacher Bar as it will not take place when the 2011 MLB season starts March 31.***&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join the Red Sox Natives from 6:00 -8:00 pm at the Bleacher Bar for a Fundraiser for Mindy's Run To Home Base 9K. Complimentary appetizers will be provided by the Bleacher Bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet and Greet with Mindy Finkelstein who is representing the Red Sox Natives in the May 22 Run To Home Base 9K at Fenway Park. Complete details are on the Natives calendar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Natives will be collecting donations to support Mindy's $1,000.00 mandatory fundraising goal. A $15.00 online donation before March 24 or donation at the event gives you 5 tickets for our raffle. As an incentive each additional $5.00&amp;nbsp;donated gives you 5 more raffle tickets. The raffle&amp;nbsp;drawing will take place at 8:00 pm with some very special wine from Mindy's private collection along with a pair of her Saturday, August 6 Yankees tickets. (No need to be present to win). And if you donate we will try to get your name on the list to enter Fenway Park, cheer for Mindy and walk the warning track after the race (at the Red Sox discretion).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hang out afterward between 8:00 - 10:00 pm to play Trivingo with Boston Happy Hour and score some prizes.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trivingo or Trivia plus Bingo&amp;nbsp;is the newest game in town at one of the Red Sox Natives favorite venues, The Bleacher Bar. Two classic games combined to form an exciting, nonstop, group game. I have&amp;nbsp;attended&amp;nbsp;and collected rave reviews from Tonya and other Boston Happy Hour members who have finished in&amp;nbsp;the top 3 almost every&amp;nbsp;week taking home Monster tickets gift cards, Bruins tickets....&amp;nbsp;So let's join Boston Happy Hour and&amp;nbsp;form a team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission is free and there is no cost to play Trivingo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prizes have&amp;nbsp;included Red Sox Monster Tickets, $50.00 Gift Cards, Celtics and Bruins Tickets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trivingo begins at 8:00 PM but you're welcome to arrive when you can and stay as long as you are able. You will find us at the bar before 7:30 PM&amp;nbsp;or ask the hostess or bartender to direct you to the Happy Hour and Natives Meetup crews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining a team, please answer the question which appears after your RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a full food and beer menu available for purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bleacher Bar is unique in that it is located beneath the Fenway Park bleachers in centerfield with a window looking out into Fenway Park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more info on the bleacher bar &lt;a href="http://www.bleacherbarboston.com"&gt;www.bleacherbarboston.com&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beth Anthony &lt;a href="mailto:banthony@lyonsgroup.com"&gt;banthony@lyonsgroup.com&lt;/a&gt; 617-351-7001&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At The Bar. Ask Bartender Joe or Ryan or the Hostess</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>3178870</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301109421000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>To help support Mindy's fund raising goal, enjoy complimentary nibbles from the Bleacher Bar and play Trivingo where the Boston Happy Hour and Native members have been winning!</why><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298342754000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mindy's Run To Home Base Fundraiser &amp; Trivingo at The Bleacher Bar Doubleheader</name><id>16654591</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301004000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/16654591/</event_url></item>