<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Conant St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.455685</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-780-9179</phone><name>Karen And TJ's</name><city>Concord</city><id>1440757</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.401711</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;"Change of Heart: What Psychology Can Teach Us About Spreading Social Change" by Nick Cooney is a brilliant new book on a topic that will help all of us wanting to effect positive change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;Scientific research has generated a wealth of information on how people can be persuaded to alter their behaviors, yet this body of knowledge has been largely ignored by those working to improve society. "Change of Heart: What Psychology Can Teach Us About Spreading Social Change" brings this information to light so that non-profits, community organizers and others can make science-driven decisions in their advocacy work. The book examines over 80 years of empirical research in areas including social psychology, communication studies, diffusion studies, network systems and social marketing, distilling the highlights into easy-to-use advice and serving as a psychology primer for anyone wanting to spread progressive social change.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Nick Cooney is the founder and director of The Humane League, an animal advocacy organization based in Philadelphia, PA that focuses on farm animal protection issues. Nick has written for publications including The Philadelphia Inquirer and Z Magazine, and his advocacy work has been featured in hundreds of media outlets including Time Magazine, the Wall Street Journal, and National Public Radio. Nick holds a degree in Non-Violence Studies from Hofstra University and formerly worked conducting nutrition education programs with the University of Pennsylvania's Urban Nutrition Initiative.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>2400541</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303734640000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299958430000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion: "Change of Heart" by Nick Cooney</name><id>16896974</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303585200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/16896974/</event_url></item>