<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3185 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02021</zip><lat>42.210796</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Park &amp; Ride lot on Rte 138 (Washington St)</name><city>Canton</city><id>7099242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120033</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's the plan?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll hike about &lt;strong&gt;8 miles&lt;/strong&gt; on the &lt;strong&gt;Skyline trail&lt;/strong&gt; in the &lt;strong&gt;Blue Hills&lt;/strong&gt;. Starting at the Park &amp;amp; Ride lot on Rte 138/Washington St, we'll climb Great Blue Hill and follow the Southern Skyline to Hillside St, and continue on the Skyline trail to Buck Hill and Route 28. Then we'll turn around and take the Skyline back to Hillside St, and take the Northern Skyline back to the Great Blue Hill and descend to the parking lot. This should take us about &lt;strong&gt;4 hours&lt;/strong&gt;.  There are a few steep climbs and we'll &lt;strong&gt;climb about 2,000 feet&lt;/strong&gt;.  We also plan to hike at a relatively &lt;strong&gt;fast pace (2.5-3 mph)&lt;/strong&gt;. Due to the fast pace, this is not a beginner hike - you should have hiked a similar distance/pace before signing up.  So you know what to expect - we're out to get exercise, not take a leisurely, relaxed stroll in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where will we meet?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at the Park &amp;amp; Ride on Washington St (Route 138) in Canton/Milton, MA. It's less than a mile north of I-93 (exit 2). Heading north from the exit, you'll pass 1 light (Hillside St) and a gas station and restaurant.  The Park &amp;amp; Ride lot is shortly after that on your left. If you get to the Blue Hills Ski Area or Trailside Museum on the Right you've gone too far. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I'll leave the lot promptly at 10:05am&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should I bring?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water, Snacks, good hiking shoes/trail runners, bug spray&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Info:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain will cancel - I'll send out an email (with my cell phone number) to participants the night before the hike to confirm details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My well-behaved dog, Della, will join us for this hike. If you'd like to bring your dog, please email me first. They should be experienced hikers (and not disruptive to other dogs/hikers on trail).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more info about the Blue Hills here: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue.htm"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find a map of the Blue Hills here: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/blueHills.gif"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/blueHills.gif&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map view of parking area:  &lt;a href="http://g.co/maps/5whhu"&gt;http://g.co/maps/5whhu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1337046230000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336495763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fast-paced Hike at the Blue Hills - Skyline trail</name><id>63936042</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336917600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/63936042/</event_url></item>