<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>13500 South Willow Street</address_2><address_1>Woodside Room</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.900352</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Best Western-Executive Court Inn</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1121473</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.436249</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We are so lucky to have Chef Frank Giglio joining us!!  Mark your calendar!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turning your favorite treats into medicine!  Medicinal Ice Creams and Gelatos.  Easy to digest and absorb ice creams are a perfect delivery system for nutrients and medicine to heal and create a healthy immune system.  Frank will explain the use of many medicinal mushrooms and superfoods as well as feature local and seasonal fruits in my favorite recipes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frank is the Executive Chef and Contributing Editor for David Wolfe's the Best Day Ever membership site.  Frank has been fully immersed in the culinary world for over 15 years and now brings a wealth of knowledge to the natural health industry.  A graduate of the New England Culinary Institute as well as the Institute for Integrative Nutrition, Chef Giglio applies the formal teachings of traditional food preparations to modern day advancements to the areas of superfood and herbal nutrition.  Frank is the owner of Frank's Finest, LLC which specializes in an organic line of herb and spice blends as well as personal chef consultations and small event catering.  For more information, including his recipe collection, Raw For All, please visit frankgiglio.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You do not want to miss this event!&lt;br /&gt;Bring a raw food dish enough for 6-8 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$10 for Adults&lt;br /&gt;Children free&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KO Bisson</member_name><member_id>4565632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281739921000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rawfood-ManchNH</urlname><id>1292928</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Manchester Raw Vegan Food Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275241687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Meetup!  Chef Frank Giglio!</name><id>13639792</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278109800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rawfood-ManchNH/events/13639792/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/b/global_9355803.jpeg</photo_url></item>