<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 and 224 Anderson Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zero Station / The Resilience Hub</name><city>Portland</city><id>11570052</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256172</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Back by popular demand!  This is a repeat of a very successful event we've held for several years, a local version of the popular MOFGA grafting workshops...&lt;strong&gt;Learn (or practice!) fruit tree grafting AND take home ten heirloom fruit trees&lt;/strong&gt; from your efforts during the workshop!!! (And compared to the cost of buying 10 trees, this is a really good deal!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn0.google.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQ5hxf5P3LbexGTdzK9dYQLfvcZxWzBgGcs5oeVnZz8xOjDNYQTSQ" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Learn to propagate and reproduce your favorite fruit tree varieties. Instructors Jennifer Ries and Bennett Verbeck of Whiffletree Nursery will explain why to graft and demonstrate the techniques for Whip &amp;amp; Tongue and T-Bud grafting of new trees as well as Top-working (outdoors) of established trees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class is &lt;strong&gt;hands-on&lt;/strong&gt; and participants will graft stock to take home and plant. Care for seedlings will be discussed.  Please bring a sharp grafting knife*, a potluck lunch dish to share (and your potluck kit) and clothes that can get a bit dirty.  Course will run from 10-4 pm. Coffee/tea/water will be provided throughout the day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/7/c/event_110946012.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;This event usually sells out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fee includes all supplies&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;including rootstocks, scionwood, grafting tape, treekote, labels, sharpies, handouts, rags, etc. *Grafting knives will be available for sale ($20-25 range) if you do not have one of your own. Handouts provided.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jennifer and Bennett live on a small farm in Brooks, Maine. They make a living at their Whiffletree Nursery for which they graft trees and propagate fruiting shrubs and ornamentals. They grow their own food and meat and use a draft horse for farm work. Bennett began grafting over 20 years ago and made his living exclusively from nursery work and homesteading for many years. Jen began grafting about six years ago. Besides homesteading and growing trees, Jen works for Fedco Trees and guides wilderness trips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Comments from the last time we ran this class:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It was a great time, very informative and there were plenty of supplies for everyone plus extra for take home use. There were over 20 varieties of apple trees, plus pear and plum trees as well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I learned alot in such a short amount of time... I even planted the trees I grafted @ the workshop today!!! This was a very important workshop for me to attend and will pay off for years to come. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This was a great workshop. Instructor Jennifer Ries of Whiffletree Nursery delivered thoughtful, informative and practical information. I learned a great deal and am very excited to have had Jennifer launch me in pursuit of this new skill. And meeting new, supportive, people is always welcome and wonderful! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learned a ton, brought 10 'handmade' trees home, had a great time with the other folks who attended, and enjoyed a sunny day under a grape arbor.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mofga.org/Portals/2/logos/MOFGA%20Logo%20Dark%20Green125.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;This event is co-sponsored by the &lt;a href="http://www.mofga.org/"&gt;Maine Organic Farmers &amp;amp; Gardeners Association (MOFGA)&lt;/a&gt;, the nation's largest and oldest organics association.  If you're not already a member, join today!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;This is a family-friendly event with kid space available.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking in front of building and/or on street.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Whitten</member_name><member_id>2670503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1365546580000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358262715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop: Fruit Tree Grafting + 10 Tree "Take Home"</name><id>99704862</id><duration>21600000</duration><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365343200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/99704862/</event_url></item>