<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>April User Group:: ODF what's in it for you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ODF standard has been developed by a variety of organizations and is publicly accessible. This means it can be implemented into any system, be it open source or a closed proprietary product, without royalties. The ODF is intended to provide an open alternative to proprietary document formats so organizations and individuals can avoid being locked in to a single vendor. Join BostonPHP along with representatives from:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OASIS  - &lt;a href="http://www.oasis-open.org/home/index.php:" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.oasis-open...&lt;/a&gt; OASIS (Organization for the Advancement of Structured Information Standards) is a not-for-profit, international consortium that drives the development, convergence, and adoption of e-business standards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ODF Alliance - &lt;a href="http://www.odfalliance.org/:" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.odfallianc...&lt;/a&gt;  The alliance works globally to educate policymakers, IT administrators and the public on the benefits and opportunities of the Open Document Format, to help ensure that government information, records and documents are fully and natively accessible across platforms and applications, even as technologies change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Commonwealth of MA IT Division (ITD) - &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/...&lt;/a&gt; ITD plans to implement ODF using translator technology plugged in to Microsoft Office, in a group of early adopter agencies, including the Massachusetts Office on Disability, by January 1, 2007. Thereafter, ITD plans to migrate all Executive Department agencies to compliance with the standard, in phases, by June of 2007. These target dates are not set in stone; they are dependent on a number of factors, including the adoption by the OASIS standard setting organization of ODF Version 1.1 (which will address minor accessibility issues related to the format itself), the timely delivery of completed translators by one or more of the multiple vendors that are currently developing this technology, and the validated accessibility of the translators themselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;as we explore:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. what is ODF?&lt;br /&gt;2. where is it going?&lt;br /&gt;3. what vendors support it?&lt;br /&gt;4. how does it impact the enterprise and why should I care?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175898746000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172709085000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston PHP Meetup April Meetup</name><id>5523904</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175725800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/5523904/</event_url></item>