<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 York Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.308987</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>GPSCY</name><city>New Haven</city><id>125725</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.931244</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Happy Hours series!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPSCY (Graduate &amp;amp; Professional Student Center at Yale) (www.gpscy.net) which is this neat Yale graduate-student run bar. Usually you have to be Yale affiliated (or with Yalie friends) to come here, but they're opening their doors just for the NHC. Normally they're not even open on Mondays, but they loved us when we came in April, so they're doing us a special favor : )  They're also getting pizza and will sell slices for $1.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now as I just said, they're normally not open at all on Mondays during the summer, but I promised them a good crowd if they opened at 6pm just for us. Don't prove me wrong!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;$3 Well drinks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$2 PBRs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$2 Miller Drafts &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$1 Slices of Pizza &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spacious, private outdoor seating &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two Pool Tables&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Directions:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GPSCY is literally located in the middle of a block - the block surrounded by Chapel, Park, York, and Elm Streets. It's close to Broadway and Downtown.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll post signs where you should turn on York (by the construction) or Park (by Yale Cabaret/Afro American Center). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to call my cell: 203-314-4329. It's 200' from the Yale Repertory Theatre (walk north on York St) so I could always lead you from there if you're confused. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More detailed directions: coming from 217 Park, follow pathway past Yale Cabaret, (slightly set back from the street on a paved pathway), past the Afro Culture building. Keep walking, and after you go through an archway, there is a gothic-looking wooden door directly to your right. You've arrived! The official address is 204 York St.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from York, walk up (north) from Chapel (the Yale Rep theatre is at Chapel and York. It will be at your back as you walk up York). Turn onto the first driveway on your left that is not blocked by construction. Follow that driveway until the door at the left before the archway. This is GPSCY!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It sounds more complicated than it is, trust me. If you have trouble just call me or flag down a Yalie and ask where GPSCY (pronounced Gypsy) and/or Gryphon's Pub is. Thanks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your contact is Devorah 203-314-4329 or Eric (number in rsvp)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPSCY is Cash-Only, as are most of New Haven's finest establishments. There is an on-site ATM and Bank of America isn't too far away. Remember, they're opening just for us, so let's fill the pub up!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we'll be downstairs, bring your ID!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219874907000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219091497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GPSCY opens just for us - Monday Aug 25th Happy Hour!</name><id>8571083</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219701600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8571083/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/0/5/global_5207125.jpeg</photo_url></item>