<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>136 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.346981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 747-2261</phone><name>Berklee Performance Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>357516</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.087547</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>32.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We first met this soon-to-be saxophone giant when Water Music booked him into his first commercial Boston-area engagement on February 11, 1992. In the ensuing 15 years, &lt;a href="http://www.joshuaredman.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Joshua Redman&lt;/a&gt; pursued his muse through a range of popular and innovative ensembles, including his Elastic Band (whose latest CD, Momentum, was nominated for a Grammy last year) and groups he led under the SFJazz banner. Now, as one of the most compelling and fearless saxophone voices in jazz, he returns in the mode of the classic sax/bass/drums trio. When the Berkeley (CA) native finally chose to document this project in a New York recording studio, he found a world of memories and inspiration, including his pre-school exposure to and fascination with the musics of Africa, Asia and the Middle East and the important cross-country recording journeys taken by such personal heroes as Sonny Rollins and Stan Getz. With all this in mind, Mr. Redman realized that Back East was the perfect title for this exploration of the musical, historical and philosophical juxtaposition of East and West. With three brilliant bass/drum teams at his service and three equally brilliant guest saxophonists, Back East, on Nonesuch, is proof positive that Joshua Redman and the trio format were made for eachother. Bassist &lt;a href="http://www.christianmcbride.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Christian McBride&lt;/a&gt; and drummer Blade (who also appear on the CD) are also bandleaders in their own right and were pivotal sidemen in Mr. Redman's early career, and, in a sense, tonight serves as a grand reunion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Berklee Performance Center is on Massachusetts Avenue near its intersection with Boylston Street in Boston. For directions, click &lt;a href="http://www.concertix.com/directions.html#Berklee" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the BPC at 6:45pm and try to get seats together. After the show we can meet up for drinks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541332000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonjazz</urlname><id>87187</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Jazz Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177423718000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joshua Redman Trio with Christian McBride and Brian Blade</name><id>5703512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178492400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonjazz/events/5703512/</event_url></item>