<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Boylston Street at 180 Lamartine Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.317017</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Southwest Corridor Park</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>317277</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104340</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;RAIN PLAN&lt;/b&gt; - Look for us on the field (we're pretty open to playing in the rain), but if we're not there then we'll be at Ula's Cafe on Amory.  From Stony Brook T follow the left path across the field and you'll reach Amory directly across from Ula's.  It's very very close.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More likely we'll be on the field - it's a very slim chance at this point that it'll rain at all between 1 &amp;amp; 3pm. We're hoping it looks more like this:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://lh4.google.com/send2robbie/Ru4Eo_3q5JI/AAAAAAAAACQ/3BobgVu34fY/Birthday07%20003.jpg?imgmax=512" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recess for Justice is going down at the Stonybrook court right off Lamartine Street in JP. (Exit Stonybrook T station on the Orange line, walk directly across the street to the park - we'll be on the field and in the courts right in front of you.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your favorite outdoor game or check out the assortment of fun we'll have on hand: frisbees, kickball &amp;amp; chalk (for 4-square!), nerf football, softball (bring a glove) and whatever other randomness we can think of.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it's hot we can run through the fountain sprinkler to cool off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Around 3pm we'll start to figure out what to do next.  We might go to Ula Cafe or Java Jo's for coffee, smoothies, snacks and board games (bring 'em!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/?photoAlbumId=226090&amp;amp;photoId=2233731"&gt;Check out the photos&lt;/a&gt; from the last time we held Recess for Justice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/a/3/event_2233731.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So look no further if you're seeking like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston, want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while perfecting your frisbee forehand, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in. If you're interested in building cross-issue coalitions courtside?even better!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events? Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the 'Message Board' and are encouraged to suggest and co-host events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt;  and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;. Learn about our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/pages/Annual_Membership_Fee_details/"&gt;Suggested Annual Membership Fee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hilary</member_name><member_id>3092728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214327429000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212975240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recess for Justice</name><id>8105774</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214154000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/8105774/</event_url></item>