<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research and Development Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1534447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This month's meetup sponsored by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/b/a/event_131651962.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Astonish is the leading insurance digital marketing company in the country.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;We have created the most comprehensive digital insurance marketing system in the world. Our unique insurance lead generating system fuses the power of insurance agency management, online marketing technology, strategic web services, social networking solutions, and so much more.  Talk to Jesse Friedman (&lt;a href="mailto:jfriedman@astonish.com" target="_blank"&gt;jfriedman AT astonish DOT com&lt;/a&gt;) about Front End Development positions available today.  We Need Talented, Motivated people!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00PM: Pizza and Networking&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:20-7:30PM: Opening remarks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30-8:10PM:  Talk 1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:15-8:55PM: Talk 2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Session 1: (for beginners)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Who is that masked man?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by Dave Werner (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/#!/BigD_TVF"&gt;@BigD_TVF&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today’s Internet 2.0, anonymity is a thing of the past. Bloggers are managers of their own brands; YouTube can provide instant (and sometimes unwanted) acclaim. Bloggers struggle with the decision to reveal their identity and collect onthe notoriety of their works, while accepting any fallout that may accompany them.  Or do they try to stay in the shadows, content in knowing that their pseudonym will learn all the accolades, but also suffer the slings and arrows that come with Internet fame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;David Werner has been a blogger since Aaron Boone broke his heart in October of 2003. He has written for websites both public and private, on topics including professional &amp;amp; college sports, professional gambling, technology and emerging technological trends, medical education, and everyday whimsy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;In 2008, he closed up shop on his personal sports blog (“The Best Seat InThe House Is The View From The Couch”) to join the founding editors of SpartyAndFriends.com - now &lt;a href="http://TheVictoryFormation.com"&gt;TheVictoryFormation.com&lt;/a&gt;. He was a founding member of TechNewsMadeSimple.com, and contributed to DocSports.com. Today, he writes when the mood strikes – but more often whenever he has a couple free hours from everyday life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Session 2: (for devs)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Custom Post Types ... and stuff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by Jon Bishop (&lt;a href="http://www.Twitter.com/JonDBishop"&gt;@JonDBishop&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A quick look at custom post types in WordPress and how you can easily make your own. We'll go over how to create and implement them on your site as well as some of the dos and don'ts to make sure your custom post types play well with others. We'll be breaking down some PHP code in WordPress so it's safe to say this talk will be more on the dev side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;Jon Bishop is a Web Developer at AMP Agency with a love for writing open source code and playing with the latest web technologies. Jon maintains a few plugins in the WordPress plugin repository and spends the rest of his time blogging at &lt;a href="http://www.jonbishop.com"&gt;JonBishop.com&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://www.ampagency.com/insights-lab/blog"&gt;AMP Agency blog&lt;/a&gt;. Jon is also one of the organizers of the &lt;a href="http://meetup.bostonwp.org/"&gt;Boston WordPress meetup.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Eng</member_name><member_id>9694496</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Bishop</member_name><member_id>13435843</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342277735000</updated><rating><average>3.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>98</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330449682000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June2012: Internet anonymity (Beg) and Custom Post Types (Dev)</name><id>54185902</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340665200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/54185902/</event_url></item>