<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Leah asked me to schedual a meet-up here and is going to help organize it.  It looks like a great place.  look to see if others who live near you are going as to weather you might be able to car pool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jenn &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moose Hill is Mass Audubon’s oldest sanctuary and one of the largest with nearly 2,000 acres. The 25-mile trail system brings you through diverse habitats— explore the red maple swamp via the boardwalk, observe amphibians at a vernal pool, or watch swallows catching insects in the meadows. Each season brings another opportunity to explore nature’s wonders—enjoy a winter stroll, watch migrating warblers, or experience the beauty of the fall foliage. Our bird-feeding station and butterfly garden bring wildlife close to the nature center. Art exhibits are shown September through June, and the gift shop is open year-round. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;293 Moose Hill Street&lt;br /&gt;Sharon, MA 02067&lt;br /&gt;781-784-5691&lt;br /&gt;moosehill@massaudubon.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nature Center/Trail Hours:&lt;br /&gt;Nature Center: Monday through Friday, 9 a.m. to 5 p.m., Saturday and Sunday, 10 a.m. to 4 p.m. Trails: Open every day, dawn to dusk. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Your Safety &lt;br /&gt;Do not feed any animals &lt;br /&gt;Stay on trails to avoid ticks and poison ivy &lt;br /&gt;Do not smoke anywhere on the sanctuary &lt;br /&gt;Do not pick or collect plants or crops without permission &lt;br /&gt;Avoid Conflicts with Wildlife &lt;br /&gt;Do not bring pets, leashed or unleashed, on to the site &lt;br /&gt;Picnic only in designated areas &lt;br /&gt;Do not bring motorized vehicles or bicycles onto the site &lt;br /&gt;Hunting, fishing, or trapping are not permitted&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;$4 for nonmember adults;&lt;br /&gt;$3 for nonmember children (3-12) and seniors &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the north: Take Rt I-95 south to exit 10 (Coney St, Sharon, Walpole). Take a left off the exit and take the first right onto Rt 27 north (Walpole). Take first left on Moose Hill Street. Follow to the top of the hill and turn left onto Moose Hill Parkway. The parking lot is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the south: Take Rt I-95 north to exit 8 (Main St, Sharon). Take a right off the exit and follow one mile. Take a left onto Moose Hill Street. Follow to the top of the hill and turn right onto Moose Hill Parkway. The parking lot is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By public transportation: From Boston’s South Station, take the Attleboro commuter train to Sharon. From the Sharon station walk to the main road, Rt 27. Follow north for two blocks and take a left onto Moose Hill Parkway. Walk 1.5 miles to the top of the hill; the nature center is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the nature center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer Lamontagne</member_name><member_id>7358665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219770958000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218228899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A walk on the wild side (hahah)</name><id>8505945</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219597200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/8505945/</event_url></item>