<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>at 100 Atlantic Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.361664</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts Beirut Memorial</name><city>Boston</city><id>9501822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051964</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Members of the Boston Atheists have planned a modest demonstration, to recognition of Blasphemy Day, and as an affirmation of our shared belief in the foundational important of free speech and the right to dissent in a healthy civic society. Boston Atheists director Zachary Bos will be emceeing a lineup of speakers -- Raja Bhattacharyy, Aly Aly, Garga Chaterjee, and Najat Kessler -- who will each talk about their feelings toward and understand of the interrelated core values of freedom of expression and freedom of thought. We will be distributing free expression cupcakes (!), and inviting passerby to add their thoughts -- whatever they may be! -- to a Blasphemy Book we'll keep and use on the same occasion in future years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Memorial where we'll be meeting is located at the north end of Christopher Columbus Park, directly in front of Joe's restaurant at 100 Atlantic Avenue. If you have trouble finding us, call 617-935-4951.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immediately after the event, we'll be moving over to Quincy Market for lunch in the food court. Join us for both events, or whichever one you can make it to!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349120339000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348770663000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A demonstration in support of free speech</name><id>84391782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349019900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/84391782/</event_url></item>