<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Whitney Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.173733</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-241-3300</phone><name>Elks Lodge #902</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>383630</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.650604</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Empire One Running Club (EORC) sponsors a timed 5k race at the Ashley Reservoir in Holyoke every Thursday from April thru September. Once a month (?3rd Thursday?) the distance is 8K.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The race starts at 6:30, be there at 6PM to register and warm up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are usually over 100 people entered, they range in skill from 5 min/mile to walkers. Baby-strollers are common. The course is mostly flat, no cars, no dogs. There is plenty of parking at the Elk's. The entry fee is $5 this year, go around to the back entrance to sign up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the race most of the runners stay at the Elk's to watch a replay of the finish line video on the wide screen TV, drink beer, eat whatever is cooking at the Elk's, and socialize. Prizes are awarded for too many categories to list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great way to meet people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter "250 Whitney Ave, Holyoke, Ma.", or the coordinates, "42.175,-72.6515" into the search box at maps.google.com to see a map of the area.There is a building (the Elks Club) with parking lots on either side. When you get there you will see a fire gate blocking the road just past the second lot, that is the entrance to the reservoir. On alternate weeks the race either starts at the gate and finishes down by the water, or vice-versa. On Thursday nights the restrooms are open.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The registration table is inside the Elks, go around the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gene R</member_name><member_id>11009036</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365124660000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Running-Hot</urlname><id>1551891</id><group_lat>42.2599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5199966431</group_lon><name>Running Hot</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363442214000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Timed Run at Ashley, Every Thursday, April - September, 6PM</name><id>qthppfyrgbgb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365112800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Running-Hot/events/109538102/</event_url></item>