<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>66 Brook Rd.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03031</zip><lat>42.917524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peabody Mill Environmental Center</name><city>Amherst</city><id>985951</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.618772</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/b/c/event_141975292.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/3/a/event_141976442.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are traveling on &lt;strong&gt;NH-101 W&lt;/strong&gt; in Bedford where the highway ends &lt;span&gt;and becomes a 2 way road at the light&lt;/span&gt; (and where NH-114 starts &lt;span&gt;and 101 intersects with Boynton St.&lt;/span&gt;)  &lt;strong&gt;turn left to stay on NH-101 W and proceed 7.2 miles.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turn right onto Horace Greely Road&lt;/strong&gt; where you will see the sign in picture one. and &lt;strong&gt;proceed 0.4 miles&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turn left onto Brook Road&lt;/strong&gt; where you will see the signs in picture two&lt;strong&gt; and proceed 1.4 miles&lt;/strong&gt; to the end of the road.  It becomes a dirt road.  Park near the small pond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below are two different links for trail maps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://amherstnh.gov/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/TrailMap.pdf"&gt;http://amherstnh.gov/wp-content/uploads/201...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.svlt.org/Trails/TractMap.asp?TownName=Amherst&amp;amp;TractName=Joe%20English%20Reservation"&gt;http://www.svlt.org/Trails/TractMap.asp?Tow...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The Joe English Reservation is comprised of 558 acres, as of 2000, and is the largest and best known conservation property in Amherst. It is composed of a number of acquisitions and it continues to be expanded. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

An extensive color coded trail system opens the complex to hiking and to cross-country skiing and showshoeing in the winter. Trails are marked with signs and sign posts which were added in 2000. The main accesses are (1) at the north end of Brook Road at Peabody Mill Environmental Center, and (2) 3/4 mile up Chestnut Hill Road on the left. Each parking area has some parking spaces. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This is a rolling wooded tract with both deciduous and evergreen trees. Several brooks and ponds are located throughout the area. Wildlife consists of beaver and usual pond denizens, migratory waterfowl, and resident birds of pond and forest, small mammals, moose and deer. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;We will be doing some new trail sections we haven't done before as well as some that we have. We will be doing an approximately 4.9 mile hike using parts/or the whole of the Hammond Brook Trail, Bicentenial Trail, Timber Trail, Ledge Trail, Highland Trail, Harding Trail, and Pine Trail to do a loop hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a few spots where one can take a shortcut back to the parking lot if anyone wants to shorten the hike. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

There will be many spots of going uphill and downhill but the elevation gain or loss ranges in between 325 - 525 feet of elevation (200 feet of elevation gain or loss) so on any particular hill there aren't many really steep sections and any steeper trail sections don't last that long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are some places for the water dogs to get wet if the water isn't iced over.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Any adult guest you want to bring should sign up on the meetup site as a member so they will be covered by the liability waiver. A minor would need a written waiver signed by a parent or guardian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Once you are on Brook Road follow it to the end to the Peabody Mill Environmental Center parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357060632000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355108749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trail Hike at Joe English Reservation - Amherst, NH - 4.9 miles</name><id>94754942</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356793200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/94754942/</event_url></item>