<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This trip will hit one of the official 4,000 foot peaks in NH - Isolation (#47 @ 4,004')&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;a href=" &lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php&amp;quot;%3E"&gt;http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click this link for the current weather forecast&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changed the time to 8:30am as I have to take sunset into account.&amp;nbsp; The group will being leaving the Trailhead at 8:30am on the nose.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No headlamp No Go!&amp;nbsp; I will check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will leave the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Glen Boulder Trailhead&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Rte 16 (approximately 1 mile South of Pinkham Notch Visitor Center) at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;NO LATER than 8:30AM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; in the parking lot. According to Google Maps this location is about 149 miles from Boston - it should take about 2 hours 55 minutes to drive there-Taking Rte 95 to Rte 16.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Please check road closures as I know Rte 302 in Bartlett is closed so no getting their from Bretton Woods.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Please call, text, or email me the morning of the hike to inform me if you &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;NOT&lt;/span&gt; are coming. Do it early so I receive it before I loose cell signal. In this way if everyone shows up and is ready before 8:30am we can start earlier and know all that are showing up are there.&amp;nbsp; Thanks.&amp;nbsp; Should be a fun hike!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;a href="&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=Pinkham+Notch+Road,+Glen,+NH&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFU_voQIddEHB-ym9kRd0-JmzTDE9CyVKmMo60w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=35.136115,79.013672&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=8" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=Pinkham+Notch+Road,+Glen,+NH&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFU_voQIddEHB-ym9kRd0-JmzTDE9CyVKm...&lt;/a&gt;"&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click this link for driving directions that are close to the Trailhead location&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will follow &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Glen Boulder Trail to Davis Path&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and return the same route. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This moderate pace hike will cover about &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;12 miles and climb about 5,050 feet&lt;/span&gt; &amp;ndash; it is considered ADVANCED because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. It should take an average hiker about &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;10 hours 00 minutes&lt;/span&gt; to complete this trip.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you. The goal of this hike is to summit safely, and to do that, everyone in the group needs to be at a similar fitness and experience level. If you have ANY questions about your ability to participate in and complete this entire event please contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Winter hiking is more strenuous than hiking in the summer. We will assess travel and weather conditions and make changes to our planned trip as necessary - &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;"Reaching the summit is optional, getting down in mandatory" (Ed Viesturs).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum clothing and equipment required to participate in this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sturdy hiking boots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Synthetic shirt and pants, including at least one insulating layer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waterproof rain jacket (with hood) and pants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High-energy snacks, food for lunch and water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Trekking poles. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a group first aid kit that contains basic items but you will need to bring any personal medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be driving a Silver Toyota Matrix with "MEETUP RANDOM HIKERS" license plate cover.  Cell is 978-973-5022 be sure to call ASAP if you are going to be late or not coming as cell coverage is spotty up north.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John (LAG) Lagasse</member_name><member_id>2667639</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1315840037000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305998860000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH48 - Mt. Isolation</name><id>19209201</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315657800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/19209201/</event_url></item>