<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's time for me to attempt my first 4,000 footer.&amp;nbsp; I want to do it before the weather gets unbearably hot.&amp;nbsp; I have chosen Mt Tom as my first peak, because it is supposed to be a beautiful trail, not horribly steep, with some good views at the top!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would like to have 8 people total on this hike!&amp;nbsp; Three of you should be people like me, who are also just getting into hiking and want to try your first 4,000 footer.&amp;nbsp; And the other four should be experienced and patient hikers who will come along and cheer us on as we (slowly) make our way up to the top!&amp;nbsp; (Anyone who has hiked with me knows my tortoise-like pace...but my stamina has really improved!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All RSVPs will be wait-listed for now.&amp;nbsp; When you RSVP, please tell me why you would like to do this!&amp;nbsp; I want to make sure that the people who sign up are really going to SHOW up before making the final list!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be staying at the White Mountains Hostel in Conway afterwards...anyone is welcome to join me.&amp;nbsp; It's a nice hostel - very comfy and clean, with a full kitchen, living room, washer/dryer and pretty spacious rooms - and cheaper than a campsite! &lt;a href="http://www.whitemountainshostel.com/index.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.whitemountainshostel.com/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the Crawford Depot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308575690000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>It's time.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302717084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>My First 4,000 Footer</name><id>17292664</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308492000000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/17292664/</event_url></item>