<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had such a fantastic turnout and response the first time we showed this movie, we are showing it again! Some of the same folks are coming back and bringing friends. It's really THAT GOOD. So if you want to get a fascinating, funny, practical, and hopeful view of the stuff going on in our world, plus a great dollop of idea and inspiration for things you can do here and now to affect our world for the better, come on down and bring your friends. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It's also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people! These events are free, and if you would like to give a donation, we will send it to an organization that's truly helping the world. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;The January Conscious Movie is I AM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/1/8/event_83846392.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 I AM, a prismatic, probing, and ultimately inspiring exploration of our world, what's wrong with it and what we can do to make it better, represents Tom Shadyac's first foray into non-fiction following a career as one of Hollywood's leading comedy directors, with such successful titles as "Ace Ventura," "Liar, Liar," and "Bruce Almighty" to his credit. I AM recounts what happened to the filmmaker after a cycling accident left him incapacitated, possibly for good. Though he ultimately recovered, he emerged a changed man. Disillusioned with life on the A-list, he sold his mansion, moved to a mobile home community, and decided to start life anew. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Armed with nothing but his innate curiousity and a camera crew, Shadyac embarks upon a journey to discover how he as an individual, and we as a race, can improve the way we live. Meeting with a variety of thinkers and doers &amp;ndash;- remarkable men and women from the worlds of science, philosophy, academia, and faith -&amp;ndash;including such luminaries as David Suzuki, Noam Chomsky, Howard Zinn, Archbishop Desmond Tutu, Lynne McTaggart, Ray Anderson, John Francis, Coleman Barks, and Marc Ian Barasch &amp;ndash;- Shadyac appears on-screen as character, commentator, guide, and even, at times, guinea pig. An irrepressible &amp;ldquo;Everyman&amp;rdquo; who asks tough questions, but offers no easy answers, he takes the audience to places it has never been before, and presents even familiar phenomena in completely new and different ways. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 All donations support the Institute of HeartMath, an internationally recognized nonprofit research and education organization dedicated to helping people reduce stress, self-regulate emotions and build energy and resilience for healthy, happy lives.&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Esther Kenny</member_name><member_id>3810301</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Michael Knight</member_name><member_id>8983786</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332288090000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330714115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night -- I AM, with legendary comedy director Tom Shadyac</name><id>54688082</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330819200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/54688082/</event_url></item>