<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>454 Charles Bancroft Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03052</zip><lat>42.881839</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-420-8008</phone><name>SpookyWorld</name><city>Litchfield</city><id>1088794</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.464054</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets go see the all new Spookyworld.  We can also have dinner at Woodmans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Spookyworld:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Voted ONE OF AMERICA'S TOP THRILL ATTRACTIONS FOR 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.spookyworld.com/press.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.spookyworl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is this the same old SpookyWorld?&lt;br /&gt;No! The SpookyWorld attractions are brand new, intense, terrifying haunted houses that are guaranteed to deliver the scares you are looking for this October! &lt;br /&gt;Are your attractions open if it rains?&lt;br /&gt;Yes, we are open rain or shine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are the attractions the same this year?&lt;br /&gt;No, we have made a lot of changes to our Attractions including the addition of 3 new never seen before haunted houses!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the hours of operation?&lt;br /&gt;Our ticket booths open at 6:00 p.m. and the Haunted Attractions open at 7:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Ticket booths close at 11:00 p.m. and we stay open until the last groups of the evening make it through all of the Attractions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the prices for the different haunted houses?&lt;br /&gt;General Admission to Nightmare New England - $29.99&lt;br /&gt;Admission includes access to the Monster Midway, and admission to all SEVEN Haunted Attractions! &lt;br /&gt;(Note I do have some $5.00 off coupons)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Attractions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;House of Eternal Darkness&amp;quot; Afraid of the dark? Afraid of what you can hear and smell but can't see? Can you find your way out through the suffocating darkness of this house of the dead? House of Eternal Darkness has no light, no way to see your path or what is right next to you; will you panic as the fear sets in? You'll succumb to the edge of your sanity left to wonder whether it is better to live or die. Don't be afraid of the dark…Fear what lurks within it…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Demented&amp;quot; Sick, twisted, and disturbing are the themes for this the labyrinth of gore and disorder. Not for the faint of heart, the darkest displays of the human character are laid bare in this horror show of atrocity and wickedness. You'll never be the same after witnessing this experiment in evil and carnage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sleep Stalkers&amp;quot; is designed to feel like an old, decrepit hospital. The patients in this hospital suffer from insomnia and are slowly being driven insane by their condition and the dreadful creatures that lurk just outside the hospital walls. Some of the scenes guests will visit include patient &amp;quot;sleeping&amp;quot; quarters, neurological testing facilities, cold storage, the laundry facility and more. With over 15 fright filled rooms, &amp;quot;Sleep Stalkers&amp;quot; is the perfect, bone-chilling way to wrap up this Nightmare.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Raven's Claw Cemetery&amp;quot; Walking deep into the woods, under the iron archway and into the cemetery, guests immediately are surrounded by crypts, tombstones, mausoleums and freshly dug graves. Corpses and zombies lurk in the shadows and fog that blanket the cemetery. &amp;quot;Raven's Claw&amp;quot; takes full advantage of the natural landscape around the historic Merrimack River and is guaranteed to deliver thrills and screams to all who dare to enter!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buried Alive: Those who dare to enter &amp;quot;Buried Alive&amp;quot; will encounter the creatures that fester below the ground during the various stages of death and decay. Navigate through 14 rooms of sheer terror and brave the infestation of cockroaches, worms, and maggots that live amongst the unfortunate souls beneath the soil. Experience the alarm of being buried underground and get your adrenaline racing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;NightFeeders&amp;quot; The smell of blood is in the air and pooling around your feet…… Come face to face with the &amp;quot;NightFeeders&amp;quot;, a bloodthirsty cult of vampires who stalk these sacred grounds. Nothing can prepare you for the horrifying scenes of victims feasted upon and abandoned lifeless throughout the halls of this bloodstained hellhole.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The 3-D Freakshow&amp;quot; The Freakshow includes classical 3-D scenes with clowns, carnival themes and toxic waste that are always crowd-thrillers. However, this event prides itself on bringing Extreme 3-D to New England by offering many non-traditional scenes not found anywhere else! This event is designed to confuse and disorient the guests as they twist, turn, and try to escape through the rooms and corridors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Woodmans:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 95 years and 5 generations of seafood and memories we've decided to branch out. Come see us in Litchfield New Hampshire-less than 1 hour from Boston and less than 5 minutes from Manchester NH airport. Fall Hours: Open Daily at 11am. We're easy to find we're located at 454 Charles Bancroft Highway at Mel's Funway Park on Route 3A. 603-262-1980 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nightmare New England &amp;amp; the Legendary SpookyWorld at Mel’s Funway Park&lt;br /&gt;When: October 2nd - October 31st More Information&lt;br /&gt;While at SpookyWorld look for the “Lobster Vampire” for Coupons to Woodman’s Restaurant and Great Giveaways!! Also, make Woodman’s your “meeting spot” in between haunts for some great food, drink specials and more! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.woodmans.com/WhatsUp.cfm#NewRestaurant" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.woodmans.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.woodmans.com/restaurant/menus.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.woodmans.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257030472000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256127992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spookyworld and a chance to meet Tony Moran (The Original Michael Myers)</name><id>11677035</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256857200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/11677035/</event_url></item>