<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Simon Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.750863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-233-1058</phone><name>Balanced Health Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>727520</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488831</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Be sure  to forward  this announcement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; around to others you think may be interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: this showing will be at the new Balanced Health - Bigger room, better sound!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month in Nashua&lt;br /&gt;We'd like to show either End Game or The Obama Deception, BUT... we don't have a copy of either one, strangely enough... Can anyone commit to bringing one of these to the meeting. We CAN show either of these from the internet, but the DVD would be nice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your blank DVDs to the meeting and be sure to get a copy of this one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Short subjects&lt;/b&gt; - bring what you think others should see - we'll see what shorts we have time to view. We also have the capability to show You Tube and Google videos, so bring your links.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have screenings every Tuesday&lt;/b&gt; somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: &lt;b&gt;1st Tuesday-Nashua&lt;/b&gt;; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; 4th Tuesdays are now OPEN.  If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, we'll have a special organizing meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive by 7:00 PM&lt;/b&gt;, since this meeting is on a tight schedule. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and the video will begin promptly at 7:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please bring healthy snacks and/or drinks&lt;/b&gt; for sharing, since some may have come to our meeting directly from work. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contributing a box of your favorite tea is always a good idea to build an inventory of available beverages at Balanced Health!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt; is in the lot in right in front of the building and Balanced Health is the last office bay on the right. You'll see the Sunset Restaurant at the far left end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Newspaper&lt;/b&gt; - For an interesting paper which covers 9/11 Truth issues and other topics of concern, visit the &lt;a href="http://RockCreekFreePress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Rock Creek Free Press&lt;/a&gt; out of Washington, D.C. and see &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/307/pages/Newspapers_and_Journals/"&gt;our meetup page for others&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have set up a &amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online&lt;/b&gt; at eRideShare.com. Ride-sharing arrangements can now be made by clicking on the link above (&lt;a href="http://mv911t.erideshare.com"&gt;http://mv911t.eridesh...&lt;/a&gt;) to go to the online ridesharing group. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. You can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride. ( Donations to the driver for gas are always appreciated.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring your friends!&lt;/b&gt; - Forward our email announcements to others you think will be interested in this important topic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Write to us at MerrimackValley911Truth@gmail.com with your suggestions for the next month. Here's &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/307/pages/Our_video_collection/"&gt;our present inventory of videos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be making tea and munching snacks</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250031074000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248720516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua August video - TBA</name><id>10969464</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249426800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/10969464/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/4/a/global_6742170.jpeg</photo_url></item>