<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie starts at 7:00, so let's meet out front of (if it's not raining, otherwise just inside) the doors to the theater, under the marquis at 6:30. Then I'll collect dough, buy everyone tickets and we can head in to get snacks and grab seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you Tuesday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Dana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;508/308-4897&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm hungry to see &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/the-hunger-games/"&gt;The Hunger Games&lt;/a&gt;. I have NOT read the books (yet), but am anxious to see what all the fuss is about. Come join me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUMMARY: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; Sixteen year old Katniss Everdeen volunteers in her younger sister's place to enter the games, and is forced to rely upon her sharp instincts as well as the mentorship of drunken former victor Haymitch Abernathy when she's pitted against highly-trained Tributes who have prepared for these Games their entire lives. If she's ever to return home to District 12, Katniss must make impossible choices in the arena that weigh survival against humanity and life against love.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;THE HUNGER GAMES is directed by Gary Ross, with a screenplay by Gary Ross and Suzanne Collins and Billy Ray, and produced by Nina Jacobson's Color Force in tandem with producer Jon Kilik. Suzanne Collins' best-selling novel, the first in a trilogy published by Scholastic that has over 26 million copies in print in the United States alone, has developed a massive global following. It has spent more than 180 consecutive weeks/more than three consecutive years to date on The New York Times bestseller list since its publication in September 2008, and has also appeared consistently on USA Today and Publishers Weekly bestseller lists.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We'll meet right outside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays or Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you for The Hunger Games!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--Dana &lt;br /&gt;

 508/308-4897&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me out front.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335417946000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334005380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hunger Games</name><id>59880222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335308400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/59880222/</event_url></item>