<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>239 W 52nd St</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10019</zip><lat>40.763027</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(212) 247-0200</phone><name>Roseland Ballroom</name><city>New York</city><id>673078</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.983986</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ticket, plus expenses</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hey all! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul van Dyk is electronica's world phenomenon, hailing from Berlin, Germany, and has been voted #1 DJ in the world many times over! His show will leave you breathless, shaking, and in awe of how far music has come since the first people banged on stones with sticks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Update: I'll be taking an early evening train to NYC, and will meet everyone at Roseland Ballroom at 10:30p, downstairs by the coat check and bathrooms. I'll have my phone on me, but it could be pretty loud, so feel free to send me a text message. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If folks are staying overnight at one of New York City's fine hotels, perhaps we could link up for brunch Saturday morning/afternoon? I had planned on staying at the Hotel Penn, and doing the whole &amp;quot;let's meet up before the show for dinner, etc&amp;quot; but plans do evolve! I'm really excited to party with everyone! Let's meet at Roseland and see where the night takes us!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Tickets for the show are currently $50, and that price expires Thursday March 13 at midnight! I think the price is becoming prohibitive for the first-timer, but it's still cheaper than Billy Joel! The show will probably sell out!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have gone down to NYC, partied to PVD, and taken the last train out of NYC (departing 1:49am and getting in at 3:57am), but this time I'd like to stay overnight and relax a bit. Not staying the night is do-able, the cheapest option, and still fun, but I would rather have the freedom to do more during my visit to the city, and therefore will be getting a hotel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.madeevent.com" target="_blank"&gt;Made, the promoter&lt;/a&gt; has the event info, as well as ticket ordering info. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric is your contact: 860-214-9361. &lt;br /&gt;Each person is responsible for ordering their own ticket, arranging transportation to/from the event, and lodging reservations (if any). I hope you'll join me- it'll be a lot of fun!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>2576129</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205719810000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200538588000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paul van Dyk at Roseland Ballroom, NYC March 14, 2008!</name><id>7133522</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205546400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7133522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/5/0/global_2996640.jpeg</photo_url></item>