<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(In the Radisson Hotel; corner of Charles Street South and Stuart Street)</address_2><address_1>200 Stuart St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350760</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 426-4499</phone><name>Stuart Street Playhouse</name><city>Boston</city><id>450165</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.067660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Another entry in this years Boston Film Festival at the Stuart Street Playhouse&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Kristen Stewart, James Gandolfini, Melissa Leo &lt;br /&gt;Director: Jake Scott &lt;br /&gt;Producer: Giovanni Agnelli, Ridley Scott, Tony Scott &lt;br /&gt;Synopsis: WELCOME TO THE RILEYS is a powerful drama about finding hope in the most unusual of places. Once a happily married and loving couple, Doug and Lois Riley (James Gandolfini and Melissa Leo) have grown apart since losing their teenage daughter eight years prior. Leaving his agoraphobic wife behind to go on a business trip to New Orleans, Doug meets a 17-year-old runaway (Kristen Stewart) and the two form a platonic bond. For Lois and Doug, what initially appears to be the final straw that will derail their relationship, turns out to be the inspiration they need to renew their marriage. &lt;br /&gt;Runtime: 1:50 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailer at the below website.  It autostarts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://welcometotherileys-movie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://welcometotheri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll head over to Rock Bottom Brewery for a post movie discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a meetup sign (hopefully) and will meet folks up near the screen after the movie.  If there is is Festival activity going on near the screen let's meet in the lobby.  Try to remember a few faces from the Yes RSVPs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>4007722</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285174489000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284652035000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Welcome to the Rileys (Boston Film Festival)</name><id>14791988</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285109100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14791988/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/global_18000205.jpeg</photo_url></item>