<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft NERD Center, First Floor Horace Mann Room</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10054772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please &lt;strong&gt;REGISTER&lt;/strong&gt; for This Event at the web-site for the MIT Enterprise Forum. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/launch-smart-clinic-with-geohelp-matchupbox/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/launch-smart-clinic-with-geohelp-matchupbox/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;November 7, 2012: 5:30pm – 9:00pm &lt;br /&gt;

 At the Launch Smart Clinic, two companies will present their full investor presentation (not just the elevator pitch) and get feedback from both our distinguished panelists and the audience. Please join us and help these companies tighten their growth and fundraising plans while you glean insights into what investors other others are advising them. Your input will make a difference to their success!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30-6:00pm Registration, networking and something to eat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00-9:00pm Two Company presentations followed by feedback&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presenting Companies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GeoHelp – Location-based Customer Service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GeoHelp is a mobile customer service platform that lets consumers communicate immediately with thousands of businesses. Consumers experience the service using a mobile app and a private web account, where they get VIP service and video FAQ answers and/or rewards. Businesses subscribe to this inexpensive SaaS service so they can differentiate their businesses by offering superior service to “Generation NOW” customers. Due to their location-based filtering inherent in the GeoHelp app, businesses are able to be “top of mind” at the EXACT time that consumers are making purchasing decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By using a unique combination of privacy rules and state-of-the-art security mechanisms, GeoHelp gives consumers FULL privacy, FULL control, and ZERO spam. This environment makes it safe and easy to opt-in to 100′s of their favorite national brands and local businesses. Highly relevant news or incentives can be sent automatically based on location, user preferences or real-world service conversations. Conversation platforms supported are Facebook, Twitter, LivePerson Chat, and a white-label GeoHelp solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bob Ofenstein, the Founder/CEO of 2du Media LLC&lt;/strong&gt; will discuss the Problem/Solution space that led to their creation of a completely new mobile concept called “GeoHelp” which will be launched in a few months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ ~ ~ ~ ~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MatchupBox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; addresses the issue of identity and trust in the digital economy, because if being visible and active online is more important than ever, consequently controlling and maintaining a strong, authentic personal digital identity has never been more crucial. This unique cross platform application provides users with a secure way for building and managing their Personal Online Identity based on the trust of their personal or professional networks and on their online activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Didier Collin de Casaubon, CEO at MatchUpBox Inc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;~ ~ ~ ~ ~&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft New England Research &amp;amp; Development Center (NERD)&lt;/strong&gt; is a research and software innovation campus located in the heart of Cambridge, Massachusetts. The NERD vertical campus spans two buildings with its primary presence and conference center located at One Memorial Drive and a recently renovated and expanded space located at One Cambridge Center. NERD is home to some of Microsoft’s most strategic teams including Microsoft Research New England, Microsoft Application Virtualization (App-V), SharePoint Workspace, Microsoft Technical Computing, Microsoft Advertising, Microsoft Lync, Microsoft Office 365 and more. NERD has become a hub of activity for the local tech community and has hosted more than 500 events and welcomed more than 40,000 visitors during the past two years.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352397352000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351536444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Launch Smart Clinic with GeoHelp &amp; MatchUpBox</name><id>89067212</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352327400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/89067212/</event_url></item>