<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 1 South </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.603548</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 774 0707</phone><name>Supino's Restaurant</name><city>Danvers</city><id>1016652</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938094</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's got together at Supino's in Danvers and watch the Superbowl, this year the Indianapolis Colts will play against the New Orleans Saints (this is the 1st year the Saint's have been in the Superbowl).  This should be a great game, both teams have had a great season. So come on down to Supino's and join us for a fun filled evening, it doesn't matter which team you are cheering on if nothing else come out to watch the commercials!  Supino's has a lot of TV's all around the bar area and free popcorn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out their website/menu at: &lt;a href="http://www.supinos.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.supinos.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Highlights of the night is:  Join us for the Superbowl at Supino's Feb 7, 2010, Have fun cheering on your favorite team and playing SPIN and WIN!!!  Everyone has a chance to win Great Prizes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Super Bowl Special&lt;br /&gt;  Prime Rib Dinner $7.95&lt;br /&gt;  Served with Potato and Vegetable (WOW!)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: Supino's has a really big parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: Let's meetup early before the game, get into the spirit and grab some good seats.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP'S/SEATING: We will be posting this on all 3 of our Meetup sites, depending on how many people RSVP for this event we may not all be able to sit at 1 big table, so please be aware that you may be sitting at a table w/only some of the people in group(s), if your plans change and you are not able to attend this event, please come back to the site and change your RSVP, seeing that there is a limit on the amount of people that can attend this event, you maybe taking a spot that someone else can have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you.&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/laughing.gif' border='0' alt='laughing' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come into the bar area and find us at the table(s).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265754976000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264982873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's watch the Superbowl at Supino's!</name><id>12477717</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265581800000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12477717/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/5/global_12885013.jpeg</photo_url></item>