<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Trafton Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01108</zip><lat>42.079709</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Forest Park</name><city>Springfield</city><id>889038</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.558846</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Folks, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Okay so a location has been chosen. Forest Park.  If the weather plans on being bad, TBD the day before, we will Meet at the Hazard Grill in Enfield. Same time and same day for both locations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note; Pizza is NOT being ordered. This is way too complicated for me to attempt with logistics of the event. Please plan on bringing your own supper. If you have a dessert you would like to share, I'm sure people wouldn't mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrance fee is 3:00 dollars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I recommend that the initial meeting place be the grandstand. to get there:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-from sumner ave. turn onto forest park main greeting road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-follow greeting road until you reach the grandstand (will be on the right, there is a right turn there which is also a&lt;br /&gt; branch of the main meeting road). The group will be meeting there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the Books we will be reading is Kings and Queens by our own book club Member Amy.&lt;br /&gt;A Link has been posted under &amp;quot;More&amp;quot; and then files for the book. Please let me know if you can't find it or open it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kings and Queens - Courtney Vail:&lt;/b&gt; Book is posted as a PDF in the attachment section of this Meetup (&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/228874/Kings%20%26%20Queens2%20for%20PDF.pdf"&gt;Kings and Queens PDF&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Cedar Creek, where mansions and urban legends bloom, forget championships; violence is the new celebrated pastime. When seventeen-year-old Majesty Alistair overhears a church shooting plot in her ill-boding town woods, she can't budge police and strives to find the teenage nutjobs before they act, but they have an agenda far bigger than she ever assumed. Violence rocks the town, leaving residents reeling and yanking Majesty into the middle of it all. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With danger always pressing, police seemingly getting nowhere and those closest to her looking guilty, she continues hunting and charges into an evil web. But the truth and her actions threaten to haunt her forever, especially since she’s left with blood on her hands, the blood of someone she loves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For our second book a poll has been posted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;07/09/2010 UPDATE: THE POLL IS NOW CLOSED. OUR SECOND BOOK FOR THE MONTH OF JULY IS LONG WALK TO FREEDOM BY NELSON MANDELA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Long Walk to Freedom –Nelson Mandela&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The famously taciturn South African president reveals much of himself in Long Walk to Freedom. A good deal of this autobiography was written secretly while Mandela was imprisoned for 27 years on Robben Island by South Africa's apartheid regime. Among the book's interesting revelations is Mandela's ambivalence toward his lifetime of devotion to public works. It cost him two marriages and kept him distant from a family life he might otherwise have cherished. Long Walk to Freedom also discloses a strong and generous spirit that refused to be broken under the most trying circumstances--a spirit in which just about everybody can find something to admire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE UPDATE YOUR RSVP WITH THE BOOK YOU WILL BE READING.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer</member_name><member_id>7372437</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280699616000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275008703000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Book Club</name><id>13619262</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280268000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/13619262/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/1/global_16415041.jpeg</photo_url></item>