<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>158 Brighton Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.352952</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-779-0140</phone><name>Brighton Music Hall</name><city>Allston</city><id>1478997</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132595</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/b/0/event_126352912.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Sierra Leone's Refugee All Stars &lt;br /&gt;

 Atlas Soul (first part) &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunday, June 24, 8:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cumbancha.com/radio-salone-north-american-tour/"&gt;Listen Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brighton Music Hall &lt;br /&gt;

 158 Brighton Ave &lt;br /&gt;

 Allston, 02134 &lt;br /&gt;

 General admission &lt;br /&gt;

 $20.00 &lt;a href="https://www.worldmusic.org/sales_searchseats.php?pb_seq=1360"&gt;Buy Ticket Now &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; 18+, Doors 7pm, Show 8pm, Standing Room Only&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Roots reggae rhythms blessed with finger-picked guitar is at the core. Fans of the early Wailers will be as beguiled as Afro-popsters. Underlying it all is a plea for peace from voices heartbreakingly familiar with the consequences of the alternative."—Boston Herald&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sierra Leone’s Refugee All Stars have gone from being unknown musicians languishing in various refugee camps to being the subject of an acclaimed documentary, touring the world to support critically revered albums, appearing on the Oprah Winfrey Show and sharing the stage and studio with Aerosmith and other international stars. They have risen like a phoenix out of the ashes of war and inflamed the passions of fans across the globe with their buoyant hope-filled songs. Seamlessly blending soukous, afrobeat and more traditional West African styles with roots-reggae, dub, funk and more, the band is a potent example of the redeeming power of music and the ability of the human spirit to persevere through unimaginable hardship and emerge with optimism intact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presented in association with Crossroads Presents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://onesheet.com/AtlasSoulLive/"&gt;Listen to Atlas Soul's New CD June 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/b/0/event_126355472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Atlas Soul is an award-winning band based in Boston performing original music that celebrates and bridge Afro-Mediterranean melodies &amp;amp; grooves with Jazz and Funk thus naturally creating new powerful genres of music one could describe as Maghrebien-Funk, Rock’n Raï and/or Shaabi-Jazz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "Atlas Soul's blend of jazz, funk and Middle-Eastern/Arabic grooves is a fascinating sonic stew that will catch any listener's ear. This is their second appearance on our CD's compilation. We like'em, and you will too". Global Rhythm Magazine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Their powerful energetic &amp;amp; tight live performance is guaranty to move any audience and soon have every one sing along (often in a foreign language) up &amp;amp; dancing &amp;amp; sharing the positive energy produced from the stage!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 They have played venues such as The Montreal Jazz Festival, The Kennedy Center, The Festival International de Louisiane, The Houston International Festival, Musikfest, The FNX/Boston Phoenix Jazz Series at the Hatch Shell, The Festival International Nuits d’Afrique (Montreal) The Boston Globe Jazz Festival, The Steppin’Out Festival, MASS MoCA , Les Francofolies de Montreal, and many more…They have been booked on the same bill and shared the stage with international artists such as Lady Smith Black Mombazo, Thomas Mapfumo, Gigi, Alpha Blondy, Hassan Hakmoun, Baba Maal and Cheb Nasro to name just a few. &lt;br /&gt;

 “What hits hardest about Atlas Soul’s sound is the natural funk of North African music and also powerful vocals, which span fluid, passionate Gnawa melodies and husky Raï hooks. There is great wisdom in a world-music outfit that embraces divergent genres (but not so many that the sound loses its identity)" NPR Banning Eyre. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Atlas Soul sings in French, Arabic, Hebrew and English. The lyrics speak of love, natural wonders, oppression, poverty, and of the melancholy of immigrants longing for their homelands. &lt;br /&gt;

 Their motto is world-music-for-world-peace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 They have won or placed 3 times the Independent Music Awards, the Billboard World Song, The Unisong International, Global Rhythm Magazine, Just Plain Folks Music Awards, Boston Music Awards and many more.. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Atlas Soul have released 4 CDs &lt;br /&gt;

 Their 2008 6 songs EP “Maktoub” (Destined) is Independent Music Awards Finalist 2008 &lt;br /&gt;

 The 2006 5 songs EP release: MABROUKA (blessings) received rave acclaims: &lt;br /&gt;

 Independent Music Awards 2007 Vox Populi Winners (world fusion) &lt;br /&gt;

 Independent Music Awards 2007 Finalist &lt;br /&gt;

 11th Annual Unisong International Song Contest (2007) Finalist &lt;br /&gt;

 Billboard World SONG CONTEST (2007) Honorable Mention &lt;br /&gt;

 Global Rhythm magazine Song Contest Winners (2006) &lt;br /&gt;

 Canary Islands International Song Contest Finalist (2006) &lt;br /&gt;

 Independent Music Awards 2004 Winners (world fusion) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The song “Mahmouma” is selected to be included in the Music For Peace compilation CD. &lt;br /&gt;

 The song “SOLE” is released by PETROL RECORDS/EMI world wide in 9/07 on a compilation called "Arabia, The Greatest Songs Ever" &lt;br /&gt;

 “L'Amour En Banlieue” appeared on the Global Rhythm’s compilation CD 8/06 (that reaches 120,000 readers each month) along with songs from artist such as Asha Bhosle, Ska Cubano &amp;amp; Salif Keita. &lt;br /&gt;

 "Angelo Mio" appeared on the Global Rhythm’s CD compilation 10/06 along with songs from artist such as T. Jobim, Marisa Monte, Lee Ritenour, Gal Costa &amp;amp; Tania Maria &lt;br /&gt;

 “Mabrouka” was also selected to be used on the Rock n Cookin’ Kitchen - TV Show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Atlas Soul sings in French, Arabic, Hebrew and English. The lyrics speak of love, natural wonders, oppression, poverty, and of the melancholy of immigrants longing for their homelands. &lt;br /&gt;

 Philosophically and politically, Atlas Soul hopes to inspire world peace through a fusion of music and culture that gets people to the dance floor. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For more information please contact Jacques Pardo at 617 923 9957 or email him at &lt;a href="mailto:jacquespardo@comcast.net"&gt;jacquespardo@comcast.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cdbaby.com/atlassoul4"&gt;http://www.cdbaby.com/atlassoul4&lt;/a&gt; -June 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cdbaby.com/CD/atlassoul3"&gt;http://www.cdbaby.com/CD/atlassoul3&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.cdbaby.com/cd/atlassoul2" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.cdbaby.com/cd/atlassoul2&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.cdbaby.com/cd/atlassoul" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.cdbaby.com/cd/atlassoul&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 websites: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.atlas-soul.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.atlas-soul.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://facebook.com/atlassoul/"&gt;http://facebook.com/atlassoul/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=52078315977&amp;amp;ref=ts" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=52078315977&amp;amp;ref=ts&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/atlassoul" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.myspace.com/atlassoul&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.reverbnation.com/atlassoul" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.reverbnation.com/atlassoul&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.ilike.com/artist/Atlas+Soul" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ilike.com/artist/Atlas+Soul&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Brighton Music Hall is probably the best venue ever for dancing! let's meet on the dance floor..</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340650845000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338819346000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sierra Leone's Refugee All Stars and Atlas Soul</name><id>67656202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340582400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/67656202/</event_url></item>