<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1100 Lexington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.412483</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 547-5655</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739900</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.233269</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This unique first-person account offers a window into the mind of a  high-functioning, 27-year-old British autistic savant with Asperger's  syndrome. Tammet's ability to think abstractly, deviate from routine,  and empathize, interact and communicate with others is impaired, yet  he's capable of incredible feats of memorization and mental calculation.  Besides being able to effortlessly multiply and divide huge sums in his  head with the speed and accuracy of a computer, Tammet, the subject of  the 2005 documentary &lt;em&gt;Brainman&lt;/em&gt;, learned Icelandic in a single week  and recited the number pi up to the 22,514th digit, breaking the  European record. He also experiences synesthesia, an unusual  neurological syndrome that enables him to experience numbers and words  as "shapes, colors, textures and motions." Tammet traces his life from a  frustrating, withdrawn childhood and adolescence to his adult  achievements, which include teaching in Lithuania, achieving financial  independence with an educational Web site and sustaining a long-term  romantic relationship. As one of only about 50 people living today with  synesthesia and autism, Tammet's condition is intriguing to researchers;  his ability to express himself clearly and with a surprisingly engaging  tone (given his symptoms) makes for an account that will intrigue  others as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311956790000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307020344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Born on a Blue Day by Daniel Tammet</name><id>20664501</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311895800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/20664501/</event_url></item>