<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The book for discussion in August is "Buddha Standard Time - Awakening to the Infinite Possibilities of Now" by Lama Surya Das (published 2011 by Harper Collins).&amp;nbsp; This book shares one of the great realizations of Buddhism, an insight that everyone can learn to apply. The minutes and hours of our days do not simply march from future to present to past. Rather, each moment is intersected by a fourth dimension. By learning to live in tihs dimension -- what Lama Surya Das calls "Buddha Standard Time" -- we reduce the amount of stress in our lives and find greater focus, fulfillment, creativity, and even wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drawing on Tibetan Buddhism and other great wisdom traditions, as well as on neuroscience and holistic traditions, renowned teacher and national bestselling author Lama Surya Das&amp;nbsp;shares real-world examples, practical exercises, and essential techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lama Surya Das is one of the foremost American Buddhist teachers and scholars. He is the founder&amp;nbsp;and spiritual director of the&amp;nbsp;Dzogchen Foundation, and founder of the Western Buddhist Teachers Network. He lives in Concord, Massachusetts.&amp;nbsp; For further information visit his website:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://www.surya.org"&gt;www.surya.org&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>First floor - Discovery Gallery (by the Commercial Street entrance)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313020837000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308340276000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discussion of "Buddha Standard Time" by Lama Surya Das</name><id>ttkxpyplblb</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312844400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/22586301/</event_url></item>