<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Henry Marliave, a French immigrant from Paris, arrived in Boston with his wife by his side, a collection of recipes, and the dream of finding success in the United States of America. After honing his cooking skills at the Young’s Hotel and mastering the English language, young Henry Marliave achieved his American dream by opening his namesake: Restaurant Marliave at 10 Bosworth Street in 1885. Henry Marliave and his successors have continued to operate at this location serving cuisine inspired from classic French, Italian and New England fare for over 120 years. The Boston dining landmark has survived World Wars, the Great Depression, prohibition (and many published liquor seizures because it operated as a speakeasy), and twenty-three different presidents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Marliave offers 4 different types of oysters nightly. We source all these oysters from the New England shores. Island Creek's Duxbury, Wellfleet, Castle Hill, and Cranberry Ledge are a few of the different oysters we have recently served on the half shell. Our oysters are presented simply with lemon, cocktail sauce, and mignonette to highlight the distinct flavor of each oyster. Beginning Friday the 8th, Marliave will feature all our oysters for $1 each from 10:00 p.m. until closing at 12:30 a.m. from now until the end of summer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leigh and Krisy </member_name><member_id>8616476</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249059558000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245943916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cocktails, Apps and Oysters on the Patio at Marliave</name><id>10733748</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248390000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/10733748/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/8/global_9336968.jpeg</photo_url></item>