<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Church Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374447</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Cambridge Unitarian Universalist</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1558733</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119555</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;Andrew Rimas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;discusses&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Empires of Food &lt;br /&gt;Feast, Famine, and the Rise and Fall of Civilizations &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Wednesday, April 13, 2011 7:01 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;FPC Parish House &lt;br /&gt;3 Church St., Cambridge, MA 02138&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;This event is free; no tickets are required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cambridge Forum and Food for Free are pleased to welcome author and local journalist ANDREW RIMAS as he discusses his latest book Empires of Food:&amp;nbsp; Feast, Famine, and the Rise and Fall of Civilizations. What does this sweeping look at the relationships among food, food availability, new foods, and developing human civilizations tell us about food security in our own warming world?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using the colorful diaries of a sixteenth-century merchant as a narrative guide, Empires of Food chronicles the fate of people and societies for the past twelve thousand years through the foods they grew, hunted, traded, and ate&amp;mdash;and gives us fascinating, and devastating, insights into what to expect in years to come. In energetic prose, agricultural expert Evan D. G. Fraser and journalist Andrew Rimas tell stories that capture the flavor of places as disparate as ancient Mesopotamia and imperial Britain, taking us from the first city in the once-thriving Fertile Crescent to today's overworked breadbaskets and rice bowls in the United States and China, showing just what food has meant to humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cities, culture, art, government, and religion are founded on the creation and exchange of food surpluses, complex societies built by shipping corn and wheat and rice up rivers and into the stewpots of history's generations. But eventually, inevitably, the crops fail, the fields erode, or the temperature drops, and the center of power shifts. Cultures descend into dark ages of poverty, famine, and war. It happened at the end of the Roman Empire, when slave plantations overworked Europe's and Egypt's soil and drained its vigor. It happened to the Mayans, who abandoned their great cities during centuries of drought. It happened in the fourteenth century, when medieval societies crashed in famine and plague, and again in the nineteenth century, when catastrophic colonial schemes plunged half the world into a poverty from which it has never recovered. And today, even though we live in an age of astounding agricultural productivity and genetically modified crops, our food supplies are once again in peril.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302740299000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301116370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Empires of Food</name><id>17061695</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302735600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/17061695/</event_url></item>