<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Front Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03833</zip><lat>42.981155</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Town Hall Gallery</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1625121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.947128</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;After the success of last fall's Ying &amp;amp; Yang show with Main Street Art (where we'll have our second annual fall exhibit in September), and because Chris Keeley said we had to, we're having our second art show for members of the Seacoast Photographers Group. This spring show is [tentatively] titled:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstraction: Abstracts and Extracts through the Lens &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;An abstract photography exhibit by local seacoast photographers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The opening reception will be Saturday, April 6th, 2013 and will run through the closing party on Sunday, May 5th, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who Can Participate:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The show is open to any photographer who is a member of the Seacoast Photographer's Association. That's this Meetup group  - if you're a member of this group, you may participate. If you're not a member, sign up before the Call to Entry Submission Date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submissions:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Head over to PhotoMeets.com. If you have an account, please login. If not, take 30 seconds to create an account. On the console page you'll see when you login, you'll now see a section on this show. Follow the simple instructions to add your photos and join the show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There is a $15 entry fee via credit card to cover the minor costs of the show. Any and all proceeds after costs will benefit the Seacoast Artists Association Scholarship Fund.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Images should represent your interpretation of "abstract" subject matter or results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;All entries will be judged for suitability by an independent panel of judges. Submissions that do not meet the guidelines (e.g. not a photograph, or includes something considered vulgar or inappropriate for public display, etc.) will be rejected by the judges. In the case that there are more submissions than space, the judges may reject pieces at their sole discretion. Every artist submitting on time is guaranteed that at least one work will be in the exhibit, assuming that the work adheres to all the guidelines related to subject, media, and framing.The decision of the judges is final.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All applicants will be notified of the judges' decisions via email by Wednesday, March 20th (three days after the submission deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanging Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 All works must be framed and wired for hanging. Mats should be cleanly cut, frames should be fully intact and unmarred, glass should be thoroughly cleaned, and a wire for hanging should be attached. Sawtooth hangers or other methods of hanging are not acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drop-Off of Accepted Works:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Drop off will be Friday, April 5th, from 4-6PM, at the Town Hall Gallery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pick-Up and Closing Party:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The final day of the exhibit will be Sunday, May 5th. We plan on a closing celebratory party from Noon until 4PM, and you can pick up your works then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exhibit: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;The opening reception is set for Saturday, April 6th from Noon-5PM. Invite your friends, family, and colleagues. Get your Facebook mojo on!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the five-week photography exhibit, the gallery will be open on Saturdays and Sundays from Noon to 4PM. We'll have Saturday ArtTalks on various topics of interest running from 12:30-1:30PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come upstairs via the front stairs or the side-door elevator.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deb </member_name><member_id>7653029</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cynthia</member_name><member_id>8758507</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>tracy</member_name><member_id>11265621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Perna</member_name><member_id>12948944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary</member_name><member_id>14262012</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pat Corlin</member_name><member_id>23420281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365872470000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360174195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring Photo Exhibit Opening</name><id>103340282</id><headcount>60</headcount><duration>18000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365264000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/103340282/</event_url></item>