<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1374 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02368</zip><lat>42.201332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Randolph Holiday Inn</name><city>Randolph</city><id>338611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062770</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We were formly know as the ASSOCIATION OF REAL ESTATE INVESTORS-SOUTH. Now Real Estate Investors of New England. We have supported investors in New England for over 10 years. Seasoned Investors to new ones COME JOIN US to figure out the best ways to buy and sell property in this market.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS MONTH WE HAVE LARRY GOINS. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry is going to share EXACTLY how he buys &amp;amp; sells 10-15 houses PER MONTH (or More!) and NEVER leaves his home or office.  &lt;br /&gt;JUST HOW DOES HE DO IT?! BE HERE TO FIND OUT! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry H. Goins is not only licensed as a mortgage lender and mortgage broker in North Carolina and South Carolina, he is also licensed in both North Carolina and South Carolina as a Real Estate Broker and General Contractor. He is a member of the North Carolina Association of Mortgage Professionals and a member of the National Association of Mortgage Professionals.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between speaking engagements and mentoring other Investors, he oversees the daily operations of Investors Rehab, Inc., of which he is a co-founder and officer. Investors Rehab, Inc. is a real estate investment company that buys and wholesales 10-15 houses per month to other investors at 70% of ARV.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   SAVE MONEY OFF THE DOOR FEE BY REGISTERING EARLY AND GUARANTE SEATING AS IT IS LIMITED. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To register follow the link to a great company we are affilated with Foreclosuresmass.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/30/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foreclosur...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hear what some people are saying about Larry's presentation and system &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry, it is our delight to inform you that you have received the highest 10 rating rate from all Speakers who have spoken to our members.   &lt;br /&gt;Dan Stojadinovic, Tampa Bay REIA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can tell you that Larry Goins has created the best real estate investment course I've seen in a year.  I've watched many people turn their life around with Larry's system.  Glen Woodfin, redhotspeakers.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry, I wanted to take this opportunity to commend you for assembling a marvelous product. I have invested in real estate coaching before, and have learned quite a lot, but the information in your course really helped me to put it all together. The systems you've developed have helped me put together a marketing plan that allows my business to spend more time working for me than I do for it. I expect great success with your methods to follow very soon. Best Regards,  &lt;br /&gt;W. Hugh Reavis III, Maidens, Virginia &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The attached check for $1,975.00 is from a deal I closed in October. It's not huge but I had a total of three hours invested in it! I used your Ultimate Property Analyzer on my first call to arrive at the price with the seller and was excited when she agreed to sell to me! Thanks for your generosity in sharing what you know!  &lt;br /&gt;Greg Branham Red Canoe Properties, LLC &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry, I just finished going through your new course The Ultimate Buying and Selling Machine. It was fantastic. It has all the information needed to start your own Home Buying and Selling Franchise. The Ultimate Property Analyzer is a very powerful tool. The forms disc and Internet searching software is worth the price alone. There is so much information that I am going to continue to go through it to make sure I learn all that I can. The course is a must for any novice or advanced real estate investor.  &lt;br /&gt;Thanks again,  &lt;br /&gt;Eric Daenecke, Charlotte, NC &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have studied in detail Larry's extraordinary Ultimate Buying and Selling Machine home-study materials and find no other system as unique and 'real world' applicable as his.  It is a pleasure to be involved with Larry in any manner because his standards of ethics and outside-the-box teaching are exactly what creative real estate investor should model after.  SCOTT RISTER Author of ?Find All The Motivated Sellers You Can Handle!', 'The Probate Profit Machine!' and 'Instant Cash Wholesaling Houses!' &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I used the Ultimate Property Analyzer to analyze the properties I made offers on. Within three weeks, I had two deals under contract and sold them for a profit of $5,000 each. Your Ultimate Buying and Selling Machine course is by far the most affordable and also has more information than most of the other courses available. Thanks a lot Larry!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ford Perry Wilmington, NC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SAVE MONEY OFF THE DOOR FEE BY REGISTERING EARLY AND GUARANTE SEATING AS IT IS LIMITED. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To register follow the link to a great company we are affilated with Foreclosuresmass.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/30/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foreclosur...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have trouble following the link copy and paste it to your browser. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing many new faces this month. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Derek Ebrecht &lt;br /&gt;Real Estate Investors of New England &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Derek Ebrecht</member_name><member_id>4695117</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186871567000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-730</urlname><id>598232</id><group_lat>42.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>EMREIA-Eastern Mass Real Estate Investors Assoc.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186004553000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Real Estate Investors of New England August Meetup</name><id>6111098</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186698600000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-730/events/6111098/</event_url></item>