<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Shaw Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02905</zip><lat>41.776336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edgewood Yacht Club</name><city>Cranston</city><id>1305073</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390270</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come down to Edgewood Yacht Club&amp;nbsp;THIS&amp;nbsp;FRIDAY evening for cocktails and a sunset from the T-Dock or under the Pavilion!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As most of you know,&amp;nbsp;our historic yacht club burned down last January. (A picture of the building is in the "Our Sponsors" window.) It was a&amp;nbsp;tragic loss for the club members, but also for the community of Edgewood, Cranston&amp;nbsp;and Narragansett Bay. She was truly a historic gem and landmark building, one of the last left on the Bay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The spirit on Edgewood Yacht Club lives on in the vitality and strength of its members who share a love for boating and Narragansett Bay that will always endure. Please come down and join me on the T-Dock&amp;nbsp;on the water to make merry and watch the last of the summer sunsets!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have never been to a yacht club, here's your chance to check it out and if you've been to EYC before, you know even without the building, being on the water can't be beat and the&amp;nbsp;EYC members&amp;nbsp;are very friendly too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your friends,&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;family and your kids&amp;nbsp;- there's room for all. Food will be available - hotdogs, hamburgers and a steak fry plus all the fixings and&amp;nbsp;various salads. The drinks are cheap, the venue is great and hanging out with friends is what its about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE RSVP BY THURSDAY!!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; I will need to let them know roughly how many people might be coming and please&amp;nbsp;mention if you think you might partake of the BBQ as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, bring a jacket or sweater if you are prone to the "chillies".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be a the T-Dock or under the tent</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316349180000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315859916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night  by the Bay - Edgewood Yacht Club!</name><id>33271662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316212200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/33271662/</event_url></item>