<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mill St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01830</zip><lat>42.780456</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-642-1683</phone><name>Plug Pond </name><city>Haverhill </city><id>1302060</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068237</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Update 9/7/10:  Please note the pow wow is at Plug Pond on Mill St, not at Winnekeni on Kenoza St, the directions are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM I-495  (including Worcester, Providence, Cape Cod)&lt;br /&gt;I-495 North to Exit 52 (Route 110).  Head West on Route 110 for approx. 1.4 miles  bearing right until you reach a set of lights.  At the stop lights, take a left to another set of lights.  Take a right and follow for .7 miles to Mill Street.  Turn left and follow road into the parking lot and to the pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM SOUTH SHORE&lt;br /&gt;I-93 North through Boston to I-495 North to Exit 52 (Route 110).  Head West on Route 110 for approx. 1.4 miles bearing right until you reach a set of lights.  At the stop lights, take a left to another set of lights.  Take a right and follow for .7 miles to Mill Street.  Turn left and follow road into the parking lot and to the pond&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;8/5/10 Update:  I finally got in touch of the Tribal Council, what I found out is that admission is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adults:  $5.00&lt;br /&gt;Children 4-12:  $3.00&lt;br /&gt;Under 4:  Free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And the activities are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will enjoy:  Intertribal and Demonstration Dancing, Storytelling and Craftmaking in front of the tipi, Traditional and other foods for sale, and the stunning performances by the Tlacopan Aztec Indian Dancers.  Craft vendors will be there selling all types of Native arts and crafts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the Problem we have is not knowing quite where to meet, so once you get there and park, please call the Meetup phone and we will let you know where we are located.  The Meetup phone is:  978-304-2811.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever want to learn about the Native Americans, there way of life, their culture, the meaning of their dances?  Well lets head out to Winnekenni Park in Haverhill to learn their culture and a little bit about the Native Americans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When was the last time you learned about another culture?  Well here is your chance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I do not have all the details on this event at this time, but have a call into the Ma Center for Native American Awareness to get a schedule for the day.  Hopefully making this connection we will be able to get a little &amp;quot;extra&amp;quot; awareness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update the event as I know more, if you think you will be interested in attending please put in your RSVP so that I know that there is interest in this.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have more details that you would like to pass on to us, please feel free to do so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you&lt;br /&gt;Janet &amp;amp; Donna&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284384124000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280192585000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chief Red Blanket Pow wow @ Plug Pond in Winnekeni Park</name><id>14223008</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284307200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/14223008/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/f/f/global_16744095.jpeg</photo_url></item>