<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>89 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351844</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-439-3142 </phone><name>The NonProfit Center </name><city>Boston</city><id>1058586</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057489</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>includes PayPal fee</description><amount>10.6099996567</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Every now and again you reach a point where you feel completely drained by your efforts to create positive change in the world. &lt;strong&gt;Join Socializing for Justice&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;on December 3, 6:00 - 8:30 PM to learn how to refuel so you're in it for the long haul.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;SoJust hosts events that draw progressives of all stripes that share common values but may work on different issues. We create social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections and run a Skillshare Series, hosted by The NonProfit Center*, which increases our individual capacity for movement building.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing - bring your own dinner (microwave and water cooler available)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;6:30-8:30 Training and Q &amp;amp; A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fee: $10-$20 (sliding scale) is split with the trainer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limited space - register ahead of time: &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Credit cards accepted online. Cash only at the door (if space available).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Feeling Burnt Out? Self-Care is a Revolutionary Act!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

This workshop is designed for activists, artists, healers, change agents and YOU. You know how to revolutionize, but do you know how to refuel? We all deserve the respect and care that we are creating on behalf of others. The more present and whole we can be, the more effective we will be in our activist work. In a culture where productivity and profit are valued more than community and caring, self-care is a revolutionary act!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ABOUT OUR PRESENTER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;LeLaina Romero, Ph.D. works at the intersections of social justice and promoting health and well-being. Trained in Counseling Psychology, she has worked with various groups and communities, including LGBTQ people, particularly queer and transgender people of color; diverse people living with HIV/AIDS; and people living in poverty. Currently, she is a postdoctoral clinician at &lt;a href="http://www.themeetingpoint.org"&gt;The Meeting Point&lt;/a&gt; in Jamaica Plain where her work includes individual, relationship, and group therapy as well as workshops such as Heal Yourself, Change the World: Social Justice Begins at Home! She is also a postdoctoral clinician at the Massachusetts College of Art &amp;amp; Design (Mass Art), where she does outreach, counseling, and programming with first generation college students, LGBTQ students, and students of color. She is also a singer and songwriter in progress, and integrates creative and spiritual practices within her healing work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* &lt;a href="http://www.nonprofitcenterboston.org/site/c.ddKGIQNuEmG/b.1363373/k.5381/About_Us__Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt; - The NonProfit Center&lt;/strong&gt; is located one block from South Station at 89 South Street. The Center is accessible through the main lobby to people who have restricted physical abilities.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;__________________________________________________&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this "Movement Moment". Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;SoJust is not a non-profit 501(c)(3). We're a grassroots volunteer-run member-supported cross-issue progressive community that's been growing steadily since August 2006. We have 2100+ members, hosted 130+ events and manage an online hub of progressive events and resources at &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;. If you've benefited from this cross-issue progressive network, please contribute the suggested annual membership fee of $25. You may do this &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/donate"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; or at any of our events. Thank you for helping us continue to provide a space for like-minded progressives of all stripes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison Brill</member_name><member_id>4034719</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jessica Critcher</member_name><member_id>46812122</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355351295000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352035887000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Feeling Burnt Out? Self-Care is a Revolutionary Act!</name><id>89884622</id><duration>9000000</duration><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354575600000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/89884622/</event_url></item>