<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Rich Internet applications (RIAs) are everywhere. With Web businesses like Google and Yahoo! and brick and mortar companies like Harley Davidson and Sherwin Williams embracing RIAs for their online presence, the media buzz is giving way to the reality of a better Internet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adobe has recently contributed AMF support to the Zend Framework, allowing PHP developers to easily build Rich Internet Applications using Flex and Adobe AIR that interact with a PHP backend (see Andi Gutman's blog post today - &lt;a href="http://andigutmans.blogspot.com/2008/07/adobe-to-contribute-amf-support-to-zend.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://andigutmans.bl...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Hoyt, a technical evangelist with Adobe, will give an introduction to Adobe Flex and Adobe AIR, and will walk through how to create a Flex application powered by PHP and the Zend Framework. Working with Zend Studio for Eclipse, and Flex Builder (an Eclipse plugin), Kevin will demonstrate how to build, debug and deploy applications built with Adobe Flex, and how to have these same applications run on the desktop using the Adobe AIR runtime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With this knowledge, developers will be able to easily build rich Internet applications that combine data from PHP and rich media like audio and video into a compelling application.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231977269000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220007047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October User Group:: Flex &amp; the Zend Framework</name><id>8645912</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222900200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/8645912/</event_url></item>