<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Faucher Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03053</zip><lat>42.888906</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Musquash Conservation Area</name><city>Londonderry</city><id>1488899</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.425854</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Musquash Conservation Area: &lt;br /&gt;

 The term Musquash comes from the Algonquin word for muskrat. Today it describes a forest block of over 900 acres in the western part of Londonderry. The area is made up of forested, rolling hills dotted with wetland areas that provide natural habitat for moose, deer, beaver, and painted and Blanding’s turtles to name just a few species. This landscape also provides an enjoyable place for outdoor recreation for the citizens of the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are over 4 different entrances to the Musquash Conservation Area so please use the correct address above for where the hike will start.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to a trail map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://londonderrytrails.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/musquashtrails_2010-final-final-draft.pdf"&gt;PDF &lt;br /&gt;

 file of the Musquash Conservation Area Trail Map&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will do a loop using the White Trail, Ravine Trail, Blue Trail, and Betty Mack Loop to do an approximately 5 mile hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any adult guest you want to bring should sign up on the meetup site as a member so they will be covered by the liability waiver. A minor would need a written waiver signed by a parent or guardian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go a little past 15 Faucher Road and go to the end of the road which ends in a circular cul-de-sac.  Park on the side of the road in the circle.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359222453000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358120593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Musquash Conservation Area - 5 Mile Hike</name><id>99442322</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358694000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/99442322/</event_url></item>