<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Church Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.768665</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-527-5151</phone><name>Hartford Stage</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1001415</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674309</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I'm thinking of going to see this play at Hartford Stage on Friday night.  As of today (Wednesday) they had a lot of tickets left.  Anyone interested in going?  We may have to sit separately but can meet up before and afterwards.  There are various ticket prices.   Sometimes they discount them on the day of the play.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dividing the Estate:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matriarch Stella Gordon is determined not to divide her 100 year old Texas estate, despite her family’s declining wealth and the looming financial crisis. But her three children have another plan. Old resentments and sibling rivalries surface, as the members of this hilariously dysfunctional family go head to head to see who might claim the biggest piece of the pie in Dividing the Estate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A MASTERWORK. A MUST SEE FOR DISCRIMINATING THEATERGOERS.&lt;br /&gt;This production—directed with hair-trigger timing by Michael Wilson—has ripened into an ideally balanced ensemble piece, with acting that matches and magnifies Horton Foote’s slyly and acutely observant writing. As the three children, Penny Fuller and Gerald McRaney are excellent and Hallie Foote plays with true comic genius—it’s hard to think of anyone on a Broadway stage right now who’s funnier. Watching them snipe and spar with different strategic blends of passivity and aggression is great sport.” —The New York Times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“A STUNNER! GORGEOUS ENSEMBLE THEATER.&lt;br /&gt;Dividing the Estate, directed by Michael Wilson, is the best show now playing on Broadway. Mr. Foote is one of America’s greatest playwrights, past or present, but this is only the second of his plays to be performed on Broadway. Go see it and find out what we’ve been missing.” —The Wall Street Journal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“THE THEATRICAL EQUIVALENT OF A PAGE TURNER.” —Bloomberg Radio&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hartfordstage.org/see_a_show/dividing_the_estate" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hartfordstage.org/see_a_show/dividing_the_estate" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hartfordst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet in the lobby prior to the show</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247353611000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246496023000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dividing the Estate </name><id>10784119</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246664700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/10784119/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/8/global_5165560.jpeg</photo_url></item>