<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Sandy Ln</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02889</zip><lat>41.711296</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Warwick Public Library</name><city>Warwick</city><id>716684</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.402734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In 
&lt;em&gt;Dying To Have Known&lt;/em&gt;, filmmaker Steve Kroschel went on a 52-day journey to find evidence to the effectiveness of 
&lt;strong&gt;the Gerson Therapy&lt;/strong&gt; -- a long-suppressed 
&lt;strong&gt;natural CANCER CURE&lt;/strong&gt;. His travels take him across both the Atlantic and the Pacific Oceans, from upstate New York to San Diego to Alaska, from Japan and Holland to Spain and Mexico. In the end, he presents the testimonies of patients, scientists, surgeons and nutritionists who testify to the therapy's efficacy in curing cancer and other degenerative diseases, and presents the hard scientific proof to back up their claims. You will hear from a Japanese medical school professor who cured himself of liver cancer over 15 years ago, a lymphoma patient who was diagnosed as terminal over 50 years ago as well as noted critics of this world-renowned healing method who dismiss it out of hand as "pure quackery." So the question that remains is, " 
&lt;strong&gt;Why is this powerful curative therapy still suppressed, more than 75 years after it was clearly proven to cure degenerative disease?&lt;/strong&gt;"&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decide for yourself after watching this film as we discuss which Federal Agencies and influential Industry Associations we would like to see downsized or discontinued entirely.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachael McIntosh</member_name><member_id>5611356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315403498000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FreedomIsFundamental</urlname><id>1191429</id><group_lat>41.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>FREEDOM IS FUNDAMENTAL Book Club and Discussion Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312683325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cancer Cure?? FREE FILM &amp; conversation about the necessity of Federal Agencies</name><id>28533581</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315348200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FreedomIsFundamental/events/28533581/</event_url></item>