<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday November 15th 6:30-9:30. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Afterwork Mixer returns,  this time we are taking the party to the brand new trendy &amp;amp; stylish Boston Public Lounge located inside the Louis Boston boutique directly across the street from the Arlington Station T stop in Back Bay.  The buzz surrounding Boston Public  has been outstanding, this venue has one of the most impressive wine and beer lists among any other place in the city.  The holidays are right around the corner, this will be one of the last few events of the calendar year,  so please come and join the group as we kickoff the start to another festive weekend in the city!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also if you have not been to any or a few of our events whether an Afterwork Mixer, New Member meetup, or even a nite on the town in the city with the group, I encourage all of you to come this Thursday and meet many of our wonderful members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: Please enter Louis Boston from the Berkeley  St entrance, at arrival please follow the signs to the restaurant.  When entering the restaurant please look for our group near the main bar.   Please look for me upon arriving my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section. I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, with this being Boston's new afterwork hotspot this venue is guaranteed to fill up fast!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation &lt;br /&gt;Green Line to Arlington/Copley &lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to Back Bay &lt;br /&gt;Commuter Rail to Back Bay &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196306750000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194842396000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Afterwork Mixer: The New Boston Public Lounge inside Louis Boston Back Bay </name><id>6724752</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195169400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/6724752/</event_url></item>