<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>560 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.340807</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South End Open Studios Info. Table</name><city>Boston</city><id>761324</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.067441</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The busy fall Open Studios season kicks off with South End Open Studios Sept. 20-21. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the 560 Harrison Ave. info table and wander Harrison  (where most of the studios are located) and surrounding studios for a couple of hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrating 22 years of art in Boston’s vibrant South End&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 20 and Sunday, September 21&lt;br /&gt;11am to 6pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South End Open Studios is your chance to meet over 250 artists…explore work that is both familiar and new to you...purchase work directly from the artist who created it...start your own list of artists you would like to learn more about or visit again after Open Studios.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you have come to South End Open Studios for a number of years or this will be your first visit, you will be impressed by the incredible range of work you will see. Each stop along the self-guided route will introduce you to artists working a in range of media…oils, watercolors, photography, sculpture, jewelry, mixed media, fiber arts, ceramics, wood, glass, and metal as well as other types of visual and performance arts.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a purple flower pin.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cristin</member_name><member_id>603739</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222637253000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221230938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South End Open Studios</name><id>8743808</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221926400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/8743808/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/3/b/global_5477691.jpeg</photo_url></item>