<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>112 ave. McGill</address_1><state>QC</state><zip>h2y 2e5</zip><lat>45.499387</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Studio Zoo Image</name><city>Montreal</city><id>1066578</id><country>ca</country><lon>-73.555000</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>275.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>(This event is organized by &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/members/7474451/"&gt;Frank Simard&lt;/a&gt;; please contact him with any questions.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Montreal, a cosmopolitan city with European overtones, fashion conscious, with vibrant nightlife and fine dining is an ideal location for a weekend of photography and enjoyment.  This shoot is designed to give freedom to the photographer for both fashion and special shoot needs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Studio Zoo Image is reserved for two days, Saturday and Sunday.  Saturday there will be 2-4 models  available for shoots, 10-1, 2-5; Sunday there will be two models available from 11 – 2; 2 – 5PM will be a Special Shoot, the shoot will be an artistic nude shoot.  The specialty models are to be paid by photographers individually or shared by pre-arrangement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday will be a two team arrangement where one team of 2 photographers works in the studio with 2 models and the other makes a tour of Old Montreal with 2 models for local shots in the surrounding historical settings.  The afternoon shoot will be a rotation of models and photographers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday will be a two model morning, studio and local, three photographers.  This will allow some flexibility for those who want to enlist other models for the day for a special shoot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost per photographer is budgeted at $275.  The cost may vary somewhat depending on the number of photographers and the models utilized.  The $275 fee is based on the above description.   Cost of an MUA is not included and is discretionary to the group.   This includes models and the use of the studio but does not include specialty models, lodging, or travel arrangements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the location of the Montreal studio please go to www.studiozooimage.com .  For travel and hotel information please contact &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/members/7474451/"&gt;Frank Simard&lt;/a&gt; at imagepro39@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bert Halstead</member_name><member_id>6804860</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256244758000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers, Models &amp; MUA</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonportraitphotographers</urlname><id>830833</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Portrait Photographers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253058639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Montreal Fashion Shoot Weekend</name><id>11382308</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255183200000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/events/11382308/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/global_10734145.jpeg</photo_url></item>