<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 112 in Passaconaway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>43.993515</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Champney Falls Parking Lot</name><city>Conway</city><id>452208</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.329460</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>April is waterfalls month. Hike to Champney Falls and Mount Chocorua (pronounced &amp;quot;Cho koor' ru wa&amp;quot;) which is said to be one of the most popular hiked and &lt;b&gt;most frequently photographed mountain in the world.  &lt;/b&gt; Don't forget the camera and extra batteries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/e/5/event_1970405.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a easier moderate rated hike which leads to incredibly scenic trails before reaching the treeless 3,500 foot summit with tremendous 360° views. Plus there are 2 lovely waterfalls to visit on the gentle descent to the trailhead. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hikers emerge out of the trees to play on smooth rock ledges with astounding views before reaching the summit with stunning views in every direction.  Looking north is the        Presidential Range including Mt. Washington.  To the west lies the Sandwich Range with Mounts Passaconaway (4,043 ft.), Whiteface (4020') the Tripyramids, with spectacular views of mountain ranges behind more mountain ranges in every direction! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elevation: 3,500 ft.&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 7.6 miles&lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain:  2250 Feet&lt;br /&gt;Book time: approximately 6 hours&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup at Champney Falls Parking Lot on Route 112 in Passaconaway. I-93 to exit 32, left on Rte 112 drive east for a half hour. This parking lot is almost 2 miles east of the Jigger Johnson Campground. On any NH map, or a trail map, when you see Bear Notch Road on your left, drive almost 1 1/2 miles more and park in the huge parking lot on your right.   There is a large sign at the kiosk that reads Champney Falls Trail.  This location is 11.5 miles west of NH Rte 16 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A minimum number of 3 &amp;quot;yes &amp;quot; RSVP's qualifies this as a meetup. Please post RSVP's by 9PM the night before the event. Maybe RSVP's will be considered no shows after this time. Weather conditions will also be posted by 9 PM the night before the hike and hikers will be notified if there is a  change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling encouraged! Share the ride, save gas and meet new friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;40% chance of Rain or weather advisories cancel this hike.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me and my green Escort sedan in the trailhead parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207688963000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><why>I have an extra set of snowshoes and trekking crampons for med-large boots should they be needed. Stabilizers are recommended for all hikes into May this year with this year's record snowfall.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205878907000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Chocorua and Champney Falls. Photo Op Hike!</name><id>7558622</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207488600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7558622/</event_url></item>