<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello All,    &lt;br /&gt;Hope you are all keeping cool!  As you all know, we will continue to host two locations for our summer season Chi Meetups.     &lt;br /&gt;All future meetings (June and onward) will be held in two locations for the summer season.     &lt;br /&gt;I have rec'd several requests from members who would like to attend the Boston Commons  at 11 AM.  &lt;br /&gt;In order to best accommodate everyone as much as possible what I will do is, post  a discussion on the message board. Any members who would like to attend the 1PM session  at the park  can make a note there, in addition to a note in your RSVP!!!! &lt;br /&gt;I believe this was effective for the last meetup. We will hold this setup for the next couple of months until we head back to being indoors only for the fall/winter seasons.   &lt;br /&gt;I believe this should leave enough options for everyone. Those of you who would like to attend the park in the morning then move onto to Doggie day at 1pm are welcome to do so , but PLEASE make a note in the rsvp so that we can keep track of the numbers :)   If anyone has any further questions regarding this please also post them on the message board thread for the Sunday meetup.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Boston Common (near the Boylston T stop/Lowes theater side)   11:00AM and 1:00 PM ( leave a rsvp on the message board if you plan to go to the park at 1pm)  &lt;br /&gt;2. DOGGIE DAY PLAYCENTER (Tremont Street, South end, Boston ...our usual location  1:00PM ONLY!!!!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, in other news, as many of you already know Charolette  recently rescued Shenzi , a chihuahua and is now in the care of foster parents....Shenzi unfortunately will need surgery after all, to find out more about her please see the following links. thanks again for all your support.  &lt;br /&gt;online at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ahimsahave.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ahimsahave...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;To make a donation:   &lt;br /&gt;check/money order to:  &lt;br /&gt;Ahimsa Haven Animal Rescue  &lt;br /&gt;287 Spring Street  &lt;br /&gt;Winchendon, MA. 01475  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This is an amazing organization which last year cared for over 1,000 animals. It is all volunteers and no one takes a salary.   &lt;br /&gt;Your tax-deductible donation helps to save animals? lives and find loving homes for them.  &lt;br /&gt;THANKS TO ALL OF YOU! - Charlotte&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://chihuahua.meetup.com/99/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3256897"&gt;http://chihuahua.meet...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THere is also still time to join our CHi team for the walk for animal , to sponsor the MSPCA in September:  &lt;br /&gt;PLEASE VISIT.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mspca.org/.."&gt;http://www.mspca.org/...&lt;/a&gt;.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the team page for Happy Tails     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mspca.org/.."&gt;http://www.mspca.org/...&lt;/a&gt;.     &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190306488000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>58</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183918190000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua August Meetup</name><id>5992095</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186930800000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/5992095/</event_url></item>