<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>near Medford Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.403164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Private Home</name><city>Medford</city><id>6860822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103050</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Everything in this Universe is vibrational energy and you attract those things that you are in vibrational resonance with. In simplest terms, there are three main states of vibration that you can resonate at. The lowest is the state of unhappiness. In this state you feel depressed, overwhelmed, bored, and/or angry. Your world is full of darkness, and that is what you tend to create. The middle is the state of monotony. In this state, you operate on automatic pilot and do things because you should do them. When you operate predominantly at this frequency, you tend to create more of the same old thing. The highest is the state of joy! At this frequency, you feel fully alive and on fire. You are excited about everything that comes your way, and you are in the flow. Your world is full of sunshine, and good cheer. You operate from inspiration, and desire. When you operate at this frequency, you naturally attract your heart&lt;span&gt;’&lt;/span&gt;s desires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notice, your feelings are your vibrational energy. It is your feelings that attract your experiences. The more you experience positive feelings the higher your vibration. Higher vibrations and feelings is the medium by which your desires will manifest more freely. The more positive feelings you can experience about yourself and your desires, the easier and faster you&lt;span&gt;’&lt;/span&gt;ll experience your desires spontaneously manifesting into your world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please join us as we will focus on understanding vibrational energy, in order to tune-up our own vibrations and attract more of what our heart desires.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Whenever you feel good, you are in vibrational harmony with your desires.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ellen Sklaver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Motivational Coach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anyone joining us for the first time Please Call&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;617-750-4830&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ellen</member_name><member_id>9941060</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336101350000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>northofbostonlawofattraction</urlname><id>567480</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The North-of-Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335277826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Understanding your Vibrational Energy</name><id>61907792</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335999600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/northofbostonlawofattraction/events/61907792/</event_url></item>