<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>In July 1968, Miles Davis happened to listen in on a performance by jazz bassist Dave Holland at London's Ronnie Scott's club. Impressed by what he saw, Davis asked Holland to move to New York and join his band. Holland spent the next two years touring with Davis, and also contributing to the classic Davis albums In a Silent Way and Bitches Brew. After a tenure with Davis, Holland left the group and, together with Chick Corea, Anthony Braxton, and Barry Altschul, formed the group Circle. Holland continued to work with many notables in the jazz field during the 1970s, including Theolonius Monk, Stan Getz, and Sam Rivers. In the 1980s, Holland was part of several jazz combos, including a quintet featuring Steve Coleman, an artist in residence at NEC in October 2004, as well as taking on full time faculty duties right here at the Conservatory which later awarded him an honorary degree. Today, Holland continues to tour with jazz legends such as Herbie Hancock and Pat Metheny, and also perform, on Grammy-nominated albums such as Joe Henderson's So Near, So Far and Jack DeJohnette's Parallel Realities Question and Answer. His latest incarnation, The Dave Holland Quintet, recorded the album Points of View for ECM in 1998.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Holland is a 2006 Grammy Award winner of Best Large Jazz Ensemble Album for Overtime by the Dave Holland Big Band.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New England Conservatory's Brown Hall is located at 30 Gainsborough St.  near the Symphony T stop on the Green E line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 7:30 inside the hall. Look for Nate holding the red and white jazz.meetup.com sign. If people are up for it, we can go out for drinks afterwards at the nearby Tiger Lily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://concerts.newenglandconservatory.edu/index.php?Date_Year=2006&amp;amp;Date_Month=02&amp;amp;Date_Day=16" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://concerts.newenglandconservatory.edu/index.php?Date_Year=2006&amp;amp;Date_Month=02&amp;amp;Date_Day=16" target="_blank"&gt;http://concerts.newen...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540068000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonjazz</urlname><id>87187</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Jazz Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1138017739000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Jazz February Meetup</name><id>4839302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1140136200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonjazz/events/4839302/</event_url></item>