<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Greetings Goddesses,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As was mentioned in my introduction to all of you several weeks ago, I had created the 3Cs (3 of Cups) women's support group last January to be a vehicle of emotional growth, support and ultimately positive change in the lives of its members, using magical techniques to initiate that change.  It is my desire to invite more women into the circle next year and introduce new means of initiating transformation in our lives such as Abraham-Hicks, NLP, chaos magick, mantra, meditation, etc..  I would like to hear from you, in an informal setting, your desires, hopes and ideas.  This is also a great way for people to connect with one other and foster sisterhood.  What better way to do for bonding between women to take place than over food!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I invite you to come and eat with us at Cafe Luna. (yes, I was drawn to this place because of the name, but I hear their brunch fare is quite good) If for whatever reason, you are unable to attend the brunch, please feel free to contact me separately and offer your thoughts and suggestions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI - Cafe Luna does not take reservations and appears to be popular with the locals, which is why I selected 10 a.m. - when it opens - as a brunch meeting time (Believe me, I am not an early riser on the weekends!)  So please make plans to arrive on time as I cannot ensure that you will be seated with us once we get a table.  Also please be sure to bring sufficient cash (they accept cards as well) to cover the cost of your meal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regular 3Cs meetings will start up again in early 2011.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blessings,&lt;br /&gt;Nelly (Bennu-Meshkenet)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291577709000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Goddess</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>goddess-327</urlname><id>1289522</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Goddess Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289968016000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Goddesses/3Cs Meet &amp; Greet Brunch at Cafe Luna</name><id>15473802</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291474800000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/goddess-327/events/15473802/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/5/global_19700149.jpeg</photo_url></item>