<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2926 Fairfield Ave # 3</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06605</zip><lat>41.156593</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Acoustic Cafe</name><city>Bridgeport</city><id>6220792</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.227837</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Go see Salsa band Mikata live, including NHCer Olivia!&amp;nbsp; Olivia will Host this meetup so you can meet up with her either before or after her performance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what Olivia had to say about the Act:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"So, although I'm not technically an organizer, I'm hosting! Woo-Hoo! You can find me hanging out with a trumpet in my hand from 8 until 9pm, then I will be on the stage playing trumpet until our set is done, then I'll be hanging out some more. &amp;nbsp;Mikata is a Salsa/Latin Jazz Band (I play trumpet with them, and it's a REALLY tight group - high level of musicianship) performing April 5 at Acoustic Cafe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a $5 cover charge, plenty of room to dance or just groove in your chair with a beverage. There will be a FREE DANCE LESSON. &amp;nbsp;This is what their website says: Small cafe tables, dim lighting, funky wall art, an intimate vibe, and a full bar make the Cafe reminiscent of a NYC Greenwich Village night club. The Acoustic Cafe has recently won "Best Place to hear Local Music", "Best Open Mic", and "Best Place to Hear Alternative Music" by Fairfield County Weekly's reader poll. Come see, hear and feel it for yourself."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If it's before/after her performance look for Olivia, it's a relatively small place and she'll have her Trumpet with her.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olivia</member_name><member_id>34106652</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333760690000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331916263000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Salsa Band: Mikata at Acoustic Cafe in Bridgeport</name><id>56615692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333670400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/56615692/</event_url></item>