<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>USNH</name><city>Hamden</city><id>180814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. John Hooper, president of HUUmanists, will give an expanded version of his part of the presentation he gave with past president Dr. David Schafer at this year's General Assembly of the Unitarian Universalist Association.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#65279;About his talk, John tells us: &amp;ldquo;Naturalists have taken a leadership role in celebrating the awesome epic of biological evolution. Humanists have celebrated the shared human experience of being alive and the inherent worth and dignity of all living human beings. Defending human freedom and drawing on the revelations of science (without resorting to supernatural hypotheses), both humanists and naturalists seek to continuously improve our objective understanding of the universe and our place in it. Exciting new&amp;nbsp; scientific studies are leading to new revelations about the nature of human experience itself. This nascent &amp;lsquo;naturalizing of experience&amp;rsquo; provides a unique opportunity for celebrating a &amp;lsquo;modern synthesis&amp;rsquo; of humanism and naturalism that requires absolutely no supernatural considerations.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Hooper is the immediate past Chair of the Board ofTrustees of the Unitarian Universalist congregation in Westport, CT. Having previously served as president of the Unitarian UniversalistReligious Naturalists (UURN), he is currently president of the Association of Unitarian Universalist Humanists (HUUmanists) and a Board Member of The Humanist Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start with twenty minutes of coffee and conversation at 7:30 p.m. The main talk will follow announcements and a brief report on the recent FFRF conference in Hartford at 7:50 PM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will most probably be in the Social Hall near the main entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>richard.s</member_name><member_id>1140524</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Siddall</member_name><member_id>1140632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322000456000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317144084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Meeting: A Non-theistic Modern Synthesis of Humanism and Naturalism</name><id>35167542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321921800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/35167542/</event_url></item>