<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be a slow walk up to the peak where the Castle Craig is located just north of Hubbard Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will It Be Raining:  Oh Yeh....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok here is what was planned:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will see what else is up at the top, spend some time socializing up there too....so bring water, or your other favourite beverage, a snack or two, we can make dinner plans with who ever is interested at a local eatery to finish off the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what i would like to do:&lt;br /&gt;Meet there at that start location anyway..so you can see where it is.. Then go have lunch at the GREAT WALL chineese food buffet, (its inexpensive and very close) or if someone else has a good suggestion im open.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then go to the Goviena Vinyard for the rest of the afternoon and throw off the people on the table next to the fire place,&lt;br /&gt;I like that table area... and watch the Rain come down and just enjoy the wine and company...&lt;br /&gt;So there, Im not wimping out, just finding something else that will make the afternoon go by.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;Castle Craig in Meriden Ct.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt 691 East: Get off at exit 5. End of ramp turn left onto Rt 71 North. Go 1 &amp;amp; a half miles &amp;amp; turn left onto Butler St. Take Butler St to first intersection &amp;amp; turn left onto Park Dr. Hike starts  a half mile down the road  where a few big cement blocks are placed in the road to stop traffic to the top, Park on the street sides. &lt;br /&gt;From Rt 691 West; the best way is to Get off at exit 4 &amp;amp; get back on the East bound side. Get off at exit 5.  Then follow the above directions.&lt;br /&gt;(this just avoids the traffic at the mall and the odd roads around the mall).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1176913063000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1175995789000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk up to Castle Craig in Meriden ?.. Back Up Plan</name><id>5648624</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1176656400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5648624/</event_url></item>