<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>129 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.459202</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Concord Free Public Library</name><city>Concord</city><id>9038392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.353310</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our next book will be &lt;span&gt;The Inner Art of Vegetarianism: Spiritual Practices for Body and Soul by Carol J. Adams&lt;/span&gt; About the book: In her beautifully composed and thoughtful new book, author and activist Carol Adams explores the inner life of spiritual growth with the outer life of practical compassion. She shows how the reasons for becoming a vegetarian (to promote health, care for other animals, and express concern for the environment) are deeply wedded to spiritual practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adams reveals how the practice of creating mindfulness and disciplining the mind meshes with becoming an activist for nonviolence, and shows how in our busy and stressed-out world it is essential to sustain and replenish the soul through spiritual discipline. Adams discusses breath awareness, meditation, yoga, journaling, and dreamwork as examples of how to keep true to yourself and your beliefs, maintain your mental equilibrium, and prepare truly delicious meals with thoughfulness and care. This is an essential book for all those who wish to have their soul nourished and follow the spiritual path of vegetarianism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the Trustees Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361757473000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358301527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club Discussion: The Inner Art of Vegetarianism by Carol J. Adams</name><id>99812632</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361732400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/99812632/</event_url></item>