<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Because of Thanksgiving, our November Meetup will actually be held on Thursday, December 1st. We'll meet at our regular hangout, Chaibo in Fitchburg, and discuss Unaccustomed Earth by Jhumpa Lahiri. Take a break from all the holiday craziness and have dessert or coffee with us as we chat about the book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of Unaccustomed Earth by an Amazon reviewer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eight stories are so intricately woven with their words and themes that each in itself is a beautiful work of art, and yet together, form the basis of a masterpiece. Former author of &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0006551793/ref=cm_cr_asin_lnk"&gt;Interpreter of Maladies&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0618733965/ref=cm_cr_asin_lnk"&gt;The Namesake (movie tie-in edition)&lt;/a&gt;, Lahiri's carrying on her success with this new bunch. The book starts with the story named after the book, a story about a Bengali woman named Ruma and her father who comes to visit her from Pennsylvania. Cultures and expectations collide as these two virtual strangers learn to exist with each other without the familiar glue of her mother, who passed away only months before. A garden, her mixed race son, and a secret love, permeate the layers of this opening story that literally leave you breathless by stories end. Similar themes are woven through the other seven stories, some which I liked more than others, but all of them written with such scope and craft.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Reading a story written by Lahiri is like sitting in a well ordered, immaculate living room, with a rich, fragrant onion sitting in front of you. As you delve into the story, you peel back the layers of the onion, and the exactitude and preciseness of her stories marvel, and the scent of the onion, not bitter or harsh, but rich and alluring, fill that perfect room, so much so that by the end, all of yours senses are heightened, and you may possibly have tears in your eyes.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;After just reading the first story, I told five people of this marvelous new book, and highly recommend you to that if you want to marvel in the worlds created by Lahiri, this is the perfect place to start.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be sitting at the first set of comfy couches by the door. See you there!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322875584000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320620881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion – Unaccustomed Earth by Jhumpa Lahiri</name><id>40195752</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322784000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/40195752/</event_url></item>