<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Sorry about changing the details again, but just finalized the time with Todd from MESDA so it looks like everything is good to go. Please RSVP or decline when you know if you can make it or not, it helps out a lot. Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the meeting topics, we have to cover some of the MESDA stuff such as setting up managers and getting all that stuff going. Again, I'm looking for volunteers here that will be able to help out. None of the tasks are very time consuming but we do need 3 people for manager types. If you are interested please let me know! Would be great to get this stuff out of the way quickly in the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As far as Ruby topics go I was thinking about covering the Active Record design pattern, and the ActiveRecord module that was writting for Rails, but can be used in any Ruby project. Also hope to go over any project ideas and get things rolling for the next meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are unfamiliar with the Westbrook and are unsure where the MESDA offices are please let me know. I'll do my best to give some more details. It is fairly easy to find however, and is a large brick building with with a big sign out front.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nick Stuart</member_name><member_id>2436503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540132000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ruby programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meruby</urlname><id>213431</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>The Portland Maine Ruby Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1141952741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portland Maine Ruby April Meetup</name><id>4872202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1146607200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meruby/events/4872202/</event_url></item>