<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Back ON THE ROAD: A Fifty-Year Retrospective  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In honor of the fiftieth anniversary of the publication of Jack Kerouac's On the Road, Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome John Leland, author of Why Kerouac Matters; Joyce Johnson, author of the award-winning Minor Characters: A Beat Memoir (and Kerouac's former girlfriend); and others for a discussion of the Beat classic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Why Kerouac Maters: The Lessons of On the Road (They're Not What You Think), Leland argues that On the Road still matters because at its core it is a book full of lessons about how to grow up. Leland?s focus is on Sal Paradise, the Kerouac alter ego, who has always been overshadowed by his fictional running buddy Dean Moriarty. Leland shows how On the Road is a primer for male friendship and the cultivation of traditional family values, and contends that the stereotype of the two wild and crazy guys obscures the novel's core themes of the search for atonement, redemption, and divine revelation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Minor Characters, Johnson portrays her relationship with Kerouac with wit, love, and a cool, critical eye. The Washington Post called Minor Characters &amp;quot;the safe-deposit box that contains the last, precious scrolls of the New York '50s.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets may be purchased at Harvard Book Store or over the phone with a credit card at 617-661-1515. Please note the $5 tickets may be redeemed for $5 off a single item at the event or at Harvard Book Store for one month following the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://diningout.meetup.com/362/calendar/6202414/"&gt;Discussion Afterwards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189289519000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187451110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kerouac Retrospective</name><id>6202389</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189116000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/6202389/</event_url></item>