<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Actual Start Time:  1:25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The destiny of a young woman caught between love and the law of the underworld is the subject of this riveting drama, as tense as 4&lt;i&gt; Months, 3 Weeks and 2 Days&lt;/i&gt;. Lorna (Arta Dobroshi), a young Albanian woman living in Belgium, has her sights set on opening a snack bar with her boyfriend, Sokol (Alban Ukaj). To do this, she becomes an accomplice in a diabolical plan devised by mobster Fabio (Fabrizio Rongione), marrying a lovelorn junkie, Claudy (Jérémie Renier, &lt;i&gt;Summer Hours&lt;/i&gt;), to acquire Belgian citizenship. However, she is then ordered to marry a Russian mafioso who's ready to pay hard cash so he, too, can get his hands on those vital Belgian citizenship papers. Fabio plans to get rid of Claudy—but will Lorna remain silent? &lt;b&gt;Winner of the Best Screenplay Award at the 2008 Cannes Film Festival&lt;/b&gt;. Written and directed by brothers Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne, acclaimed makers of the award-winning features &lt;i&gt;L'Enfant, The Son, Rosetta&lt;/i&gt; and&lt;i&gt; La Promesse. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sonyclassics.com/lornassilence/" target="_blank"&gt;Lorna's Silence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the New York Times Critics Pick Review:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Lorna’s Silence” is engrossing and powerful, which may be just another way of saying it’s a film written and directed by Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne, Belgian brothers whose highly recognizable, frequently imitated style has won them recognition nearly everywhere in the world. . . Their fictional features, fixtures of the Cannes Film Festival (where two, “&lt;i&gt;Rosetta&lt;/i&gt;” and&lt;i&gt; “The Child,”&lt;/i&gt; have won the top prize, in 1999 and 2005), are similar enough in method and mood that “Lorna’s Silence” is as good a place as any to make or renew their acquaintance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we will gather at the front of the theater, and have a friendly discussion at Tommy Doyle's where there will be no Silence, whether Lorna joins us, or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time is approximate.  This event will be updated when the actual start time is posted.  Also, as this is opening night for a highly acclaimed film, advanced purchase of tickets is highly recommended:&lt;a href="http://www.landmarktheatres.com/Market/Boston/Boston_Frameset.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Kendall Square Theater Tix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be silently holding a red Meetup side at the front of the theater at the end of the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249120315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lorna's Silence</name><id>11006948</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250442900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11006948/</event_url></item>