<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Somerset Parkway (bypass)</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.760000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crowne Plaza</name><city>Nashua</city><id>318581</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.470000</lon></venue><fee><label>Varies with food choice</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Sunday, September 23 The NH Center for Constitutional Studies will be holding its annual Constitution Day Celebration at and Dinner, with events and exhibits starting at 12 noom and ending at 8:30 PM. What better place to promote Ron Paul?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be held at the Crowne Plaza in Nashua N.H., which is in Hillsborough County. Therefore I will be manning a table there inside during the day of the celebration. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are workshops and displays all day with speakers and demonstrations during the dinner. This is always a fun and educational event attended by like-minded people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View more details on their website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhccs.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhccs.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fee varies depending on what you have to eat, but it covers all 4 events that happen during the day and the maximum is $55.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we have a table of 8, the exhibit table will be free.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;from Corie Whalen of teh Boston RonPaul meetup:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to our prescence functioning as a way to promote Ron Paul and show that he has support, we are also making this event a celebration of Constitution Day, which is officially on Monday the 17th. Flyers and posters drawing parallels between Ron Paul and the Founders will be printed up, displayed and distributed. Any other Constitutionally themed messages and images are a must for this event, so get creative! If nothing else, please try to spare some ink to print and distribute this image: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://highrankings.com/corie/saveconstitution.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://highrankings.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a good opportunity to share with our friends from Boston, Leicester, Worcester, SE Mass, RI, Connecticutt etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190736651000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187809893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Constitution Day Celebration and Dinner</name><id>6225817</id><headcount>300</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190563200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6225817/</event_url></item>