<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 102</address_2><address_1>15 Channel Center Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210 </zip><lat>42.345477</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 439-3900 </phone><name>Elevin Studios </name><city>Boston </city><id>1274845</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051438</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Its always nice to see local fashion professionals succeed. When you hear from somebody else who started at the bottom and worked their way to the top, it can very inspiring. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To that end, we have decided to set up a tour of Elevin Studios. Never heard of Elevin Studios? Well, it is the national photography business owned by Eric Levin, one of Boston's Top Fashion and Celebrity Photographers. He will be opening up his studio for us to see and setting aside some time to talk with us about what its like run a successful business and answer questions. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;His Bio is below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;It was 2003, Eric Levin had a punk rock band and no money. On a whim he decided to sell art prints on the side of Newbury Street. Little did anyone know it was the start of something much bigger.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soon after, a local magazine editor noticed the new, young street artist and offered him a job shooting the Boston based magazine, Slammed. Before long, Eric had a few covers under his belt, so he tried his luck at other magazines. Within a year, he was photographing cover and editorial spreads for almost every magazine in the city. He won first prize for the New England Press Association -- five years in a row -- and picked up another award from the Boston Society of architects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, Eric operates his own national photography business and studio where he specializes in portrait, fashion and celebrity photography. His subjects include Morgan Freeman, Kanye West and Rihanna for clients such as Clear Channel, Pepsico and Conde Nast.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you are a photographer, model, stylist, designer, or fashion entrepreneur, this is a tour you should not miss. I encourage those who are free to stop by. Eric knows everyone there is to know in the Boston Fashion scene and might also be able to offer you some tips to take your work or business to the next level. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please try to arrive no later than 6:15pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Ranere</member_name><member_id>975035</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jamall Oluokun</member_name><member_id>6487580</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Prithi Pais</member_name><member_id>7208428</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shelley Dery</member_name><member_id>9760349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277421287000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273767673000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tour of Elevin Studios</name><id>13473254</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274825700000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/13473254/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/f/global_9836927.jpeg</photo_url></item>