<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;We will not be meeting at Microsoft this month due to weather.  Instead, please find us at our Google Hangout: &lt;a href="https://plus.google.com/u/0/events/crund2ejoc9jp8gqouss19uqu4k"&gt;https://plus.google.com/u/0/events/crund2ejoc9jp8gqouss19uqu4k&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Google Hangout: (for everyone)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All You Ever Wanted to Know About Automattic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Erick Hitter (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ethitter/"&gt;@ethitter&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, a lot has been written about Automattic, Inc.'s distributed workforce, hiring process, and company culture. Despite the coverage, the company behind Gravatar, VaultPress, Polldaddy, and WordPress.com is still a mystery to many in the WordPress community. If you've ever wondered how the company started, how we manage a workforce spread across 26 countries, or what relationship we have with the open-source WordPress project, this talk is for you. Have questions about our services? I'll do my best to answer those as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Erick Hitter is a Design Engineer with Automattic, the company behind WordPress.com, Gravatar, Polldaddy, and more. As part of Team Custom, he helps create awesome features that let WordPress.com users tailor sites to their personalities with more than just a great theme. He was formerly a web developer with Oomph, Inc., where he specialized in complex WordPress implementations for high-traffic sites, including several on the WordPress.com VIP platform. Erick has created a number of plugins available from the official repository, including WP Print Friendly, View All Posts Pages, and Taxonomy Dropdown Widget, as well as the WordPress.com VIP External Permalinks and View All Posts Pages plugins.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The following session&lt;/strong&gt; will be rescheduled for a future meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;An intro to Inclusive Web Design with WordPress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;By Mark Sadecki (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/cptvitamin/"&gt;@cptvitamin&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;So you have yourself a Wordpress site and are wondering if your site is accessible to *everyone* regardless of their ability. Can a blind person access your site using a screen reader? Can a paraplegic easily navigate your site with a "wand" or "sip-and-puff" device? What's a screen reader? What's a sip-and-puff device? Do you have an accessible theme, but are worried the content you or your staff are creating with Wordpress is not accessible? Is your theme accessible? What does accessibility even mean? This presentation hopes to answer all of these questions and then some. If time permits, we can even demonstrate how a blind user navigates the web.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mark Sadecki. Mark is a Web Accessibility Consultant and Webmaster at The Carroll Center for the Blind who has been building accessible web interfaces for more than a dozen years. While he loves the meticulous nature of evaluating and remediating other peoples' code, he enjoys training web developers on the nuances of inclusive interfaces the most.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #c0c0c0"&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>https://plus.google.com/u/0/events/crund2ejoc9jp8gqouss19uqu4k</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Eng</member_name><member_id>9694496</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Bishop</member_name><member_id>13435843</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351595375000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>73</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346346350000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BWPM Oct2012: ONLINE! [see details below]</name><id>80097882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351551600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/80097882/</event_url></item>