<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Causeway St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364704</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Harp</name><city>Boston</city><id>429530</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>When:&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 1, 2007, 5:30 PM 20071201T223000Z &lt;br /&gt;Where: starting at the &lt;br /&gt;The Harp&lt;br /&gt;85 Causeway Street &lt;br /&gt;, MA 02114&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info/Map&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;The pub crawl has a theme, the twelve pubs of Christmas so the aim is to make it to 12 pubs, a little optimistic but I think we can do it. In order to achieve this we will be spending about 1/2 an hour at each pub, maybe an hour at the fist to allow for everyone to meet. We will be starting at The Harp near north station, heading down Canal Street and across to the Bell and Hand and Faneuil Hall area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will visit the pubs in this rough order and I will email my mobile number out to those who rsvp so if anyone is late or gets lost they can call me. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting at The Harp, McGanns, The Fours bar and Grill, Boston Beer works, The Grand Canal, Bell in Hand, Green dragon, The Tap, Hennessey of Boston, Purple Shamrock, Ned divines, Black Horse tavern. Happy for suggestions and I'm sure the plan will change as we get a few drinks in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOU WILL NEED A MASS ID OR YOUR PASSPORT. YOU NOT GET INTO MANY PUBS UNLESS &lt;br /&gt;YOU HAVE A MASS DRIVERS LICENSE OR YOUR PASSPORT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your friends along, this will be a fun night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers Amy and the meetup group&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>3466832</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196905982000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Larrikins</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aussie-145</urlname><id>222356</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Aussie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193176320000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pub Crawl - The Twelve Pubs of Christmas</name><id>6604717</id><headcount>46</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196548200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aussie-145/events/6604717/</event_url></item>