<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Arlington</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.415130</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Minuteman Trail</name><city>Arlington</city><id>583778</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.176620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It looks like the weather is going to be nice Tuesday.  Let's meet to skate the Minuteman Trail.  We'll go at a leisurely pace.  I'll be on the trail behind Not Your Average Joe's.  On the trail directly down from the parking lot driveway is a sign on a stand with information about Arlington Center's history.  You can see it in the photo above.  I'll post a Meetup sign on it.  As long as the Meetup sign is there I'm around.  I may be at my car or sitting on the bench-like rock putting on my skates.  Just wait by the sign.  We'll wait until about &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;6:40 p.m.&lt;/span&gt; (not 7:10 p.m.) or so and then take off.  If you choose not to post a photo of yourself, please be aware that I will not walk up to random people on skates and ask if they are with the Meetup, you'll will need to approach me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather prediction changes, i.e. rain or cold, I will cancel and schedule for another day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dee&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not your Average Joe's is at 645 Mass Ave in Arlington.  Next to it is a driveway to the parking lot.  We'll meet on the trail accessible from the parking lot.  I'll post a Meetup sign on the sign stand in the picture.  (Driveway is in background.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214067557000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>So far the weather looks like it's going to be nice.</why><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212276062000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Minuteman Trail skate</name><id>8050993</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212532200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/8050993/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/c/global_4305148.jpeg</photo_url></item>