<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This month we'll continue our open door policy for dream sharing, which has been so very valuable for our community of dreamers.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Carl will present some ideas for how to interpret the characters in our dreams.&amp;nbsp; Dream Dictionaries can give us some good starting points for what places and things may symbolize, but what about people?&amp;nbsp; You can't just look up Aunt Mabel or that ex from high school, except in the most general of ways as a role.&amp;nbsp; Dream characters make it clear just how very personal and rich with emotional associations are our own dreams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some traditions say to interpret all characters as sides of yourself, which can be a good place to start, but this excludes the fabulous mystical possibility that we really do dream of each other as well as nonphysical beings and higher friends. In fact, dreams are most useful to guide our lives when we don't just dream about ourselves, but see how we are interacting with the hidden unspoken energies&amp;nbsp;of the actual relationships that are important to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carl has many years of experience in navigating the continuum between sides of ourselves and aspects of others that can and do show up in dreams, so he'll present some perspectives and examples that could help you crack the riddle of recurring dream figures. Hints: someone you know in a dream often isn't that person, but someone in that role energetically, and how much it is you or another person can change from night to night, depending on what you're working on during the day, with clues to help you sort out possibilities&amp;nbsp;including boundary symbols,&amp;nbsp;sidekick characters,&amp;nbsp;replays, and how much you can see and feel from the other's&amp;nbsp;position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, you're welcome to bring a dream to work on, or just come to listen to other people's processing. Dream sharing is never required to attend, only encouraged. Sharing dreams in a group provides&amp;nbsp;a rich validating resource&amp;nbsp;to understand the many layers and facets of subconscious communication. It is always helpful to gather together and share dreams with others, to get ideas on what our dreams tell us about ourselves and our lives, and what they foreshadow of the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come, share, explore, learn, and grow with the knowledge and wisdom of our bold and adventurous dream explorers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer Deerheart before attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For directions and other information about location please visit the &amp;lt;a href="&lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com"&gt;http://www.swedenborgchapel.com"&amp;gt;Cambridge&lt;/a&gt; Swedenborg Chapel&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; website.&amp;nbsp; There's a little parking lot to use on the side that usually won't fill up for our meetings.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323825697000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322763559000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Interpreting Characters in Dreams &amp; Dream Sharing</name><id>43041522</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323820800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/43041522/</event_url></item>