<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>401 Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.343983</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 424-6111</phone><name>Regal Fenway 13</name><city>Boston</city><id>721114</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102784</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've received the following invitation. Please RSVP if you're interested so I can provide them with a count and I'll see if I can get the tickets to you, even it appears a print out of this invite/e-mail might be enought:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello! I am contacting you on behalf of Summit Entertainment regarding their upcoming film, PUSH. We are having a complimentary advance screening in the Boston area and would love to invite your group to attend. This screening will take place on Tuesday, February 3 at 7:00 p.m. at the Boston Common Theatre.  I have included a synopsis and information about the film below for your convenience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would be delighted if you would distribute passes to your members. If this is acceptable to you, please respond with an address where we can send them. We also would appreciate you including to whose attention the passes should be directed. &lt;br /&gt;Please note that seating at this screening is not guaranteed and is subject to availability.  It is strongly advised that you and/or your members arrive early to ensure a seat.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Screening details are as follows:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Boston Common Theatre&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, February 3rd&lt;br /&gt;7:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;US Theatrical release:  February 6, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Director:   Paul McGuigan &lt;br /&gt;Writer:    David Bourla &lt;br /&gt;Cast:    Chris Evans, Dakota Fanning, Camilla Belle, Djimon&lt;br /&gt;Hounsou &lt;br /&gt;Producers:   Bruce Davy, William Vince, Glenn Williamson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A riveting action-thriller, PUSH burrows deep into the deadly world of psychic espionage where artificially enhanced paranormal operatives have the ability to move objects with their minds, see the future, create new realities and kill without ever touching their victims. Nick Gant (Chris Evans) and Cassie Holmes (Dakota Fanning), are among a group of unique individuals who have inherited and developed special psychic abilities that originated from experiments conducted by the Nazi regime during World War II. They find themselves on the run from Agent Henry Carver (Djimon Hounsou) and his troops, part of a clandestine government agency determined to hunt them down to harness their powers for evil.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christian Loidl</member_name><member_id>1035154</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233936743000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232148223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PUSH Movie Screening</name><id>9540137</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233705600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/9540137/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/f/global_3081279.jpeg</photo_url></item>