<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update 8/21/2009:&lt;/b&gt;Gentleman, our colors shall be Blue, for we fight on the side of the Revolution! I have received an important letter from General Washington. It reads:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Greetings fellow colonials,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The king has refused our demands and thus, you have been drafted along with 450 other soldiers into the Boston Minutemen, fighting alongside your countrymen!  We shall put those Tories in their place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;New Announcements:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Every soldier is now asked to bring 2 filled water balloons&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;Specific Army Meetup Location:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/colonialsmeetup" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly/colonia...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;1:30PM Sharp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Uniform Color:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Blue shirt of any sort&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Necessary Supplies&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 filled water balloons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Water Gun (empty upon arrival)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Backpack&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;At least 2 two-liter water bottles full of water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;One bottle of bubbles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Weather Intelligence&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;War is hell!  There might be a bit of rain tomorrow, but this battle is taking place regardless!  You can bet our countrymen never gave up due to a little bit of precipitation. All our past events have had record number of participants, and two of them happened during blizzards.  We are Bostonians, we never negotiate with bad weather. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Expect an all-out battle,  we shall see you on the field.  If this be treason, make the most of it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With sincerest regards,&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;General Washington&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Company Officer Commander&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Boston Minutemen&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://misteriosos.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://misteriosos.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again, the secret location has been revealed! &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/colonialsmeetup" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly/colonia...&lt;/a&gt; ... the Colonials meeting point is at the foot of the bridge. We need to be there at 1:30 pm sharp, at the foot of the bridge on the far corner of Clarendon and Storrow Drive. That's when we start marching to fight the British. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet up at &lt;i&gt;1:00 pm&lt;/i&gt; at the site. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and an ORANGE backpack. He'll be casually holding a red MEETUP sign, trying not to look like a chauffer. An assistant organizer, Amy Hughes, made up rolls of red MEETUP stickers. He'll be handing 'em out so we can distinguish our Nerds from the other nerds around us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rain shouldn't be coming until tomorrow evening I think. Care to meet up for lunch? I was thinking we could all grab lunches beforehand and meet up at 12:00 noon at the Hatch Shell on Mugar Way &amp;amp; Storrow Dr, Boston, MA&amp;#8206; and walk over to the location at 12:50 pm. If there is an excessive amount of water coming from the sky, with a risk of soggy sandwiches, T.J. will probably just eat somewhere beforehand. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update 8/17/2009:&lt;/b&gt; I warned Banditos Misteriosos that we have 30 - 40 people coming to their Water Gun fightand I don't yet have everyone's email address...  and they said it is fine! I don't have to collect email addresses from people anymore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Care to attend? Banditos Misteriosos will be sending out me an email what color team we are on (the Red Shirt team or the Blue Shirt team) by Friday at 8:00 pm and the location of the water gun fight. I'll then update the sign-up sheet about what is our team color, the location of the field of battle (I love saying that!) and I'll pick a place we can all just drop-in for lunch at around 12:00 noon in some food court and socialize before the battle and where we can hook up with the 1:00 pm people who are meeting us near the secret location. Once I have all this information I'll update the site and send out an email letting people know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Er, I need to go pick up a backpack somewhere to carry the extra &amp;quot;ammunition&amp;quot; and a dry change of clothes I can store in a plastic bag. Oh, and I'll need to keep my iPhone in a zip lock bag. Can't get that thingie wet! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, once again, if you are a MAYBE, feel free to just drop in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be leading us Nerds into glorious battle! ... Huzzah! Huzzah! By the way, does anyone have a spare drum or a fife? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Banditos Misteriosos site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.misteriosos.org/?p=112" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.misterioso...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; Saturday August 22nd, 1:30PM Sharp (1:30pm - 2:15pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt; Free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The summer is heating up, thus, it is with pride, after many requests, that Banditos Misteriosos announces our Second Annual Revolutionary Water Gun Fight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Last year over 375 warriors rushed into battle, complete with marching armies, drums, fifes, and bubble blowing robots. And this year, we plan on holding another battle. But this time, even larger.[...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Consider this event the combination of a good ole fashioned water gun fight and the revolutionary battle of our forefathers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Staying true to Boston's historical roots, this water gun fight shall focus on two armies, marching and meeting each other for a battle in a specific location&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... where is it being held? &amp;quot;You will be receive an email on August 21st at 8:00PM with your army assignment, color shirt and meet up location. If you have any additional revolutionary wear that you don't mind getting wet, well, get dressed up. Besides that, you are all set! [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;P.S. As noted/repeated-multiple-times, if you have a fife/drums or any revolutionary re-enactment experience overall, please do&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pictures from last years battle:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.misteriosos.org/?page_id=81" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.misterioso...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let's be on the same side!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I'll let people know what side they assign us when the email goes out Friday at 8:00 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Supplies (from their site):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;- 1 UNLOADED water gun of your choice.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;- At least 3 FILLED two-liter bottles (bring more if you desire!) &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;- 1 back-pack to hold water bottles. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;- 1 either red or blue shirt (depending on army assignment). &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;- Any other revolutionary paraphernalia you don’t mind getting wet (hats, flutes, etc) &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;- As always, your fighting vigor and a bandana!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rules:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Please be aware of electronics during this event. If you see someone with a camera or camcorder, please shy away from getting them wet. Also, we like public property. Lets be nice to it&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Other:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If you have any marching drum/flute experience or if you have in your own possession, a revolutionary soldier outfit, please do e-mail us as we would love to talk to you! - Don’t worry, instruments and professional outfits will not get wet- contact@misteriosos.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Besides that, its pretty straight forward. Everything will make sense when you receive your enlistment email on the 21st. It’s hot out, so lets have a good old fashioned water gun fight! Spread the word, call your Sons and Daughters of Liberty to arms! Let’s do Sam Adams and Lord Cornwallis proud!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Banditos Misteriosos:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.misteriosos.org/?page_id=2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.misterioso...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Banditos Misteriosos is an organization composed of numerous Bostonians who walk around Boston and ask two simple questions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; * Who are these people we pass in the street?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; * How could we use those big open public spaces?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;To answer these questions, we refer to our belief that we all have the capacity for “selective immaturity”, that we are all willing to step out of our shells for a brief moment and act like fools with our fellow Bostonians.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;All we need is a time and a place. Banditos Misteriosos aims to answer that call to arms. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our events have the goal of getting Bostonians participating in ways just a little out of the ordinary, while all the meanwhile utilizing the cities great public spaces.  Every event is open to all ages, safe and most importantly, free&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Facebook Link for Event:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=124604955880" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>23</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253552325000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>48</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248706850000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Second Annual Revolutionary Water Gun Fight @ Banditos Misteriosos</name><id>10967382</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250960400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/10967382/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>