<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>167 Neck Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06443</zip><lat>41.272118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mercy Center At Madison</name><city>Madison</city><id>11203052</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.636864</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Full Moon Labyrinth Walk&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a spring labyrinth walk near the ocean at &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mercy Center in Madison, a retreat center blessed with 33 acres of breath-taking, waterfront property with a beautiful, private beach. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will begin with a social time for introductions and coffee/tea at 7:30 pm. The labyrinth program will begin at 8 pm. You'll learn about the history, tradition and purpose of labyrinths before entering into its meditative and relaxing space. A path to the center leads us in and back out while walking in quiet reflection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mercy Center is tucked away in a residential neighborhood and the driveway is accessed through the parking lot of Our Lady of Mercy elementary school. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Take I-95N to Exit 59 (Goose Lane, Guilford).&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;At light at end of exit, take a right,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;then take an immediate left onto Rte. 1.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Travel about two miles and take a right onto Neck Rd.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;(It’s the first right after Ford dealership on left and JJ Autoworks on right, and immediately before the School House Deli).&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Another quick right at stop sign (still Neck Rd.).&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Travel about ½ mile to the Mercy Campus.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Turn left into the driveway immediately before&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Our Lady of Mercy School (brick building).&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Keep left past the school building and school parking lot,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;and then follow the long, narrow driveway.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;At stop sign, keep Emmanuel House (two-story house) on left,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;and continue into the parking lot in front of the main building.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT LABYRINTHS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Labyrinths are different than mazes. There is only one winding path that leads to the center, and the walker basically retraces their steps in to get back out to the entrance/exit. Basically, it’s a way of physically reflecting on the twists and turns of life and what will bring you or has brought you to this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the labyrinth is outside, you'll need to dress warmly! Following the walk, there will be time for conversation, cookies, hot tea and apple cider indoors while people warm up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no right or wrong way to walk the labyrinth. Respond to the questions, insights, and emotions that arise from within and from the beautiful ocean beach surroundings as seen in the light of the full moon. Following your walk you are invited to remain for a shared reflection with all gathered for the evening's journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Mercy Center offers this event for a free will donation which means you can pay what you like. I'm going to suggest that we all try to give at least $10 to further their mission and work... &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Our vision is to nurture a relationship with the Sacred in self, others and creation that seeks to foster a just and compassionate world.... The profound spiritual and personal transformations experienced at Mercy Center are carried by each attendee into each aspect of their lives... These inner shifts are to be shared with the world today. If each person who has come to Mercy Center affects even just 1 other person, then our impact is truly lasting and our vision of a more just and compassionate world will be realized." &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/3/c/event_213881532.jpeg" width="468" height="187" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See Directions Below...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364692948000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363270019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Labyrinth Walk</name><id>109226932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364427000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/109226932/</event_url></item>