<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE TRIPLE OR QUADRUPLE RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi folks, Biagio (Social Fun) invited our group to his event.  It should be a good chance to meet people from across several meetup groups.  I'm not sure if I can go, but Sid from Nightlife has generously volunteered to be the point person for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;posting, taken from Social Fun's site: &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Kitty OShea's is an awesome spot to host another Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party for 160 members on Friday Oct 23, 2009. This is not a Singles Party. Meaning anyone can come which including couples. All are welcome to Party and Socialize.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kitty OShea's is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100 Website &lt;a href="http://www.kittyoshea.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kittyoshea...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2nd floor can hold 160 people.  There are 2 Bars upstairs, 4 huge comfy couches, AC, its own DJ area with light machine and dance floor, plus its own bathrooms upstairs so we would truly have our own private party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Music will be medium levels in main room upstairs. Music will be tuned very low in the back room so members can have a separate area to chat!&lt;br /&gt;Till about 9PM then the Dancing and music starts, then its gets loud . Please do not complain since people came to dance and hear the music too&lt;br /&gt;There will be 3 Bartender upstairs: 2 at the upfront Bar and 1 in the back .&lt;br /&gt;I have ordered and paid for over $200 worth of appetizers (Wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) because their Kitchen is too small and we will never get enough food for 160 members. The bar will refill any appetizers platter just once.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The $5 I collect covers the cost to rent us the whole 2nd floor, 3 bartenders +the DJ so its not all just to cover the food. Please find Biagio at the party and please give Biagio the $5. Please no one dollar bills .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After you get inside there is a Security at the stairs please tell them you are with Social Fun to get in (Even if you are with a different group) . If you say ANY other group they will not let you in. I had a few issues with this last time and Security did not let some people in, because they could not remember to say they were with Social Fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please have $5 ready in hand at the top of the stairs if you take too long Security will make members to go back downstairs. Sorry we cannot block the stairs&lt;br /&gt;Please introduce yourself to me, let me know what group you are in, and be Social.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Let me make this clear everyone, but the Core (1+year) Social Fun Organizers + Invited groups Organizers pays $5.&lt;br /&gt;2. After 9PM you will have to pay another $10 as a cover charge for the Bar Entrance fee to get in so that $15 total. $10 to bar and $5 to cover the cost to rent the 2nd floor.&lt;br /&gt;3. If you get in before 9PM you ONLY have to pay $5 to Biagio to cover the cost to rent. Hint Hint: Make sure you get there early!&lt;br /&gt;4. It will be packed.&lt;br /&gt;5. If you come after 7:30PM you might not even get in right away and will have to wait in line downstairs to go upstairs. So come at 7PM to get in.&lt;br /&gt;6. They will not let you upstairs till 7PM so please wait downstairs till 7PM.&lt;br /&gt;7. Tell Security you are with Social Fun to get in -Even if you are with a different group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you say ANY other group they will not let you in. I had a few issues with this last time and Security did not let some people in, because they could not remember to say they were with Social Fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With all that aside and if I have not scared you away then please join us for all this fun Friday starting at 7 till the cows come home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 6 Meetup Groups that are invited to come:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Social Fun &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Biagio)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Happy Hour &lt;a href="http://nightlife.meet.."&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Tonya)&lt;br /&gt;    * Beantown and Beyond 20-40 Singles &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.."&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Catherine)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://euro.meetup.co.."&gt;http://euro.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Noelle)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Night Life Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Rebecca)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe RSVPs will be moved to NO RSVPs 1 week before the event with no exception. We try to target 250 YES RSVPs to hopefully get 160 members to actually show up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had over 175 members at last Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party .&lt;br /&gt;It should be fun and I hope you can all join us for this blast of a party!&lt;br /&gt;Ciao Biagio&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Read instructions below</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>6966003</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257648231000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255967275000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mix and Mingle across Meetup party </name><id>11660517</id><headcount>51</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256338800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/11660517/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/c/global_11309676.jpeg</photo_url></item>