<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It is not ethical to always tell the truth, as Kant’s absurd insistence that it would be wrongful to lie to a murderer in pursuit of his victim exemplifies. (No, I’m not making this up: he makes his case in “On a Supposed Right to Lie because of Philanthropic Concerns”). This is really a surface example of the profoundly deeper issues that underlie and do not always support the applicability of simple ethical rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The subject of this discussion, however, is not the applicability of everyday ethical principles, but big questions that are belittled by the conventional wisdom of the culture and the powers that be. I specifically have in mind conspiracy theories and the challenging of scientific paradigms that have encountered political power—the complex of government, media, corporations, academia, the military-industrial complex, etc.—that orchestrates evidentiary suppression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I repeat what I stated in the Philosophy of Conspiracy discussion back on April 9, 2010: “Philosophically, however, there is perhaps only one way to approach these theories, which is to question whether they are reasonable or unreasonable and to do so with an open mind and—to the extent possible—to produce judgments that are undistorted by bias and preconception. With this attitude it is likely that we will have a fair share of conspiracy theories that either seem reasonable or appear to have the preponderance of evidence on their side, as well as those that appear to have little merit or justification and are likely the result of whimsy or distortion &lt;em&gt;with&lt;/em&gt; prejudice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth itself is always a matter of perspective. However, the first ethic of truth requires that barriers and blockades that obstruct and prevent the examination of evidence be removed. There are the instances of blatant suppression by government and other foci of power. Consider the FDA’s enforced confiscation and burning of Wilhelm Reich’s books on August 23rd 1956 (see &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wilhelm_Reich"&gt;Wikipedia article&lt;/a&gt;.) Book burning? Yup, book burning right here in the good old FDA of the U.S.A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In my mind 911 has plenty of areas that scream out for further Congressional investigation of evidence that very clearly seems to have been suppressed. Of course, subjects as heinous as 911 can, understandably, produce the ostrich effect in many; if this should be the case we may feel free to keep our heads stuck in the sand. It would be easier to dismiss 911 questions if &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pentagon_papers"&gt;The Pentagon Papers&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gulf_of_Tonkin"&gt;Gulf of Tonkin&lt;/a&gt; incident, and the sinking of the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/USS_Maine_%28ACR-1%29"&gt;USS Maine&lt;/a&gt; e.g. did not exist as precedents of how far commercial and military interests are prepared to go in order to foment war and to suppress the truth.&lt;/span&gt; Or is the suppression of the truth all for the best? There may be issues of such social significance that there may be justifiable reasons for their suppression. Really? If so, what are they? We can discuss these issues in a spirit of openness and mutual respect, or we can just choose to have more fun in the sandbox!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people).   After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.  It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.  And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!  While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt; expenditure of $12 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill for food and/or drink plus tax and tip is under $12 the balance will be added to the gratuity).  Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks. To simplify, many folks just round off to $20 and add and adjust if they order drinks. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.  However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*****************************&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP for one of our events it is expected that you have every intention of attending. Please refrain from impulse reservations and impulse cancellations!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342943761000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339592622000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ethics of Truth</name><id>68978512</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342825200000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/68978512/</event_url></item>