<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>54 Merrimac Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.812057</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newburyport Whale Watch</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>7753622</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.873146</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATES -- BOARDING PASSES, PARKING, and FINDING US&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BOARDING PASS.&lt;/strong&gt; Call soon to reserve your ticket -- over 75 tickets have already been sold. To reserve your place, call (978) 499-0832. THE DAY OF THE CRUISE you have to go to their ticket office at 54 Merrimack Street, Newburyport, to PAY for your ticket (before, they were just holding your place) AND to pick up your BOARDING PASS. You need a boarding pass to get on the boat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING. Allow LOTS of time for parking&lt;/strong&gt; -- There are many things happening that day and night in Newburyport. There is "free" parking at the whale watch ticket office (54 Merrimack Street), but I have another suggestion. &lt;strong&gt;GETTING TO THEIR FREE PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt; If you don't mind potholes and narrow allys, put their address into your GPS or MapQuest. Look carefully, and you will see a picture of a whale and a sign that says "Newburyport Whale Watch and Boat Camp". Turn down the ALLY at that sign. Go to the end, and you're facing a sign that says "Brown Wharf". Turn LEFT and then make a quick RIGHT down another ally. There are lots of potholes. That takes you to their parking. &lt;strong&gt;ALTERNATE PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt; If you're on Merrimack Street and "their" whale picture and sign are on your LEFT, drive past it and in a few seconds there is a sign saying "NEWBURYPORT VISITOR'S CENTER". Turn left there into a parking lot. There's an opening on the right into a much larger parking lot. There is a kiosk at which you pay, but it only costs around 50 cents per hour. Machines take cash or credit cards. &lt;strong&gt;LARGEST PARKING LOT&lt;/strong&gt; is past Market Square, on the left. Marked with a "parking" sign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FINDING US.&lt;/strong&gt; Let's meet on the boardwalk where we board the boat. Sign says "Prince of Whales, Whale Watch Tour." It is very close to the Black Cow restaurant. Boarding is at 6:30. I will be at the "meeting" location at 6:10. I look like my photo (look for the blond curls), and (UNTIL we board) I'll be carrying a BRIGHT ORANGE SIGN that says MeetUp.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's enjoy 4th of July fireworks from a great boat leaving from Newburyport. A DJ will be spinning our favorite songs, and a delicious dinner by Starboard Gallery Restaurant includes grilled steak tips, grilled chicken, pasta salad, caesar salad, and strawberry shortcake. Come join the fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost is $50 for one, or $45 per person if two people sign up together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boat boarding is at 6:30. To make a reservation, call 1-800-848-1111&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>To find us, see the "Updates" section below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gale_2</member_name><member_id>10931980</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341505554000</updated><rating><average>2.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339884530000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4th of July fireworks cruise from Newburyport -- include DJ music and dinner.</name><id>69474632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341442800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/69474632/</event_url></item>