<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1623 Main St</address_2><address_1>Route 159</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01001</zip><lat>42.051804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 786-9300</phone><name>Six Flags New England</name><city>Agawam</city><id>704345</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.615913</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NHC does Six Flags.  Need I say more?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;:D&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We (Devorah and Janel) are planning a fun trip to the thrill-a-minute park. Our plan is to meet in a commuter parking lot, condense cars (with passengers contributing towards gas and parking) and then head up north.  Janel will head up the meeting place.  At the lot, we will pass out Janel’s ‘kid’s price’ coupons ($31) and decide on central meeting places and times at the park. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE:  So we decided that the best, safest, free parking lot would be the commuter parking lot in North Haven.  To get there, go on I-91N to exit ten, merging onto Route 40. Get off exit 1, taking a left.  The commuter parking lot will immediately be on your left. Message Janel if you have a problem getting transportation to North Haven.  **Please also text her to let her know that you intend to meet us at the lot** – we don’t want to either leave w/o you, or wait around for people who don’t intend on meeting us there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s google directions to the commuter lot from the New Haven Public Library: &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/NHCtoCommuterLot" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/NH...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TICKETS: Janel will still bring her kid’s price passes, but the identical deal can be found online.  We highly suggest (if possible) buying your ticket online to save time on-line (sidenote: I read this line three times before I realized I was making a terrible pun…I’m awesome).  However, Janel said that for the Flash passes, the more people who buy them, the cheaper they are.  For example, I checked online, and a 6-person flashpass is $99 – so for only $16.50 extra a person, we could really minimize our time in line waiting for rides.  I highly recommend it.  So, in summary, we’ll probably have to get in line to buy the flash passes anyway, but Janel and I thought it would still be best if people could buy their tickets online.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case people get lost, decide to join us later, etc, we thought that we could set up a 12pm meeting place for lunch.  I looked online at the 6 flags map, but unless I’m a total idiot (…which is a possibility), it was just a picture map.  Meaning, while there’s pictures of the rides and shops and whatnot, there was zero labels.  So I couldn’t pick an educated central spot for lunch.  I’m guessing that we can get a more detailed map when we arrive (or if anyone else can figure out what I’m doing wrong, feel free – I didn’t want to fiddle around with it too much during work).  So since Janel and I will have our cell phones on us, and I think only Neil/Natalie are going up separately, we will text Neil (since I have his number) once we pick a lunch meeting spot.  If anyone else gets there later/separately, just call/text Janel or I and we’ll let you know the spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please wear comfortable shoes.  I would also recommend sunscreen, hats and possibly sunglasses and a water bottle.  Please note that there is no glass or outside food allowed. Also, some thrill rides prohibit cameras. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can’t wait! We should have a great time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! Devorah and Janel (Or, in anticipation of her correcting me… Janel and Devorah) :P&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250549377000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248707101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Six Flags!!</name><id>10967422</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250341200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/10967422/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/0/2/global_9897074.jpeg</photo_url></item>