<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>284 Amory Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.314777</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-522-0222</phone><name>Bikes Not Bombs</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>1223763</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104602</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Wednesday Volunteer Nights&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Get your hands dirty with a wrench, flattening bikes to prepare them for international shipment, stripping bikes for parts, or sorting used parts. Or, help our office staff with database updates or mailings. Anyone is welcome to drop in to the &lt;a href="http://bikesnotbombs.org/locations" target="_blank"&gt;B&lt;/a&gt;ikes not Bombs between 7pm and 10pm, on Wednesday night. A supervisor will show you what to do, and no experience is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also earn points to get parts or refurbished bikes, so don't forget to fill out a time sheet. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Who We Are&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Bikes Not Bombs promotes bicycle technology as a concrete alternative to war and environmental destruction.&lt;/strong&gt; For 25 years, BNB has been a nexus of bike recycling and community empowerment both in lower income neighborhoods of Boston and in the nations of the Global South. BNB's programs involve young people and adults in mutually respectful leadership development and environmental stewardship, while recycling thousands of bicycles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We currently receive approximately 6,000 used bicycles and tons of used parts each year. We ship about 4,800 of these bikes to economic development projects (micro-enterprise bike businesses, sustainable technology projects, and youth training programs) in Ghana, Tanzania, South Africa, Guatemala, Nevis Island every year. BNB also sends technicians and tools for start-up projects to these same countries. (In the past we have worked in Nicaragua, the Dominican Republic, Haiti, and El Salvador, and we continue to accept new requests for assistance from projects in Latin America, the Caribbean, and Africa.) We use the remainder of our collected bikes at our Jamaica Plain Center; some are used in our co-ed youth Earn-A-Bike programs, and others are repaired by teenage mechanics as part of our Vocational Training programs and are for sale in our bike shop. BNB also offers girls-only programs all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We operate a full-service bike shop, staffed by local teen graduates of BNB training programs and supervised by professional adult bike mechanics. The shop repairs customer bikes, offers hard-to-find used parts and sells new parts, locks, accessories and refurbished bikes with a warranty. Shop specialties include renovated upright-bar 12 speeds, single-speed coasting and fixed-gear bikes, reconditioned mountain and hybrid models of all brands, and higher-end touring and road bikes. We sell frames alone, including used Titanium Merlin frames. The BNB Bicycle Shop and Training Center opened the doors of its new location in February, 2007. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Please save gas by using public transportation to get to this event. The &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/trip_planner/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA Trip Planner&lt;/a&gt; will help you do this.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for clicking and see you there! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Josh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. Connect with everybody else with our Facebook community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very popular. Learn more: &lt;a href="http://on.FB.me/fEGBoo"&gt;http://on.FB.me/fEGBoo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Boston Volunteers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big enough to Deliver, small enough to care&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.BostonVolunteer.org"&gt;www.BostonVolunteer.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;P.S. Learn more about your popular fellow Boston Volunteers:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/BostonVolunteers"&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/images.wisestamp.com/facebook.png" alt="Facebook" width="16" height="16" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/#!/BostonVolunteer"&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/images.wisestamp.com/twitter.png" alt="Twitter" width="16" height="16" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Derek</member_name><member_id>60788962</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364522921000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Boston Volunteers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BigEnoughtoDeliver</urlname><id>1343564</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Volunteers. Big enough 2 deliver, small enough 2 care</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317656265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bikes Not Bombs: Thursday Volunteer Night!</name><id>drxjdcyrfblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364511600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigEnoughtoDeliver/events/107520352/</event_url></item>