<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;***Due to a larger than expected turnout, they are changing the meeting location to the Trailside Museum entrance 1904 canton ave. in Milton.***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Let's get out of hibernation and do something different (and fun). We'll join Hike4Life for their season opening hike. Why does Hike4Life recommend hiking? "Hiking is a fun and inexpensive way to improve your health!  Hiking and other outdoor activities, also offer a spiritually and mentally refreshing experience. Studies show that African-Americans are at the greatest risk of being diagnosed with Type 1 &amp;amp; 2 Diabetes, higher cholesterol, and high blood pressure (Hypertension) than any other race and our numbers are on the rise." Read more on their&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.hike4life.org/aboutus.htm"&gt;About Us&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;page.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description of the event their website below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;It’s become tradition for Hike4Life members and friends to kick off a new year’s Hiking season with a memorable hike through the Blue Hills. This will be another year of great hikes, great people and great opportunities. We’ve put together a great group of people to help make this a successful year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We’re looking forward to adding more friends, family, supporters and volunteers to our Team!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Our first hike of 2013 will be the kick off to another great year. We’re going to meet at location 1203 (Border Path) on your Blue Hills Reservation Map.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;You can find it here at: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue%20hills%20brochure.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue%20hills%20brochure.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;I was tempted to put in GPS coordinates but, I don’t have them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;From there we'll tackle a couple of hills right from the road and continue on the trail upward and around the best the Hills has to offer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;I ask everyone to bring water/food so we can make a day of our first day this year together in the woods. Hopefully the weather will be favorable. I will update the invitation as we get closer to the date. Please invite your friends, let them know about Hike4Life and share with stories and pictures of our previous adventures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ill post where we are when I get there. Other groups will be there too.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cabral Thomas</member_name><member_id>9824758</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366034728000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362747398000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Go for a Hike!</name><id>108251152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365861600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/108251152/</event_url></item>