<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>140 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.177994</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 429 1500</phone><name>The Meadows</name><city>Holliston</city><id>959576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.442941</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have our next meet on February 21st from 12:30 to 4:30 pm at Holliston Meadows, 140 Summer Street,, MA (508) 429 1500.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because we had &lt;b&gt;so many&lt;/b&gt; people attending last time, which was so wonderful, I'm going to ask people to sign up for 2 different time periods, 12:30 to 2:30pm and 3:00 - 5:00  pm to make sure we have enough chairs and enough room for the dogs to play.  I am putting an RSVP list together, and there will be a limit of 20 people per time slot, so please letme know if and when you'd like to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know what type of food or beverage you'd  like to bring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can RSVP on the meetup.com site, but also please send me an email to let me know:  laptopmaltese@aol.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On other subjects:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1)  Anne Byers, the director of Holliston Meadows and her husband just gave birth to a new baby boy, William two weeks ago.  8 lbs 6 oz.  This is grandpa Dr. Poling's FIRST grandchild!!!  He and his family own Holliston Meadows and Holliston Animal Hospital and many of you know him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Holliston Meadows has two brother Maltese that are 3 years old up for adoption.  They are such sweethearts, already neutered, and &lt;b&gt;Pete Westland&lt;/b&gt; is giving them training lessons  right now so they will come with that advantage. He says they are doing unbelievably well with the training.  Pete and I think that they should be adopted by separate homes so that they get a lot of individual attention and focus on their new owners and vice versa. If you are interested, please call Pete at (508) 429 1500.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) I'm trying to convince Pete Westland to come to our meet again, and I think he is interested in attending some time in the near future!  He was absolutely so wonderful at our first meet in Holliston and paid a lot of very nice attention to those owners and dogs attending!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Smalll dog best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;508 561 6881&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask someone where I am.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266946962000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265324119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BOSTON MALTESE &amp; TINY DOG MEETUP  SUNDAY February 21, 12:30 pm - 5 pm</name><id>12521916</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266773400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/12521916/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/c/global_83228.jpeg</photo_url></item>