<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(between Beach St &amp; Kneeland St)</address_2><address_1>9 Tyler St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351131</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 426-4338</phone><name>China Pearl</name><city>Boston</city><id>827016</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060692</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's get together for dim sum again with the possibility of seeing a movie afterward.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This link has a very helpful dim sum primer written by fellow BBLDer Pam Phillips; &lt;a href="http://home.comcast.net/~pam_phillips/TCC4335/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://home.comcast.n...&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: Call China Pearl at (617) 426-4338  for suggestions    &lt;br /&gt;Create your own train &amp;amp;/or bus route @ mbta.com or www.hopstop.com    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RULES of Engagement:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation,    &lt;br /&gt;please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If an event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be wait listed.    &lt;br /&gt;If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must contact me directly by calling or texting 617 445-7549.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will arrive by 10:15 AM to arrange seating as well as welcome you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet outside at 10:30 AM. Please call me at (617) 445 7549 if you're running late.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213108504000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><why>This is one of the best places which offers good dim sum for large groups.</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210875063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>China Pearl Dim Sum</name><id>7945505</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212935400000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/7945505/</event_url></item>