<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;Times and Winds is a lyrical portrait of everyday life in a small village told through the lives of three young friends coping with the isolation of their remote location and their perceived mistreatment by their respective parents. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shot on location in Kozlu, the film features beautiful widescreen vistas and a mesmerizing score by Arvo Pärt. (111 mins., 35mm)- Wexner Center for the Arts&lt;br /&gt;Kudos for the Arvo Part score- Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Times and Winds is a finely etched portrait of remote village life in Turkey composed of small, meticulously observed moments of great beauty, melancholy and lyricism. ?Erdem has a profound and innately poetic sense of the rhythmic passing of time - TIFF&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Times and Winds (Bes vakit) by Reha Erdem (2006, 111 min.). ?A hypnotic portrait of village life?largely through the eyes of three youngsters?that packs a poetic-spiritual punch way beyond its placid surface? (Derek Elley, Variety). This magical film portrays the tensions that lie beneath the seemingly composed surface of a remote and rugged mountain village perched between sea and sky, untouched by the modern world. Erdem?s fourth feature recounts the dreams and desires of villagers whose simple lives are regulated by the calls to prayer that divide the day (and the film) into five sections (the Turkish title literally translates as &amp;quot;five times&amp;quot;). The main characters are three youngsters, two boys and a girl living in this harsh, strictly disciplined culture...In subtle touches, the picture deals with the early sexual awakening of the three, their communion with nature, and revolt against their parents. Winner of the two main prizes at the 25th Istanbul International Film Festival. - MFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a remarkable attention to the vicissitudes of life in a remote Turkish village; director Reha Erdem captures the delicate transition between childhood and adulthood, as three young friends explore the fraught territory of love, lust and death. A humanist-pastoral epic in the tradition of Pudovkin.--LA Weekly &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yet another upbeat film hosted by Tom. As is our custom, I'll be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the movie's end and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. Serious kudos to anyone who attends who knows Pudovkin (might help with the talk afterward).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196715124000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194655090000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Times and Winds- A Film from Turkey</name><id>6712309</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196541900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6712309/</event_url></item>