<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Downtown</address_2><address_1>49 Peck St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 272-1212</phone><name>Red Fez the</name><city>Providence</city><id>205815</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: The Red Fez (on Peck St. near 10 Prime and McFaddens) in downtown Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So the holiday season is beginning and its time to think about the cozy places in Providence that befit this time of year. The Red Fez has been around forever and is so ultra arty-hip that the RISD students hang out there (as do some designers I know - lol!). Its so cool the sign is just a red fez (look for the hat on the sign - its a cone-shaped hat with a gold tassel). Incidentally, the grilled cheese is amazing. We'll be upstairs at the bar and there are tables to sit at too. Its unbelievable that we haven't been here since August 2010!!!! I can't believe it! If you've never been&amp;nbsp; here's your chance and if you have, well, you know....Its always a good time, so let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a scarf or silver flower pin!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323218786000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322927719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - The Red Fez!</name><id>43256862</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323126000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/43256862/</event_url></item>