<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Village Inn Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01473</zip><lat>42.544853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wachusett Village Inn</name><city>Westminster</city><id>12152772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.874443</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>31.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This year we will be going to the very haunted Wachusett Village Inn, in Westminster Mass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meet up will include a buffet dinner at the Black Diamond Restaurant, a mini investigation with Sandy Mcleod in the haunted part of the Inn, and those who would like to stay over in the haunted section can rent a room, as I have all (7) of the rooms in the Chipper Wing reserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are planning on coming for dinner and the Investigation, you must pay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$30.00 per person by cash or check to Robin Paladino, in person, or mailing info upon request at &lt;a href="mailto:talawitch@charter.net"&gt;talawitch@charter.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or with paypal, through the meet up extra $1.00 charge per payment for paypal fees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Friday April 12th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Inn is haunted by the original owner, Thomas Palmer who owned farmland there in the 1800's, and is a very active and friendly ghost, known to haunt Rm 204. There is also a ghost of a woman, and a little girl who some think is the famous Lucy Keyes who is shy and resides in Rm 206, among various other less known spirits. Sandy's paranormal group has been to this location on (2) other occasions, and have gotten alot of activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People attending this meet up can come for the dinner and investigation only, or stay the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you plan on staying the night, you need to call the Inn and reserve your room ASAP- Rooms in the haunted section are $107.00 per night, I believe that rooms in the rest of the Inn are a bit cheaper, details for reserving room will be added in the next week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be having an Italian Dinner at the Restaurant for 14.95- 19.95 per person which will be as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tossed Garden Salad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parmesan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Penne w/ marinara sauce&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sausage &amp;amp; Meatballs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Italian Vegetables:  Zucchini, summer squash, Eggplant Ragout&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garlic and Italian Breads&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dessert:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creme Broulee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chocolate Mousse&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheesecake&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dinner, Sandy will be doing a mini investigation in the haunted section of the Inn. She will do a talk about the inn, ghost investigations, the equip that is used, and give people a chance to play with some of the equipment prior to the investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the talk we will do a "mini" investigation for about an hour and a half.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandy has asked that if anyone has any equip to please bring it with you, and to also bring flashlights (esp "mag" lights, as the spirits like to flash them), digital recorders, cameras and pendulums.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When doing your RSVP please state whether you are coming just for the dinner and investigation or reserving a room. Look for more information about this meet up in the coming week :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on the Inn:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;h&lt;a href="http://www.wachusettvillageinn.com/"&gt;ttp://www.wachusettvillageinn.com/&lt;/a&gt;en&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368893675000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362773429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ghostly Encounter at the Haunted Wachusett Village Inn</name><id>108311912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366491600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/108311912/</event_url></item>