<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our purpose: It's a Wine Tasting and buying opportunity with Lynn and  TheTraveling Vineyard!  Most wines are rated 90 and above and cost between $10-$20. Wines are available by filling out an Interest to Order form which will later be confirmed by TTV.  TTV only accepts credit cards and checks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our method: Wine Tastings members who might be interested in purchasing boutique wines are invited to a private wine tasting by Traveling Vineyards. This will take place at 6:30...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no charge for admission. Guests are asked to bring a food item that will pair well with wines such as cheese, crackers, strawberries, chocolate, appetizers, sparkling water etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Limit: &lt;br /&gt;Only 19 members (including guests) could RSVP 'Yes' for this event.&lt;br /&gt;Participants must be 21 and older ( ID required)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: private home or private setting in and around Southern CT to be announced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If interested in booking a private tasting in your home for your guests, please contact me .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to meeting you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lynn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lynn</member_name><member_id>4669226</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188513183000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185880290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Traveling Vineyard Wine Meetup Group, Southern Ct. August Meetup</name><id>6102739</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188340200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/6102739/</event_url></item>