<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Julio Medem, considered by many the voice of post-democracy, Basque cinema steps aside from his wonderfully surreal romances (The Red Squirrel, Sex and Lucia, Lovers of the Artic Circle) to direct his first documentary. This was not his original goal. He began filming interviews for what was planned to be a  fictional work about the Basque people and could not stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What does it mean to be Basque? Their language, Euskera, can lay claim to being the oldest spoken in Europe - but it is in decline, and no longer used by many who consider themselves Basque. Their land is currently divided into seven regions in southern France and northern Spain - but arguments still rage as to whether they should be fully absorbed into their host nations, attain some autonomy or even outright separatist status. These issues, far from being merely academic, have led to one hundred and fifty or so years of repression, misery and bloodshed, especially between the Basque and the Spanish authorities.   Movie Gazette&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This gold-mine of material is beautifully edited, and even the interviews are shot with Medem's ethereal beauty. As the film gets deeper into the political aspect of the conflict, it all gets fairly bewildering--and also very universal, as this could easily be Northern Ireland, the West Bank or anywhere people feel oppressed for their ethnicity.     Shadows on the Wall&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a full review: &lt;a href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/films/2004/05/04/basque_ball_2004_review.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bbc.co.uk/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, we will meet near the front row after the film and then go to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189983944000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187304685000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Basque Ball- A Documentary by Julio Medem</name><id>6193630</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189810800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6193630/</event_url></item>