<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>199 Sundeen Pky</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03077</zip><lat>43.034565</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Riverside Park</name><city>Raymond</city><id>841436</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.201180</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a Family event to help promote Riverside Park in Raymond, NH. It is a dog friendly event, however due to the many different activities, and lots of people, etc. it will be required that all dogs outside of the fenced in area must be on leash at all times. There will be plenty of play time within the fence, followed by a Doggy Winter Wear Contest, and a doggy parade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dog parade will start at 1pm, at which time we'll line up the dogs on leash and parade up the trail to the main field.&amp;nbsp; Everyone will be voting for their favorite doggy.&amp;nbsp; The owners/handlers will be asked to safety pin a number to their sleeve (2 numbers if you are walking 2 dogs, etc) and the carnival participants will vote on their favorite number! :) Please plan to arrive an hour or so early, at the least, to let the dogs run around and burn off some energy prior to the parade.&amp;nbsp; We will be meeting in the fenced in area of the park. There will be hot soups and hot dogs and burgers for sale. Remember to bring baggies in case your doggy decides to "go" while at the park! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the article from The Union Leader!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newhampshire.com/article.aspx?headline=Couple+plan+Winter+Carnival+in+Raymond&amp;amp;articleid=3993"&gt;http://www.newhampshire.com/article.aspx?headline=Couple+plan+Winter+Carnival+in+Raymond&amp;amp;articleid=3993&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298903559000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Hey Everyone! Save the date! February 26th starting around 10am and going until about 3pm will be the 1st Annual Winter Carnival at Riverside Park. Doggy parade is at 1pm.</why><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296147197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1st Annual Riverside Park Winter Carnival and Dog Parade!</name><id>16327374</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298732400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/16327374/</event_url></item>