<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>JCT Route 128 N and Route 114E</address_2><address_1>Andover Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01960</zip><lat>42.545739</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 531-4850</phone><name>North Shore Mall</name><city>Peabody</city><id>1097567</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.945377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy topics such as wellness, acupuncture, feng shui, herbs, natural cooking, yoga, spa, meditation, senior services, family, children, home, financial and pet health.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Over 45 exhibitors,  free samples, free admission, free screenings and more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Health &amp;amp; Wellness Expo&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, February 27 from 10 AM - 3 PM&lt;br /&gt;Northshore Mall in Peabody, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by the Salem, Peabody &amp;amp; Beverly Chambers of Commerce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over 45 local and national companies will provide free information, screenings, demonstrations and product samples. The Expo will encompass a broad range of products and services including traditional and alternative health practitioners, senior services, healthy food, non-toxic cleaning solutions and much more! The Expo is free to attend and offers something for the entire family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who will be participating?&lt;br /&gt;Hospitals, Health Care Professionals, Physical Fitness Organizations, Personal Trainers, Nutritionists, Dentists, Orthodontists, Home Health Aids, Childcare Centers, Childcare Providers, Home Care Providers, Financial Planners, Health Insurance Providers, Homeopathic Solutions, Emergency Services, Substance Abuse Programs, Alternative Therapies, Yoga Instructors, Optometrists, Day Spas, or any product or service that focuses on health and wellness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet at the food court, then we can all find it together.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299422005000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294544440000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Health &amp; Wellness Expo</name><id>15976538</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299344400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/15976538/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/d/6/global_20677494.jpeg</photo_url></item>