<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Concsious Movie * Saturday * July 31 * 7pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pray the Devil Back to Hell is a captivating new film by director Gini Reticker. It exposes a different story angle for the largely forgotten recent events of the women of Liberia uniting to bring the end to their nation's civil war. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film is amazing in the way it captivates your attention from the earliest frames. It doesn't shy away from showing footage of the violent events that took place during the Liberian civil war. But the main story of the film is that of Leymah Gbowee and the other women uniting, despite their religious differences, to force action on the stalled peace talks in their country. Using entirely nonviolent methods, not only are the peace talks successful, but Charles Taylor, the president of Liberia, is forced into exile leading to the first election of a female head of state in Africa. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The women of this film are truly an inspiration and no one can fail to be moved by the message of hope that comes through clearly in this film. These are heroes that deserve to be remembered and with Pray the Devil we are able to do that, gaining both a knowledge of the history we are ignorant of through archival footage and an understanding of the leaders of this movement through close-up interviews with the many women who lead it. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280621956000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279552956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie:  Pray the Devil Back to Hell</name><id>14145872</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280617200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/14145872/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/b/c/global_16553820.jpeg</photo_url></item>