<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>296 Main Street #102</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.136208</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Franklin Back &amp; Joint Care of Milford MA - Chiropractic Center</name><city>Milford</city><id>1489857</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.523430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Arrive any time between 10:30 am and 11:30 am.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;We'll go out to brunch around 12 noon at Johnny Jacks (walking distance).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a chiropractic adjustment, acupuncture, massage, protein smoothies, get your antioxidant level measured, win some fabulous prizes... and more!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free demonstrations - see below...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prize Raffle*:&lt;/strong&gt; $25 gift cert to either Uno's, Best Buy or Bed Bath and Beyond; 1-HOUR FREE MASSAGE at our office; a $50 gift certificate towards Tastefully Simple; a SONY wifi Blu-Ray player; 26" LED tv (the newer skinny ones); an XBOX 360 with Kinect motion sensing camera bundle (comes with a free game), $50 Gift Certificate to Tastefully Simple; a Free Consultation for improving your public speaking skills; Blissful Meadows Golf Package (free round of golf for 2 and a gift certificate to use in their tavern), $50 gift certificate to Alicante's Restaurant in Mendon, a Free 1hour Initial Consult on Kicking the Sugar Habit and Improving Healthy Eating...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*TO WIN A PRIZE:&lt;/strong&gt; you have to come in and get adjusted OR send someone in that gets their spine adjusted!&amp;nbsp; But come in and mingle and try some of the free things too! Read below..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHERE:&lt;/strong&gt; Franklin Back &amp;amp; Joint Care of Milford MA (296 Main St)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CALL: 508-473-1750 to set up appointments for Chiropractic, Massage&amp;nbsp;or Acupuncture.&lt;/strong&gt; Walk-Ins are welcome for chiropractic (though you will have to wait until there is a break, so please call to reserve a spot) or for any of the free services!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;SERVICES ON THIS DAY:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chiropractic adjustments&lt;/strong&gt;: $15/adult, $10/child under 16. We can tailor the adjustments to your liking (low low force or soft tissue, or normal).&amp;nbsp; Dr. Craig Julian and possibly his brother Dr. Nicholas Julian of Franklin Back &amp;amp; Joint Care of Milford and Franklin will be the chiropractors on hand. &lt;br /&gt;**730am-5pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Massage Therapy&lt;/strong&gt;: $20 for a 30-min massage (normally $30+). Mandy Beaudet of Mandy's Mobile Massage; Mindy Ruddock of LaRose Muscular Therapy and Liz Bishop of Sterling Therapeutics and Massage. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BioPhotonic Scanner&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt;! Andrea Longo, fitness professional and AgeWell Unlimited Consultant, will be using a scanner to measure the amount of antioxidants in your skin and offering information of AgeWell products. See your antioxidant score and find out how to improve it!  &lt;br /&gt;**9am-2pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Warm AromaTherapy Neck Wraps and Protein Smoothies&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt;! Lisa Vasile, nurse practitioner and Arbonne Consultant, will be doing these in the waiting room and offering information on Arbonne's great products and ways to improve your overall health with simple tips!  &lt;br /&gt;**8am-3pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sEMG Muscle Tension Test - FREE&lt;/strong&gt;!&amp;nbsp; A pain-free computerized scanner that measures the amount of muscle tension in your neck and/or low back.&amp;nbsp; See your scan immediately and learn how to improve the health of your back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**8am-4pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Balloons &amp;amp; Stickers for Kids - FREE&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacki</member_name><member_id>6777705</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301147161000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295972932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Health Appreciation Day  2011</name><id>16179552</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300631400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/16179552/</event_url></item>