<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday July, 26th Tias on the Water  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike  along  the heart of Boston's Waterfront  6:30-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its a great time to be  living in the city of Boston right now, we've had plenty of sunny days as of late, Entourage season 4 is in full swing, and football season is around the corner!  Although,  its even better to be apart of the Boston Nightlife group, we have had 2 fantastic events as of late including a new member mixer and a nite on the town at 33 lounge last Friday!  So what better way to keep the party going?  I'm thinking Tias on the Water   this Thursday!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tias has been  regarded by many as the best afterwork outdoor spot in the city. Perched on the water's edge, this hotspot is where many come to relax after a day in the office with a frozen margarita or a cold beer. The brick patio gets jam-packed starting at 6pm on summer nights. So come and join the group as we kickoff the start to another wonderful summer  weekend! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also if you have not been to any or a few of our events whether an Afterwork Mixer, New Member meetup, or even a nite on the town in the city with the group, I encourage all of you to come this Thursday and meet many of our wonderful members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: We will meet on the patio  near the bar area closest to the water. Be sure to bring your phone and please look for me upon arriving my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section. I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, this is Boston not  Omaha lines in this city develop fast! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation:  Blue Line to Aquarium&lt;br /&gt;                                 Green line to Goverment Ctr&lt;br /&gt;                                  Orange Line to State St. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185916589000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185152554000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Party like a Rockstar this Thursday!! Afterwork Mixer Tia's on the Water!</name><id>6062462</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185489000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/6062462/</event_url></item>