<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Norman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.407853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-387-7625</phone><name>MetroRock Everett</name><city>Everett</city><id>669182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Metrorock Everett is hosting their second Annual Climb for a Cure, benefitting cancer research. Last year that meant climbing routes to accumulate vertical feet. Some people clocked in over 1500 vertical feet in a four-five hour climbing session and had donors matching the vertical feet climbed with corresponding dollars. A true test of endurance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see the announcement below from Bill Schifone, to sign up just email him at  schifone1@verizon.net:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CLIMB FOR A CURE II&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the friends and families of MetroRock&lt;br /&gt;1.) EVENT – “CLIMB FOR A CURE”  a Jimmy Fund Sponsored Event&lt;br /&gt;a. “Climb New England’s Indoor Cannon Cliff”&lt;br /&gt;b. PLACE: MetroRock, Everett&lt;br /&gt;c. DATE: April 24, 2010&lt;br /&gt;d. TIME: 4 PM to 10 PM&lt;br /&gt;e. WHAT IT IS: fundraiser to benefit the Jimmy Fund and Dana Farber in their fight against childhood cancer&lt;br /&gt;f. GOAL: raise $10,000&lt;br /&gt;2.) PARTICIPATION&lt;br /&gt;a. Registration is now open&lt;br /&gt;i. To register participants should email Bill Schifone at Bill@metrorock.com or by picking up a pledge sheet from the front desk or MetroRock&lt;br /&gt;ii. A MetroRock Jimmy Fund Pledge Sheet will be given/sent to you upon registration.&lt;br /&gt;1. This must be completed by every participant&lt;br /&gt;2. It must be turned in before or on the day of the comp&lt;br /&gt;3. It must have the participants name on it&lt;br /&gt;4. It must have all the pledges’ names and the amount of the pledges&lt;br /&gt;b. Sponsored climbers will attempt to climb 600 vertical feet on April 25th from 4pm to 10pm&lt;br /&gt;i. Open to any climber&lt;br /&gt;ii. Must be already in MetroRock’s data base having passed a belay test OR&lt;br /&gt;iii. Must be able to pass a belay test&lt;br /&gt;c. Registration closing on Friday, April 23rd, 2010&lt;br /&gt;i. Climbers showing up on the 24th will be allowed to climb for a nominal $25 fee which will go 100% toward the fundraiser&lt;br /&gt;d. Our goal is to have 100 participants that each collects at least $100 in pledges.&lt;br /&gt;3.) PLEDGES&lt;br /&gt;a. Sponsored climbers are encouraged to solicit pledges from private individuals or businesses.&lt;br /&gt;i. Pledges must be collected in cash or checks&lt;br /&gt;ii. Checks must be made out to the Jimmy Fund&lt;br /&gt;b. All pledges MUST be recorded on a Metrorock Jimmy Fund Pledge Sheet&lt;br /&gt;c. Pledge Sheets must be turned in on or before April 24th.&lt;br /&gt;d. Sponsored Climbers can attain one of three levels of sponsorship&lt;br /&gt;i. Gold - $250 or more in total pledges&lt;br /&gt;ii. Silver - $100 or more in total pledges&lt;br /&gt;iii. Bronze - $50 or more in total pledges&lt;br /&gt;e. MetroRock will reward sponsored climbers based on COLLECTED pledges with associated Metrobucks (good for anything including merchandise in the gym) as follows:&lt;br /&gt;i. Gold - $25 Metrobucks&lt;br /&gt;ii. Silver - $10 Metrobucks&lt;br /&gt;iii. Bronze - $5 Metrobucks&lt;br /&gt;f. The Metrobucks will be one aspect of MetroRock’s contribution to the receiving organization.  The benefit of this is that MetroRock can declare the retail value of merchandise/services without that outflow of cash.&lt;br /&gt;4.) EVENT LOGISTICS&lt;br /&gt;a. Gym will be closed to general public for event hours, thus it will be OPEN up to 4PM and all normal morning lessons/parties etc. will carry on as usual&lt;br /&gt;b. Two methods of ‘scoring’; donations will be based on feet climbed however. &lt;br /&gt;i. Based purely on vertical feet climbed&lt;br /&gt;1. Gym routes will be given a ‘value’ of 35 feet for each route, meaning a participant will have to climb 17 routes to attain the 600 foot goal.  This is not an easy task regardless of grade.&lt;br /&gt;2. Routes can be done toprope or lead.  No premium/penalty for grades&lt;br /&gt;ii. Based on vertical feet and grade&lt;br /&gt;1. Point system – combines grade and vertical feet. I will post this on all (or many of) the climbs in the gym at the time of the event.&lt;br /&gt;2. This will make it more interesting for the competitors, especially those that are experienced climbers&lt;br /&gt;iii. Routes do not have to be linked; I.E. the climber can rest on the rope&lt;br /&gt;iv. Boulder problems – bouldering will be allowed.  A donation of $25 will be requested on the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;c. Climbers will be given a ‘scorecard’ to keep track of their climbs.  There will be a place for a peer’s initials (only one).  I will generate those in a separate file.  Participant will chose which type of score sheet they want.  The scoresheet based on points will also have a column for vertical feet too.&lt;br /&gt;d. MetroRock will provide food and beverage for the participating climbers either a pizza party or a barbecue starting at 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;e. Walk ins on day of event (people will invariably forget that we’re closed and come)&lt;br /&gt;i. ALL roped climbers, members and non-members, unaware of the event and simply coming to climb will be asked for a nominal donation of $25 and will be able to climb.&lt;br /&gt;ii. ALL boulderers, members and non-members,  unaware of the event  and just coming to climb will be asked for a nominal donation of $25 and will be able to climb&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jens</member_name><member_id>7100014</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272312835000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270208102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metrorock Climb for a Cure 2010</name><id>13066611</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272139200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/13066611/</event_url></item>