<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Salsa Fans:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join me for a night of great music and dancing. See the details below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Saturday, October 16, at Ryles Jazz Club for a Ritmo Masacote concert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gear up for an INTENSE night of Music and Dance. EVERYONE IS INVITED!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrive early for dinner &amp;amp; stay to Listen to the band, Watch them tearing it up live on the stage, and Groove with Ritmo Masacote on the dancefloor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you're a music aficionado just wanting to hear and watch the high energy ensemble in action or you're a dance lover wanting to dance your heart out to the intoxicating rhythms of Salsa and Timba, there's something for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Show time: 8:30pm &lt;br /&gt;Only $10 cover charge...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Ryles Jazz Club, 212 Hampshire Street, Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************** &lt;br /&gt;Ritmo Masacote is a 12 piece Salsa/Timba/Latin Jazz orchestra comprised of some of Berklee’s most talented students/alums and Boston’s finest musicians. The orchestra was created with the purpose to bridge the growing divide between the music and dance genres. This young, charismatic cast produces commanding &lt;br /&gt;presentations full of life, spirit, and energy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ritmo Masacote was founded out of Boston, MA in 2006 by Composer/Pianist Joel Massicot, also known as “Masacote”. Joel earned the alias Masacote in 1998 as an introduction into his piano solos while playing in Washington, DC. Masacote, Cuban slang, specifically refers to the rhythm created by combining the basic percussive instruments in Salsa/Mambo (the congas, guiro, timbales, clave, and bongo). More generally, this term refers to the design of merging various elements.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note that there is a 30 minute beginner lesson for the meetup at 8:30!  This is a great opportunity to meet other salsa fans.  I'm also always willing to talk about beginner steps and show a little and bet that others are willing to do the same.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Try to get there a little early so that we can all mingle for a bit before the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Angel S.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a fedora hat !!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angel Santiago</member_name><member_id>5161614</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288395006000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285441681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>By popular demand, Ritmo Masacote is back at Ryles Jazz Club !!</name><id>14893693</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287273600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/14893693/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/c/global_18212396.jpeg</photo_url></item>