<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>970 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.761542</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-521-8495</phone><name>COSI</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>867623</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.743376</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Cosi's is a good place to get together and just chat. Some times we just need others to listen, and just have a good old fashion dialog about life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its all about making friends &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is a Friend? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A friend is one of the nicest things you can have, and one of the best things you can be. &lt;br /&gt;A friend is a living treasure, and if you have one, you have one of the most valuable gifts in life.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A friend is the one who will always be beside you, through all the laughter and each and every tear.  &lt;br /&gt;A friend is the one thing you can always rely on; the someone you can always open up to; &lt;br /&gt;the wonderful person who always believes in you in a way that no else seems to. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A friend is a sanctuary. &lt;br /&gt;A friend is a smile. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A friend is a hand that is always holding yours, no matter where you are, no matter how close or far apart you may be.  &lt;br /&gt;A friend is someone who is always there and will always-always-care. A friend is a feeling of forever in the heart. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A friend is the one door that is always open.  &lt;br /&gt;A friend is the one to whom you can give your key. &lt;br /&gt;A friend is one of the nicest things you can have, and one of the best things you can be. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The poem &amp;quot;What is a Friend&amp;quot; is by Colin McCarty and can be found in the Blue Mountain Arts Collection &amp;quot;The Best Thing in life is a Friend&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the big group by the couches</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218670939000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Because we are fun and like good conversation and Smores and Cheesecake  LOL</why><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212275585000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's That Time Again to Meet Up at Cosi followed by The Cheescake Factory</name><id>8050958</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218497400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8050958/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/3/2/global_3269426.jpeg</photo_url></item>