<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Kate has so graciously offered to host a pot luck event for the Ethnic Dining Group. This is a chance to honor your own ethnic heritage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a main dish, side dish, or dessert from your own ethnic background (or any &amp;quot;ethnic&amp;quot; dish you know how to make). All drinks (bottled water, sodas, beer, wine, some spirits) will be provided. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GUESTS ARE LIMITED TO A MAXIMUM OF 18 DUE TO LIMITED SPACE, SO RSVP QUICKLY BEFORE SPOTS FILL UP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, please indicate what type of dish you plan to bring so that we do not end up with all Baklava or egg rolls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Kate has cats, so if you have allergies, be warned.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91 Northbound:&lt;br /&gt;Exit 39 &amp;amp; 41 (Kennedy Rd/Center St Exit) - Continue straight on Archer Rd - Turn right at Hayden Station Rd - House is on left side of the street (green, two-story colonial).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91 Southbound:&lt;br /&gt;Exit 41 &amp;amp; 39 (Center St Exit) - Turn left at South Center St - Turn right at Hayden Station Rd - House is on right side of the street (green, two-story colonial).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking/Entrance:&lt;br /&gt;You can drive up the driveway and park in the backyard or sideyard if you arrive early enough to grab a space. There's also street parking. Enter either through the red sidedoor (off the driveway) or the double glass doors (off the backyard).&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159467597000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1155153171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ethnic Pot Luck</name><id>5069279</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1158444000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/5069279/</event_url></item>