<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC's Cabot Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1487529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Chapter of the Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC) runs an annual Rock Climbing Program. This year it starts in March and runs through May of 2011 and is geared for those with little or no outdoor rock climbing experience. The program includes one informational night, one lecture and five field sessions (held on weekends). It is a great program and I highly recommend it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ultimate goal of the course is to have successful graduates safely second an experienced leader on a traditional-style multi-pitch climb. Participants will learn many technical rock climbing skills with an emphasis on safety. If you are interested in taking the Rock Climbing Program, please attend the informational meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The informational meeting will be held on Wednesday, Mar 9, 2011, at 7:00 PM in the Cabot Auditorium, at 4 Joy Street, Boston, MA.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Please click the following link for directions: &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/about/facilities/facilities-boston-directions.cfm"&gt;http://www.outdoors.org/about/facilities/facilities-boston-directions.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details and information on the 2011 Rock Climbing Program and information for the online registration will be described at this meeting, so attendance is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The field sessions of the Rock Program will be held on the first weekend of April and will run till first weekend of May at the Blue Hills Reservation just south of Boston. Instruction will include learning how to tie and use various climbing knots, belaying, rappelling, ascending, seconding and building anchors for top rope climbing. The Mountaineering Committee will also host two optional weekends of climbing in May. These weekends are only open for those who complete the program, giving participants an opportunity to climb as seconds on multi-pitch climbs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost of the program is $160 for AMC members and $200 for non-members. Please contact: rock@amcbostonclimbers.org for questions and more details.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a detailed schedule please go to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://amcbostonclimbers.org/instruction_rock_schedule.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://amcbostonclimbers.org/instruction_rock_schedule.shtml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Climb on,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lilly&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lilly</member_name><member_id>8472361</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299891709000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297746898000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Attend the AMC Rock Program Info Night</name><id>16569603</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299715200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/16569603/</event_url></item>