<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>266 Commercial Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.364317</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-742-3922</phone><name>Four Winds Bar &amp; Grill</name><city>Boston</city><id>1066225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051352</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;THIS IS RAIN OR SHINE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;We're meeting at a restaurant so we'll sort out once we're all there whether to brave the weather or not - but SoJust is about more than the activity - it's about the people you get to meet. So I'm sure there'll be great people and some will want to run around in the rain learning about the North End.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join SoJust for &lt;b&gt;Scavenger Hunt for Justice* on Saturday, October 3rd&lt;/b&gt;.  The search is on with a fun-filled list of historic, cultural and quirky items to locate (and photograph) in one of Boston's most famous neighborhoods - the North End. &lt;b&gt;Meet at Four Winds Bar &amp;amp; Grill at 2pm&lt;/b&gt; - which is also where we'll end up for dinner at 5pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No need to create a team&lt;/b&gt; - we'll randomly assign folks the day of the event - since getting to know new people is what SoJusters are all about. Instructions and the item list will be given out the day of the event at 2pm. There will be prizes for creativity and quantity so be sure to join us for dinner at Four Winds!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? Join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HEY ORGANIZERS!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers to share during dinner - there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Four Winds Bar &amp;amp; Grill is located at 266 Commercial Street. We'll gather there at 2pm and assign teams. Scavenger Hunt begins at 2:30 - so don't be late!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255993078000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253037573000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scavenger Hunt for Justice</name><id>11379211</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254592800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/11379211/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/c/global_10730716.jpeg</photo_url></item>