<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join me for brunch as well as our first Casino Night planning meeting for our group.  Please plan on attending if you are interested in helping out for our upcoming Casino Night in the works with the group. &lt;br /&gt;Joes American Bar and Grill offers a brunch menu as well as a regular lunch menu we can order from. &lt;br /&gt;Some topics we will be discussing and possiblely would need to gather a commitee to work on these topics: &lt;br /&gt;                                                    A. possible Location&lt;br /&gt;                                                    B. Casino Games/ supplies- who may have a craps/ black jack table, cards, card holder, etc..... &lt;br /&gt;                                                    C. Decorations/ coasters- paper supploes streamers&lt;br /&gt;                                                    D. food- thinking appetizer items like cut up veges/dip, spring rolls, chicken wings, etc.... &lt;br /&gt;                                                    E. Entertainment- alsways entertainment of some sort at a casino &lt;br /&gt;                                                    F. Members to teach us the games&lt;br /&gt;                                                    G. possible prizes&lt;br /&gt;                                                    H. Casino props&lt;br /&gt;                                                     I. other related topics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE be sure to stop by an ATM and have some cash on you before you arrive so the bill can work out perfectly at the end.   &lt;br /&gt;I am looking foward to our first meeting and a second meeting will be planned in the works. Hope you can attend!!! Lastly, please be 90 percent certain you are going to attend if placing a yes. I understand if things do come up last minute however its important to respect other memebers in the group who may have wanted to attend.  Also, If the event is full and would like to attend, please write a note in the &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; section and I will let you know if there is an opening available.&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, please remember to answer my questions whether RSVPing yes or no. It helps me out planning future events by getting members imput.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet at host stand and I will have a balloon w/ me as it seems to work</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>krista</member_name><member_id>3604506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249692343000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1958</urlname><id>1096649</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge and Boston Singles Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245800001000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch/ Casino Night Planning Meeting One </name><id>10720040</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246807800000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1958/events/10720040/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/8/global_3699192.jpeg</photo_url></item>