<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>165 Angell St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.827911</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Coco Pazzo</name><city>Providence</city><id>6733862</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.401184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurants and events in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Coco Pazzo - upstairs from the English Cellar Alehouse off Thayer St.!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coco Pazzo is one of the newer additions to the Thayer Street scene opening about a year ago and connected to the English Cellar Alehouse. So in many ways, its the best of both worlds! It has an expansive and tasteful bar and dining area that has large, long high-top tables down the center, making it a great place to mingle and chat. This will be the second official MNM at Coco Pazzo, the first time was totally fun and we had a great time, so let's do it again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coco Pazzo features Mugnaini oven baked traditional and modern Italian cuisine and tapas, so whether you have a big or small appetite, this one's for you!!! I personally LOVE the fig pizza and have been back several times with friends for early evening gatherings, particularly in the the summer when sidewalk seating available. Any season is a good time to go and its also a great place for a few people at the end of the bar near the windows. No matter when, it's always a good time! So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cocopazzori.com/default.html"&gt;http://www.cocopazzori.com/default.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Meetup. Ever. Except Hurricane Sandy and NYE 2012!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the scarf or hat in the picture, but we're not hard to find!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360632579000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359701816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Coco Pazzo!!!!!</name><id>102470862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360018800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/102470862/</event_url></item>