<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.359150</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 4, Room 231</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6010332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Steel giant POSCO's proposed mining project in India is the largest foreign direct investment in the country and will displace thousands of indigenous people. Panelists will discuss the political economy of the project, the social and environmental costs and benefits of such development models, and frameworks for understanding and challenging such models in the Global South.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moderator: &lt;br /&gt;

Balakrishnan Rajagopal - Associate Professor of Law and Development at the Department of Urban Studies and Planning, MIT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Panelists: &lt;br /&gt;

Sirisha Naidu is Associate Professor in the Department of Economics at Wright State University. Dr. Naidu earned a Ph.D. from the University of Massachusetts Amherst in 2007. Her research, mostly interdisciplinary in nature, focuses on the political economy of development and environment in countries of the global south. She conducts research on collective management and access to environmental commons, the effects of neo-liberal policies on human and environmental well-being, and the distribution of costs and benefits of environmental pollution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Balmurli Natrajan is Associate Professor of Anthropology, and Director of the University Core Curriculum at William Paterson University of New Jersey. His research and teaching interests include Group Formation (Caste, Class, Community), Development, Artisans, Agro-Science, State, Culture, South Asia, USA.His recent book is titled Culturalization of Caste in India: Identity and Inequality in a Multicultural Age (London: Routledge, 2011). He is currently working on the issues of rice farmers in Chhattisgarh. Balmurli is actively involved in popular education projects and solidarity work in in New Jersey and New York City. He is a member of the Mining Zone People’s Solidarity Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsored by: &lt;br /&gt;

Displacement Action and Research Network &lt;br /&gt;

Left@MIT &lt;br /&gt;

Association for India's Development MIT Chapter (www.aidboston.com)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supported by: &lt;br /&gt;

Alliance for a Secular and Democratic South Asia (www.southasiaalliance.org)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/296816673785032/?notif_t=plan_user_invited" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/296816673785032/?notif_t=plan_user_invited&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>swapna</member_name><member_id>8664561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368065639000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367205278000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Development for Whom? POSCO in India. Documentary+ Panel Discussion</name><id>116694842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368054000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/116694842/</event_url></item>