<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>back to Basics - A backyard Bar-b-Que! June's Friday the 13th theme is backyard bar-b-Que. My Weber coal Bar-B-Que is ready to go, the table and chairs are in the yard. Bring a lawn chair with you if more than 10 folk sign up! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be indoors and in the backyard.  &lt;br /&gt;Bring something to put on the grill or something that goes great with grilled foods. I am opening this up to more people than usual so that will be extra fun! I am going to invite my neighbors and make it more than a Meetup party.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By now everyone should know the routine. Plan to cook onsite unless your recipe takes longer than an hour to prepare. If the recipe calls for unusual equipment bring it with you. Any doubts just email Jennifer or myself. Remember someone will ask you how your dish fits the theme so have your answers ready! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It helps if people bring what they want to drink and are willing to share. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All adult folk are welcome. This is a monthly event with a good mix of ages and personalities. Come join us!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are back to basics - as in back to the second Friday night, and back to West Hartford! Back to my place and back in the backyard!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213663091000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>This will be fun because food always brings folks together. I've done cooking clubs before and they are always so much fun! We might play a board game after eatting or not...anything is possible.</why><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207959082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes June Meeting</name><id>7722968</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213398000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/7722968/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/global_4074206.jpeg</photo_url></item>