<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Drum Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.624310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-654-7990 </phone><name>Panera</name><city>Chelmsford</city><id>984022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.362696</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We all have diverse reasons for coming around to atheism. For some of us, human rights is one of them, or maybe the issue just confirms our choice to be an atheist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the history of many religions, protecting the religion and its sacred beliefs is put before human rights and the right to think freely. Many religions don't seem to care about minorities, or anyone outside the religion. Some even actively persecute minorities. The same is true of many governments, whether secular or not. Obviously a fundamentalist Islamist government like that of Iran squelches the human rights of its citizens. And the communist-emerging capitalist Republic of China likewise squelches criticism and limits the freedom to access information. But what about &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; civilizations like ours in the U.S.? As a minority, are the human rights of atheists put aside by &amp;quot;modern&amp;quot; governments?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shouldn't a government be about protecting the human rights of its citizens, including the right not to believe? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also discuss the human rights issues surrounding the new law in Arizona that requires law enforcement officials to inquire about the citizenship of people who appear to be illegal. Do you think the law is reasonable and necessary, or unreasonable and unfair? Does protecting our nation and our economic interests require that we border on infringing human rights? Our opinions are bound to be as varied as our fingerprints!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your thoughts about human rights, and/or any discussion materials such as articles, research, feedback from programs you've viewed, books you've read, etc. We typically have a laptop so we can cruise the web during the meeting. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the large group, some might be wearing atheistic shirts</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul S</member_name><member_id>4811434</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>5222022</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Valerie </member_name><member_id>7248057</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277055886000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lowellatheists</urlname><id>13032</id><group_lat>42.6300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3300018311</group_lon><name>Atheists of Greater Lowell</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273419448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Morning Topical Meeting--Human Rights</name><id>jqmnnynjbbc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277044200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lowellatheists/events/13428880/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/2/global_10991506.jpeg</photo_url></item>