<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>990 Great Plain Avenue </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02492</zip><lat>42.280225</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-449-4050</phone><name>Masala Art</name><city>Needham</city><id>1157180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236439</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Note that this meetup is on the THIRD Saturday (we usually meet on the second Saturday).  This is a change just for this one month!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Restaurant:  Masala Art in Needham&lt;br /&gt;Masala Art offers a buffet, including dosa and papri chat.  The buffet cost is $14, plus $1 for the meetup, plus tax and tip -- figure $19 per person (plus any extras, beverages, etc., ordered by individuals). If you opt to order from the menu, cost of your food plus 26 % (Tax and tip) + $1 to support the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Review from Library Journal:&lt;br /&gt;What irony that one of Calcutta's most devastating slums should be known as Anand Nagar, ``the City of Joy.'' By interweaving impressionistic glimpses from the lives of a French priest, a rickshaw driver, and an American doctor, Lapierre creates a searing vision of the struggle for survival, the flashing violence, and the social and cultural practices of the slum. His theme that from human misery can emerge joy might seem to some readers as a bogus acceptance of a terrible evil. Yet Lapierre's narrative slides skillfully in and out of both history and fiction to create an effective but horrible montage of disease, death, and destruction amid elements of charity, hope, and love. The City of Joy should elicit strong reactions from readers. BOMC and Quality Paperback Book Club alternates. John F. Riddick, Central Michigan Univ. Lib., Mt. Pleasant&lt;br /&gt;Copyright 1985 Reed Business Information, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276992406000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266089800000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June 2010 - The City of Joy, by Dominique LaPierre</name><id>12597143</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276963200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/12597143/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_5395668.jpeg</photo_url></item>