<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/d/a/3/event_7188547.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We are hosting Master Teacher of Christian Mysticism, Father Peter Bowes, for three days in New Haven. Father Peter will be teaching a seminar each evening that he is here this week. This is a very special event, and we are already anticipating that many group members will be attending all three seminars with this very dynamic and knowledgeable teacher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first evening: Why Did You Choose the Spiritual Path? Have you felt the calling of your heart and soul to seek God, or Spiritual Truth? That calling you feel is also the force of God calling out to you. When a person's soul begins to truly awaken to higher consciousness, this is felt as a pull toward a more spiritual way of life. This pull is God's invitation to come into a direct and intimate relationship with the Creator, the Source of life, love, and power. If you want to answer that call, or get closer to its source so that you can understand what it is calling you to, come and learn of the spiritual path that can lead you to your purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$25 Bring a friend for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-----------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;about the presenter: Father Peter Bowes is an ordained Priest and Master Teacher in the Order of Christ/Sophia, a Mystical Christian order. He is also an accomplished musician with mulitple albums to his credit. He travels nationally; giving workshops on the Inner Mystical Path. Listen to his podcasts at &lt;a href="http://www.askfatherpeter.com/"&gt;AskFatherPeter.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329076945000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328497054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Master Teacher Seminar: Why Did You Choose the Spiritual Path?</name><id>51183732</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328747400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/51183732/</event_url></item>