<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>380 Winter Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.397719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-7800</phone><name>Best Western</name><city>Waltham</city><id>746917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.258767</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;November 19, 2009- Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;Joe Craft, CPA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Top 10 mistakes even your Tax Professional can make.&lt;br /&gt;It’s your money!!  So no one is going to watch it like you will&lt;/b&gt;!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;You don’t have to know every detail of how your accountant does your taxes – but you know what they say:  You don’t know what you don’t know.  So come and find out! It may change your investing life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The more you know about your money and taxes, the more you’ll keep of the money, and the less you’ll pay of the taxes.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topics he'll cover:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to exclude the gain on a rental property &lt;br /&gt;How to know when you are keeping the property too long &lt;br /&gt;Do you sell the building, or the entity that holds the building? Which is better for you? &lt;br /&gt;When to plan for higher capital gains tax rates &lt;br /&gt;Be careful how you limit risk - it can cost you &lt;br /&gt;How to treat your business like a business &lt;br /&gt;Tax ramifications of options - both buying and selling &lt;br /&gt;Can you take 100% depreciation on that office furniture - (hint: when you can write off the whole amount NOW) &lt;br /&gt;Land improvements and why they are not land, and not a building, and why you care &lt;br /&gt;Write off even more - with cost segregation &lt;br /&gt;And lots more!! Joe gives real-world information that you can use today, to keep more in your pocket.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LEARN WHY IT’S NOT WHAT YOU MAKE THAT MATTERS, IT'S WHAT YOU KEEP THAT MATTERS THE MOST &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come hear from the expert - Joe Craft, CPA&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Joe Craft has been a Certified Public Accountant for over 20 years and is the author of &amp;quot;Annual Record Keeping Kit for Small and Home-Based Businesses.&amp;quot; His focus is to help people keep more of the money they make.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This meeting is good for 1 hour of Management credit for our PHP Program. Visit www.bostonareia.com for more information on PHP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:15 PM - Power Hour - Networking &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Best Western Hotel, 380 Winter St, Waltham, Ma &lt;br /&gt;Free to members, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258848484000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256237816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Top 10 Mistakes Even Your Tax Preparer Can Make</name><id>11687917</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258675200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/11687917/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/b/global_1787963.jpeg</photo_url></item>