<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 W Brookline St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.340148</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blackstone School Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>698342</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join us this and every Monday this summer for Salsa in the Park!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These fun outdoor events are sponsored by the Mayor's Office and are FREE and open to everyone--bring the whole family if you'd like! Whether you've been dancing salsa for years or you'd like to learn how, or if you'd just like to relax after work to the sounds of salsa music, join us in the park on Monday nights!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each night will feature live performances, dance instruction for all levels (beginner to advanced), and lots of time to dance and socialize. There will be food and drinks for sale, as well as other items. We have a great dance floor, and over 150 friendly dancers (of all levels) to connect with! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Please note:&lt;/u&gt; If it rains, the party will be inside the Community Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DiSponsors include: SalsaBoston.com, Boston Dance Alliance, El Show de Fernandito, Teddy's Shoes, BostonSalsero.com, MetaMovements and Boston ROCKS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dates &amp;amp; Times:  Mondays, June 30-August 18; 6:30 PM - 9:30 PM; at Blackstone Community Center and Park in the South End&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Location:&lt;/u&gt; Near the corner of W. Brookline &amp;amp; Washington Streets, in the South End. Look for the community center and the basketball courts, and we will be right next to them! (The fountain is visible from where we are, directly across W Brookline St from us.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Parking:&lt;/u&gt; On-Street parking available&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more information:&lt;/u&gt; www.metamovements.com&lt;br /&gt;Telephone: 617 983-1418&lt;br /&gt;Its great if you can RSVP through the meet-up group, but its not required!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions via Public Transportation:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a) Orange line to Back Bay, exit Dartmouth Street side (Its about a 10 minute walk).  Take a left on Dartmouth and continue, till you cross over Tremont Street and it becomes W.Dedham Street...then go right on Shawmut Ave, and right onto W Brookline St.; walk down and the basketball courts, center &amp;amp; park are on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;b) Silver Line (Washington St line):  Get off at the Newton St. stop.  You will be on Washington St.  If you were coming from Dudley and towards Boylston, you will continue in the direction the bus is going for one more block, and take a left at W. Brookline; walk down and the basketball courts, center &amp;amp; park are on your right.  If you were coming from Boylston and towards Dudley, you will walk back one block, and take a left on W. Brookline as described above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;c)  #1 bus down Mass Ave.  (from Harvard or Central Squares).  Get off at Washington St, and take a left (heading towards downtown, away from Roxbury).  Continue to W. Brookline St, and take a left; walk down and the basketball courts, center &amp;amp; park are on your right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anara</member_name><member_id>2988644</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219271569000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215837765000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salsa in the Park--don't miss the final party of the summer!</name><id>8325143</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219098600000</time><rsvp_limit>150</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/8325143/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/3/global_522835.jpeg</photo_url></item>