<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Sandy Ln</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02889</zip><lat>41.711296</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Warwick Public Library</name><city>Warwick</city><id>716684</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.402734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The &amp;quot;RI&amp;quot; Tea Party  will hold their first open meeting of thier strategy to engage in active citizen governance.  It is time for us to roll up our sleeves and get involved in real political action. When we met at the State House in June we told our elected officials, &amp;quot;You work for us.&amp;quot; It is time for us to exercise our right to supervise our government and hold it accountable. &lt;br /&gt;We envision a somewhat decentralized organization of members conducting a variety of projects to accomplish this.  You may also contribute your ideas by emailing to: ideas@riteaparty.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The purpose of our meeting is to begin organizing and establishing action plans for the Tea Party's future. This is a very important meeting and we seek your active participation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We the People of the RI Tea Party endeavor to promote good government practices by advocating for fiscal responsibility, accountability, and a return to the core principles set forth in our State and US Constitutions by our forefathers.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To achieve this vision we must go far beyond protests. Our strategy is to engage in active citizen governance.  It is time for us to roll up our sleeves and get involved in real political action. When we met at the State House in June we told our elected officials, &amp;quot;You work for us.&amp;quot; It is time for us to exercise our right to supervise our government and hold it accountable. &lt;br /&gt;We envision a somewhat decentralized organization of members conducting a variety of projects to accomplish this.  You may also contribute your ideas by emailing to: ideas@riteaparty.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Listed on our calendar as a courtesy to support other Patriotic groups.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hockeygirl</member_name><member_id>9250309</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347732910000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers</urlname><id>1425841</id><group_lat>41.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258836542000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"RI" Tea Party Kick Off Open Meeting  RSVP to riteaparty.net</name><id>11927759</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259105400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers/events/11927759/</event_url></item>