<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join Conserving Tolland to take a walk with the llamas at the Tobiasson forest. The group will be guests of the Joshua Trust which owns the lovely 82 acre piece donated by the late Al and Doris Tobiasson. Free and open to the public. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Echo, Stratus, and Nimbus will take a gentle stroll with the group on this 1 hour, slow paced walk through a fairly flat forest. Owners George and Lisa Pizzi will be on hand to tell the group about llamas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Rain cancels the event! 4/2/08 has 40% prediction of rain for the event day. Please e-mail (no phone provided) Conserving Tolland at conserving_tolland@comcast.net to see if canceled for Sat. morning if not sure. *** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;* From I-84 take Exit 68 in Tolland &lt;br /&gt;* Go left at end of exit &lt;br /&gt;* Take right onto Cider Mill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;* Go to Grant Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;* Left on Noah Ln. &lt;br /&gt;* Drive to end, park at end of cud-de-sac. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions via Mapquest: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/199+Noah+Ln+Tolland+CT+06084-3847/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership may be at this event. Just mingle with the other hikers! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conserving Tolland has protected over 1,000 acres and their purpose is to proactively encourage action to conserve and preserve land in Tolland, CT. See their website at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.conservingtollandct.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.conserving...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Joshua Trust has protected over 3,000 acres in eastern CT. For further information on the trust, please call (860) 896-1502 or visit their website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.joshuaslandtrust.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.joshuaslan...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership may be at this event. Conserving Tolland will sponsor the event as guests of the Joshua Trust. Just mingle with other hikers.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207577291000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>This hike harkens back to times past in the South American Andes as Llamas were the only animal large enough and domesticated enough to act as pack animals. Unique experience with these interesting animals.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207187984000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike with Llamas at the Tabiasson Forest in Tolland Ct</name><id>7662703</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207404000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7662703/</event_url></item>