<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076322</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rusty Hammer</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1023192</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/6/c/event_179961612.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOLIDAY BOOK SWAP! - Our tradition for the Portsmouth Book Club has been a Secret Santa book swap for the December meetup.  If you would like to participate, bring a wrapped book with you to book club.  It can be new or used - any book at all.  A favorite book, or one that you've always wanted to read.  Bring a book, get a book!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book club selection for December is &lt;strong&gt;The Weight of Water&lt;/strong&gt; by Anita Shreve.  Here is a description from the publisher:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"I wonder this: If you take a woman and push her to the edge, how will she behave?" The question is posed by Jean, a photographer, who arrives on Smuttynose Island, off the coast of New Hampshire, to research a century-old crime. As she immerses herself in the details of the case--an outburst of passion that resulted in the deaths of two women--Jean herself enters precarious emotional territory. The suspicion that her husband is having an affair burgeons into jealousy and distrust, and ultimately propels Jean to the verge of actions she had not known herself capable of--actions with horrific consequences. Everywhere hailed for its beauty and power, The Weight of Water takes us on an unforgettable journey through the furthest extremes of emotion.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And from Publishers Weekly:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In 1873, two women living on the Isles of Shoals, a lonely, windswept group of islands off the coast of New Hampshire, were brutally murdered. A third woman survived, cowering in a sea cave until dawn. More than a century later, Jean, a magazine photographer working on a photoessay about the murders, returns to the Isles with her husband, Thomas, and their five-year-old daughter, Billie, aboard a boat skippered by her brother-in-law, Rich, who has brought along his girlfriend, Adaline. As Jean becomes immersed in the details of the 19th-century murders, Thomas and Adaline find themselves drawn together-with potentially ruinous consequences. Shreve (Where or When; Resistance) perfectly captures the ubiquitous dampness of life on a sailboat, deftly evoking the way in which the weather comes to dictate all actions for those at sea. With the skill of a master shipbuilder, Shreve carefully fits her two stories together, tacking back and forth between the increasingly twisted murder mystery and the escalating tensions unleashed by the threat of a dangerous shipboard romance. Written with assurance and grace, plangent with foreboding and a taut sense of inexorability, The Weight of Water is a powerfully compelling tale of passion, a provocative and disturbing meditation on the nature of love.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the books which were voted on but didn't win the vote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Unbearable-Lightness-Being-Novel/dp/0061148520/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1352907773&amp;amp;sr=1-1&amp;amp;keywords=the+unbearable+lightness+of+being"&gt;The Unbearable Lightness of Being&lt;/a&gt; - Milan Kundera&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Pym-Novel-Mat-Johnson/dp/0812981766/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1352907797&amp;amp;sr=1-1&amp;amp;keywords=pym"&gt;Pym&lt;/a&gt; - Mat Johnson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Night-Circus-Erin-Morgenstern/dp/0307744434/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1352907825&amp;amp;sr=1-1&amp;amp;keywords=the+night+circus"&gt;The Night Circus&lt;/a&gt; - Erin Morgenstern&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed seeing everyone for last night book discussion on &lt;strong&gt;Gone Girl&lt;/strong&gt; by Gillian Flynn.  We had a lot to discuss!  Here is my review for Gone Girl on Seacoast Online:  &lt;a href="http://blogs.seacoastonline.com/seacoast-nh-books/2012/10/31/gone-girl-by-gillian-flynn/"&gt;Gone Girl Book Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357698393000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352907342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club December - The Weight of Water</name><id>dpskncyqqbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355270400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/91358712/</event_url></item>