<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>238 Deer Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.077565</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Portsmouth VFW Hall</name><city>Portsmouth </city><id>883909</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.761881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000099 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/a/e/event_188122702.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Hi Trailblazers come join us for an fun evening of dancing to Christmas music as we listen to the Jumbo Circus Peanuts band play.  Doors open at 8 the band start's playing around 8:30, come early to grab a table. Cost about $5  or  10. Well worth it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000099 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;Love it or not, Christmas happens, so why not get out and make the best of it? Huh? (Or, do you wanna fight?) There is no better way to relieve the stresses of the season than our annual Winter Soulstice Ball and Throw Down. We'll have classic Christmas songs from Alvin and the Chipmunks, Johnny Marks, the Ray Coniff Singers, and Tennessee Ernie Ford. Also an old-fashioned Yankee swap with Roger Maris, Mickey Mantle, Whitey Ford and Yogi Berra. Not to mention appearances by Rudolph, Snow White, the Easter Bunny and Richard Simmons dressed as Totie Fields. Where you gonna top that? Huh? Zombie Biker Elves admitted half price. Please come and reduce the chances you'll be at home when your tree catches fire and burns the condo down. We'd hate to see you suffer like that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on who you talk to, this 12-piece band is either a Seacoast institution or should be confined in one. Others have observed that the group is merely a collection of professional drinkers with a music problem. Debate aside, one thing is clear — the Jumbo Circus Peanut philosophy starts and ends with fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000099 ; font-size : x-small"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000099 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;Like any great musical organization, the band was born one night in a tiny smoky kitchen when two trombonists, a clarinet player and an alto saxophonist collided over a case of beer and a couple of sheet music fake books. Collectively, at that time, the founding musicians had not picked up their respective instruments in something like 60 years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000099 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;With the later addition of a rhythm section and even more melody instruments (not to mention two more trombones,) the Jumbo Circus Peanuts outgrew their kitchen home, performing in local bars and street events for the benefit of friends, family and those who came to confirm the existence of what one observer described as a "musical Loch Ness monster in drag."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000099 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;Today, after nearly 15 years of Seacoast performances, the Jumbo Circus Peanuts are the area's &lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;top-drawing musical group&lt;/span&gt; with an ever-expanding repertoire that sails around the musical worlds of pop, funk, swing and rock — with stops that include Hollywood, Broadway, Detroit, Latin America and Hawaii.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356235463000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355618609000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Solstice Dance</name><id>95494042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356224400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/95494042/</event_url></item>