<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paradigm Shifts&lt;/strong&gt; - How visionary businesses at all stages lead, leverage and profit from new technology!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfoct2011.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you working to form a cutting edge technology startup? Is your goal to lead, identify or align with changes in Technology, industry and investment? Do you have a clear view on where technology and the future are headed? Working in a technology startup can change the world. Shifts in technology tools and platforms have fundamentally altered how we view and perform in our professional and private communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do visionary leaders identify potential technologies or markets that may have major marketable potential? How do investors pick those &amp;lsquo;big waves&amp;rsquo; to ride? What are some of the basic signs that a technology has the potential to become a major market force? How can you lead and align with the changing technology and investment landscape? What resources are available in incubators that can help support launching significant technical ideas and business plans? How do you survive the early and maturing stages of a startup and maintain the inventiveness that lead to success?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next Entretech Forum we will explore the paradigm shifts of major technology and how entrepreneurs and investors have lead major change in businesses and communities. Our forum will discuss how businesses have formed around change, resources available to new startups and more. We will open up the floor for an interactive discussion with our panelists and audience. We welcome startups in all fields to join us. The forum&amp;rsquo;s panel will draw from leaders in industry, academic and government fields. The panel&amp;rsquo;s goal is to help startups better understand, utilize and leverage their experience in launching businesses, identifying major changes in technology and supporting startups. Please join us for what will be an informative and interactive discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/gregory.jpg" width="90" height="102" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dan Gregory&lt;/strong&gt; has been the CEO and a member of senior management teams at multiple publishing and digital media companies. Dan has worked for Capital City Communications, Scholastic, New England Business Services, and Vertigo Development Group. Most recently, he co-founded Turnstone Publishing Group and founded The Launch Group, a consulting practice advising clients on his great passion: launching new companies and product lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, Dan is on the faculty of the College of Business Administration where he oversees a venture incubator within the Masters of Technological Entrepreneurship program, which grants academic credit to students for starting new technology ventures. He is the faculty adviser to IDEA, Northeastern&amp;rsquo;s student-run venture accelerator, which in two years has helped over a hundred students and young alumni/ae start companies (www.neu.edu/idea). Dan received a BA from Wesleyan University and an MBA from Harvard Business School, where he concentrated on Marketing and Entrepreneurial Management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/spilgelman.jpg" width="90" height="90" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ori Spigelman&lt;/strong&gt; Co-Founder and VP of BD at TIGI (www.tigi.co.il), Israel based maker of next generation solar collectors for high-energy throughput in adverse conditions. Prior to TIGI, Co-Founder and Head of BD at Akiban Technologies (www.akiban.com), Boston based database-virtualization company. VP BD at Fundtech Corp (www.fundtech.com). Project Manager of Axonix, medical device company (under the Israeli Incubators Program).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ori served in Israel&amp;rsquo;s Armed Forces as officer in the Signals Corps and is a graduate of MIT&amp;rsquo;s Sloan (MBA) and Tel-Aviv University (Mathematics and CS).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/goldschmidtt.jpg" width="90" height="131" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Marv Goldschmitt &lt;br /&gt;

Consultant Marv Goldschmitt has been involved in the &amp;ldquo;bleeding&amp;rdquo; edge of the computer industry since he ran one of the country&amp;rsquo;s oldest computer stores in 1979 where he helped to introduce the first spreadsheet, Visicalc. He then joined Lotus Development as the initial head of product marketing with overall responsibility for the introduction of 1-2-3 to the market. As Lotus&amp;rsquo; VP of Business Development, he created the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy for international operations, OEM relationships, product acquisitions and its role in leading the effort to combat software piracy, the latter by heading the software industry&amp;rsquo;s first committee to fight for the general recognition of software as intellectual property.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since Lotus, Marv has continued to work with and help companies foster innovative new technologies in such disparate areas as development environments, free email (where he filed the first patent for advertiser supported email), healthcare information, database security, strategic decision support, virtual worlds and digital photography. He currently is a member of the IBM Data Governance Council; provides strategic consulting to a variety of young companies; and spends an unreasonable amount of time as a professional photographer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/Chipalkatti.jpg" width="90" height="136" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Makarand H. Chipalkatti, Sr. Dir. SSL &amp;amp; Emerging Market Initiatives, OSRAM SYLVANIA INC&lt;/strong&gt;. Dr. Makarand &amp;ldquo;Chips&amp;rdquo; Chipalkatti is Senior Director, Solid State Lighting and Emerging Market Initiatives for OSRAM SYLVANIA since March 2010 with special focus on SSL advocacy and standards for OSRAM in the NAFTA region. Chips began his professional career with GTE Laboratories and joined OSRAM SYLVANIA R&amp;amp;D in 1993. His work included research on advanced materials and organic light sources. In 2000, he started-up OSRAM&amp;rsquo;s LED lighting business in North America and led the business till 2005. Since then, Dr. Chips served as Head of Strategic Innovation Management for OSRAM SYLVANIA and continues to serve as a key member of OSRAM&amp;rsquo;s strategic innovation community. Chips&amp;rsquo; role as a corporate entrepreneur has led to several new business and open innovation initiatives. Dr. Chips has played a pioneering role in the SSL industry and was a founder member and chairman of the Solid State Lighting Section of NEMA till 2006, and a founding member of NGLIA and ASSIST.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderator:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frederic Bowne is the Founder and Managing Principle of Perpetuation, LLC a Management Consulting and Investment Company (est. 2007). Fred has over 20 of years experience in Financial Service Information Technology and private investing. Other market segments he has served include government administration and finance, and non-profit. Perpetuation helps startups and growth companies with organization, planning and strategy in business development and information technology. The company actively manages a private fund that invests in technology and other markets. Fred also works with market risk analysis, technology research, project management, business continuity, cyber security and disaster relief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Cost: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;$25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Grumer</member_name><member_id>12792562</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318982243000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314975910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paradigm Shifts - How visionary businesses at all stages lead, leverage and prof</name><id>qflkbcypnbxb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318977000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/32003852/</event_url></item>