<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>101 Ashmun St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.315670</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yale Police Headquarters-Rose Center</name><city>New Haven</city><id>264390</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.929020</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Childrens' Crisis Center is hosting a 'Back to School' party for the kids and they are looking for our help in making this a fun day for them! We've been asked to sponsor a craft table and do something fun with the kids.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW YOU CAN HELP!&lt;br /&gt;The target audience is kids K-12, but according to the Executive Director, the high school kids are less enthusiastic than the little ones. So I would say our real audience will be K-6. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be face-painting supplies, a station to help kids make book markers, and other miscellaneous crafts. The great Fire Fighters of New Haven will be present with a truck for the kids to climb on. There will also be a bunny petting station. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be spread throughout to help the kids. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MORE OPPORTUNITIES:&lt;br /&gt;.... and for those of you looking to lend a hand but can't take Thursday off - you're in luck! The Crisis Center also needs some help in packing back packs for the kids any time leading up to that day. We will be hosting a Pizza Party on the 16th to officially stuff the bags. &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/calendar/6151436/"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to sign up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Each year, we collect new school supplies for the young children of our clients and distribute them at a 'Back-To-School' Party. We usually have about 75 kids in attendance. This year's party is scheduled for August 23 from 2:00-3:30 pm. Do you think any of the New Haven Collective members would be interested in attending the party and leading some activities with the children? In the past, we have either had tables set up with different activities that the children could choose from, or we have also had the children seated at tables, all doing the same activity. This is a great volunteer opportunity because the more volunteers we have, the better.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info on the Coordinating Council For Children In Crisis, Inc. check out their website at:  &lt;a href="http://www.ccccnh.org/"&gt;http://www.ccccnh.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT:&lt;br /&gt;Amanda O. -203-823-5332&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188061386000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176742489000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Can You Play Hooky From Work for a Good Cause???</name><id>5676375</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187888400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5676375/</event_url></item>