<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>649 Shirley Street</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.368465</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Winthrop Yacht Club</name><city>Winthrop</city><id>4700382</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.971848</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Hello MassBaySailors, &lt;br /&gt;

 Please consider attending this event. &lt;br /&gt;

 Get yourself away from Christmas shopping and the Holiday hustle &amp;amp; bustle for 1 evening and come hang out with a bunch of sailors for an evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The Sxith Annual MassBaySailors Winter Solstice Holiday Party! &lt;br /&gt;

 Also, get your “Galactic Alignment On” &lt;br /&gt;

Galactic Alignment 2012 | 21-12-2012 Winter Solstice Conjunction With Dark Rift &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.2012rising.com/article/the-galactic-alignment-in-2012-part-1" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.2012rising.com/article/the-galactic-alignment-in-2012-part-1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Friday December 21, 2012 7:00 to ???? &lt;br /&gt;

 (please mark your calendars!) &lt;br /&gt;

 Winthrop Yacht Club &lt;br /&gt;

 649 Shirley Street, Winthrop , MA 02152&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill’s cell # (617) 256-4822 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.win-yc.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.win-yc.org/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 As busy as we all are, I ask you to make time for another MassBaySailors get together. &lt;br /&gt;

 This is an open invitation to all MassBaySailors, their guests and any area sailing enthusiasts. &lt;br /&gt;

 Planning is underway for the&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sixth Annual MassBaySailors Winter Solstice Holiday Party; &lt;br /&gt;

 Yup, the 6th. In 2005 we had 19 people attend an evening of dinner and drinks at Ironside’s Grill in Charlestown. The next 4 years we had 20 to 30 people attend each time at WYC. I hope we can get everyone back again this year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each year we’ve had an optional Yankee Swap (with a nautical gift theme) which turns out to be pretty fun. &lt;br /&gt;

 This year it’ll again be held at WYC, you can’t beat FREE. I’m coordinating with our Bar Manager to insure we have adequate accommodations. It’ll be a cash bar with our full Pub Menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll play some music, do a Yankee Swap (with a nautical gift theme in the $20 to $25 range) and maybe even a photo/video presentation. &lt;br /&gt;

 Please understand that the most important element of this event will be us all getting together to celebrate the shortest day of the year, sharing some Holiday enthusiasm and rounding the mark towards next season. &lt;br /&gt;

 Get your “Galactic Alignment On” ; &lt;br /&gt;

 The winter solstice of 2012 will occur at 11:11 GMT on of course 21-12-2012 the same day the Long Count flips over. On that morning the sun will appear to rise into the patch of sky we refer to as the galactic center or nuclear bulge. It is the location of the super-massive black hole at the center of rotation for the Milky Way galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doomsday countdown for Maya 2012 calendar on Winter Solstice today&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.examiner.com/article/doomsday-countdown-for-maya-2012-calendar-on-winter-solstice-today" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.examiner.com/article/doomsday-countdown-for-maya-2012-calendar-on-winter-solstice-today&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 In a story that getting more buzz than the Mega Millions, the longest night of the year begins tonight (Wednesday) at 11:30 CST, it also marks the shortest day as well. For the science geek in you, it simply means the sun will be at its lowest in the Southern Sky, or tilted 23.5 degrees away from the North Pole. &lt;br /&gt;

 While celebrations are planned around the world at the milestone, some people are feeling the doom and gloom of the 2012 end of the world countdown as predicted by the Maya. In short, today is somewhat bitter-sweet if you're fixated on the apocalypse and end of world predictions, post Orwellian era. Remember George Orewell's 1984 doomsday prediction in his epic novel? &lt;br /&gt;

While the world did not end in 1984 as the master story teller predicted, geophysicists and astronomers are paying close attention to the countdown Maya buzz. Like anything else, there is a scientific explanation of about anything for non-biblical believers. Even the winter solstice and Mega Millions are scientifically explained. &lt;br /&gt;

Mayan Calendar in 2012: Baktuns, Pole Shifts Behind end of world predictions&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>BillS</member_name><member_id>2822960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356155982000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353775324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Sixth Annual MassBaySailors Winter Solstice Holiday Party </name><id>92625472</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356134400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/92625472/</event_url></item>