<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>297-2053</phone><name>Trinity College Life Sciences Center Auditorium</name><city>Hartford</city><id>440540</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join international film buffs as well as Spanish language speakers and learners at Trinity College's free weekly showings of Iberian and Latin American films.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's film is Calle 54, directed by Fernando Trueba (Spain, 2000).&lt;br /&gt;If you appreciate Latin Jazz, CALLE 54 is the film for you. Musicians get to express how they feel about the music, but this is kept to a minimum. It's not really a documentary per se. It is literally - visually - seeing the soundtrack LIVE in all its colors, and putting faces to the various musical artists featured. I was most impressed with Chucho Valdés. His lyrical piano artistry is simply exquisite! The musical journey starts out at New Jersey with Paquito D'Rivera on the alto sax and clarinet, and his 11-person band with trumpet, guitar, piano, bass, drums, vibes, marimba, and batá drum sounds. Next is a samba from New York with Eliane Elías on the piano - barefoot on the pedals - with accompanists on bass and drums. We are treated to the blend of flamenco and jazz from Chano Dóminguez and co. Continuing is Michel Camilo delivering his piano artistry with bass and drums accompaniment. Yes, Tito Puente in his impish smile and white suit (his all stars combo also in white) provided an energetic performance as expected. Tito striking magic on his timbales and vibes, teamed with flute, piano, tenor sax, congas, and bass, all capably interchanged on timbales and cowbell to keep the rhythm a-lively! Along the dance vein, we have Puntilla and Nueva Generación, with voices, congas, batás, bass, percussion, and dance! Such lively beats! To wrap up, yes, two pianos: Chucho playing with his father Bebo Valdés. Four hands a-dancing on the Steinway keys simply transport you to a state too marvelous for words! &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0260775/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Tom Harrington&lt;br /&gt;Films start at 7:00 in the Life Sciences Building. &lt;br /&gt;For directions to Trinity, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.edu/AboutTrinity/VisitingTrinity/DirectionsToTrinity.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Or call (860) 297-2053.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.edu/NR/rdonlyres/92062DC6-138A-430E-9ADA-5A209B506787/0/campusmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can come earlier than 6:45, please join me for supper in the Cave cafeteria (basement of Mather Hall, no id required). Prices are reasonable and the food is quite good. I usually get there by 5:15.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll display a Meet-up sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret Vincent</member_name><member_id>1777042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236813240000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233944098000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film: Calle 54</name><id>9688075</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236211200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/9688075/</event_url></item>