<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>East Hill Farm is working farm &amp;amp; is nestled at the base of Mt. Monadock, next to a beautiful lake, in southern Troy NH which was considered sacred by the Native American Indians &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;is also known for its healing energy.&lt;br /&gt;It has rooms in the Inn, cabins, and rooms over looking the lake at Trails End, which is where we will be staying.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It has an indoor, and outdoor swimming pool, a sauna, and hot tub.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Including in the price&lt;br /&gt;($120 per person, per night, not counting tips) Is (3) homecooked delicious meals, made from the farm, served family style.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have the entire building at Trails end, reserved just for us!&lt;br /&gt;The rooms are beautiful, with (9) rooms with queen size beds, and (9) with twin beds, and a refrigerator.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a common living room to ourselves, with a tv and dvd player.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People can have lunch before they come, or pay extra for lunch there, at noon on Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;The price for the extra lunch is about $12.00 including tax and tip. If you are interested in getting there early for lunch on Saturday, you need to let the inn know&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule of Events:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00- 1:00 pm- Lunch (optional) $12.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00- 2:00 pm- Meet &amp;amp; Greet In Living Room at Trails End- Settle into rooms, Tour of the Farm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sat April 25th 2:00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Option #1- There will be a trip to hike Mt. Monadnock scheduled on Sat from approx 2pm- 4:30pm- Tony will be leading this expedition, &amp;amp; will be following the easiest trail on the mountain, which is an easy climb.&lt;br /&gt;Will have snacks for top of mountain. If you are interested in this option, please note this on rsvp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about Mt. Monadnock, check out the following links.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.monadnockmountain.com/ - 4k&lt;br /&gt;www.nhstateparks.org/state-parks/alphabetical-order/monadnock-state-park/&lt;br /&gt;- 26k&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Option #2- For those who do not want to climb the mountain, horseback riding is available for $40 per person for 1/2 hour guided trail ride.&lt;br /&gt;This must be scheduled with inn prior to time of ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Option #3- Activities w/ Tala at the Inn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:00- 3:00 Free channeling class- Have your pineal and pituitary gland activated for channeling and learn techniques to channel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:00- 4:00- Short Walk to the Waterfall&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:00- 4:30- Trip to Store&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:30- 5:30- Free Time/ Happy Hour Social in Dining Room&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30- 6:30- Dinner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30- 8:30- Trails End Living Room&lt;br /&gt;Divinations Games: Rune reading, angel cards, wishing on a star &amp;amp; tea leaf reading&lt;br /&gt;Evening Discussion- Book of questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30- 10:30&lt;br /&gt;~ Pagan/ Spiritual Movie- TBA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:00- Hot Tubbing/ Free Time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, April 26th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00- 10:00 am- Breakfast&lt;br /&gt;(Please note, you have to be in the dining room by 9am if you want&lt;br /&gt;breakfast! )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:00- 11:00- Spell Craft- Make money pentacles &amp;amp; learn money correspondences (donation for supplies)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:00- 12:00 Free time/ Pack-Up&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00- 1:00 Lunch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~You can choose to participate or not participate in the above mentioned schedule&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Kids and families are welcome :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ If you do not like the options on the menu, the Inn will cook just about anything to your request...&lt;br /&gt;Vegetarian meals are also available, please let the inn know upon reservation....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Alcohol policy is BYOB&lt;br /&gt;(Bring your own booze)&lt;br /&gt;We will be making a trip to the store on Sat where you can buy that and anything you need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Massages are available, $40 for 30 mins and I believe $60 for $65 minutes ( I think) These must be scheduled ahead of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Upon making your reservation, please let the inn know if you are staying in a room with another person (two twin beds) or if you want a room of your own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Dogs ARE allowed,&lt;br /&gt;$10.00 extra, and you MUST let them know, and book a CABIN, rather than a room, as dogs can only stay in the cabins.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VERY IMPORTANT PLEASE NOTE!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; You can still call and put a $25 deposit down for this meet up, however, you should do it as SOON as possible, as they will start booking other people in Trails End rooms after Jan 17th-&lt;br /&gt;As long as there are rooms still available, you can book a reservation for this meet up until&lt;br /&gt;April 23rd. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*ALSO*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This reservation can be canceled up until (3) weeks- 21 days prior to the reservation, though you will only get $10 of the $25 dollars back, as they will take a $15 cancellation fee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ANYTHING LESS than 21 day cancellation, and you will be charged the total $120 fee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their cancellation fees are pretty strict, so please keep this in mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can reserve by calling East Hill Farm at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(800) 242-6495&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For information, call:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(603) 242-6495&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will need to put a credit card deposit down, and if you are unable to do this, you can call and ask them if you can send a check.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To check out the link for East Hill Farm, go to:&lt;br /&gt;www.east-hill-farm.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the Living Room At Trails End</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252446349000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pagans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pagan-1307</urlname><id>1221723</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pagan Learning Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230859912000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trip To East Hill Farm</name><id>9421944</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240678800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pagan-1307/events/9421944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/c/global_4771708.jpeg</photo_url></item>