<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Four Seasons lounge (We'll be in the lounge to LEFT of main entrance when you walk in -- it's just before the restuarant!)</name><city>Boston</city><id>204721</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Everyone - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know it's busy before the holidays but we wanted to throw a date in if anyone is interested. (I love it that others are helping out!) Brian had a great suggestion.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steppin' it up a little for some pre-holiday festivity at thet FOUR SEASONS. There is a nice cocktail area just before you enter the restaurant. Big windows allow a nice view of the park across the street. Wednesday evening shouldn't be too crowded--there is also a piano bar (live music at 6).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we arrive just after work hours we should be able to get a nice spot. So let's try to make this for 5:30-6.. but we'll be there a while, so we can do like last time and call me to see if we're still there. Easy access to transportation. Street parking if you're skilled, shopping nearby (and open late this time of year). Parking for a price at hotel  o nearby garages. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully this downtown spot is convenient for some who couldnt join last time.... next time Framingham!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael B</member_name><member_id>2958968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1166828582000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>divorcesupport-249</urlname><id>368805</id><group_lat>42.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Boston/Burbs Life after Divorce Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1165672402000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pre-Holiday Festivities at the Four Seasons</name><id>5316679</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1166655600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/divorcesupport-249/events/5316679/</event_url></item>