<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This month's presenter will be Kate Beeders, speaking on &amp;quot;What is Tapping?:  The Meridian Tapping Technique&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This powerful technique is known as Meridian Tapping Technique, which includes EFT (Emotional Freedom Technique).  It’s a combination of mind/body medicine and acupuncture(without the needles), and is also known as “emotional acupuncture”.  Clients can be helped quickly, easily, painlessly,  over the phone or in person with “tapping”.  Although, its not a “miracle cure” it can often get results where nothing else has worked.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate Beeders is a Success Coach who utilizes “tapping” with her clients to help them overcome obstacles that are blocking their success.   She’s able to help people overcome life long negative beliefs or changing previous self-sabotaging behaviors.   Her favorite part of helping people with this technique is the quick change in them after the session- it’s as if a huge weight has been taken off of them.  Kate had previously held a very successful career in the business world, but after being exposed to many life altering experiences and and inspiring people,  made a change to a career to the world of energy healing.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her speciality is helping people eliminate stressful issues that result in cravings/overeating, teeth grinding, insomnia,procrastination and poor work performance.  She tries to incorporate the following in her daily life: mediation, Law of Attraction, Quantum Physics, and lots of positive energy.  Kate’s training background includes: EFT, MTT, Ethics and Legal Principles for Practitioners of Energy Therapies; The Sacred Contract Between Practitioner and Client.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate hosts a live radio show in Boston that can also be heard/seen over the internet.  You can view a list of upcoming guests on her show at www.successcoachingwithKate.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This powerful technique is known as Meridian Tapping Technique, which includes EFT (Emotional Freedom Technique).  It’s a combination of mind/body medicine and acupuncture(without the needles), and is also known as “emotional acupuncture”.  Clients can be helped quickly, easily, painlessly,  over the phone or in person with “tapping”.  Although, its not a “miracle cure” it can often get results where nothing else has worked.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate will be demonstrating the use of &amp;quot;tapping&amp;quot; by eliminating a volunteer's craving.  If you would like to be that volunteer, please bring the food item to the meeting that you would like to eliminate.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings begin with a potluck lunch and time to get to know everyone in the group a bit better.  Let us know what you'll bring when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup fee: $10&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will welcome you at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Marks</member_name><member_id>5692888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260551404000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Alternative Health Practioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>alternative-703</urlname><id>1152400</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247670616000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup:  What is Tapping?</name><id>10882046</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258129800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/alternative-703/events/10882046/</event_url></item>