<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;Picture yourself sitting in your lounge chair or on a blanket, outside, on a glorious summer evening with stars twinkling overhead and a gentle breeze wafting through your hair.  Well here we go again!! The group is having another road trip to the Mendon Drive-In and here's to having some fun!!  Should prove to be a nostalgic re-visit for some and a first -time experience for others. We'll meet at the large letter &lt;b&gt;T&lt;/b&gt; at the  Alewife Station outside the Bertucci?s Restaurant where Susan and Tom will coordinate the drivers and passengers.  People who are willing to drive for this event, can park in the Summer Shack Restaurant parking lot across the street from the T Station.  Those who need a ride, should arrive on the Red Line and wait at the large &lt;b&gt;T&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be no Maybe RSVP's. Since the drive-in charges $20 a carload, both drivers and passengers will be depending on each other to be there and share the cost.  The total number of people that can go will depend on the number of people who will be driving. Cars should probably seat 4 people and passengers will of course have to chip in for gas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll plan to get there well before sunset and do some tailgating. There's a tasty concession stand there (word is that locals go just for the food sometimes)and you can bring in food and non-alcoholic drinks.  Bring Frisbees and other such stuff for a little relaxation before showtime. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When you RSVP, please write in the comments if you can volunteer to drive or if you are going to be a passenger.&lt;/b&gt;  Also, if you?re a driver, please indicate how many passengers, not counting yourself, can go with you.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alas, we won't know the movie that is showing until the Monday before. Since we are all in this one together, for better or worse?. dropping out at the last minute would be grounds for being removed from the group and would not at all be appreciated.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll keep updating this posting with more info and ideas as we get nearer to the big night.  The movie will start around 8:30 so we?ll plan to meet at Alewife at 5:45.  Rain or shine event.   Also, for liability purposes, we can only include people over the age of 18. &lt;br /&gt;Here's the link to the Mendon Drive-In &lt;a href="http://www.mendondriv?" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mendondriv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you decide to join us for what should be a fun evening, &lt;br /&gt;Susan and Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom and Susan will have MEETUP signs with them.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217886016000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214011056000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Second Annual Drive-in Movie at Mendon!!!</name><id>8182434</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217712600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8182434/</event_url></item>