<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join in on the tour of Gillette Castle which will be all decked out for the Christmas holiday season in a Victorian theme. We'll first tour the castle and then hike the trails on the grounds of the castle. The trails are easy-moderate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We'll first get our tour tickets:&lt;/span&gt; $6 for adults (13 and up), $2 for children (6 -12), and small children free (1 - 5). Start touring the Castle by at about 10:30 AM. The tour should be done by around 11:30 AM. &lt;span&gt;We'll then take up to 30 min. to eat a picnic lunch (please bring your own or some for others if you want to share) at "Grand Central Terminal/Picnic Shelter" as marked on the map. There are some picnic tables. Note it tends to be a bit brisk out this time of year so please dress warmly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At about Noon, we'll hit the trails. Mostly we'll hike the old railroad bed of the mini steam train that ran on the property. We should even be able to hike through the old tunnel dug for the train! We should finish by about 2 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Children are very welcome for the event. Pets on a leash are permitted in picnic areas and on hiking trails. Pets are not allowed in buildings or on decks, terraces or walkways leading to the castle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the outbuilding (marked as Visitor Center on the trail map) next to the main (i.e. big) parking lot as you head towards the castle. That building has bathrooms. Just look me, Kevin the Organizer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; (67 River Rd., E. Haddam, CT), &lt;strong&gt;park in the main parking lot by the Visitor Center&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://mapq.st/11BzihU"&gt;http://mapq.st/11BzihU&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 [Lat.=41.42756, Long.=-72.4286]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail map:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/gillettecastlemap.pdf"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/gillettecastlemap.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information about Gillette Castle State Park: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325204&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325204&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Grey Ford Escape SUV, CT plates. Meet at Visitor Center by main parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355067374000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354685508000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike and Holiday Celebration at Gillette Castle in East Haddam CT</name><id>94133152</id><duration>14400000</duration><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354978800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/94133152/</event_url></item>