<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>306 Northern Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.348064</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harpoon Brewery</name><city>Boston</city><id>519083</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.037100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NOTE&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;As indicated below, I only have ONE extra ticket.  If you were already planning on going because either you, or someone you know, has a ticket, feel free to RSVP &amp;quot;NO&amp;quot;, and indicate that you will be there.  I will keep an eye out for any members that indicate they will be there.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to their &amp;quot;regular&amp;quot; offerings, each year the good folks at Harpoon also put out a variety of different, one-of-a-kind limited batch creations. Every couple of months a different Harpoon brewer will choose a style, develop a recipe, and brew the beer—from selecting the ingredients to the final filtration. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The current 100 Barrel Series edition is Oak Aged Dunkel.  And if you can still find some, I highly recommend you grab it before its gone.  It's an excellent, very drinkable and tasty brew.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next edition will be Catamount Maple Wheat, and there will be a special, invitation only tasting tomorrow night.  As luck would have it, I have &lt;b&gt;one&lt;/b&gt; extra ticket for the tasting.  So for one person, this is your chance to try it before the general public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Harpoon:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Catamount Maple Wheat is a full-bodied, smooth wheat ale made with genuine Vermont maple syrup. The original version of this beer was brewed in the winter of 2009 by Harpoon Vermont sales representative John Baker.  Harpoon brewer Brett Simmons based his 2011 version on John's recipe, with some tweaks to make it his own.  It is brewed with a combination of wheat malt, pale malt, caramel malt, and mildly hopped with Willamette. The balance of malts and hops allows the distinct flavor and aroma of real Vermont maple syrup to take the lead.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The pure Vermont maple syrup used in the beer came from Baker Farm in East Dummerston - the family farm of John Baker - and Scrag Mountain Sugar House in Waitsfield. The maple sweetness and body that blankets this velvety amber beer showcases one of New England's most beloved traditions.   &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295991020000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295832386000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harpoon 100 Barrel Tasting - Catamount Maple Wheat</name><id>16158675</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295910000000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/16158675/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/2/global_21013538.jpeg</photo_url></item>