<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Lang Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.898380</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>237586</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.701836</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I work on getting back in hiking form after a long hiatus, another afternoon walk at Northwest Park in Windsor. It will be more of a walk in the woods than a serious hike as we'll cover about 3 miles of rolling trails, likely with views of Rainbow Reservoir. Meet in the parking lot at 3:00 and expect to be out on the trail about 2 hours at a social (slow) pace. Kids and dogs welcome.   Check back that morning to see if I have updated the plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone is interested, pizza after at the nearby (and very good) Tunxis Grill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me with my dogs in the parking lot area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363475208000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362954405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northwest Park in Windsor</name><id>108603212</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363460400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/108603212/</event_url></item>