<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color : #eb1a1a"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #140202"&gt;Izon Launch New US Office, Nanotech Champs, NZ Wine &amp;amp; Networkin&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #1f0303"&gt;g&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt; When: Wednesday, September 21st, 2011, 5:30 p.m. &amp;ndash; 8:00 p.m Where: Main Foyer, Building 600, One Kendall Square, Suite 6101, Cambridge, MA 02139 Register: 
&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/2100676179" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eventbrite.com/event/2100676179&lt;/a&gt; Join Dr. Susan Windham Bannister, CEO of the Massachusetts Life Sciences Center, Robert Coughlin, President and CEO of MassBio, and Ken Brown, Executive Director of the Massachusetts Office of International Trade and Investment, as Izon Science Ltd officially opens its new US Headquarters on September 21st, 2011. The office and lab - located at One Kendall Square, Cambridge, MA - will serve as the new US hub for the nanotechnology instrument manufacturers who have an expanding client base in 23 countries. The evening will feature an Inter-University Nanotechnology Measurement Championships - between Harvard, MIT, Boston University and University of Massachusetts. The contest will require the University representatives to accurately measure a complex set of nanoparticles in real time. The winner will be the fastest to achieve this. Izon Science has developed the qNano and qViro set of portable instruments using size-tunable nanopores. Improvements over previously available techniques are advancing research in a number of fields including - drug delivery, hematology, biomedical diagnostics, and vaccine development. The launch party will provide guests with the opportunity to network and enjoy a range of high quality New Zealand wine, which has been specially arranged for the event. Tasting notes and a selection of light food will be available. As places are strictly limited, please RSVP as soon as possible. 
&lt;strong&gt;Organizers&lt;/strong&gt;: Izon Science Ltd ViThera Laboratories Massachusetts Biotechnology Council (MassBio) Massachusetts Life Sciences Center Massachusetts Office of International Trade and Investment</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316645145000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315357851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Izon Launch New US Office, Nanotech Champs, NZ Wine &amp; Networking</name><id>32532532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316640600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/32532532/</event_url></item>