<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Bonds in a Day&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;- short notice, fast paced hike&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott &amp;amp; Judy are calling all fast paced hikers interested in a full day adventure to the Bonds.  Bondcliff (4,265 ft.), along with neighboring Mt. Guyot and Mt. Bond, offers some of the most stunning views in the Whites, with virtually no sign of roads or buildings visible from the summit.  Thursday's weather looks great - clear skies and temperatures in the mid 70s.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that are interested and available the plan for this fast paced hike is to take the Zealand Trail to the Twinway.  From the Twinway we would continue on the Bondcliff Trail hitting all three peaks.  For the return we would retrace our steps back to the Zealand Road trailhead parking.  Our total mileage for the day will be approximately 19.8 miles!  This hike will be fast paced and incur major elevation gain.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further information about this hike visit AMCs website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/recreation/tripplanner/plan/bondcliff.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If interested please RSVP ASAP.  The cutoff to RSVP will be 8:00 pm this evening.  Please email me directly with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott&lt;br /&gt;tourbusiness@altazone.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the NEHAAG disclaimer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>details TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213552431000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213198551000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Bonds in a Day - short notice, fast paced hike</name><id>8122798</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213270200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8122798/</event_url></item>