<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>358 Springside Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.338080</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-389-4333 ext 213</phone><name>Common Ground High School</name><city>New Haven</city><id>283040</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.958240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From the official &lt;a href="http://www.rocktorock.org" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Explore New Haven by bicycle.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock to Rock is a day-long celebration of Earth Day, and of New Haven's rich environmental and cultural resources. Here's how it works: You and a few hundred others will travel between West Rock and East Rock, with celebrations on both sides of the city. Along the way, you will eat tasty food, hear great music, take on environmental service projects, explore Edgewood and Beaver Ponds Parks, and ride Farmington Canal Trail and official city bike lanes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't have a bike?&lt;/b&gt; Rent one from &lt;a href="http://www.thedevilsgear.com/service/rentals" target="_blank"&gt;The Devil's Gear&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Think you're hard-core?&lt;/b&gt; Take detours to the top of the two rocks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Have a little kid in tow?&lt;/b&gt; Join us from Common Ground to Edgewood Park.&lt;br /&gt;Families and college students, 20-something hipsters and teenagers, young and old, serious riders and weekend warriors will all be welcomed. Join our rock band.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock to Rock starts with a &lt;b&gt;free hot breakfast&lt;/b&gt; at Common Ground High School--at the base of West Rock--at 9am, where you'll also pick up the &lt;b&gt;t-shirt and water bottle&lt;/b&gt; included in the registration fee ($25 online, $30 the day of the event); the ride begins at 10:45; you'll make stops at two parks along the way for &lt;b&gt;snacks, music, and activities&lt;/b&gt;; and then you'll end up at an &lt;b&gt;expo&lt;/b&gt; at East Rock Park, where vendors will include the fabled Caseus Cheese Truck.   &lt;a href="http://www.rocktorock.org/flyer.php" target="_blank"&gt;Full schedule and logistics explained here. &lt;/a&gt;  Online preregistration is &lt;a href="http://www.rocktorock.org/register.php" target="_blank"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will a easy, flat, amateur-friendly mass ride through city streets and some great parks--last year even the mayor showed up on his bike, and you should too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;The NHC contact for this event is Monica:  860-770-0266&lt;/span&gt;  You can start the day by showing up at Common Ground High School directly (parking is available), or by joining a group ride to Common Ground High School leaving from Orange and Cold Spring Street (outside of East Rock Park) at 8:45am.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272293605000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271597859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2010 Rock to Rock Earth Day (Bicycle) Ride!</name><id>13214701</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272120300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/13214701/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/f/global_14449135.jpeg</photo_url></item>