<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Save the Date!!! Thursday, April 8th!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a wonderfully successful concert in February, the Ritmo Masacote 12-piece Salsa/Timba Orchestra will be playing again at Ryles Jazz Club on Thursday, April 8th, with Special Guest from New York, Christelle Durandy...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us for an INTENSE night of Music and Dance. EVERYONE IS INVITED!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you want to hear and watch the high energy ensemble in action, dance your heart out to the intoxicating rhythms of Salsa and Timba, or watch a Salsa Dance show by the Masacote Salsa Dance Company, there's something for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Show time: 8:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Only $10 cover charge...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Ryles Jazz Club, 312 Hampshire Street, Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cIgPrI7bNJI" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH A YOUTUBE VIDEO OF THE RITMO MASACOTE BAND!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shows full of Life, Spirit &amp;amp; Energy! For Music and Dance Lovers alike!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLUS! Join us at Temporada Latina Upstairs between sets and after event close for a special show by the Masacote Dance Company and salsa dancing to Boston's best djs. All concert attendees can move upstairs for only $5!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Temporada Latina Schedule Upstairs&lt;br /&gt;(only $5 more for concert attendees!)&lt;br /&gt;8:45pm-10:00pm -  Salsa Lessons for all levels&lt;br /&gt;10:00-11:00pm -- Dancing&lt;br /&gt;11:00pm -- Masacote Dance Company Showcase at Temporada Latina upstairs!!!&lt;br /&gt;11:00pm-1am -- Dancing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**How to find us**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Angel:&lt;/b&gt; Look for the Grey Fedora Hat. If later than 8pm, then look for him at the reserved meetup tables. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ellen:&lt;/b&gt; Look for a scarf around her neck. She'll be your friendly greeter at the front door of Temporada Latina! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****************************&lt;br /&gt;Ritmo Masacote is a 12 piece Salsa/Timba/Latin Jazz orchestra comprised of some of Berklee’s most talented students/alums and Boston’s finest musicians. The orchestra was created with the purpose to bridge the growing divide between the music and dance genres. This young, charismatic cast produces commanding presentations full of life, spirit, and energy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ritmo Masacote was founded out of Boston, MA in 2006 by Composer/Pianist Joel Massicot, also known as “Masacote”. Joel earned the alias Masacote in 1998 as an introduction into his piano solos while playing in Washington, DC. Masacote, Cuban slang, specifically refers to the rhythm created by combining the basic percussive instruments in Salsa/Mambo (the congas, guiro, timbales, clave, and bongo). More generally, this term refers to the design of merging various elements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With this design in mind, Joel set about creating an ensemble that would serve to merge various components of music and dance, shaping the perception of Latin Music Today. Often coupled on stage with the Masacote Dance Company, the ensemble is making an impact in cultivating an international appreciation and demand for danceable and captivating band performances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ritmo Masacote’s reach extends internationally as far as Australia, China, Japan, Singapore, Turkey, Germany, Lithuania, Colombia, Brazil, and across North America, among others. The ensemble’s music can be found on motion pictures, instructional DVDs, and can be heard on major radio stations and satellite radio both nationally and internationally. Everyone can relate to the orchestra’s unique compositions and arrangements with focused directions in Timba, Salsa, and Latin jazz grounded in Cuban roots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With two critically acclaimed Latin Jazz albums to its credit, Ritmo Masacote is working to deliver its first Salsa/Timba-focused album for its growing fan base around the globe. This third release is scheduled for 2011.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Creating the bridge between music and dance” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****************************&lt;br /&gt;What they're saying about Ritmo Masacote:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Joel and friends deliver an irresistible, percussive-driven project, which is hypnotic to listeners and toe-tapping to the swinging dancers.&amp;quot; -- Rudy Mangual, Latin Beat Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Irresistible, toe-tapping, hip, and head-shakingly groovy. Everyone can relate.&amp;quot; -- Kevin Ball, Host/Producer of Jazz Gallery (WGBH 89.7)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Pianist Joel Massicot leads his group Ritmo Masacote through a unique set of compositions and arrangements on Fantagious that mix a wide palette of musical spices into a fantastic dish. Several tracks draw upon a straight-ahead Cuban influence, interpreted with a modern edge.&amp;quot; -- Chip Boaz, The Latin Jazz Corner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There is an independent spirit at work here, a sense of playfulness and adventurousness... The Ritmo Masacote band are a fabulous bunch of players, and on this date their talent really shows. Massicot’s piano playing is fluid and inventive, easily switching from intense Latin figures to gentle, almost classical ruminations...Highly Recommended.&amp;quot; Pablo Yglesias, Editor's Pick, Descarga.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Angel in the Grey Fedora Hat!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angel Santiago</member_name><member_id>5161614</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270945720000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268122260000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Music &amp; Dancing at Ryles with Ritmo Masacote Orchestra</name><id>12826278</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270772100000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/12826278/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/f/global_13554943.jpeg</photo_url></item>