<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>327 Newbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sonsie Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>1548358</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086121</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Join us this month&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; in conjunction with DWC Boston, for a special author event with Maria Murnane on how to find and follow your passion in life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;. Maria Murnane is the author of the award-winning romantic comedy, &lt;em&gt;Perfect on Paper: the (Mis)adventures of Waverly Bryson.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Enjoy an evening at the wonderful Sonsie restaurant on Newbury Street as Maria talks about her career change from a 10 year climb in the corporate world in Silicon Valley to discovering that there was more to life than being miserable in her job. How did she cut through the fear to follow her passion? Maria will discuss her personal struggles of identifying her passion and breaking through her fear with her humorous adventures and lessons learned. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;She will also discuss how she became a successful, published, author. Sometimes the greatest inspiration can come from a person who has already faced those road blocks and fears that prevent us from taking that one step forward toward our calling. Maria will inspire us and remind us that life is too short to spend it doing something that doesn't make you happy&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt; if you need a change, it&amp;rsquo;s up to you to make it happen and in the end&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;... no one is keeping score of your life but you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The price for this event is $20, and you must pay in advance. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Attendees &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;will enjoy appetizers at Sonsie and will also receive a signed copy of Maria's book!&lt;/span&gt; DWC &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Boston and Cambridge chapters have only 25 spots each for this event, so please make sure that you can attend before you RSVP! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Downtown Women's Club:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Downtown Women's Club &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;is a business network and career website that makes professional networking affordable, effective, and fun! Premium members receive free e-books, teleclasses, member profiles and much more. Visit the DWC website &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;and join today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Sonsie:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Sonsie celebrates seventeen years on Boston&amp;rsquo;s famous Newbury Street serving top-notch International cuisine from award-winning Chef Bill Poirier. Open seven days a week from 7:00am to 1:00am, Sonsie boasts beautiful French doors that translate to an open sidewalk cafe in season, as well as a European lounge with deep leather chairs and sofas. The mahogany bar serves the best martinis in town from an experienced lot of friendly bartenders and the brick-oven churns out eclectic pizzas and focaccia throughout the day. It is easy to relax at Sonsie and enjoy the classic music that reflects the ambiance of the restaurant as day progresses into night.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Sonsie has reserved a room for us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noona Joseph</member_name><member_id>5632804</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1302007880000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Join us with Maria Murnane as she discusses "Finding and Following your Passion!" Enjoy appetizers, networking, and a signed copy of Maria's book.</why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandnetworkforwomen-com</urlname><id>1463004</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>New England Network for Women :: Cambridge</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299332238000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Finding and Following Your Passion" with Author Maria Murnane at Sonsie</name><id>16806422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301439600000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandnetworkforwomen-com/events/16806422/</event_url></item>