<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suita A-312</address_2><address_1>122 Western Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01851</zip><lat>42.640163</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-771-3101</phone><name>Western Avenue Studios</name><city>Lowell</city><id>956129</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.319710</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a 100% hands-on workshop that will focus on studio photography with professional models. It is open to photographers at all levels. You will be working in a fully equipped commercial studio &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Greater-Boston-Studio-Glamour-Photography/photos/612052/"&gt;(link)&lt;/a&gt;, using a full range of high-end studio lighting gear with experienced and professional models. Individual training and assistance will be available throughout the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will run 4 hours from 10AM to 2PM. This event will be limited to 10 photographers with a 3:1 (or better) photographer to model ratio. The event will be run such that each photographer will have focused time with each of the models. This means that no other photographer will be permitted to shoot while you are shooting. 2 or 3 sets will be arranged for multiple models so there will be plenty for shooting time and sets to choose from. And, since we're so close to St. Patrick's day, there might even be a little &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; in the day's theme ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These Meetups are characterized as having very attractive, professional models. Read the feedback and check out the photos: these events fill up quickly and you will get some fantastic shots! We're working on some new talent for this seminar but here are some links to previous events: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Greater-Boston-Studio-Glamour-Photography/photos/680345/"&gt;Cassie&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Greater-Boston-Studio-Glamour-Photography/photos/641415/"&gt;Perstephanie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Seats will go to the 1st 10 paid attendees. (when you RSVP you will be required to pay).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a free (no charge) pre-meetup workshop from 9AM-10AM to discuss and review studio lighting. If you are interested in attending this workshop, please let me know. It will only be open to the 1st 5 photographers that contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions or need more information, please don't hesitate to contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: Sunday, March 14th 10AM – 2PM (#)&lt;br /&gt;Place: Jerry Bedrick Studios, 122 Western Avenue, Suite A311-A312, Lowell, MA 01850&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Rich Norton - Richard@TheDustyNegative.com - (617) 680-0450&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $65 (##)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(#) There will be a free pre-shoot workshop on studio basics from 9:00AM-10AM&lt;br /&gt;(##) You are required to pay at the time you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich</member_name><member_id>9500088</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1303660511000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Studio Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Greater-Boston-Studio-Photography</urlname><id>1454286</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2799987793</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Studio &amp; Glamour Photography</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267835033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Studio Photography with Professional Models</name><id>12796881</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268575200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Greater-Boston-Studio-Photography/events/12796881/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/5/3/global_10036947.jpeg</photo_url></item>