<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Well the time has come and we are ready to share it!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome all teens. We are offering a 5 weeks of the Law of Attraction for Teens Program. This is an after school program to start the wheels turing. This program is just one of 5 classes being held weekly through the month of March. Tuesdays are Psychic Teen Network, Wednesdays Yoga for Teens, Thursdays Hip Hop Zumba, Friday Vision Boards and Creating Abundance. Each month until summer we will be offering more classes, the kids get to vote on which classes we keep each month!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In our Law of Attraction class Teens will learn how to build self confidence, learn to listen to their intuition, hear how everything is made of energy and how to focus the positive in life to create amazing results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please share this information with the young people in your life that are ready to start creating their own prosperity, good grades, great friends and fun family life. I have been teaching this information for 4 years and I have always wanted to share it with a younger generation. By the time these students are my age they will have a whole new way at looking at life, abundance and empowerment!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So please share&lt;br /&gt;Mondays for the month of March, 3:30 to 4:30&lt;br /&gt;The Holistic Self Care Center&lt;br /&gt;12 Murphy Drive Nashua, Nh 03062&lt;br /&gt;603-883-1490 for questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a guest speaker and teacher for our first class. Meet Kerri!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kerri has been practicing the Law of Attraction for almost 3 years. She has been a member of the HSC Center’s “Abundance, Empowerment, and the Law of Attraction” group for almost 1 year, and regularly attends workshops to continue her education. Kerri grew up, and continues to live in the Nashua, NH area. She obtained a Bachelors of Arts in Psychology from Colby-Sawyer College, and is currently enrolled at Rivier College to obtain her Masters in Mental Health Counseling. In addition, Kerri participated in a performing arts camp for children and adolescents for 18 years, and taught art for 5 years. She has her certification in Usui Reiki I, utilizes healing stones for energy work, and has had experience with premonitions. Through her field of counseling, she hopes to one day offer guidance using the Law of Attraction as a tool for her clients’ healing and success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Preregistration is strongly suggested.&lt;br /&gt;Cost, $12 or $50 for 5 weeks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267649055000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266987991000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Teen After School Program- Law of Attraction!</name><id>12692503</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267475400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/12692503/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/4/global_9559044.jpeg</photo_url></item>