<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Winter Solstice Celebration Event&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience a connection with Mother Earth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday 12/21. Come join us for our second annual Winter Solstice Celebration. Candlelight vigil, chanting/walking meditation along main street Middletown. 6:30 p.m. ? 7:30 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Middletown South Green near the Christmas Tree (the block between Main Street and Pleasant Street) Dress warmly. Pit stop at Javapalooza for hot drinks, half way. Weather update or details (860) 759-4081.  All are welcomed and bring your friends. please try to arrive 10 minutes before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What does the Winter Solstice have to do with Buddhism?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On December 8th, or on the Sunday immediately preceding, Buddhists celebrate Bodhi Day (meaning Enlightenment Day). It recalls the day in 596 BCE, when the Buddha achieved enlightenment. He had left his family and possessions behind at the age of 29, and sought the meaning of life -- particularly the reasons for its hardships. He studied under many spiritual teachers without success. Finally, he sat under a large Bo tree and vowed that he would stay there until he found what he was seeking. On the morning of the eighth day, he realized that everyone suffers due to ignorance. But ignorance can be overcome through the Eightfold Path that he advocated. This day is generally regarded as the birth day of Buddhism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being originally an Eastern tradition, Bodhi Day has none of the associations with the solstice and seasonal changes found in other religious observances at this time of year. However, this holiday together with the solstice signify the the dawning of spiritual light in the mist of darkness; that is, it points to the historical event when the Buddha was attained by enlightenment, thereby transcending the endless cycle of birth, death and rebirth  -- The general theme of birth and death, and light and darkness are all observed in other religions in December.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198452657000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-469</urlname><id>836707</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>12 Step Buddhist &amp; Recovery Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195842618000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Solstice in Middletown</name><id>6792019</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198279800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-469/events/6792019/</event_url></item>