<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>355 Congress St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.350210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bocoup Loft</name><city>Boston</city><id>1236793</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.048282</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There has been a change of location for this event.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: black"&gt;Unfortunately Microsoft were over-booked this month, so we will be holding January's meetup at The Bocoup Loft, 5mins walk from South Station. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South Station is on the same line as Kendal, so people taking the T should stay inbound on the Red Line and hop off four stops later. For those of you coming by car, we recommend the Limited meter parking on Summer St. The &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=+parking&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;cd=3&amp;amp;ei=7YaOS4GALIr2ygSg5ZBK&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;view=map&amp;amp;cid=261369615591789052&amp;amp;iwloc=A&amp;amp;ved=0CBoQpQY&amp;amp;sa=X" target="_blank"&gt;Vpne Parking Garage&lt;/a&gt; is a block away on Necco St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can read more about the Bocoup Loft and find a Google Map here: &lt;a href="http://loft.bocoup.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://loft.bocoup.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://loft.bocoup.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This talk will introduce Closure, an open-source suite of JavaScript tools from Google. Closure has been used to build popular, sophisticated web applications such as Gmail and Google Maps. As JavaScript does not lend itself to &amp;quot;programming in the large,&amp;quot; additional tool support is needed to manage large JavaScript codebases. This talk will explain how the tools in the Closure suite solve this problem. In particular, it will discuss how the Closure Compiler helps reduce the size of the JavaScript needed to load a Rich Internet Application by 95% while also validating JavaScript code via type checking and other techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation, we will go around the room introducing ourselves and asking the group for advice/opinions on any JavaScript-related issues members are facing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP and bring guests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio: Michael Bolin&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Bolin is a software engineer who spent four years at Google working on Calendar, Tasks, and the Closure Compiler. He recently published Closure: The Definitive Guide (O'Reilly 2010), which explains all how all of the Closure Tools (Library, Templates, Compiler, Inspector) work and how best to use them. JavaScript has been Michael's primary programming language since 2003 when he started his work on a Firefox extension named Chickenfoot, which was the focus of his MEng thesis at MIT under Professor Rob Miller of the User Interface Design group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free Stuff!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael will be bringing &lt;b&gt;three copies of his Closure book&lt;/b&gt; to give away. Winners will be picked at random from the list of members &amp;quot;checked-in&amp;quot; on Meetup.com.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;+ Free pizza and refreshments!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date / Travel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See above.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Bocoup</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alistair MacDonald</member_name><member_id>9070213</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296779689000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>JavaScripters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>javascript-2</urlname><id>884541</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>The Boston JavaScript Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>81</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291989798000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Closure Tools: Principles and Practice - Michael Bolin</name><id>15696752</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294356600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/javascript-2/events/15696752/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/c/c/global_19957996.jpeg</photo_url></item>