<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>metropolitan drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02806</zip><lat>41.753341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Haines Memorial State Park</name><city>Barrington</city><id>1268823</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.348539</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;It is time to start planning our Bike and BBQ on Memorial Day weekend. The scheduled date will remain for Sunday May 27th at 11 AM. Rich has volunteered to hold our spot at the park and to do the cooking on the BBQ! (thanks Rich, don’t burn it). There is a large parking lot for all the cars and bathrooms at the park.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;This day is your day to have fun. Join us for a bike ride, BBQ, or both. Please bring along any guests, the more the mirthful. Stay as little or as long as you like.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Rich and I are providing the chicken on the BBQ and plates with eating utensils. If you would like to help cover the cost of the supplied items look for the donation can at the park. It would be appreciated by the event organizers if people would bring a dish, bag of chips, or sodas etc. to share. Please email me if you plan on bringing some food.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We plan to ride to Bristol then eat lunch afterwards. It may be a good idea to bring extra chairs and recreational gear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Hopefully the weather will cooperate and be sunny and warm. We need to know by May 24th how many people are attending for real, for purschasing of food. Looking forward to seeing and meeting everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tables near restrooms with an American Flag</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda</member_name><member_id>32033792</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338598784000</updated><rating><average>4.94999980927</average><count>21</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334497919000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BikeRide + Bar-B-Q, Haines Memorial Park, East Bay Bike Path, 15 miles-20 miles</name><id>60644742</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338130800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/60644742/</event_url></item>