<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>“The unexamined life is not worth living.” – Socrates&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In EXAMINED LIFE, filmmaker Astra Taylor (Zizek!) accompanies some of today’s most influential thinkers on a series of unique excursions through places and spaces that hold particular resonance for them and their ideas. By pulling philosophy out of academic journals and classrooms, Taylor puts it back on the streets where it began and creates an engaging intellectual smorgasbord.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter Singer’s thoughts on the ethics of consumption are amplified against the backdrop of Fifth Avenue’s posh boutiques. Slavoj Zizek questions current beliefs about the environment while sifting through a garbage dump. Michael Hardt ponders the nature of revolution while surrounded by symbols of wealth and leisure. Judith Butler and Sunaura Taylor stroll through San Francisco’s Mission District questioning our culture’s fixation on individualism. And while driving through Manhattan, Cornel West – perhaps America’s best-known public intellectual – compares philosophy to jazz and blues, reminding us how intense and invigorating a life of the mind can be. Offering privileged moments with great thinkers from fields ranging from moral philosophy to cultural theory, EXAMINED LIFE reveals philosophy’s power to transform the way we see the world around us and imagine our place in it.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be up front with a Meetup sign and it's off to discuss at a local eatery.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fay </member_name><member_id>3089505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237518323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Examined Life"</name><id>9993768</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238967000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9993768/</event_url></item>