<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>161 Hillstown Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.762010</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-647-3084</phone><name>Manchester Community College Bandshell</name><city>Manchester</city><id>304918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.568880</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TODAY 4:00 - 11:00 - Look for 3 shiny BLUE STAR-shaped BALLOONS flying high in the sky (taken down prior too the Fireworks).  I'll have a small 4'x4' blue blanket w/ multi polka dots on it and sitting in a low beach chair (great for tilting back to watch the Fireworks).  I'll wear a YELLOW sleeveless t-shirt with BLACK &amp;quot;BUS13&amp;quot; logo on it.  I'm 55, 5'11, 215#, brown hair, and wear tinted glasses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If that doesn't work, I (or a friend) will hang out for a few minutes - every hour on the hour - to the LEFT side of the Bandshell holding a GOLD-colored Star balloon w/ &amp;quot;MeetUp&amp;quot; on it.  Also, periodically, we'll try to play Bocce (bright, solid colored balls of various colors) to the LEFT of the Bandshell, by the grove of trees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a last resort, my cell# is (860) 690-9595.  If you roll into VM, please leave your name and number and how I can find you, as I may not hear it ring, but will check it frequently.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.s.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a &amp;quot;dress rehearsal&amp;quot; as we'll do this all over again next Saturday at Hartford's &amp;quot;RiverFest&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dutch Fogarty INDEPENDENCE DAY CELEBRATION&lt;br /&gt;Join this popular annual community event with the whole family. There will be live entertainment (David Foster and the Mohegan Sun All Stars), chicken barbeque, concessions, fireworks and fun recreation activities for the kids. (Fireworks begin at 9:30 p.m.)&lt;br /&gt;Rain Date: 7/1&lt;br /&gt;Sponsor: Fourth of July Committee, 647-3084.&lt;br /&gt;Admission Fee: Free - but they do request a voluntary donation per carload. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Fireworks display is among the best in the state, yet not as overcrowded as many, being held on the sloped lawn of Manchester Community College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to the Fireworks display, the bandshell features a variety of live music starting at 4:00 with optional dancing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm be putting together a group of old and new friends to join me in the afternoon and staying through the Fireworks... even partying after the Fireworks as we optionally wait out the traffic congestion, then drive peacefully on our way.  Please drive responsibly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I find it's best for everyone to simply bring their own food &amp;amp; drink, chairs, blankets, sweatshirt, bug spray, litter bag, &amp;quot;glow-in-the-dark&amp;quot; necklaces, flashlights, etc., working out carpooling, if desired, on your own. Those who show up are &amp;quot;ready to go&amp;quot;  w/o waiting for missing supplies, etc. Food will be on sale on site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Too crowded for volleyball, but bring Bocce, cards, backgammon, Frisbees, Trivial Pursuit, party games, etc. to enjoy a leisurely afternoon and early evening prior to the Fireworks display.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP ASAP so we know how large an area to stake out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather forecast looks wonderful and I'm inviting others from various groups to join us, so expect a good turnout.  If not, those present will have fun and make new friends, anyway!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a &amp;quot;family friendly&amp;quot; event and your kids / grandkids are welcome to join us.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183406955000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182827484000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FIREWORKS - music, picnic, &amp; party! - MANCHESTER</name><id>5936298</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183233600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5936298/</event_url></item>