<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>249 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395308</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yoga In The Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>941611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121885</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;If you have not yet taken this workshop, now's your chance!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Graduates of this workshop are invited to join a six-month Process Group which meets monthly to go deeper into releasing core issues and practicing intimacy skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embody Your Authentic Masculine Power&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Oct 4, 2009, 12:00-4:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an experiential course for men who desire greater authenticity, ease and erotic fire in relation with women. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Would you like to have a relationship that is full of passion, integrity and ease?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Are you tired of being the nice guy who doesn’t get any?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you want to know what women want?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a unique opportunity to get compassionate, constructive feedback from a female expert on gender dynamics on the impact you have on the opposite sex. You will receive expert guidance to uncover and convey core aspects of yourself that women want. Often the qualities that are most attractive are the ones we try to hide out of fear or shame. Allowing yourself to receive deep acceptance and honoring in those places can set you free to truly be the man you were meant to be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830;         Get insight into the challenges you are facing in your intimate relations with women – and practical skills to address them.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830;         Learn powerful energy practices to access greater confidence.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830;         Discover the inner key to attracting the connections you desire.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Tap into your authentic sexual magnetism.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Discover the three most desirable qualities within You - (They’re not what you think!) &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; … And five methods to cultivate them!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What past participants are saying:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Highly recommended for healing and increasing understanding of gender similarities and differences.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I really don't have the words to express the release I felt in the group last Sunday.  The final role play and you sharing your own personal journey helped me see... I can work towards having transparency with my wounds, my failures, but also reconnection to my joy... You are giving me new tools to work with. Today, I am feeling more in my heart than I have felt in many years.  And, your work continues to nurture me.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The workshop included much helpful information including what do women want in a man and how to be more masculine... The role play was valuable and I would like to see Brynn do that with each man based on his unique &amp;quot;issue&amp;quot; concerning women. I like the way Brynn includes movement in her workshops. She offers a rare and extremely needed educational experience for men to learn from a wonderfully prepared, intelligent, playful, mature, grounded, and compassionate woman.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>door to the left of the Burren.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254961333000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252780144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Embody Your Authentic Masculine Power</name><id>11355380</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254672000000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/11355380/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/global_9120349.jpeg</photo_url></item>