<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Theater District</address_2><address_1>279 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349686</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-338-7699</phone><name>Royale Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>1245569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065331</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Barry (barry@gdgt.com) of &lt;a href="http://gdgt.com/" target="_blank"&gt;gdgt&lt;/a&gt; has invited us to a fun &lt;b&gt;FREE&lt;/b&gt; event featuring some of the country’s top tech brands and hottest startups. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;gdgt.com, a social network for gadget lovers, is bringing its gdgt live event series to Boston on Wednesday, September 22, 2010 at &lt;a href="http://royaleboston.com/corporate-events/" target="_blank"&gt;Royale&lt;/a&gt; (formerly the Roxy) from 7 PM until 10 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over 25 great gadget brands will be demonstrating their latest gadgets. You will have a chance to play with them, meet face-to-face with the companies that make them, and maybe even win them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Drinks are on the house if you’re 21 and the first several hundred folks get a free gdgt T-shirt or a gdgt-branded iPhone case.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out their Facebook page at &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/gdgt" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; and click on the Events tab for more details. Click on the Event Sponsors tab for a short description of their sponsors and what they're showcasing and giving away and click on the Photos tab to see photos of past events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can see a video from their recent Chicago event on YouTube - &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/gdgtLive" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Details on Some Cool Stuff Happening at the Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gadgets for Good, gdgt has teamed up with &lt;a href="http://www.gazelle.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Gazelle&lt;/a&gt; to raise a little cash for a good cause at the Boston event, but need your help. &lt;b&gt;Bring your used cell phones, cameras, media players, video games, DVDs, and other geeky stuff to the event, and Gazelle will donate the buyback value to &lt;a href="http://www.strategiesforchildren.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Strategies for Children&lt;/a&gt;, a local Boston NPO that works to ensure children in the Bay State have access to high-quality education and become proficient readers by third grade. Don't forget that charger!&lt;/b&gt; Check out &lt;a href="http://gdgtforgood.gazelle.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://gdgtforgood.ga...&lt;/a&gt; for more details or to contribute your used gadgets in advance of the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://scvngr.com/" target="_blank"&gt;SCVNGR&lt;/a&gt; will be giving out some swag to people who complete some gdgt live in Boston challenges. Download their app and be ready to use it when you get to the show!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An After Party hosted by &lt;a href="http://www.gazelle.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Gazelle&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://bostinnovation.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Bostinnovation&lt;/a&gt;, will make gdgt live in Boston the first gdgt live event with its very own after party! The fun starts at 9 PM around the corner from Royale at the &lt;a href="http://www.starwoodhotels.com/whotels/property/dining/attraction_detail.html?propertyID=1787&amp;amp;attractionId=1004569644" target="_blank"&gt;W Hotel Lounge&lt;/a&gt; 100 Stuart Street and goes until 1 AM. This is not your typical after party; Gazelle has planned an old school gadget theme, and even a custom cocktail designed specifically for this event. Oh and of course there is a &lt;b&gt;cash bar and plenty of hors d’oeuvres from the W will be passed all night.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;AS ALWAYS YOU MUST MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt;  or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. N.E. (Tufts) Medical (orange line) subway station is closest, less than (five (5) minute walk) Boylston (green line) subway station is less than a ten (10) minute walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;gdgt was founded by Peter Rojas, co-founder of Gizmodo and founder of Engadget and Ryan Block, former Editor-in-Chief of Engadget. Here's a Wall Street Journal blog about gdgt &lt;a href="http://blogs.wsj.com/digits/2010/04/07/gdgt-raises-new-financing-with-new-concept/" target="_blank"&gt;http://blogs.wsj.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send a message on how and where to find us the day before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285259820000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284127083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gadget Happy Hour</name><id>14722705</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285196400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/14722705/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/8/global_6854760.jpeg</photo_url></item>