<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Explore a shrouded landscape of hemlock groves, a magnolia swamp, and other trees species where you’ll find remnants of Colonial habitation.  If you enjoy scenery and wildlife, we will be particularly excited to have you on our walks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Walk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave the parking area at 11:10.  The walk will be about 3.5 to 5 miles long.  We will definitely follow the Ledge Hill Trail to the scenic overlook to Gloucester Harbor and cross the boardwalk through the Great Magnolia Swamp, home to native sweetbay magnolias (Magnolia virginiana).  In fact, Ravenswood is the northernmost home of the sweetbay magnolia tree, which is endangered in Massachusetts.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take a lunch with you, as we'll have a quick bite on the trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You should definitely stop to use the restroom before your arrival, in case they are not open.  Just a warning:  We had to drive quite far in the direction of Manchester by the Sea to find public restrooms.  According to one of our hikers, the restrooms in the Visitors/Discover Center, &lt;u&gt;should&lt;/u&gt; be open from 10 AM to 3 PM on Saturdays and Sundays, but I wouldn't count on it.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;After the walk&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At least a couple of us plan on visiting a popular birding location which also has amazing views nearby. The Audubon society owns the property which is a favorite spot for walking, fishing and birding. Those who are interested are welcome to follow us to this location which is about 15 minute drive after the walk.  Also, if some of you are interested, feel free to coordinate coffee or dinner amongst yourselves after the walk.  At least a couple of you have ideas for a nearby dining spot.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hiker Code of Conduct&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please try not to get too far ahead of the group. I go to a lot of effort to organize these walks, and it's not enjoyable when people run ahead and create their own event. If you have an emergency, I completely understand. Otherwise, these are designed to be leisurely, social walks, with time to appreciate the critters around us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can always use more organizers, and if anyone feels that the pace of the walk is not appropriate for their needs, they should consider organizing their own event in the future. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Trails&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ravenswood Park is 600 acres large.  There are 10 miles of carriage paths and trails that meander through the park.  It is considered moderate hiking.  Carriage roads are covered with dense crushed stone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Getting There&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address of the house across the street is 392 Western Avenue in Gloucester, MA.  This would be a good address to plug into the GPS, but  please don't pull into the neighbor's driveway!  From Route 128, take exit 14 (Route 133) and follow east towards Gloucester for 3 mi. until it dead ends into Route 127. Turn right onto Route 127 and follow for 2 mi. to the entrance.  (If you pass the Magnolia Recreational Area on the left, you've gone too far).  The parking area (12 cars) is on the right.  You may also park along the road if the lot is full.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;How the Waiting List Works&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When someone from the hike drops, everyone on the waiting list is automatically emailed. The first person on the the waiting list to add themselves to the hike will get in. I realize that this doesn't seem fair for the first person on the waiting list, if someone lower on the list gets in. However, I found that the automatic waiting list resulted in a very high percentage of no-shows. A number of people didn't check their email, even days before the hike, and therefore didn't know they had gotten in to the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking lot with meetup stickers on.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1289085566000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288491077000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Nature Walk at Ravenswood Park- Many Stops-Followed by Optional Birding</name><id>15283106</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289055600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15283106/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/3/global_13612691.jpeg</photo_url></item>