<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>225.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Announcing a new event from Erb Photography!&lt;br /&gt;What: Workshop: Stunning Lighting ~ Stunning Styling: Photographing the Fine Art Nude&lt;br /&gt;When: Saturday, March 13, 8:30AM-5PM&lt;br /&gt;Workshop fee: $225.00 per person Limit: 10 Photographers- (First Come First Served)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will be about having a great makeup and hair stylist use her talents to create two unique looks for our models. Hiring a great stylist can make a photo shoot go in creative directions you never fully realize until things are happening before your eyes. We will be drawing from and using two key points of inspiration - beautiful long hair and Renaissance style paintings. With an exchange of ideas and creative brainstorming between stylist Erin Gregg Brown, workshop leader Scott Erb, and our two fabulous models, Jade and Kerri, we will be creating a workshop environment that will encourage and support you to create beautiful fine art nude images. Since photographers know it’s all about the light when it comes to capturing great images, we will be setting up an open lighting pattern using earth tone palettes to enhance the skin tones of our beautiful models. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is about building portfolios pieces by working with a professional stylist, talented models, and having fun doing it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can’t you think of a better way to spend a day then surrounding yourself with creative people and a camera to capture it all? Then this is the workshop for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who: Scott Erb will be teaching a workshop about the art of photographing the nude. Scott has many years of personal experience selecting models and capturing their beauty. 2 Professional Models with fine art nude experience will be at the essence of this workshop.&lt;br /&gt;Where: Visions By Baker, &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When: Basic Outline for the Day&lt;br /&gt;8:30-9:00AM Meet and Greet: Meet the instructor and the day’s models. Make introductions and discuss the day’s events. Workshop will run from: 9:00 am to 5:00 pm (1:00pm - 2:00pm - 1 Hour Lunch Break (we usually provide pizza and beverages)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is a female nude figure workshop for advanced beginners through professional photographers. We will be learning, playing with, and discussing Open Lighting techniques in the studio setups. There will be a discussion about the importance of pre-production and professional styling. This workshop will cover the basics of lighting, posing, and communication. There is a significant amount of time dedicated to shooting for each participant and the opportunity for each photographers to create their own images. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We provide studio lighting, backdrops, models, and handout materials for your reference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class size limited to 10 people and $225.00 deposit is required to hold your place. Please note that space for this workshop fills up fast - so please register as early as possible. No Refunds unless we can fill your slot before the day of the workshop. Payments- Can be made by check, money order, or PayPal and should be send to: Scott Erb, 380 Bridle Path, Worcester, MA 01604 with your name, address, email, and phone number. If you have a PayPal.com account and would like to send your payment this way, please got to the PayPal.com web site and click on the “Send Money” tab. You can then send payment to scott@erbphoto.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269485764000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266013506000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop: Stunning Lighting ~ Stunning Styling: Photographing the Fine Art Nude</name><id>12591604</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268487000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/12591604/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/d/global_13061981.jpeg</photo_url></item>