<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02532</zip><lat>41.748756</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Train Bridge Parking Lot</name><city>Buzzards Bay</city><id>1539285</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.605919</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;So we've been doing these Canal Walks since February now!..Let's keep it up, even though Summer might actually come and this day might be warm...I moved the start time of the walk itself to 10 am, and thought a picnic lunch might be fun after...Everyone bring your own sandwich and beverage, and if anyone wants to bring&amp;nbsp;a little something to share, chips, a desert, sidedish, etc that would be nice too..I'll bring my world famous&amp;nbsp;Rice&amp;nbsp;Krispie Treats;)..I&amp;nbsp;think that would be easier than trying to make it an actualy pot luck...Hopefully we can snag one of the tables in the shade near the start/end of the walk, if not, Roger will have to come and set up the tailgating table!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who haven't joined us yet, we start at the Train Bridge and walk to the Herring Run and back, 7 miles....It takes about two and a half&amp;nbsp;hours, with a little rest/restroom/regroup at the herring run...If anyone just wants to come for lunch, we should be&amp;nbsp;back to the parking lot to grab our food&amp;nbsp;by&amp;nbsp;around 12:30 or so...Hope to see all my favorite walkers and some more new faces too:)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Can't miss us, maybe I'll actually wear the Tiara this time! The parking lot  entrance is directly across from Buzzards Bay Antique Center, which is at 61 Main Street, Buzzards Bay...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joanna</member_name><member_id>8537777</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309183242000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307275105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk, Walk, Walk...</name><id>21024311</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309096800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/21024311/</event_url></item>