<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>303 South Main St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821968</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-453-3660</phone><name>Pakarang </name><city>Providence</city><id>495930</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.404690</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>OK all, I will be out of town for the weekend that the March meetup is scheduled.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, I put in the polls to see what would be the most popular option for rescheduling.  I will hold the poll open until February 25th.  Whatever is most popular is when I will schedule the event.  If there is a tie, I will flip a coin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;***Ta-da!  The overwhelming response was to have the meetup on Friday, March 21.***&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this affects your plans for attending, please update your RSVP.  Thanks everyone for understanding!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It looks like one of the most popular cuisine's per the polls is &lt;b&gt;Thai&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.  As a result I picked the restaurant Pakarang in Providence.  Please see their website &lt;a href="http://www.pakarangrestaurant.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for menu information.  Bring on the spice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because I called so early, they have all 3 options available for our reservation, so don't forget to vote for what date works best for you!   Once the date is chosen, I will work with them about dividing the bill or providing individual checks.  Please see the polls &lt;i&gt;again&lt;/i&gt;(yes, I know, but it's for your own good!) to vote on your preferred method of handling the check.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should we fill up and you are still interested in attending, please enter a &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; RSVP and put a note stating that you want to be wait-listed.   If spots open up, I will contact you in order of RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has not attended previous events, please plan on bringing a dollar to help me defray the cost of posting on meetup. That would be such a big help to me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Abi&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See my picture- I'm the one with the red hair. ;-)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206789465000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>We are a great group of people who love to dine out!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201045449000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Rhode Island Dine Out Group March Meetup- PAKARANGNG- March 21</name><id>7174158</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206140400000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/7174158/</event_url></item>