<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 King Street Ext.</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.527874</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Higgins Middle School</name><city>Peabody</city><id>4237282</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.928658</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;New York City, here we come!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;10.22 UPDATE: I am opening this event back to RSVPing &lt;strong&gt;BUT&lt;/strong&gt; what you need to know is that they have started a waiting list.  I have nothing to do with this it is from the bus company I am thinking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;I do not know how they are doing the waiting list and if you are still not able to go after you get on the waiting list then know that I am not responsible for that, nor can I do anything about it, as you have read below you see that I am posting this from the Peabody Rec. Dept. So don't delay and get on the waiting list NOW, cause I have NO clue when they will remove it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Follow the directions I have posted below and you will see the waiting list button that you need to press to add your information into.  Good Luck, hopefully you will be able to come along.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Please put in your RSVP: On waiting list, so I know that you are, thank you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10.14 UPDATE: This event is closed to new RSVP's because the bus is full.  If you RSVP'ed on the site but didn't get your ticket please remove your RSVP.  If you DID get your ticket, please update the site so we know to be looking for you.  Thank you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YUP we are going on the bus, you coming with????  This is a FULL day event and we are going even if there is rain or bad weather, all the directions are below about how to get your &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OWN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ticket. Please make sure you read it all you understand what the day’s details are, it is a long day and you are able to spend the day as you want in the city!!  I checked today and there are &lt;strong&gt;not a lot of seats left&lt;/strong&gt;, so are YOU going to be one of those spots??  You better act quick I am being told this trip WILL sell out, no time for thinking go get your ticket now…..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: The bus ride is $54.00, not including tip to the driver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I suggest you getting your ticket after you put in your RSVP here on the site, just cause you say here you are going it doesn't hold/pay for your ticket to get on the bus......&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: Peabody Recreational department is doing this bus tour and anyone can go with them, let that will be us!  There are 2 ways to get your ticket you can register in person at Peabody Rec at 50 Farm Ave Peabody OR you register/purchase your own ticket.   You can register/pay by following the directions below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1--&lt;/strong&gt; To start the process and to see what the day adventure will be, click on: &lt;a href="http://www.activityreg.com/clientpage.wcs?clientid=PEABODY&amp;amp;siteid=1"&gt;http://www.activityreg.com/clientpage.wcs?clientid=PEABODY&amp;amp;siteid=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2--&lt;/strong&gt; On the left side of the screen (Additional Info):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on trips&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3--&lt;/strong&gt; See on the left of the grid Dec. 8 &amp;amp; 15 then across New York City Day Trip:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on New York City&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4--&lt;/strong&gt; The new page comes up and gives you the COMPLETE description of the day, remember we are jumping in on their trip so we will have to go with their plan, no changing anything, as this trip isn't anything that you or I can change.  NIOTE: WE are going on the 12/8 trip!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5--&lt;/strong&gt; Hit the back button and on the top of that page you will see Register, click that.  A window will come up step 1 of 5, under register for Activities, click on TRIPS, then click on 2012 trips (right below).  Below will come up all the descriptions of the trips they have coming up.  Pull down the side bar on the middle of the page, to get to the “Nyc Day Trip Dec 8 event”. Click register fill out the form.  In the box Group or Party Name: Put Meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6--&lt;/strong&gt; You do NOT have to fill out the waiver form.  Scroll to the bottom and hit Add to Cart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7--&lt;/strong&gt; Next screen make sure all the information is correct, and click Check out I am finished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8--&lt;/strong&gt; Fill out the information for your credit card. Click process payment, print your receipt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9--&lt;/strong&gt; Please remember to come back to the Meetup site and let me know that you have paid for your ticket.  So I know to be looking for you, but be prepared if you are not there, then the bus will be leaving with out you, and that will be sad!  You will get a confirmation email, print that out and bring it with you to the bus&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once in New York you are free to run-a-muck in the city, I am not your tour guide and I will want to go where I want to go, just as you will, just as long as you get back in time to catch the bus......&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you in the parking lot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be leaning against my car.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354975855000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349052551000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Road trip..... NYC here we come!</name><id>84859832</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354964400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/84859832/</event_url></item>