<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>4.7 miles beyond the First Connecticut Lake Dam (First Sign for the Tower)</address_2><address_1>Route 3</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03592</zip><lat>45.102159</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Magalloway Mountain</name><city>Pittsburg</city><id>1343398</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.287654</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>So there are  the 48 White Mountain 4,000 footers and the NE 4,000 footers and then there are the New England 100 Highest....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But what if you aren't quite ready for all that time and elevation gain? Or what if you just need some small worthwhile hikes and inspiring views in-between those trips to the Whites?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why not climb our State's fire towers for a little exercise?  The State of NH has a program to &amp;quot;increase the public's recognition of, and appreciation for, the critical roles that our fire towers play in the protection, stewardship and sustainable use of New Hampshire's forests.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who doesn't appreciate that?  And with all hikes less than 2 miles (and many less than 1 mile!), who wouldn't be willing to get a little workout for a guaranteed view?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There are 15 Fire Towers currently in use on public land in New Hampshire.  Ascending just 5 of these towers, some of which are accessible from State Parks and auto roads, qualifies you for a Tower Quest Patch.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Information about the Fire Tower program can be found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.nhdfl.org/fire-control-and-law-enforcement/fire-towers.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhdfl.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a series of short trips and hikes to visit these locations.  I'm hoping to do most of them in the fall, when the foliage will make the payoff even better. I hope you'll join me!  And if not, I hope you'll pass on the word about this program to others who might be interested!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Magalloway Mountain&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Pittsburg&lt;br /&gt;3,360'&lt;br /&gt;State Owned&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the first in a series of short hikes and trips to various fire towers in NH.  This one is pretty far north, but since I plan to be camping at Umbagog that weekend anyway, I figured I would make it the first!  Join us for camping at Lake Umbagog that weekend if you are able (that trip is also posted on the NE Hiking Meetup).  If you are spending Labor Day weekend in the Mountains, meet up with us for a relaxing Sunday hike!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3 North of Pittsburg, 4.7 miles beyond the First Connecticut Lake dam, take the woods road east (there is a sign for the tower) and follow the signs at several junctions.  The tower access road leaves the main haul road to the right at 5.3 miles.  Follow this road approximately 2.5 miles to the trailhead.  &lt;b&gt;We will meet at the FIRST SIGN FOR THE TOWER off of Route 3 at 11am.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two different trail lead to the tower and are designated by signs.  &lt;b&gt;Both trails are about .7 miles to the tower site and negotiate steep and rough terrain.&lt;/b&gt;  At the top is a cabin, which I have *heard* is now available for rent from the NH Park system.  Come check it out!  Maybe you will want to book your honeymoon here! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that are interested in camping at Umbagog, we will return to the State Park from Magalloway Mountain.  Even if you can't camp, come stay a while and join us for dinner!  On the way home from Umbagog  (the next day), I intend to stop at Milan Hill State Park, where another fire tower (requiring no hike at all) is located.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soak in the NH scenery and start working on your Tower Quest Patch!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283780671000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281319472000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH Fire Towers Series:  Mt Magalloway </name><id>14361626</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283698800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14361626/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/6/global_17052246.jpeg</photo_url></item>