<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Wallingford</address_2><address_1>1339 Whirlwind Hill Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.436100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Goeveia Vineyards</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>345258</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.764336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>About The Vineyard&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our winery, mostly through word of mouth, has been growing by leaps and bounds, because of this we had to expand our facility. We completed this expansion, to the western side of our winery, in May 2007 and have been able to accommodate many more visitors. This added space has allowed us to expand our wine cellar, but more importantly it has opened up the winery building to allow people to sit inside and enjoy the spectacular sunset views. It is truly a bucolic masterpiece that waits just outside the windows of the entire winery. From this high of a vantage point you are able to see the growing vines, the changing leaves, and horses grazing in the pasture next door. From the front of the building you are able to look over rolling hills covered in vines and a pond with an inviting dock. Just imagine yourself sitting on the edge of the dock and your bare feet swinging back and forth over the side while you read a novel and enjoy your favorite glass of wine. &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290555090000</updated><rating><average>2.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286499751000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gouveia Vinyards</name><id>15040702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287262800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/15040702/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/d/global_2165245.jpeg</photo_url></item>