<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : xx-large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YOU THOUGHT&lt;/strong&gt; Mount Agamenticus was the highest point in the Seacoast area, didn't you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/event_105060082.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Well, think again! ...Located at the tip of North Berwick,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Bauneg Beg Mountain&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;has three peaks, the highest of which is 866' higher than Mount Agamenticus!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;The hills can be seen from the Atlantic Ocean and have been used by mariners navigating the Maine Coast. On a clear day, from the top, you can see both Mount Washington to the northwest, and the Atlantic Ocean to the southeast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mountain is the only one in southern Maine that does not have a radio tower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/4/5/event_22525157.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Bauneg Beg is an elusive mountain, seen only from a distance and in certain weather conditions. It seems to hide from those who approach, and hikers rarely expect the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;awesome rock formations&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;panoramic view&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;they find at the top. It has a few steep steps at the top, but is otherwise very manageable for just about anyone. And even the parking lot has a view!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The trails wind&lt;/strong&gt; through a deciduous forest, then up past a pine grove, snaking through a &lt;strong&gt;large boulder section&lt;/strong&gt; known as Devil's Den (not the Devil's Den in NH) and on to the view from the high peak. There is a choice of longer &amp;ndash;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ginny's Way&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; or steeper &amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Linny's Way&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; routes to the top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*I hadn't heard of this place, either until my never-ending research uncovered it today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time/Distance&lt;/strong&gt;: This should be a fairly short, &lt;strong&gt;easy&lt;/strong&gt; hike of a couple of miles &amp;amp; hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Afterward&lt;/strong&gt;... We'll head to the &lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://thebackstreetgrill.com/"&gt;Back Street Grill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in Sanford, ME a few miles away. They have a nice outdoor seating area in front and great food.&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/0/event_105061792.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/0/2/event_105065122.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dover&amp;nbsp;Carpool&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;10:45&amp;nbsp;AM&lt;/span&gt; -&amp;nbsp;Dover Park &amp;amp; Ride - Spaulding Tpk&amp;nbsp;to Exit 9. Left @ light. Then left again @ 2nd light.&amp;nbsp; Pull straight in and congregate in the rear by the fence. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't forget to share expenses with your driver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bauneg Beg Mountain Conservation Area&lt;/strong&gt;, purchased by the Trust in 2001, consists of 89 wooded acres of peaceful logging trails, surprising rock formations, and a panoramic view. Visitors will find that a new gravel parking lot has been constructed, making access to the Devil&amp;rsquo;s Den Trail a bit easier. &lt;strong&gt;Even the parking lot has a view!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The trail begins&lt;/strong&gt; at the parking lot on Fox Farm Hill Road in North Berwick, between Hammond and Ford Quint Roads, across from a large brick house. Follow the newly cut lower trail above the parking, then head left into the woods. Turn right to pick up the wide trail toward the summit. Near the top, when the trail splits, go right, wind around the big rocks and up the narrow trail to your left and out onto the cliffs, which face back over the trail. Be sure to see both sections of open face, as the views are a little different. Keep going to take the easy way down&amp;ndash; stay left! If you want to take the easy way up, rewind to &amp;ldquo;when the trail splits&amp;rdquo; and head left there, instead. The gentle trail will take you back and forth and up. On a very clear day, you&amp;rsquo;ll see both the ocean and the mountains.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/e/a/event_20038090.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.&amp;nbsp; Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving&amp;nbsp;home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>43.394477, -70.781382</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333398220000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332863600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bet You Never Heard of Bauneg Beg!</name><id>58062172</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333294200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/58062172/</event_url></item>