<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>58 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01966</zip><lat>42.655319</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rockport Community House</name><city>Rockport</city><id>3201751</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.622498</lon></venue><fee><label>Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per photographer</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;**Please check this site for updates. I'll post if there are any changes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Here's a link to the spreadsheet I tried to send via email....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/9/0/highres_85281392.jpeg"&gt;http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/even...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: Sunday, January 15, 2012 4:00 PM&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fee&lt;/strong&gt;: $3.00 per photographer + one food dish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: Rockport Community House (walking distance from the train station) &lt;br /&gt;

 58 Broadway&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Rockport, MA 01966&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year's holiday event was a huge success. Very fun. Since we've outgrown Passports, I've decided to get creative. We're going to do something a little different!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this year's event we're holding a potluck dinner at the Rockport Community House. The Community House was recently restored inside and out, it's beautiful. We'll have plenty of space to mingle, eat and look at prints.&amp;nbsp;The person I spoke with believes there's seating for up to 100. It's a wonderful venue that will be comfortable and give us a chance to catch up with each other. It'll be lovely to "talk shop" with like-minds in above freezing temps for a change :).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who are interested may arrive early to shoot. I'm setting up so can't organize that part of the day, but don't let that stop you. Feel free to utilize our message board to find others who are interested. Rockport is beautiful dressed up for the holidays!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a fun part of this meetup we'll continue the tradition of our annual "gift exchange"--with a twist. We have space to DISPLAY the prints. I thought it a wonderful opportunity to get to see each other's work.&amp;nbsp;Those interested in participating should bring along a matted or matted/framed print of one of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;your own&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;favorite photographs to exchange. It's a great way to share your photography with the group and spread a little holiday cheer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;The specifics:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Only your own photography may be exchanged.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Ideally prints would be 8x10 or larger, but really prints of any size are fine.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Please remember to sign your work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Don't wrap the prints&lt;/span&gt; so they may be displayed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Each photographer may bring 1-2 extra prints to share. They won't be part of the exchange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;- We'll draw names on the day of the event as usual.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Have fun :-)!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Happy Holidays!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The boring fine print:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rental fee is $80 ($50 rental + $30 kitchen use) since I'm a resident. Included in the fee is building rental, kitchen use, tables and chairs. I'm opting not to pay the additional fee for custodial service. If everyone could help pick up afterwards that would be wonderful. I'll supply disposable cups, silverware, and plates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FYI The building rental fee is paid upfront. The Town of Rockport doesn't offer refunds so neither can I. &lt;strong&gt;If you truly can't use Paypal, or if the fee/food is a hardship, please drop me a private email.&lt;/strong&gt; I'm much more concerned with everyone getting to attend. We'll figure out a way to make it work for all :).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329055682000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321298516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Belated CAPE Group and Seacoast Holiday POTLUCK Dinner and Print Exchange</name><id>41134772</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326661200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/41134772/</event_url></item>