<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>605 Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><lat>41.564325</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-347-4957</phone><name>Buttonwood Tree Center</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1082311</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.652057</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Quieting the Mind, Quieting the Body&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an engaging evening of exploration into your own psychic and intuitive abilities. Tonight is the first of this new monthly series! For this first class, Paul Rice will explain three important techniques for clearing away &amp;quot;the garbage&amp;quot; that can interfere with psychic awareness. These will include The 'Uh-huh' technique, Onion Layering and Felt Sense (see below for details about these techniques). These are just a few of the different techniques you will learn to help you build awareness of the invisible psychic world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be the first class in the series, Developing Psychic Skills with Paul Rice. We're expecting other people to join Paul along the way with interesting topics like aura readings and palmistry. Another class may be on moving the mind around the body, and touching injured areas to communicate with them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This class is free and open to all members of the healing community! Please join us in sharing and exploring our psychic skills together under the guidance of a highly skilled and talented teacher. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Rice stumbled into Empathetic Palm reading by sensing thoughts, feelings, opinions and sensations through touch. Paul is currently working in the medical field and has also studied the chakras, meridians, and a variety of energy techniques while attending the CT Center for Massage Therapy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Three Techniques to build Psychic Awareness:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;uh-huh&amp;quot; technique is a simple way to quiet the mind but takes practice.&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Onion Layering&amp;quot; technique comes from EST, starts with an &amp;quot;Upset&amp;quot; then following how it grows, and then how to shrink it. Useful in freeing up areas of life that are blocked.&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Felt Sense&amp;quot; comes from a psychological technique called &amp;quot;Focusing&amp;quot; done with another person or solo.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Open to the public, just come and enjoy</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jo-Ann Blanchette-Silverio</member_name><member_id>9921229</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259885458000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257716799000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quieting the Mind, Quiteting the Body</name><id>11826832</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259712000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/11826832/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_11962913.jpeg</photo_url></item>