<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Moose Hill is Mass Audubon?s oldest sanctuary and one of the largest with nearly 2,000 acres. The 25-mile trail system brings you through diverse habitats? explore the red maple swamp via the boardwalk, observe amphibians at a vernal pool, or watch swallows catching insects in the meadows. Each season brings another opportunity to explore nature?s wonders?enjoy a winter stroll, watch migrating warblers, or experience the beauty of the fall foliage. Our bird-feeding station and butterfly garden bring wildlife close to the nature center. Art exhibits are shown September through June, and the gift shop is open year-round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is $4 for non-members/$3 for non member seniors/chilldren&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the north: Take Rt I-95 south to exit 10 (Coney St, Sharon, Walpole). Take a left off the exit and take the first right onto Rt 27 north (Walpole). Take first left on Moose Hill Street. Follow to the top of the hill and turn left onto Moose Hill Parkway. The parking lot is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the south: Take Rt I-95 north to exit 8 (Main St, Sharon). Take a right off the exit and follow one mile. Take a left onto Moose Hill Street. Follow to the top of the hill and turn right onto Moose Hill Parkway. The parking lot is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By public transportation: From Boston?s South Station, take the Attleboro commuter train to Sharon. From the Sharon station walk to the main road, Rt 27. Follow north for two blocks and take a left onto Moose Hill Parkway. Walk 1.5 miles to the top of the hill; the nature center is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will Dine at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bickfords&lt;br /&gt;973 Providence Hwy&lt;br /&gt;Sharon, MA 02067&lt;br /&gt;(781) 784-8633  &lt;br /&gt;bickfordsrestaurants.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183386967000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178309315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moose Hill Wildlife Sanctuary</name><id>5742535</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183213800000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5742535/</event_url></item>