<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Reservation Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03037</zip><lat>43.104805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pawtuckaway State Park</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>632081</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.205055</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>CLIMB, SWIM, AND BOAT ALL W/ OUT MOVING YOUR CAR!  Pawtuckaway is a well known climbing area w/ lots to discover if you've never been.  &lt;br /&gt;May be buggy so BRING THE BUG STUFF!  &lt;br /&gt;Directions for those who will be still coming: You don't go to the big lake side of Pawtuckaway!&lt;br /&gt;From 101 take Raymond exit to 107 go right if coming from East.  Follow 107 to  light Past all the stores (end of road) Take a left on 27 W follow for mile or so You will pass a sign for 156 and Pawtuck. (don't take this road!)  continue on 27 bear right on 107.  Mile or so on right is Revservation rd.  Down a bit the road turns to dirt, and may be bumpy.  there will be a fork in the road, go right.  When you see a left turn w/ an open gate turn, follow this road until round pond. Going straight through the intersection.  If you pass the &amp;quot;short cut&amp;quot; you will pass tthe Tower trail and loop around to the intersection and go right to round pond.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Large green van, meetup signs.  We will start on LakeSide Jam near round pond, can see the cliff from the parking.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kellie Barr-Foster</member_name><member_id>6992283</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213024216000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Pawtuckaway has many climbs, both short top rope or bouldering.  There is a place to swim on round pond.  Easy access to kayak/canoe also.</why><group><who>Rock Climbers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>rockclimbing-134</urlname><id>1120342</id><group_lat>43.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>The NH Rock Climbing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212545772000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pawtuckaway Outing</name><id>8074049</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212850800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rockclimbing-134/events/8074049/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/e/7/global_4349095.jpeg</photo_url></item>