<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2934 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06033</zip><lat>41.723716</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sacred Rivers Yoga</name><city>Glastonbury</city><id>969718</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.614641</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt; If you are new to Yoga, or have taken Yoga classes before, don't miss this opportunity to take a great Yoga class at a discount price - and hang out with a bunch of cool people after the class!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Relieve Stress The Safe and Healthy Way and Meet Other Smart and Healthy Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join SinglesCT.com for a specially designed Yoga for Stress Release class – that is designed for anyone who wants to lean the natural and healthy way to reduce stress – and meet some great people before and after the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 7 pm class for about an hour of specially designed class that focuses on Stress Relief. After the class, we will go down the street to Burtucci's Restaurant to hang out, share a pizza or sample some great Italian food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great class for both beginners and the more experienced, and you will leave this class feeling calm, stress-free, relaxed and enjoying the natural high that comes with Yoga and deep breathing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING: Wear loose comfortable clothing and bring water. You can bring your own Yoga mat ($5 at Ocean State) or one will be provided for you at the studio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO EXPECT: You can expect to meet many quality, healthy local Singles, and feel refreshed and stress-free with this centuries old tested method for stress-relief that focuses on the healthy Holistic approach to total body health – and managing your stress without the use of chemicals is a very important part of total body health.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;* This class is only $10 ADV TIX online, or $15 at the event *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPACE IS LIMITED TO 20 PEOPLE AND WILL FILL UP QUICKLY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: - To reserve your spot, you NEED to purchase your ticket&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sacred Rivers Yoga&lt;br /&gt;2934 Main Street &lt;br /&gt;Glastonbury, CT 06033&lt;br /&gt;860.657.9545&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sacredriversyoga.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sacredrive...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can get your ticket here, or at &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SinglesCT....&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or call (860) 236-3343&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEE YOU AT THE STUDIO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our group will be in the room across from the front desk</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287534163000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279034162000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Relieve Stress The Safe and Healthy Way and Meet Other Smart and Healthy Singles</name><id>xcfbpynnbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287529200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/14963832/</event_url></item>