<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>162 Ives Street</address_1><state>Rh</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.822685</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Captain Seaweed's</name><city>Providence</city><id>2851251</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.392159</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series! This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and event scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Captain Seaweed's - on the East Side of Providence on Ives St. 3 blocks north of Wickenden St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Captain Seaweeds is a &lt;strong&gt;FAVORITE&lt;/strong&gt; P-Collective spot (just ask anyone) and the site of one of the largest Monday Night Meetups on record.  FREE FOOD!  The management at Captain Seaweed's was so happy about the turnout last time, and had such a great time hanging out with us, they are repeating the cookout they threw for us last year - and we know how amazing THAT was!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drinks will still be their usual low prices, but the burgers, hot dogs, and sides will be on the house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please be sure to RSVP by 9am on the 9th**&lt;/strong&gt; We need to give an accurate head count to the bar's management so they know how many people they are feeding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remember, they don't take plastic, so bring a fist full of dollars.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Other than a handful of the bar's regulars, we'll be taking up most of the place.  If the weather is nice we'll be outside on their fantastic patio.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341977583000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>99</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340999853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Captain Seaweed's!!!!!!!!</name><id>71319442</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341871200000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/71319442/</event_url></item>