<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>****Updated Parking/Train Directions.  See below.****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come one come all to the first event in our new house.  The place is huge so no worries about some of the crowding we've had at the apartment.  We should have more chairs by that time as well, but if it's not too much trouble you may want to bring one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time line:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;1:00&lt;/u&gt; people can show up and have fun with games.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;6:00&lt;/u&gt; or so Your hosts will stop for few hours to eat and mingle with the non-gaming people who can make it out.  Feel free to continue playing or mingle as you wish.&lt;br /&gt;The games/party will continue for as long as people want to stay or until Monday afternoon whatever comes first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to bring&lt;/b&gt; (select all that apply ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Games&lt;/u&gt; - We have plenty, but we don't have them all&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Food (non-snacks)&lt;/u&gt; - We will be having a dinner time and can refrigerate or heat whatever you want to bring.  I'll keep you posted on whether or not we buy a grill, but probably not given all of the other costs with moving.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Food (snacks)&lt;/u&gt; - We can't fit all of the eating for an event like this into one meal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Drinks (non-alcoholic)&lt;/u&gt; - Sometimes everyone brings some; sometimes no one does.  &amp;quot;You pay your dime you take your chances.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Drinks (alcoholic)&lt;/u&gt; - I'm not driving and we'll have plenty of room for those who want to crash, but we're not big drinkers ourselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Chairs&lt;/u&gt; - We should have more than we have in the past but we probably won't have enough.  You can even bring them and leave them if you have any you want to get rid of.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Other&lt;/u&gt; - Bring anything you like as long as it doesn't get anyone in trouble with the law&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Travel/Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Parking&lt;/u&gt; - I live close to the beginning of the street, so at soon as you make the turn start looking for parking.  Most of the parking in the area is resident only.  We have a driveway that can fit 3 tandem so if you drive, pull all the way in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;*Parking update&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;: I have received special parking consideration for the day so I will have permits for everyone's dashboard.  Just remember to ask me for one when you get in.  This is only valid for my street, so please save the driveway for those who arive late or are dropping things off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Train&lt;/u&gt; - we live 6-8 minute walk from the back exit of Alewife.  Just walk away from the main road (the only one you can see from that exit) When you come to a fork in the trail take the middle one.  Clay street is a strait shot from there.  Turn left at Clay and we are on the left in a brown building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Bus&lt;/u&gt; - nearby is the 350, 77, 79, 83, 87, 88, 89&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call me if you have any questions at all.  Ben 617-997-3545&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben Warmus</member_name><member_id>5401423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283823799000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281501198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>House warming game day/ party</name><id>14387292</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283619600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/14387292/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>