<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>401 Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.343983</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 236-0746 </phone><name>REI</name><city>Boston</city><id>846863</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102784</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is a presentation by Jeff Alt (www.jeffalt.com).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jeff Alt walked the 2,160-mile Appalachian Trail along, hiked the 218-mile John Muir Trail with his wife, and trekked across a 50-mile path of Ireland with his wife, young daughter, and extended family. The Alts are so passionate about hiking, they even wore backpacks out of the church on their wedding day. His son was taken on his first hike when he was only 8-weeks old. The Alts camp and hit the trail every chance they get.&amp;nbsp;Alt is a member of the Outdoor Writers Association of America (OWAA). Jeff has had his adventures featured in media nationwide including ESPN, the Hallmark Channel, AP, CNN-Radio, and NPR. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While you can use this event listing to coordinate with other randomites you should call the number listed for the event to get more information or to register&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;October 27, 2011 @ 6:30 PM "&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Appalachian Trail Show"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;REI Boston &lt;br /&gt;

401 Park Drive &lt;br /&gt;

Boston, MA 02215&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attendance is Free&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reserve a seat: &lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/event/24409/session/30150" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.rei.com/event/24409/session/30150&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bears, bugs, blisters and hilarious food cravings in an epic outdoor adventure story&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff takes you along every step of his 2,160-mile Appalachian Trail adventure filled with hilarious and engaging tales, stunning photography, and music based on his new edition of A Walk for Sunshine (book &amp;amp; DVD). You will hear humorous, frightening, and inspirational stories including: bears, bugs, blisters, interesting characters, skunk bedmates, mice, and hilarious food cravings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff shares hilarious food cravings from the trail&amp;mdash;the tree branch looked like New York Strip, the dirt kicked in with the snow, looked like Oreo cookie ice-cream. You will learn how he ate a large pizza as a snack, a dozen donuts before breakfast; and still lost 30 pounds from burning 4-6,000 calories a day on the trail&amp;mdash;the equivalence of running two marathons a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff made his original trek to raise money for Sunshine, the home where his brother with cerebral palsy lives. Alt&amp;rsquo;s journey changed the lives of Sunshine&amp;rsquo;s residents with special needs by inspiring an annual walk that has raised over $250,000. For additional information, visit &lt;a href="http://jeffalt.com/media.asp" class="linkified"&gt;http://jeffalt.com/media.asp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff's Appalachian Trail Show is based on his book, A Walk for Sunshine: A 2,160-mile expedition for charity on the Appalachian Trail $15.95 paperback; (ISBN: 978-0-9679482-3-2; Dreams Shared Publications, printed on recycled paper). A Walk for Sunshine is a Book of the Year GOLD medalist and a winner of the 2009 National Best Books Award. Alt&amp;rsquo;s presentation is available on film: A Walk For Sunshine Appalachian Trail Show ($19.95 DVD; ISBN: 978-0-9679482-5-6). A Walk for Sunshine contains valuable hiking tips and gear suggestions to help anyone plan an adventure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This story is for anyone seeking inspiration to achieve their own goals." &amp;ndash; Roger, WNRI&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...There are numerous books on hiking the Appalachian Trail, but Alt tells the story best..."&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; Carey Kish, Maine Outdoor Journal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;The one-man show will find author Jeff Alt humorously recounting his 2,000-mile journey, which included encounters with bears and skunks along with elaborate cravings traced to the burning of about 4,000 calories a day&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Nick Chordas, The Columbus Dispatch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information visit www.jeffalt.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319759409000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316656684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Appalachian Trail Show (Educational Series)</name><id>34502692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319754600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/34502692/</event_url></item>