<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Washington St., Suite 6B</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.518270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-639-1236</phone><name>A Higher Balance Healing Center</name><city>Salem</city><id>1342529</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895192</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Spiritual Awakening and Divine Openings &lt;em&gt;with Judy&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Join us for an evening of radiant bliss with sacred ceremony, chakra meditation, light discussions and Divine Openings. &lt;br /&gt;

This group now meets monthly; third Thursday of each month&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;This program is for anyone interested in accessing and sustaining higher consciousness. We will enter sacred ceremony to lift our hearts and energy fields for chakra illumination and meditation. You will receive two or three Divine Openings and learn about ways to open and sustain freedom through higher vibrations. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;     Divine&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Openings is an enlightenment activation. No matter where you are on your path of awakening, you will love this sacred way of being in divine energy! The Divine Presence becomes apparent as divine love and joy. &lt;br /&gt;

Judy will share light teachings based on the book &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Everything is Going Great in my Absence&lt;/span&gt; by Lola Jones (available through Judy), as well as her ongoing deep studies in the area of conscious awakening. At our meetings we can freely express and connect with like- hearted souls as we share in the powerful energy transmissions that provide expanded awareness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Divine-Openings-New-England/events/69759742/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comments after other programs... &lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;"I just want you to know I feel incredible! The energy is so powerful and the sense of expansion is remarkable! Thank you for introducing me to this!" -Sylvia" &lt;br /&gt;

"Well that was pretty special last night. Thank you so much for offering these Divine Openings; working my way through the book alone was, well, lonely...so I am delighted to have a community of kindred spirits to share parts of the journey with."- Pat &lt;br /&gt;

"I stayed really happy and energized after the last group. I'm laughing a lot!" &lt;br /&gt;

"A lot of remarkable coincidences happened, and things I want are coming my way easily, no effort!" &lt;br /&gt;

"I saw so much bring light and felt so much love!"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy Copp</member_name><member_id>8642061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348194324000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Evolving Beings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Evolving-Beings</urlname><id>1429576</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>Evolving Beings</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345999476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spiritual Awakening and Divine Openings</name><id>qrdhfdyqmbbc</id><headcount>11</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348182000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Evolving-Beings/events/79432922/</event_url></item>