<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;A FULL day with Louis Brown&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://Register Today!" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.memberize.com/clubportal/EventDisplayNew.cfm?clubID=1762&amp;amp;EventID=67966&amp;amp;mo=9&amp;amp;tDate=%7Bd%20" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.memberize....&lt;/a&gt;'2008-09-25'%7D&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come learn the step-by-step, nuts and bolts Money Making Secrets of Finding, Buying, Structuring, Holding, Managing, Financing and Selling Real Estate revealed by a Full Time Professional who has been buying and selling houses since he was a teenager!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You’ll learn the Street Smart™ Wealth Strategy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to Create Credibility Even if You’re Broke &lt;br /&gt;Finding Deals NOT in Competition with Others &lt;br /&gt;Buying the Non-Traditional Way &lt;br /&gt;Uncovering Hidden Profits Available in ANY Deal &lt;br /&gt;How to Take Over Someone Else’s Loan with NO Money &lt;br /&gt;Moneymaking Management Secrets &lt;br /&gt;Deals Using Telephone Secrets &lt;br /&gt;Which Properties to Hold and How to Do It &lt;br /&gt;Buying and Selling Using Lease Option and Agreement for Deed Techniques &lt;br /&gt;Renovations - What You Need to Make the Most Money &lt;br /&gt;Accelerating Your Cash Flow Using “Profit Centers” &lt;br /&gt;Case Studies: Secrets of How They Were Found, Negotiated and Sold &lt;br /&gt;Secrets to Protect Your Deal From Being Sold to Someone Else &lt;br /&gt;Creating Your Mind Set for Real Estate Wealth &lt;br /&gt;How to Pay ZERO Taxes on Your Real Estate Portfolio &lt;br /&gt;Taking Title the Right Way for Maximum Safety and Profit &lt;br /&gt;When &amp;amp; How to Quit the Full Time &amp;quot;Golden Handcuffs&amp;quot; of the Corporate Job &lt;br /&gt;Having Your Tenants Leave Your Property in Better Condition Than When You Gave It to Them &lt;br /&gt;How to Become Manager Rather than Owner &lt;br /&gt;Why to use Land and Personal Property Trusts &lt;br /&gt;How to Protect Your Assets with Trusts &lt;br /&gt;Multiple Trust Strategies &lt;br /&gt;How to Paper Train Attorneys on Land Trusts &lt;br /&gt;The Due-on-Sale Clause - What it is and How to Avoid it Legally &lt;br /&gt;How to Create Retirement Accelerators &lt;br /&gt;And MUCH More &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About our Speaker… Louis “Lou” Brown&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Students in all fifty states have long regarded the training, systems and forms created by Louis Brown at the best in the industry, across Canada and ten foreign countries including as far away as Australia and New Zealand.  Quoted as an expert by many publications and authors, “Lou” draws from a wide and varied background as a real estate investor having been buying property since 1977.  He’s invested in Single-family homes, apartments, hotels, developed subdivisions and built and renovated homes and apartments.  Each of these experiences has given him a proving ground for the most cutting edge concepts in the real estate investment industry today.  He’s widely known as a creative financing genius with his deal structuring concepts.  Being a teacher at heart he enjoys sharing his discoveries with others.  He has served the industry in many volunteer positions such as past President and designated lifetime member of the Georgia real estate investor association, the worlds largest investor group with over 3,200 members.  He was also founding President of the National Real Estate Investors Association, which serves as the umbrella association of local investor groups. Husband, Father, Author, Lecturer, Inventor, Investor, Builder, Designer and real estate expert are all descriptions of this exciting trainer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Details&lt;br /&gt;7:30 Check-in starts &lt;br /&gt;8-4:30 Seminar &lt;br /&gt;Location: Best Western 380 Winter Street, Waltham, Ma. &lt;br /&gt;Members $39 &lt;br /&gt;Members plus guest $59 &lt;br /&gt;Visitors $79 &lt;br /&gt;Visitors plus guest $99 &lt;br /&gt;Everyone pays $125 at the door! You must pre-register for the discounted rate!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224193065000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219976680000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LOU BROWN - Learn Street Smart Strategies</name><id>8644655</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221910200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/8644655/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/b/global_1787963.jpeg</photo_url></item>