<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Tanager St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.421910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-648-3737</phone><name>Herb Pearce's</name><city>Arlington</city><id>899371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188564</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Herb Pearce continues to teach us amazing tools to learn more about ourselves and how to relate with others. Here is a description from Herb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Are you more auditory, visual or kinesthetic and in what order do you use these senses to learn and communicate? Learn more about yourself and others and how to communicate more effectively to the other 5 types. Add this tool to other systems you might know such as the Enneagram or Myers-Briggs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 -10:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sliding Scale for Unique People is $15-40. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15, it helps the presenter and those who might pay less. No one is turned away because of money, so pay what you can honestly afford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. You are also welcome to bring vegetarian appetizers and drinks, including wine.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce ******&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce, M.Ed., has been teaching personality systems for 20 years and has been a psychotherapist for 30 years, having worked with thousands of individuals, couples and families, as well as teams in corporations and agencies. Author of The Idiot's Guide to the Enneagram, he has also taught different personality systems to explain the unique flavor of how people experience life.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255129479000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252710246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Personal Thinking Patterns - Auditory, Visual and Kinesthetic Perception</name><id>11350655</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254524400000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/11350655/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/e/global_9483022.jpeg</photo_url></item>