<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join &lt;b&gt;Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneurs Group&lt;/b&gt; for the Seminar Series Presentation!  The Seminar Series adds value by presenting focused topics in law and business that are critical to the success of entrepreneurial organizations.   Revolve Nation is a national community of entrepreneurs and small business leaders dedicated to building and growing revolutionary businesses nationwide.  The Boston Chapter is the largest community of entrepreneurs in the city of Boston.   We look forward to seeing you at our seminars and events.  See below for more details. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOPIC:&lt;/b&gt; Contracts:  What You Need and How To Negotiate Them&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME:&lt;/b&gt; 6-8pm &lt;a href="http://www.exemplarlaw.com" target="_blank"&gt;Exemplar Law Partners (Boston)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: About to hire an employee or land your first big deal?  Did you find your first joint venture or strategic alliance?   Whatever the situation, contracts are the key to successful business relationships.  Don't let what you don't know bring your business down.  Join us for this informative seminar on business contracts and negotiations and learn how to walk the line between being economical and risking your success! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPONSORS:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Revolve, Inc - Presented By:  &lt;a href="http://www.revolvethis.com" target="_blank"&gt; www.revolvethis.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exemplar Law Group - Space   &lt;a href="http://www.exemplarlaw.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.exemplarlaw.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP as space is limited!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Marston</member_name><member_id>2731493</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219356631000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218310482000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar Series:  Contracts: What You Need and How To Negotiate Them (Boston)</name><id>8510877</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219183200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/8510877/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/f/global_1065599.jpeg</photo_url></item>