<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you have suddenly found yourself widowed at a young age, or if you were widowed in the past but would still benefit from interaction with others in the same situation, please join us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An informal drop in meeting held on the 4th Tuesday of every month (Sept thru June) from 7 - 8.30pm.  &lt;br /&gt;The discussions cover topics such as family, work, financial changes, social changes, grieving through the holidays and finding the day to day strength to move forward.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being widowed at a young age can be a very isolating experience. This group provides a safe and supportive environment in which to discuss day to day issues as well as larger questions about the future.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to join us at one of our monthly meetings.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: We are no longer meeting in the Coffee Shop due to the front door being locked at 6pm. All future meetings will be held in Conference Room A located next to the ER on the lower level. Please park in the lower lot to the right of the Hospital and enter thru the ER door which is at the back of the Hospital. Conference Room A will be on your right after entering the Hospital.  &lt;br /&gt;Thank you for your patience and understanding while we looked for a more convenient room at the Hospital. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to meeting you in our new location, Conference Room A. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take care and have a nice day, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Olive McMeel &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540662000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Widows and Widowers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>widow-38</urlname><id>165673</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Young Widow and Widowers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1161734643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Young Widows and Widowers November Meetup</name><id>5220509</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1164758400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/widow-38/events/5220509/</event_url></item>