<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>US 302 </address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.254135</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>DAVIS PATH</name><city>BRETTON WOODS</city><id>4693422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449745</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The path leaves US 302 on the west side of the Saco River at a paved parking lot near the Notchland Inn, 5.6 mi. south of the Willey House site in Crawford Notch State Park.starting at Davis Path Trailhead Back to here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The path leaves US 302 on the west side of the Saco River at a paved parking lot near the Notchland Inn. It follows the bank of the river about 200 yd. upstream to the new suspension footbridge (Bemis Bridge). Beyond the east end of the bridge, the trail passes through private land, continuing straight east across an overgrown field near a camp, then turns left into a path along a power line and crosses a small brook. It then swings right and enters the woods and the WMNF, and soon joins and follows a logging road along the bed of a small brook (normally dry in summer). It crosses the brook bed at a point where there may be running water upstream, soon crosses a tributary, and begins to climb away from the main brook, shortly passing into the Presidential Range&amp;ndash;Dry River Wilderness. It turns sharp right and soon enters the old, carefully graded bridle path and begins to ascend the steep ridge between Mt. Crawford and Mt. Hope by zigzags. Attaining the crest, the Davis Path follows this ridge north, rising over bare ledges with good outlooks, particularly to Mt. Carrigain and the Tripyramids. to the junction of Mt Crawford spur hike 0.30 mi/15 min/+196 ft on the Mt Crawford spur to Mt Crawford Totals Distance 2.50 mi Time 2 hr 19 min Elev Gain +2125 ft Elev Loss -14 ft Elev Change +2111 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.30 mi/15 min/-196 ft on the Mt Crawford spur to the junction of Davis Path The Resolution Shelter (located off the Davis Path nearly 4 miles from the trailhead) has been posted closed by the WMNF due to safety concerns associated with the deteriorating condition of the shelter. No camping is allowed within the shelter, or within the 1/4 mile Forest Protections Area (FPA) around the shelter and 200' from trails. Alternate sites are available at Stairs Mountain. hike 2.20 mi/2 hr 4 min/-1915 ft on the Davis Path The Davis Path follows this ridge south, descending over bare ledges with good outlooks, particularly to Mt. Carrigain and the Tripyramids. It then leaves the crest and soon enters the old, carefully graded bridle path and begins to descend the steep ridge between Mt. Crawford and Mt. Hope by zigzags. It then leaves the Presidential Range&amp;ndash;Dry River Wilderness. It climbs toward the main brook, crosses a tributary and then crosses the brook bed at a point where there may be running water upstream. It then follows a logging road along the bed of a small brook (normally dry in summer). It swings left and leaves the WMNF and the woods. It crosses a small brook and then turns onto a path along a power line. It continues straight west across an overgrown field near a camp and into private land. It crosses the new suspension footbridge (Bemis Bridge) and follows the west side of the Saco River about 200 yd. downstream to the paved parking lot near the Notchland Inn on US 302. to Davis Path Trailhead Totals Distance 5.00 mi Time 4 hr 38 min Elev Gain +2140 ft Elev Loss -2140 ft Elev Change 0 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER SUBARU LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323822720000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323111434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT CRAWFORD</name><id>43461352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323615600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/43461352/</event_url></item>