<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Photo Shoot at Mount Auburn (Cemetery) Cultural Landscape&lt;br /&gt;Loctaion: Mount Auburn Cemetery, 580 Mount Auburn Street, Cambridge, MA 02138.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ORGANIZER: Biagio (Note there is a photo of me so you can find me) &lt;br /&gt;CONTACT Biagio: &lt;a href="http://socialnetwork.meetup.com/422/message/?recipientId=3847345"&gt;http://socialnetwork....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TARGET AUDIENCE: All Members that enjoy Photography, nature and good views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Description: Mount Auburn Cemetery has been designated a National Historic Landmark by the Department of the Interior, recognizing it as one of the country's most significant cultural landscapes. Founded in 1831, it was the first large-scale designed landscape open to the public in the United States. Today its beauty, historical associations and horticultural collections are internationally renowned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Auburn Cemetery is one of the most beautiful and historic landscapes in America. Its impressive collection of over 5,000 trees represents 630 taxa. Thousands of shrubs and herbaceous plants weave through 175 acres of hills, dells, ponds, woodlands and clearings. The landscape reflects different styles ranging from Victorian-era plantings to contemporary gardens, from natural woodlands to formal ornamental gardens, and from sweeping vistas through majestic trees to small enclosed spaces. The Cemetery is widely known for its meticulous maintenance. Plant species from around the world that grow in a northern temperate climate can be seen on the grounds, including individual specimens recorded as Massachusetts state or New England champions of their species. Display labels with scientific and common names are found on many trees and on shrubs and herbaceous plants in some special landscaped areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Auburn Cemetery is a privately owned institution. Its grounds and historical collections are open to the public and visitors are welcome. Open from 8:00 AM to 7:00 PM September. A variety of maps and materials about the Cemetery are available at the Entrance Gate and in the Cemetery office. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wonderful view of Boston and Cambridge from Washington Tower in Mt. Auburn Cemetery: &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/point08/sets/72157600645503795/"&gt;http://www.flickr.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special notes: Visitors are allowed to drive in the Cemetery and may park on any roads without a green line.  Bicycles and motorcycles are not permitted but may be parked at the Entrance Gate area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Etiquette: Mount Auburn is still an active burial place. It is a sacred site, and visitors are expected to behave appropriately. Pets are not permitted. Recreational activities such as picnicking, jogging, and rollerblading are not permitted. Gravestones are fragile. Please do not touch them. Gravestone rubbing is prohibited. &lt;br /&gt;Photographing funerals is prohibited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets meet in front of Bigelow Chapel: see photo of it at this Web site: &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Image:Bigelowchapel.jpg"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bigelow Chapel is on Chapel Ave which on the right about 600 feet after you enter the of Mount Auburn Cemetery from the Mount Auburn St. Enterance.&lt;br /&gt;Note: When you enter Mount Auburn Cemetery from the Mount Auburn St. Enterance please stop off at the at the side of the front gate for a minute and pick up a Map of Mount Auburn Cemetery (Do not park there long)  ?.yes you should donate a dollar for the Map and some money for what other brochures or pamphlet you take. There is a box in that area to put your money in. It costs them money to keep this place nice so contribute please.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Park your car somewhere safe in the surrounding area inside the Mount Auburn Cemetery and walk back Bigelow Chapel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can break for lunch at 12:30PM if people like and eat nearby and come back if people still want too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.mountauburn.org/"&gt;http://www.mountaubur...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wikipedia  link: &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Auburn_Cemetery"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;a href="http://www.mountauburn.org/visit_participate/directions.cfm"&gt;http://www.mountaubur...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh and yes this is T Accessible (MBTA or Public Transportation as you may call it)&lt;br /&gt;At Harvard Square Station (Red Line), take either the Watertown Square or Waverley Square trolley (#71 or #73). Get off on Mount Auburn Street at Aberdeen Avenue. Cross Mount Auburn Street to the Entrance Gate. (Check schedules on the MBTA website.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190294851000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187045339000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photo Shoot at Mount Auburn (Cemetery) Cultural Landscape</name><id>6174978</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189951200000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/6174978/</event_url></item>