<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>531 Pearl Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02072</zip><lat>42.138496</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Foley's Backstreet Grille</name><city>Stoughton</city><id>9277622</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113846</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join members and guests of the SSDOMG as we discover another restaurant on the south shore!  Foley's Backstreet Grille has been highly recommended by a friend of Angela's, who has dined here several times.  The portions are big, the atmosphere is laid-back and casual, and they cater to everyone from singles to families of all ages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything on the menu is less than $21, with approximately 2/3 of the menu under $15!!  We hope you will join us for Angela's 1st official event as an Assistant Organizer as we dine out on a Friday night... inexpensively!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inexpensive Friday Night Dinner!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, October 5th @ 7pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Foley's Backstreet Grille&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;531 Pearl Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stoughton, MA 02072&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone: 781-297-0100&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: www.backstreetgrille.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Please meet inside the front door. We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizers&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: [Current] Annual Members - FREE, Members - $2 each; Guests - $2 each&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: Minimum of 6 people 48 hours in advance.  Maximum of 12 people (reduced from 16 @ 9:30pm on Thursday night to 12 @ 2pm on Friday).  We may be separated into 2 tables if there are more than 10 people attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Two adults per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Thursday, October 4th @ 8pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our Group's No-Show Policy. Whatever we call in for a number tonight is the maximum we can have in attendance.  No drop-ins please.  You can RSVP up until 4pm on the day of the event (to take any vacated spots).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No-Show Policy on Membership Information Page:&lt;/em&gt; (Please click on the following link to be taken directly to the page.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/em&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Based on the weather forecast we should be OK.  There may be a passing shower but we will meet rain or shine.  Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather").&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the Pages tab for more information about the SSDOMG's policies and procedures which help ensure a smoother, relaxed, fun dining experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;: Courtesy of the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overview: Pearl Street runs parallel to Route 138 to the west.  This is a short distance (probably just under a mile) from Stoughton Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;FROM  ROUTE 24:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;TAKE EXIT 19B AND FOLLOW CENTRAL ST. 2.7 MILES, TAKING A RIGHT AT THE 7TH SET OF TRAFFIC LIGHTS ONTO PEARL ST. RESTAURANT IS .4 MILES ON RIGHT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;FROM  BROCKTON OR STOUGHTON:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;FOLLOW RTE 27 INTO STOUGHTON CENTER. ONCE IN THE CENTER, TAKE THE STREET TO THE LEFT OF RTE  138 THIS IS PEARL STREET (TOWN HALL WILL BE ON YOUR LEFT). PROCEED STRAIGHT AT STOP SIGN AND   THROUGH 2 SETS OF LIGHTS. THE RESTAURANT IS ON YOUR RIGHT AFTER THE 2ND SET OF LIGHT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;FROM ROUTE 93 SOUTH OR ROUTE 128 SOUTH:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;TAKE EXIT 2A STOUGHTON AND FOLLOW .6 MILES TO 1ST SET OF LIGHTS, BEAR RIGHT ON WASHINGTON ST. AND FOLLOW 1.5 MILES TO 1ST SET OF LIGHTS, TAKE LEFT ONTO PLEASANT ST. (PLEASANT ST. BECOMES PEARL ST.), RESTAURANT IS 2.8 MILES ON LEFT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;FROM PROVIDENCE / ROUTE 95 NORTH&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;TAKE EXIT 11A NEPONSET ST. CANTON AND FOLLOW .7 MILES TO 1ST SET OF LIGHTS, TAKE LEFT ON CHAPMAN ST. FOR .3 MILES, TAKE RIGHT ON SPAULDING ST., GO TO END (APPROX. 100 YARDS), TAKE RIGHT ON SHERMAN ST., FOLLOW 1.3 MILES TO FLASHING LIGHT, TAKE RIGHT ON PLEASANT ST. (PLEASANT ST. BECOMES PEARL ST.), RESTAURANT IS 1.7 MILES ON LEFT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Landmarks&lt;/em&gt;: Denneno's Pizza appears to be on the same block with Faith Baptist Church up the street just past the next street, both on the same side of the road.  Driving south, you will pass the church and then the pizza restaurant.  Driving north, you will pass Columbia Street and then Donahue Way on your left before the restaurant, which is on your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside the front door or at our table after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349627023000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347728216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inexpensive Friday Night Dinner!</name><id>82531522</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349478000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/82531522/</event_url></item>