<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Walbach Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03854</zip><lat>43.070872</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>PORTSMOUTH HARBOR LIGHTHOUSE</name><city>New Castle</city><id>921808</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.714063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a great place to visit and bring your friends and families.  Something different &amp;amp; fun, and a little bit of history at the same time. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am usually unable to attend, as Real Estate has kept me pretty busy, but I hope you can make it at least once this year...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;susan tisbert&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and from Jeremy, who runs the lighthouse...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friends of &lt;span&gt;Portsmouth Harbor&lt;/span&gt; Lighthouses, a chapter of the American Lighthouse Foundation, will host the first open house of 2012 at Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouse in New Castle, NH, on Sunday, May 27, from 1:00 to 5:00 p.m. The open houses will continue every Sunday through Columbus Day weekend in October.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No reservations are needed; the guided tours are on a first come, first served basis. Children under 42 inches tall are not permitted to climb to the top, and adults are not permitted to carry children up the stairs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visitors are invited to climb to the lantern room to enjoy the magnificent view at the mouth of the Piscataqua River and to see the 19th century lens up close. Volunteers will tell visitors about the history of the light station, and there will be souvenirs for sale. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 44 stairs and a 7-rung ladder to the lantern room. Flat shoes (not sandals or flip-flops) are strongly recommended to climb to the top.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The suggested donation to climb the lighthouse is $4 for adults and $2 for children 12 and under. Visitors should park outside the gate to Coast Guard Station Portsmouth Harbor and walk to the lighthouse. For more information, visit &lt;a href="http://www.portsmouthharborlighthouse.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.portsmouthharborlighthouse.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, &lt;br /&gt;

Jeremy D'Entremont &lt;br /&gt;

Operations Manager, Friends of Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouses &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At Coast guard station take a right, look for fenced area to park near, and enter through gate.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy D'Entremont</member_name><member_id>12517576</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349643704000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349115113000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tour the Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouse in beautiful Newcastle, NH</name><id>dvptddyqnbkb</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349629200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/84968972/</event_url></item>