<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Nina and I were contacted by one of the managers of the Village Gate Retirement Community in Farmington with a interesting offer: They'd let us use their space (their BEAUTIFUL space, I've since found!) for game nights in exchange for us "letting" a few of their 160 residents join us. We'll probably only get 10 or so of them the first time around  --  hopefully we'll get more of them and more of us each time!  It sounds like a win-win to me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/9/c/event_124463452.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The residents there are VERY active. Their social calendar is booked to the gills: They literally have 6 - 8 activities scheduled every single day. I really don't get the impression that we'll be playing with residents who will fall asleep between turns or who will have too hard of a time picking up a new game or two.  Many of them still drive!  I'm excited to teach them Wizards, and I bet they'd get a kick out of Taboo or Apples to Apples, or whatever!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So here's the deal: I hope to do this every month, on the third Tuesday of the month. Bring whatever games you want to play, and bring a willingness to teach your games to some eager new friends.  They'll probably have some ideas, too, of course!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can, you're encouraged to bring a snack to share and BYOB. Alcohol or not is fine. Residents can imbibe if they choose to -- staff members just can't pour for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We won't ask residents to contribute to our group, but if you learned of the event through this site, please bring a Nina buck to help keep the group going!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any questions?  Just ask!  :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the "South Living Room."  Just ask one of the residents to direct you to it.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340393089000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338325832000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Play Games with the Residents of Village Gate in Farmington</name><id>qffpxcyqjbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340146800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/66829032/</event_url></item>