<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Friday Night&lt;/b&gt; France 2002  90 minutes  and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trouble Every Day&lt;/b&gt; France 2001 101 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please Note:&lt;/b&gt; These films are being screened on Saturday night.  As the first film is titled &amp;quot;Friday Night&amp;quot;, this might be a bit confusing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Friday Night&lt;/b&gt; screens at 7pm but since Claire Denis will be present I am suggesting that we meet in the lobby at 6:15 as tickets are on a first-come/first-served basis.  With 3+ hours of film and Q&amp;amp;A sessions, more than likely we will not be going to a restaurant afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Claire Denis: A provocative director whose films offer richly textured, contemplative examinations of cross-cultural tensions and alienation, Claire Denis is one of French cinema's most distinctive and humanistic storytellers. A prolific filmmaker who is more concerned with the drive of her characters rather than the plot that weaves them together, she has been dubbed by one critic as one of the only current French directors who &amp;quot;has been able to reconcile the lyricism of French cinema with the impulse to capture the often harsh face of contemporary France.&amp;quot; All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Friday Night&lt;/b&gt; Denis' poetic exploration of the pleasures and discontents of 21st century heterosexuality follows the nightlong odyssey shared by a woman and the hitchhiker who she spontaneously picks up during a Paris traffic jam. In signature Denis fashion Friday Night deliberately cultivates a rich ambiguity on its every level. Is the mood suffused with lust, ennui or menace, or some combination of the three? Are the two protagonists connecting and communicating or fundamentally alone with each other? The remarkable cinematography by Agnès Godard is equally paradoxical, both gauzy and crystalline. The sensual pleasure in surfaces and the attention to mood so important to Denis’ work come to the fore in &lt;b&gt;Friday Night&lt;/b&gt;, alternately reflecting and refracting the film's gossamer plot and almost anonymous protagonists. HFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;b]Trouble Every Day&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A hard-hitting mélange of science fiction, body horror and AIDS allegory, &lt;b&gt;Trouble Every Day&lt;/b&gt; is perhaps Denis’ most underappreciated work. Although the film's apparent coldness and glimpses of carnal savagery immediately marked it as a controversial aberration in Denis' oeuvre, Trouble Every Day is perhaps best understood as an important, albeit darker, variation of the restless, lonely searching for connection between people that remains the central theme of Denis’ work. While the film centers upon the relationship between an American and French vampire, Denis’ real interest, is not in the trappings of genre, whether mad-doctor imaginings or bloodshed, but in the limits of love, sex and forgiveness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Harvard Film Archive website is listing these films together with one admission of $10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Meet-up sign in the lobby before the films.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224632628000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Claire Denis Double Feature- Director Present</name><id>9006128</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226186100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9006128/</event_url></item>