<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This discussion touches on what I view as the essence of ethics.&lt;/span&gt; What matters, good will and intention or the acts and consequences that follow from them? Any ethical theory must grapple with the dilemmas that can develop between these basic perspectives. The problem may be encapsulated by the famous saying that “The road to Hell is paved with good intentions!” But if this saying is the whole story, then so much for intentions; but is it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Are you a utilitarian in which the utilities of actions are all that matter?&lt;/span&gt; Or are you a Kantian in which a “good will” is structured by a fiction that Kant invented called the “categorical imperative?” Or is the form of intention known as compassion (Schopenhauer) the true basis of morality? Or is Nietzsche’s “will to power” the real deal, in which case intention (will) but also consequences are key because what good are consequences without power. Buddhistic mindfulness and American pragmatism are other perspectives on this critical issue, and there are many more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clearly, both intentions and their consequences are vital, but which is more vital? And what needs to be done or can anything be done to make ethics more relevant, and what role could  conceptualizations of good intentions and consequences play in making ethics more relevant and applicable?&lt;/span&gt; I tend to think that intentionality is the more critical component of ethical conceptualizations of morality, and I go into detail on this matter in a nearly finished book (the writing of which will be completed before the end of the year). So I am eager to get your take on the question of ethical intentions and their consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people).   After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.  It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.  And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house! The basic cost is $20 (this covers your entree, 3 or 4 shared appetizers per table, tax and gratuity but &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; drinks). If you order drinks please pay the cost of the drink times 125% to cover additional tax and tip (e.g. if you order one drink that costs $6.00 then your total cost for food and drink would be $27.50). If on a &lt;em&gt;rare&lt;/em&gt; occasion you only order a drink or an appetizer, or if you do not order anything, then you will owe a minimum charge of $12 to compensate the restaurant for their service.  If there should be a shortfall, which is unlikely, then the group agrees to chip in to cover the difference. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.  However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*****************************&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP for one of our events it is expected that you have every intention of attending. Please refrain from impulse reservations and impulse cancellations!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354398603000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351542187000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Core of Morality: The Question of Intentions, Actions and Consequences</name><id>89082852</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354320000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/89082852/</event_url></item>