<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Got this email from the ever-helpful Cheryl (she works for the Coolidge Corner theater, I think):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Thought the following would be of interest to members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best,&lt;br /&gt;Cheryl White&lt;br /&gt;Coolidge Corner Theatre/Museum of Science&lt;br /&gt;617/699-7285&lt;br /&gt;cheryl@coolidge.org or cwhite@mos.org&lt;br /&gt;_______________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Coolidge Corner Theatre’s Science on Screen series returns on Monday, October 19 at 7:00 p.m. with a presentation of &lt;b&gt;Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde&lt;/b&gt;, Victor Fleming’s 1941 adaptation of Robert Louis Stevenson’s classic Victorian horror tale. The film will be introduced by MIT professor John Durant and Harvard professor Anne Harrington. The pair, both specialists in the history of science, co-taught a course on science and medicine in Victorian England at London’s Imperial College last summer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Screen legend Spencer Tracy stars in the dual title role in Fleming’s Oscar-nominated film. In 1887 London, Dr. Henry Jekyll is a socially upstanding physician whose unorthodox theories alarm his older colleagues. Jekyll believes that each man has two selves, one good and one evil, that can be separated through science, freeing the good so that it can triumph and allowing the bad to “destroy itself in its own degradation.” Toiling in his lab, he develops a drug which transforms him into the cruel and remorseless Edward Hyde. Initially, Jekyll is able to dispense of Hyde whenever he chooses. But as he repeatedly takes the potion, Hyde begins to dominate, until he can no longer be controlled. Lana Turner co-stars as Jekyll’s loving, forgiving fiancée and Ingrid Berman as a luckless barmaid pursued and abused by the malevolent Hyde.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before the film, John Durant and Anne Harrington provide a fascinating window into some of the scientific theories and debates of the era in which Stevenson’s famously divided character was born. In the late 19th century, man’s animal origins, as revealed by Darwin, and the idea of degeneration (that humanity could fall downwards on the evolutionary ladder as easily as it could move upwards) had a strong hold on the Victorian imagination. It was a time when physicians circulated a theory of a double brain, when dual personality and other cases of mental illness were often attributed to brain hemisphere imbalance, and when people anxiously wondered where the soul lived in relation to the brain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Our Speakers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;John Durant&lt;/b&gt; is director of the MIT Museum, adjunct professor in MIT’s Science, Technology and Society Program, and executive director of the Cambridge Science Festival. He was formerly assistant director and head of science communication at the Science Museum, London and professor of public understanding of &lt;br /&gt;science at London’s Imperial College. Dr. Durant has a PhD in History and Philosophy of Science from the University of Cambridge. His areas of research have included the history of evolutionary and behavioral biology, particularly debates about animal nature and human nature in the late-19th and 20th centuries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anne Harrington&lt;/b&gt; is chair of the Department of the History of Science at Harvard University and a professor in that department, specializing in the history of psychiatry, neuroscience, and the other mind sciences. She is also visiting professor for medical history at the London School of Economics, where she co-edits the journal Biosocieties. Dr. Harrington is the author of three books, Medicine, Mind and the Double Brain (1987), Reenchanted Science (1997), and The Cure Within (2008), and has also produced a range of articles and edited collections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science on Screen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Science on Screen, the Coolidge presents a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, medicine, or technology, paired with exciting introductions by noted guest speakers in a related field. This monthly series is co-presented by the Museum of Science, Boston and New Scientist magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: $9.75 regular admission; $7.75 for students and Museum of Science members; free for Coolidge Corner Theatre members. Tickets are available on-line at www.coolidge.org or at the Coolidge Corner Theatre box office, located at 290 Harvard Street in Brookline. For more information, visit www.coolidge.org/science.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI, I'm planning on attending. I'm going to buy my tickets now to ensure I get a seat. I recommend you buy online, as well, in advance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP (even though there are no discount tickets to this venue) so I know who to wait for that evening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256249192000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254606050000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde </name><id>11539341</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255993200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/11539341/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>