<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>351 Atwells Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.824112</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 454-8951 </phone><name>Don Jose Tequilas</name><city>Providence</city><id>948824</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.429261</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>OK, to switch things up and try to accomodate some members who can't make Fridays, February's meetup will be on a Saturday! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE note, the reservation is for ***6:30***.   This is because we are meeting on a Saturday and have such a large group, I had to take the time they gave me.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month we are going to do MEXICAN at Don Jose Tequilla's(not to mention a few margaritas)!  See the link for their menu at &lt;a href="http://www.donjoseteq.com" target="_blank"&gt;Don Jose Tequila's&lt;/a&gt;. The menu looks fantastic and it looks like they have quite an authentic flare.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The owner was very helpful, but because we are such a large party and it is a Saturday, they will not be able to do individual checks.  So, please be sure you plan accordingly.   He also took a deposit, so hopefully you guys will be willing to be patient when I work on the bill.  I am sure it won't be a problem, but I just wanted to let you all know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to get your opinion regarding bill payment, I've added another poll &lt;i&gt;again&lt;/i&gt;(yes, I know, but it's for your own good!) to vote on your preferred method of handling the check.  Whichever seems the most popular selection, I will do my best to accomidate.  Regardless, I will be making every effort to discuss options of payment at  the beginning of each event from this point forward, in order to meet the needs of those attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should we fill up and you are still interested in attending, please enter a &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; RSVP and put a note stating that you want to be wait-listed.   If spots open up, I will contact you in order of RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;PLease be sure to update your RSVP should your plans change.  I look forward to seeing everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the front.  I am plus sized, have long red hair and wear glasses.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203982658000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><why>We're good people and it will be fun!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194453483000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Rhode Island Dining Out February Meetup- SATURDAY- Don Jose Tequilas</name><id>6695234</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203809400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/6695234/</event_url></item>