<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Have you heard Digital Asset Management (DAM) and wondered how it might apply to you as an aspiring or professional photographer? If you have 100's or even 1000's of images you will need some sort of Digital Asset Management!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Digital Asset Management (DAM) refers to the protocol of downloading, renaming, backing up, rating, grouping, archiving, optimizing, maintaining, thinning, and exporting digital photographic images. In this workshop, we'll define DAM, adding metadata, and provide a framework for workflow for the whole process, beginning to end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to bring your laptops but it will not be a necessity. We do strongly suggest you take notes during the workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workshop will be held on Saturday, May 30, 2009 beginning at 1:00 PM at Visions By Baker, 61 Harvard Street, Worcester, MA 01609. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking for Visions By Baker is in the public lot on (at 30) Highland Street between Harvard and Lancaster Streets. The DAM Workshop will be limited to the first 15 people to RSVP on the Worcester Photography Meetup site. We will not be providing drinks or food at this event. This is a free workshop to Worcester Photo MeetUP Members but we will be &amp;quot;passing the hat&amp;quot; to collect donations.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>First floor First Door on the Right!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244380429000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239065282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Digital Asset Management Workshop-  You don't want to miss this!</name><id>10131434</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243702800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10131434/</event_url></item>