<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We'll be hiking up the fairly easy Devil's Den Mountain. &amp;nbsp;Located in New Durham, NH. It's very close to home and only about 1000' high. There's a small cave to explore and great views at the top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's also a fish hatchery we can stop by on the way back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a flashlight or headlamp for the cave if you have one. The weather on Sunday should be in the 60s so it'll be a nice, mild day. Bring a snack &amp;amp; we can eat afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool&lt;/strong&gt;: 12:30 pm DOVER C&amp;amp;J TRAILWAYS LOT - Spaulding Tpk - Exit 9. &amp;nbsp;Left @ light. &amp;nbsp;Then left again @ 2nd light. &amp;nbsp;Pull straight in and congregate in the rear by the fence. (We'll all meet at the carpool location and drive from there. If you live in the other direction and want to meet us at the trailhead, email me for directions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Fee is for meetup site expenses and planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From "Back Porch Tales" by Karl M. Frost - 1974&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in East Alton, Devil's Den was a very popular visiting spot years ago. It is located on a high site of land, pretty much in the wilderness. Devil's Den is a large rock. The story goes that at least 100 years ago, maybe more, it was struck by lightning. The bolt must have hit the top and gone down through the rock and cut at ground level. For some unknown reason, as the bolt of lightning neared the ground, it cleared out a complete circular room and left an entrance large enough for an average person to walk in. Although the Devil's Den rock is not in itself more than twenty feet or so tall, being on a high elevation the view from the top, over a wide valley, is beautiful. Some sixty years ago an iron ladder up one wall on the inside allowed a person to climb easily to the top and sticking one's head out of the hole offered an unobstructed view. There are, or were, at least three or four niches cut into the wall of the room, probably to hold candles. Today, (1974) the ladder is gone and only one or two iron spikes are left to show where the ladder was once located. (There's a wooden ladder now.) There are many stories about the den - some claim it was first used as an indian lookout. Others say it was a smuggler's den where liquor run in from Canada was stored. Once, years ago, there was a fairly good road right to the foot of the den. Parties were taken there by horse and team for outings. Treks were made every summer from many local towns. A fairly good set of directional markings were put up for directions. Today it is just wilderness. Devil's Den is an unusual sight created by nature's own handiwork. Most any of the local people in Alton or Alton Bay can give you directions if you want to visit the cave, but be sure to take a flashlight along with you. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322477320000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321059328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Devil's Den Cave Hike</name><id>40860122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322415000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/40860122/</event_url></item>