<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our July BizSpark Meetup will be held on Tuesday, July 20th at Microsoft Research Center located at One Memorial Drive in Cambridge. The security officer will direct attendees to the correct floor. There is parking available in the building. Parking is free on the street in front of the building at 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 6:30 PM &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/bettinahein" target="_blank"&gt;Bettina Hein&lt;/a&gt; will pitch her startup Pixability to Graham Brooks as a live pitch for potential funding. &lt;a href="http://www.pixability.com" target="_blank"&gt;Pixability &lt;/a&gt;offers the easiest, quickest, most economical way to create quality video to help you market your company or organization. Now anyone, from company president to cashier, can be part of the web video revolution. Graham Brooks is a Principal at .406 Ventures, joined them in 2007, and is involved in all aspects of the investing and portfolio management process and also leads the university outreach initiatives. He brings nine years of technology-oriented operating, investing and start-up experience. He is actively involved with RatePoint, WoodPellets.com, and DigitalSmiths.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then at 7:30 we have the venerable and completely amazing Rachel Blankstein of &lt;a href="http://www.evolution-partners.com" target="_blank"&gt;Evolution Partners &lt;/a&gt;presenting on &amp;quot;Market Strategies for Startups.&amp;quot; Rachel works with clients on their marketing and business strategy challenges, online presence and online marketing, marketing planning and implementation, and planning and execution of new product and service launches. Rachel launched and grew online media company eConfidant which focused on providing online dating &amp;amp; relationship advice through a monthly subscription model. She sold the  company to Innovive Technologies LLC. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So it's going to be a big female entrepreneurs event! If you're female and interested in starting your own company, then this is the event to be at and meet Abby, Rachel, Hadley, and Holly in person and, of course, one of my favorite VC principals Graham Brooks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation | demonstration, we will go around the room introducing ourselves and asking the group for advice | opinions on any startup-related issues members are facing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Microsoft will provide pizza. What a generous organization! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are also looking for someone to video record the event as well.  Any volunteers please contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP and bring guests. We're always open to suggestions for topics for experts to speak on as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Marsh Sutherland&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marsh Sutherland</member_name><member_id>3795141</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287615320000</updated><rating><average>4.44999980927</average><count>22</count></rating><group><who>BOSSparkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-BizSpark-Meetup</urlname><id>1535927</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston BizSpark Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>163</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277772762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Market Strategy for Entreprenrs, Pixability Pitch to Graham Brooks of .406 Vntrs</name><id>13942639</id><headcount>160</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279665000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-BizSpark-Meetup/events/13942639/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/5/7/global_11095623.jpeg</photo_url></item>