<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;You are number one in my world!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif' border='0' alt='love struck' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The DECember theme is &lt;u&gt;First Ladies&lt;/u&gt; TAKE TWO.  Who is your favorite first lady? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you know President Johnson’s wife first name without googling or otherwise looking it up?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She said: “The clash of ideas is the sound of freedom.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Martha Washington said: “Party Under the Bridge.” I do not know why she said this, but I like her attitude.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Which first lady do you think said: “My makeup wasn't smeared, I wasn't disheveled, I behaved politely, and I never finished off a bottle, so how could I be alcoholic?”  This should be an easy one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you identify the first lady in this month’s photo? It is art so no one should be offended. Wait till you see Michelle’s portrait!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who is the first lady in your life? Mom, wife, sister, friend, or your own sweet self?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Find a recipe the reflects that lady numero uno and plan to cook on site unless your dish takes 45 minutes or more to prepare.  If you’d like to share your recipe send it to me electronically and I will post it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring what you would like to drink and share as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need help with finding a recipe call me and I'll loan you my president's cookbook.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>my home so you will notice me and the dogs, will send address a few days before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260749147000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258160685000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes December Meetup</name><id>gwhmhymqbpb</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260576000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/11870218/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/d/global_11139677.jpeg</photo_url></item>