<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>790 Iyannough Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02601</zip><lat>41.668919</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>KMart </name><city>Hyannis</city><id>1082387</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.295608</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You are invited to America's most exciting Halloween Festival in the bewitching seaport of Salem Massachusetts!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at KMart in Hyannis for the carpool at 9:00 A.M. sharp! &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once we get to Salem, we'll start by attending The Annual Psychic Fair and Witchcraft Expo, then go for lunch:  there is a Food Court that will be selling delicious fair foods on Salem Common!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rest is up to us what we want to do!  Poke in shops, etc. You can go to &lt;a href="http://www.hauntedhappenings.org/dailyevents.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hauntedhap...&lt;/a&gt; to see a list of the days events, and you can find a list of shops on the site.  Free things to do included!  You don't have to spend alot of money to have a good time!&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is so much to do and see in Salem so please plan for a long day. . . if you are going in the carpool we won't be &lt;b&gt;departing Salem until 8:00 p.m.&lt;/b&gt; UNLESS the majority agrees to it otherwise depending on how the day goes!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Annual Psychic Fair and Witchcraft Expo at the Museum Place Mall&lt;br /&gt;176 Essex Street in Historic downtown Salem! • Free Admission!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore the future with a psychic reading and make contact with the Spirit World at Salem's longest-running psychic fair! Hosted by Christian Day and the Witches of Salem, The Annual Psychic Fair and Witchcraft Expo features the Witch City's most gifted Psychics. Wander an emporium of magical gifts, meet and speak with real practicing Witches, and make an appointment with one of Salem’s talented psychic readers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Annual Psychic Fair and&lt;br /&gt;Witchcraft Expo Features:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Tarot Card Readings&lt;br /&gt;    * Clairvoyant Visions&lt;br /&gt;    * Spirit Mediumship&lt;br /&gt;    * Palm Readings&lt;br /&gt;    * Aura Photography&lt;br /&gt;    * Crystal Ball Scrying&lt;br /&gt;    * Angels and Spirit Guides&lt;br /&gt;    * Past Life Readings&lt;br /&gt;    * The magical products of Bewitched in Salem, including jewelry, ritual items, crystal balls, pendulums, candles, antique Salem spoons, incense, staves, art, cards, and more! *WitchSchool.com will be on hand to answer questions about the Craft!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore the future with a psychic reading and make contact with the Spirit World at Salem's longest-running psychic fair! Hosted by Christian Day and the Witches of Salem, The Annual Psychic Fair and Witchcraft Expo features the Witch City's most gifted Psychics. Wander an emporium of magical gifts, meet and speak with real practicing Witches, and make an appointment with one of Salem’s talented psychic readers! &lt;b&gt;Readings are $30 for fifteen minutes or $60 for the half hour. You can make an appointment once you get there if you wish, or just browse!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Car Pool or Come on Your Own.&lt;/b&gt;  If you come on your own, we will meet at the entrance to The Annual Psychic Fair and Witchcraft Expo at 11:30 A.M.  It takes about 1 hr 50 minutes to get to Salem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My vehicle can accommodate 5!  And if anyone else is willing to drive please let me know.  If we go beyond what I can accommodate in my car we'll need volunteers!  We can form a posse to Salem!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is between $15.00 - $20.00&lt;/b&gt; so depending on the number of women attending and the size of the carpool will depend on the amount you need to bring to chip in for parking!  Also if would be very much appreciated if you give your driver a few dollars toward gas as well!  After the reservations are in, I'll shoot you an email letting you know the exact amount to bring to chip in for parking!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions for those that wish to drive on their own&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To Salem:&lt;/b&gt; Take Route 93 North Exit 18 (Mass Avenue/Frontage Road) and go to the far right lane.   At the second traffic signal, take a right onto the South Boston Bypass Road and follow signs to access the Ted Williams Tunnel and I-90 East/Logan Airport. From the Williams Tunnel, take Route 1A North. Follow Route 1A all the way into Salem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can go to &lt;a href="http://www.hauntedhappenings.org/directions.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hauntedhap...&lt;/a&gt; for further details and parking for Salem if you choose to drive on your own! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear your walking shoes, and bring your cell phones!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear something you might be caught dead in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan your $$ accordingly to buy lunch, shop, and if you want to get a Psychic Reading!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt;  There is no obligation to attend the Psychic Fair if you wish to go off on your own.  We'll meet up with you later at an agreed upon designated meeting place!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a "Blaring Blue" Saturn Vue SUV!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharon</member_name><member_id>8235187</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257643204000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254497268000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Annual Psychic &amp; Witchcraft Expo and Exploration of Salem!</name><id>11529092</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255870800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/11529092/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/4/global_5975620.jpeg</photo_url></item>