<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>225 Newbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.580006</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Village Green</name><city>Danvers</city><id>4668442</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.968719</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a trivia buff? &amp;nbsp;Even if you aren't, what would you say to a heavily discounted dinner? :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight we are going to do a STUMP Trivia night. &amp;nbsp;We have a lot of smart people in this game group and a couple of people have expressed interest, so tonight we are going to try it and see if we want this to become a regular thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who haven't been to a STUMP trivia night at a pub before, here's basically how it works. &amp;nbsp;For 2 hours we will be asked questions in a variety of different subjects, everything from pop culture to local news to obscure scientific facts. &amp;nbsp;Prior to each question, we will assign it a point value based on how well we know the category the question is going to be asked in. &amp;nbsp;If we answer it correctly, we get that many points. &amp;nbsp;If not, we won't get a penalty (until the last question where we have to gamble some of our points). The team with the most amount of points at the end of the night wins. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But here's the kicker:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; The top 2 winning teams receive gift certificates to the restaurant. &amp;nbsp;When I did this with my co-workers 2 years ago, we consistently came in first place in our local restaurant for like 4 months and won $50 gift certificates for our team of 6 people. &amp;nbsp;This meant that each subsequent week, we used the gift certificate to pay for our dinner (you can't use it the week you win), and our meals pretty much came out to only &lt;em&gt;$3 each&lt;/em&gt;! &amp;nbsp;So there is some serious incentive to participate in these games. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One final note. &amp;nbsp;I sampled a lot of different places around the north shore that were offering STUMP trivia and I picked this for a variety of reasons as our testing grounds. &amp;nbsp;If this becomes a regular thing, we can pick a different night or location. &amp;nbsp;For this event, I am limiting RSVPs to initially only 8. &amp;nbsp;We are going to do teams of 4 and because this is a small venue, I don't want to try and reserve too many tables at once. &amp;nbsp;If enough people want to come and are on the waiting list and we can get enough people to arrive at exactly 6:30, I am happy to reserve more tables but let's cross that bridge when we get there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there! &amp;nbsp;:-) You don't have to be a genius to win these things. &amp;nbsp;Everyone knows something and we need people from all different backgrounds in order to win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;. Anyone can sign up, but I would please ask that you&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;allow new or previously inactive members get a slot if they are on the waiting list since there is limited seating. &amp;nbsp;Thanks.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;See this&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, for tonight's event people on the waiting list may be able to join. &amp;nbsp;I'll message you if you are on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food theme:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no food theme as this is a public venue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 The Village Green is a function center and dining space all in one located right along Route 1 in Danvers. &amp;nbsp;They host public events almost every night of the week, including cribbage leagues, dance lessons and karaoke. &amp;nbsp;The main restaurant is the Tavern on the Hill and where we will be meeting. &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.villagegreendanvers.com/tavernmenu.html"&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is a link to their menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327238846000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325278948000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Team Trivia Tryouts</name><id>45997242</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327015800000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/45997242/</event_url></item>