<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>154 Hayward St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.979950</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-622-9505</phone><name>KO's</name><city>Manchester</city><id>778116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.459038</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone!  Our next potluck is Friday Sept 10.  &lt;b&gt;I am so happy to let you know that we have a guest speaker!  Julie Netti M.S, LMT...she is an amazing woman who will be talking about Chinese medicine, the 5 elements and Tuina (sounds like Tweena).  Tuina is one of the oldest treatments recorded of medical massage for trauma and other conditions for both children and adults.  Tuina is one of the six major therapies in Traditional Chinese Medicine.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julie is an International Consultant, Educator and Tuina Specialist.  Julie has been a practioner and educator for the last 20 years.  In 2007, Julie returned to China to study and work in a Chinese medicine clinic in Shanghai.  She was the first Westerner to be trained in the new Tuina technique, &amp;quot;Meridian Networking&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be an informative and interesting evening.  There is no other place you can go and get this kind of knowledge for $2.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been making food for the past 4 days....yummy!  What kind of amazing raw delights are you bringing?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are planning on coming and have not signed up....please do.  See you Friday!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KO Bisson</member_name><member_id>4565632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284213071000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rawfood-ManchNH</urlname><id>1292928</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Manchester Raw Vegan Food Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283428842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September Potluck!!  Sept 10 UPDATE</name><id>14630571</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284157800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rawfood-ManchNH/events/14630571/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/b/global_9355803.jpeg</photo_url></item>