<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This for a Zealand Bonds Traverse sometime between 2/19/2009 and 3/19/2009. RSVP Yes if you are interested in doing this hike in that time frame not specifically on this day. Please read full details below before RSVPing.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am hoping to do a Zealand Bonds Traverse before winters end (March 20th). This will be a day hike starting early morning and finishing in the evening. I have no specific date in mind but will pick a day for me when weather and trail conditions look favorable. The day will be sometime between Feb 19th and March 19th. This calendar event is a place for those with similar interest to do so. When I see a good day coming I will notify those that express interst here so they can start preparing or update their availibility. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP YES you will be asked some questions. Please answers these or I will be force to pester you to do so. I will try to organize people as best I can based on ability and availibility. If things work out there may be more than one group on a single day or there may be more than one day in this time period for different groups. This is a long tough hike, so in the best interest of all so I reserve the right to decline RSVPs if I do not find they are a good fit. On the other hand everyone should realize this is a group hike and we will stick together in the assigned groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now the details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Distance&lt;/b&gt;: 23.48 miles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation gain&lt;/b&gt;: ~5467 ft  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time&lt;/b&gt;: 14 hours and 30 minutes  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trails&lt;/b&gt;: Zealand Rd, Zealand Tr, Twinway, Bondcliff Tr, Wilderness Tr, Lincoln Woods Tr plus spurs to Zealand and West Bond&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will require an early start (5 AM ish), a long car spot at Lincoln Woods and Zealand Rd winter parking lot on 302, headlamps at the beginning and end, and long flat slogs at the beginning and end. This will be a long day for sure but I expect it to take 12-15 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike starts with a 3.8 mile road walk on Zealand Rd which closed for the winter, but partly plowed and usually packed as it accesses the Hut. Then it is Zealand Trail to the Hut, where we can take a break. From the hut is the steepest part of the hike as we ascend to Zeacliff by the Twinway. From Zeacliff we continue with some up and downs to Zealand Mtn spur, tag the summit, and move on to Guyot. After some downs and up to Mt. Guyot we come to the first exposed scetion of the hike as we hit the alpine zone around Guyot before descending into the col before the Bonds. Then it is the half mile spur to West Bond. Back at the junction we continue a half mile to exposed summit of Bond. Then we dip back into some trees before the long exposed ridge of Bondcliff. After the victory dance at Bondcliff we realize we still have 9.4 miles to go. The descent from Bondcliff is steep in parts but downhill is the easy part. Then it is what may be the toughest part mentally. The last 5 miles of flat, wide, and boring Wilderness Tr and Lincoln Woods Tr, with headlamps none the less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that you're late or lost.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/What_to_wear_on_a_hike/"&gt;What to wear on a hike&lt;/a&gt; and pack water and food.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy F</member_name><member_id>3324456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237039307000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234393608000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Zealand-Bonds Traverse</name><id>9723494</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236679200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9723494/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/c/global_7277612.jpeg</photo_url></item>