<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 302</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.193851</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Route 302 and Sawyer River Road Intersection</name><city>Waterville</city><id>4103792</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.572395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;**I have tentatively rescheduled this hike to Sunday in hopes that the rain will clear up.  Tomorrow looks like a wash-out.**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE ANSWER ALL THE RSVP QUESTIONS COMPLETELY.  I ask for &lt;strong&gt;specific&lt;/strong&gt; information about your &lt;strong&gt;last three hikes and DATES and conditions.&lt;/strong&gt; I do this to gauge preparedness, so I need complete answers.  If you don't answer the question completely, you will be removed until I have this information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Mts. Nancy and Carrigain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've been trying to finish up my NE100 Highest points in NH and redline some new trails.  &lt;strong&gt;This will not be your traditional peakbagging climb of Carrigain.&lt;/strong&gt; Instead, we will create a loop that begins at Nancy Pond, tags the summit of Nancy, climbs Mt. Carrigain via Desolation and descends to Sawyer River Road (and includes a 2 mile road walk)  This would be roughly 17 miles.  There are shorter, easier alternatives if you are interested only in grabbing Carrigain for your 48 4ker list.  This will be a full day hike, likely to come out after dark unless we make fabulous time on the easier parts of this trail and don't stop for too many pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will take the Nancy Pond trail to Carrigain Notch and then ascend Carrigain via the Desolation trail.  We will pass Nancy Cascades, Nancy Pond and Norcross Pond which should provide for some good views on the early part of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ascent of Nancy *may* be optional, depending on whether people need it as a "list" peak and what the group's goals are.  I want to keep this trip somewhat flexible since it is so ambitious.  Leaving via Carrigain Notch is an option too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for cool and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poor weather conditions cancel this hike.&lt;/strong&gt; I will keep any eye on the weather and notify everyone of a final decision on Friday.  I may postpone this hike to another day if the weather does not look good..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This IS a traverse, so we WILL need to carpool to another location.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please do not rely on the map above that Meetup generates. It is often wrong.  If you don't know where the location is, please ask.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will meet at the Sawyer Road parking lot and carpool up to the parking lot for Nancy Pond.  Sawyer Road is closed, so we will have a road walk at the end of this hike.  That walk is about 2 miles.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunset will be at  about &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;6:30&lt;/span&gt; pm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hike will not be very exposed.  The summit of Carrigain and the tower are, however, out in the open.  It is fall, so come prepared for rain, sun AND cold conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There do not appear to be a lot of water sources once we pass the ponds on the Nancy Pond Trail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headlamps are required.   &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;This is a long hike that will probably exceed daylight and it requires a road walk.  It will probably be dark about when we get to the road or just before.&lt;/span&gt; Hikers should  always be prepared to come out in the dark.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you.   &lt;strong&gt;I require participants to wait at trail junctions, major water crossings and summits so that the group can exchange information and reset their pace.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am NOT a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.  I'm doing about book time these days.  I stop to eat every few hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The distance, pace and elevation gain means that is a very advanced hike.  I expect people to average book time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day.  I would like you to be around for another day too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog &amp;amp; bring appropriate amounts of food and water.  I try to make sure the dogs don't outnumber the humans!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike. I rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No, I will not change the start time for this hike.  I choose my start times carefully based on when we should be off the mountain or at least safely into the homestretch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors.  If the weather looks like it will be miserable, I will reschedule (because I really want to do this route!), possibly to the next day (Sunday) if it looks clearer.  Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RSVP Questions are NOT optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book time is approximately:  7.5 to the summit of Carrigain; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;12.5 hours&lt;/span&gt; total (including the 2 mile road walk).&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I am hoping to cover the Nancy Pond trail in less than book time to save some time on this climb.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance is:  9.8 miles on the ascent; 5 miles on the descent; 15 "White Mountain Miles" total + a 2 mile road walk = &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;17 miles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ----------------------------------------------------------   &lt;br /&gt;

 Copyright © the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nancy Pond to Carrigain Notch Trail (7.1 miles; 4 hours 40 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carrigain Notch to Desolation Trail (.8 miles; 30 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desolation to Summit of Carrigain/Signal Ridge (1.9 miles; 2 hours 10 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Signal Ridge to Parking Lot - (7 miles; 5.5 hours)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). WHILE I HAVE CLIMBED THIS PEAK BEFORE, I HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic with a bumper sticker in the back window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349013851000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347201019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rescheduled:Carrigain (4Ker) and Nancy (NEHH) Loop - VERY ADVANCED</name><id>81564912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349002800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/81564912/</event_url></item>