<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Salem Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.260864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-799-1655</phone><name>Worcester Public Library</name><city>Worcester</city><id>999847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.800133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We just got bumped from the library to a later time. Please not ethis and make arraignments accordingly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna - I had to bump you to 2:15. This rarely happens, but I had a Library program that was rescheduled because of the storm (it is part of the Big Read), so three events (including yours were rescheduled to a later time). I hope this doesn't cause any problems with your group. My apologies. Denise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Framing Party for the City Hall Gallery Show Landscape and...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 March 23, 2013 from 1:30-3:30 Banx Room Worcester Public Library&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 If your image appears on the list below, you are in the show. Congratulations!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Next step...you need to make a print and have it matted to a 16x24 outside dimensions. Please use a white mat... read on for more details...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;This meeting will be for the members who are participating in the upcoming show but also for the folks who had an image in the last show. Please come and pick up your prints!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Landscapes and..." to get details, learn about framing the prints, and discuss the opening of the show. Participants; We will have your frame ready for you at this meeting. We will show you how to take your matted print and put it in the frame with the glass and how to seal it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 What you need to bring to the meeting: &lt;br /&gt;

 Please bring with you a Flat Head Screw Driver!! Everyone will need one to put the frames together. &lt;br /&gt;

 Your Print &lt;br /&gt;

 Your Mat - cut to fit your print. &lt;br /&gt;

 Your Print should be mounted to a back board and attached to your mat. &lt;br /&gt;

 Our frames are 16x24 in size. This means- All accepted photographs must be matted to a 16x24 outside dimensions - we will accept white mats only. You must come to the framing party on March 23rd between 1:30 and 3:30pm at the Worcester Public Main Library to frame your own matted pieces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are responsible for labeling the artwork on display with artist name, title and price (if your image is being offered for sale). So you need to supply this information at the framing party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 So, Bring your matted print. This means you need to have a mat cut! The frame size is 16x24 so the over all mat must fit into a 16x24 frame. &lt;br /&gt;

 We suggest making your prints 11x14 or 9x12 so they can have a nice white boarder around the image. We will not be accepting images that are not matted. SO no flush mounted images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 VERY IMPORTANT: &lt;br /&gt;

 IF YOUR IMAGE IS SQUARE---- PLEASE Check with me on whether it should be vertical or horizontal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We want everyone to sign the mats in the lower right corner of the mat's opening- if you do not know what this means -don't sign it- just bring it to the meeting and we will discuss where to sign the mat. &lt;br /&gt;

 You will need a back board to mount the print to and then place the mat over it. This back board should be the exact same size as the mat you had cut for your print. I recommend it be the same material as the mat. &lt;br /&gt;

 Simply tell whomever is cutting the mats that they need to fit into a 16x24 frame. &lt;br /&gt;

 Please check in with me about the title of your print and the price you want to sell it for before you leave this meeting. &lt;br /&gt;

 Please let me know if you have any questions! &lt;br /&gt;

 Cheers, &lt;br /&gt;

 Donna &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Landscape and... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Bob Bernier Landscape 2 &lt;br /&gt;

 Bob Bernier Landscape3 &lt;br /&gt;

 Cl Padden 1 LR &lt;br /&gt;

 Dana Lane Landscape 1 &lt;br /&gt;

 David Snay Landscape 3 &lt;br /&gt;

 Deb Faucher Night tracks &lt;br /&gt;

 Dick Trafaglia Landscape 1 &lt;br /&gt;

 Don Ricklin Former Crompton &lt;br /&gt;

 Howard Kong A blue Distance &lt;br /&gt;

 Jurgen Lobert Landscape and City &lt;br /&gt;

 Jurgen Lobert Landscape and FairyTale &lt;br /&gt;

 Mike Greenslit Landscape 1 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mike Greenslit Landscape 2 &lt;br /&gt;

 Pam Pollen Landscape 3 &lt;br /&gt;

 Paul Goodwin Landscape 2 &lt;br /&gt;

 Priscilla M Landscape 1 &lt;br /&gt;

 Rebecca Weiner I heart Elm Park &lt;br /&gt;

 Russ Garre 290 Bridge &lt;br /&gt;

 Scott Erskine Landscape 3 Fire Truck &lt;br /&gt;

 Sharon Freed Landscape 2 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sheila McDowell Landscape 2 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sheila McDowell Landscape 3 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sherri Haber Landscape 1 &lt;br /&gt;

 Troy Thompson Landscape 2 &lt;br /&gt;

 Jim Wojdylak Landscape 3&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Banx Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Lane</member_name><member_id>5229126</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364178169000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362697366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framing Party for the Landscape and... Show</name><id>108164892</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364063400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/108164892/</event_url></item>