<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-245-1525</phone><name>Harrington's Pub</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>733190</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;*****EVENT UPDATE: Please update your RSVPs as we have&amp;nbsp;about 100&amp;nbsp;RSVPs from Wakefield Weeknights, Red Sox Natives and&amp;nbsp;4 other groups.&amp;nbsp;We are at capacity. If you are not attending please change your RSVP. We can not open the RSVPs up to any more people until the probable No Shows RSVP out. (If you want to be placed on a waiting list E Mail Frank) Harrington's will be closed to the public for 2 private parties with guest lists. We will be on the first floor. Upon arrival please check in with one of the Red Sox Natives Event Hosts. They will direct you to the Wakefield Week Nights section, seats and tables in the dining area. Harrington's will be packed. Please be considerate of others as we have fans who want to watch the whole game and&amp;nbsp;the commercials once the game begins!&amp;nbsp;All are encouraged to wear Patriots gear.*****&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From The Red Sox Natives site:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The New England Patriots are the AFC Champions and are going to the Super Bowl!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game is on against the&amp;nbsp;New York Giants.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please RSVP&amp;nbsp;ASAP as this event&amp;nbsp;has been&amp;nbsp;announced to&amp;nbsp;6 meetup groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE&amp;nbsp;EVENT ANNOUNCEMENT!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is for the suburban Natives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives have been organizing Patriots Game Watching Events over the past&amp;nbsp;4 months with&amp;nbsp;up to&amp;nbsp;65 people attending&amp;nbsp;at Boston, Wakefield&amp;nbsp;and Woburn venues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week we will&amp;nbsp;return to&amp;nbsp;our&amp;nbsp;suburban venue on Sunday&amp;nbsp;February 5&amp;nbsp;at 5:30 pm to watch the Patriots&amp;nbsp;play in the&amp;nbsp;Super Bowl.&amp;nbsp;We watched the&amp;nbsp;AFC Championship Game at&amp;nbsp;Harrington's on&amp;nbsp;January 22 and polled our guests with many&amp;nbsp;being open to returning for the Super Bowl.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harrington's Food and Spirits in downtown Wakefield is a cozy Irish Restaurant and Pub with two floors. We have been there before. The food is great and the full menu will be available for purchase. Owners Lisa and Dan have offerred us&amp;nbsp;the entire first floor bar and restaurant area and are adding an additional 60 inch television screen for&amp;nbsp;the Super Bowl. Harrington's will provide some complimentary appetizers&amp;nbsp;as well.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive early at 5:30pm&amp;nbsp;and get yourself a prime seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game Time is 6:30pm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking in downtown Wakefield in the public lot across from Harrington's in front of Bank of America and along Water and Main Streets. The location is T accessible by the 136 and 137 Bus from the Orange Line in Malden Center. And Commuter Rail accessible from North Station&amp;nbsp;via the&amp;nbsp;Haverhill Train stopping at Wakefield Station&amp;nbsp;with a less than 10 minute walk up Albion&amp;nbsp;Street, right on&amp;nbsp;to Main Street and 1 block to Water Street. If you are joining us from the City this is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own food/drink.&amp;nbsp;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER AND TIP YOUR SERVERS!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please&amp;nbsp;RSVP early if you think you can attend. Invite, guests, friends, and co-workers.&amp;nbsp;We are&amp;nbsp;inviting several&amp;nbsp;other groups to join us so space&amp;nbsp;will become limited. Let's have as many&amp;nbsp;Wakefield&amp;nbsp;members&amp;nbsp;there as possible and take over Harrington's!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*****Due to the constant large number number of "No Shows" we are limiting members to RSVP with only 1 guest and reserve the right to further limit members who have more than 1 No Show. We have been taking attendance. To better insure entry to the event we suggest that&amp;nbsp;any potential guests join the Wakefield Weeknights or Red Sox Natives meetup. Wait listed people for our January 22 event&amp;nbsp;were unable to attend because of all the RSVP No Shows.*****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following groups&amp;nbsp;are participating:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Sox Natives (Frank)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wakefield Weeknights (Melody)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Happy Hour (Tonya)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TWIOP (Ziggy)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social Fun&amp;nbsp;(Isabele)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Single Geeks, Nerds &amp;amp; Professionals (Alison)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fenway Frank and The Red Sox Natives Team&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have the entire first floor and bar area with an additional new 60 inch screen added for our event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329129215000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>91</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327287215000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Super Bowl Game Viewing Party -  Patriots vs New York Giants at Harrington's</name><id>49201932</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328481000000</time><rsvp_limit>95</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/49201932/</event_url></item>