<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gale River Loop Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03595</zip><lat>44.270813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Garfield Trail Trailhead</name><city>Twin Mountain</city><id>968375</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.539917</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mt. Garfield, located just miles east northeast of Mt. Lafayette and Franconia Ridge in New Hampshire's White Mountains is the 14th highest among the four thousand foot peaks in the White Mountains. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes this mountain stand out from many of the other White Mountains is &lt;br /&gt;1) the relative ease of the hike to the top via the Garfield Trail (class 1) from Gale River Loop Road (off Route 3), &lt;br /&gt;2) the grand view from the from the top looking at the Pemigwasset Wilderness towards the south.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.summitpost.org/images/original/5079.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last .2 mile on Garfield Ridge Trail is the only steep section to the magnificent 360* views from the 4500' open summit. &lt;br /&gt;The round trip is a moderate 10.0 miles, 3000' of elevation in a book time of 7 hours with unforgettable views. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Views from Mt Garfield are some of the finest of all the Whites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Normally done by the Mt. Garfield Trail (rt: 10.0 miles, 3,000 feet, 7:00), an old tractor road, hence the grades are easy and the footing is good. The final ascent to the summit of Mt. Garfield is by a short, but very steep and rocky, segment of the Garfield Ridge Trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While there are no views along the trail, the views from the summit are excellent.  the first time on this peak, you climb in the forest and then emerge over a ridge and WOW what a view of the pemi. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Expect to encounter ice on the trail with this weeks freezing temps. carry traction, the trail is moderate with only the last section being steep for the ascend. The trail follows a brook on the lower elevation so again- expect ice. Remember your layers of clothing- it will feel like full winter on the summit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a day hike but for your information:&lt;br /&gt;Lodging and Camping:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the Forest Service has two Designated Roadside Camping Areas along the Gale River and Haystack roads:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Gale River Road - Consists of ten widely scattered sites along the road. Each includes off road parking, and camper or tent space. There are no formally developed sites, no potable water sources, and no fire rings or rest room facilities. There are no camping charges but the fee pilot program applies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Haystack Road - There are 11 widely scattered sites along the road. Each includes off road parking, and camper or tent space. There are no formally developed sites, no potable water sources, and no fire rings or rest room facilities. There are no camping charges but the fee pilot program applies.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256479575000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250976266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Garfield  4500ft</name><id>11174372</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255865400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11174372/</event_url></item>