<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>bpl.org</phone><name>Rabb Auditorium at Boston Public Library in Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>883985</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You thought Boston By Foot only toured the exteriors of buildings in the Back Bay? Well, during the regular tour season that's true -- but it's cold outside so we decided to hook up with the BPL and go inside this winter.  There are a whole bunch of guides who do both BBF and Boston Public Library tours - so why not get them to show us around?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us on a tour of a masterpiece of American architecture -- the wonderful Copley branch of the Boston Public Library. The tour will discuss the art and architecture of this edifice built by McKim, Mead and White.  The BPL was built as a temple to learning and knowledge as well as a &amp;quot;palace of the people.&amp;quot; This hidden jewel of a tour includes: murals by John Singer Sargent and Pierre Puvis de Chavannes.; marble lions; sculpture by Daniel Chester French; and a statue that was once 'Banned in Boston'. Best of all, as the front of the building says in stone it's &amp;quot;Free To All.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guides will start from the Dartmouth St lobby (that's the entrance facing Copley Square).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the Dartmouth Street lobby and look for guides with badges</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen G</member_name><member_id>7594534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269097855000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>18</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>65</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260657570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tour of  the Boston Public Library</name><id>12072754</id><headcount>81</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264276800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/12072754/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/7/global_12198951.jpeg</photo_url></item>