<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>163404</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>9/11: LET'S GET EMPIRICAL is David Ray Griffin's recent video release based on his book &amp;quot;Debunking 9/11 Debunking.&amp;quot; It brilliantly rebuts Popular Mechanics and other defenders of the official conspiracy theory, and shows how their arguments do not stand up to empirical analysis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pointing out that most objections to the alternative theory, according to which 9/11 was an inside job, are based on purely a priori arguments and a propagandistic use of the term ?conspiracy theory,? he shows that if we get empirical about 9/11, we can quickly see that the official story cannot be true. - Generously illustrated with graphics and video clips. This one hour film also includes an additional 30 minutes of Q &amp;amp; A. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film screening will begin at around 7:00 PM following an organizing meeting beginning at 6:00 PM. It is OK to bring food to the meeting. During the meeting we will decide on future films, events, and actions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film we will open the venue to discussions. At our last Meetup, Frank from Berkshire 9/11 Truth mentioned that their showing the History Channels put-down-film of the 9/11 Truth movement actually did more to convince attendees of Government complicity than the new Loose Change film. So, we will consider, if we get a copy, to screen this film too.. if decided by the group at our meeting, and if we get a copy in time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[This event is organized by Jonathan Mark, Valley 9/11 co-founder with Stepen Goodale]&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203116638000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>David Ray Griffin is a leading spokesperson for questioning the government's version of what happened on 9/11. It can help unite those against war and government corruption.</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201104229000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9/11: LET'S GET EMPIRICAL - film &amp; discussion!</name><id>7178625</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202943600000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/7178625/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/9/a/global_3047274.jpeg</photo_url></item>