<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For details check here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/home.php#!/event.php?eid=153483904708930"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/home.php#!/event.php?eid=153483904708930&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



Time

Tuesday, March 29 &amp;middot; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;6:00pm&lt;/span&gt; - &lt;span&gt;9:00pm&lt;/span&gt;




&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;





Location

&lt;span&gt;Boston University Photonics Building room 206, 8 St. Mary's Street, Boston MA&lt;/span&gt;




&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;





Created By

&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ross.caputi"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0066cc"&gt;Ross Caputi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;



&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0066cc"&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;




More Info


Please join the Boston University Anti-War Coalition for a free screening of the documentary MEETING RESISTANCE, followed by a question-and-answer session with the directors.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;What would you do if America was invaded? MEETING RESISTANCE raises the veil of anonymity surrounding the Iraqi insurgency by meeting face to face with individuals who are passionately engaged in the struggle, and documenting for the very first time, the se&lt;span&gt;...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;ntiments experienced and actions taken by a nation's citizens when their homeland is occupied. Voices that have previously not been heard, male and female, speak candidly about their motivations, hopes and goals, revealing a kaleidoscope of human perspectives. Featuring reflective, yet fervent conversations with active insurgents, MEETING RESISTANCE is the missing puzzle piece in understanding the Iraq war. Directed by Steve Connors and Molly Bingham, this daring, eye-opening film provides unique insight into the personal narratives of people involved in the resistance exploding myth after myth about the war in Iraq and the Iraqis who participate. Through its unprecedented access to these clandestine groups, MEETING RESISTANCE focuses the spotlight on the "other side", clarifying why the violence in Iraq continues to this day and providing a deeper understanding of both the toll of occupation and the human condition of resistance. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;





&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetingresistance.com/trailer.html"&gt;http://www.meetingresistance.com/trailer.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301440695000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Its free and it would be interesting to partake in the question-and-answer session with the directors.</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298525103000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3/29 6pm Free Screening of MEETING RESISTANCE. Q + A with directors</name><id>16685029</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301436000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/16685029/</event_url></item>