<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>24.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>ICC members, Cheryl Dauphin and Nancy Simonds have joined forces to publish &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;A Tool Chest for Self-Marketers.&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; The book offers resources to anyone involved in creating marketing materials for their small business, nonprofit or new company. Topics cover everything from proper print resolution to understanding the role of demographics in your communications. After years of working with clients who did not understand many of the basics of marketing, the book evolved as a way for Cheryl, a designer, and Nancy, a copywriter, to share their knowledge with their clients to streamline projects. The two will &lt;br /&gt;discuss their experience in putting the book together and the process of self publishing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Networking opportunities &amp;amp; cash bar at 6pm&lt;br /&gt;The dinner is served by 7pm. Presenters usually begin while dessert is being served. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TO RESERVE YOUR PLACE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;- Go to: www.paypal.com and select the &amp;quot;Send Money&amp;quot; tab - Insert &amp;quot;kolkdesign@usa.net&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;Recipient's Email&amp;quot;. - Type in the amount you wish to send. ($24 per person) - Select &amp;quot;Service&amp;quot; for &amp;quot;Type&amp;quot; (of money sent). - Put ICC meeting-Jan 29 in the &amp;quot;Subject&amp;quot; box. - Note: Use the &lt;br /&gt;PayPal message box to type in your meal preference. This time our meal choices are:&lt;br /&gt;- Eggplant Parmigiana&lt;br /&gt;- Potato Crusted Basa Sole&lt;br /&gt;- Chicken Caprese&lt;br /&gt;If you do not indicate a choice, you will be assigned a vegetarian entree. All meal choices include bread, salad, dessert &amp;amp; coffee or tea. Cash bar available. Don't forget to select &amp;quot;send money&amp;quot; to complete your order. Your completed PayPal transaction will confirm your reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OUR RESERVATION DEADLINE&lt;/b&gt; is Jan. 23. You must be paid in accordance with &lt;br /&gt;the instructions above before your reservation is considered accepted. Because we have to plan ahead, we need to collect money in advance. If you need to cancel, we will be able to refund your money only if you &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;PHONE&lt;/span&gt; Laura Kolk at 860.646.0542 by the end of the day on Jan. 23, so &lt;br /&gt;that we can cancel your reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Confetti's restuarant is a small venue. Ask for the "ICC" party.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda Bedard</member_name><member_id>5621944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ginger LaBella</member_name><member_id>5838547</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette Mayer</member_name><member_id>5934991</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Kolk</member_name><member_id>6023842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201820583000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Our mission is to share ideas in a relaxed casual forum. Network &amp; make new friends in the group, treat yourself to a nice meal and enjoy the speaker's presentation.</why><group><who>Network Marketers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>networkmarket-792</urlname><id>818489</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4400024414</group_lon><name>Independent Creative Club of Greater Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195061935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Independent Creative Club of Greater Hartford January Meetup</name><id>6740599</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201647600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/networkmarket-792/events/6740599/</event_url></item>