<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Think Big Innovation Challenge Day&lt;br /&gt;When is it?&lt;br /&gt;January 19 2011 9:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;What's happening at your Meetup? Give as many details as you can&lt;br /&gt;Is 2011 Your Year to Think BIG?&lt;br /&gt;Are You Ready to Take BIG Strides?&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a Think BIG Innovation Challenge&lt;br /&gt;Innovate in 2011, Think Bigger than you have ever thought before and create a new level of success. The Holistic Self Care Center is hosting a very special event.&lt;br /&gt;This year, jump off, right in January with your Think BIG goals that push out boundaries and ignore limitations.  Set your Think BIG goals for 2011 and put them into ACTION.&lt;br /&gt;Join other inspired innovators for a day of thinking big and then thinking bigger, brainstorming, and setting your plan for 2011.&lt;br /&gt;During your Think Big Innovation Day you will be guided through a process of creativity, inspiration and limit pushing.  Boundaries are exploded, ideas are born and strategies created. But it doesn’t just stop there.  The real energy of the day comes from the collaboration of the people in the room.&lt;br /&gt;In the past you have set your New Year’s Resolutions, you were excited, you were motivated, but then they quickly faded away and come the end of the year you set them again.  Or perhaps you had a strategic plan or business plan, and still the year came and went without the level of achievement you set out for.&lt;br /&gt;It is time to change this pattern and learn how to set real world goals that are Think BIG goals that are put into action.  When you come to the end of the year, you look back at your year and celebrate a year of achievement, of going beyond and are astonished at all that has occurred.&lt;br /&gt;The energy in the room is beyond electric.  You can feel the swirl and the power of the universe right there in the room.  You are excited. The other people in the room are excited. The energy is reaching out of the room and touching the world.  You are getting new ideas for your Think BIG Goals. ..Register by 1/12 and receive a copy of the Think BIG Manifesto at the event.  Leave the day with your plan, strategies and new ideas!&lt;br /&gt;I’ve secured a special discount just for you. &lt;br /&gt;You can also sign up here using the promo code “Innovation” and attend the whole day for 97.00 instead of 297.00.  Register here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://realworldleader-innovationchallenge-nashua-affiliate1wellness.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://realworldleade...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295452117000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294711149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Think BIG Innovation Challenge</name><id>16001964</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295447400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/16001964/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/4/global_9559044.jpeg</photo_url></item>