<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;My comment:&lt;/em&gt; The Tour&amp;eacute;-Raichel Collective is on Cumbancha, the same record label as Bombino and many other fantastic musicians. I find their music really refreshing and relaxing, warm and genuine, with echoes of many different musical and cultural influences. More info: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - &lt;a href="http://www.toureraichel.com/"&gt;Their official site&lt;/a&gt; (you can listen to their whole forthcoming album) &lt;br /&gt;

 - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/toureraichel" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - &lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/derek-beres/global-beat-fusion-where-_b_1315025.html"&gt;Global Beat Fusion: Where Muslims and Jews Make Music, Not War&lt;/a&gt; (HuffPo article) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Tickets are $27 each for assigned seats. Should we set a day by which we should RSVP so we can book them as a group?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- - - - - - - -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Official bio:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.worldmusic.org/vieux-farka-toure-idan-raichel-0-923"&gt;Vieux Farka Tour&amp;eacute; (Mali) and Idan Raichel (Israel)&lt;/a&gt;, virtuosic superstars from very different backgrounds, join together to create masterworks of collaboration and improvisation. After a chance meeting in an airport in Europe, Idan and Vieux forged a deep friendship that led to an impromptu get together at a small studio in Tel Aviv in November 2010. The resulting recording session &amp;ndash; acoustic, spontaneous, entirely improvised, and stunningly beautiful &amp;ndash; could only be described as magic, and The Tour&amp;eacute;-Raichel Collective was born. On the upcoming album The Tel Aviv Session, to be released by Cumbancha on March 27, 2012, Idan and Vieux have captured an inspired musical moment that will bring to mind classic albums such as Talking Timbuktu by Ali Farka Tour&amp;eacute; with Ry Cooder, Keith Jarret&amp;rsquo;s The K&amp;amp;ouml;ln Concert or Vincent Segal and Ballake Sissoko's acclaimed Chamber Music. The live concert reflects the natural spontaneity and free-form creativity of the recording sessions, allowing audiences to experience firsthand the invention of sublime and transcendent music that crosses boundaries of country, culture and tradition.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334619553000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331849693000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Touré-Raichel Collective</name><id>56519052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334530800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/56519052/</event_url></item>