<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 2</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03593</zip><lat>44.366652</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Appalachia Parking Lot</name><city>Randolph</city><id>3558392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.315083</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE ANSWER ALL THE RSVP QUESTIONS COMPLETELY.  I ask for &lt;strong&gt;specific&lt;/strong&gt; information about your &lt;strong&gt;last three hikes and DATES and conditions&lt;/strong&gt; as well as for &lt;strong&gt;your history in climbing the higher Presidentials (which peaks you have climbed and when).&lt;/strong&gt; I do this to gauge preparedness, so I need complete answers.  You will not be taken off the waiting list until I have this information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Mts. Adams and Madison via King Ravine to the Airline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This will not be your traditional peakbagging climb.&lt;/strong&gt; King Ravine is one of the most important glacial cirques contained within the northern Presidential mass and one of my most favorite locations! Some of the most spectacular trails can be found here along with many interesting geological features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will create a loop begins at Appalachia and uses lower Air Line and Short Line trails to reach the most scenic area of the ravine, joining the King Ravine trail near Mossy Falls. The hike continues to the Subway at the junction of the Chemin des Dames.  We will take some time out to allow people to explore the subway, then climb the Chemin des Dames trail which steeply returns to the (now very exposed) Airline Trail.  We will take the Airline Trail to the summit of Adams and then work our way down to Madison Hut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we reach Madison hut, those that are interested may summit Madison (or not).  We have various return routes planned.  With two leaders, we can make that decision at the hut, split up and regroup if we choose.  Our options include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.  Descend directly from Madision via Watson Path (or return to the hut)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.  Descend from Madison Hut via Valley Way, cut up to the Airline Trail and follow the Airline trail down to the Scar Trail, where there are supposed to be some excellent views.  The Scar trail also avoids the steep section of the Air Line trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.  Maybe incorporate some other features at the lower elevations on Madison to allow additional sightseeing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short daylight requires an early start and you will need headlamps. This will be a LONG DAY. Plan on a full day of snacks, food and water and be prepared for cold temperatures and the DARK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;I don't usually do this, but everyone will be waitlisted for this hike until I have had a chance to confirm that each person is prepared for the distance and elevation gain involved. This is a joint hike with the Boston Hiking Meetup, so please &lt;strong&gt;*do not*&lt;/strong&gt; sign up on both sites. It will just confuse my limited counting skills!  :)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for cool and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poor weather conditions cancel this hike.&lt;/strong&gt; We will keep any eye on the weather and notify everyone of a final decision on Saturday.  We may choose an alternative hike (maybe a lower elevation exploration of some features?) if Adams/Madison is not feasible this day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This IS NOT a traverse, so we will NOT need to carpool to another location.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will meet in the Appalachia Parking Lot.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Sunset will be at  about 5:54 pm&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hike will be VERY EXPOSED.  It is fall, so come prepared for rain, sun AND cold conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are a lot of water sources on this trail but the water is not potable.  Bring enough potable water for a long, rugged hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will pass Madison Hut.  The hut will be CLOSED.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headlamps are required and you should expect that we will come out of the dark on this hike.  Hikers should  always be prepared to come out in the dark if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you.   &lt;strong&gt;I require participants to wait at trail junctions, major water crossings and summits so that the group can exchange information and reset their pace.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am NOT a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.  I'm doing about book time these days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The distance, pace and location means that is a VERY ADVANCED hike.  I expect people to average book time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day.  I would like you to be around for another day too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog &amp;amp; bring appropriate amounts of food and water.  This is a rugged trail with a lot of exposure and rock scrambling.  I will not be bringing my dogs on this hike &amp;amp; typically do not bring them into King Ravine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike. I rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No, I will not change the start time for this hike.  I choose my start times carefully based on when we should be off the mountain or at least safely into the homestretch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors.  If the weather looks like it will be miserable, I will reschedule (because I really want to do this route!), possibly to the next day (Sunday) if it looks clearer.  Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RSVP Questions are NOT optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Plagerized" Trail Descriptions  from the AMC Guide will follow shortly  &lt;br /&gt;

----------------------------------------------------------   &lt;br /&gt;

Copyright © the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Air Line to Randolph to Short Line Trail (1.2 miles; 1hr 10 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Line to King Ravine (1.9 miles; 1 hr 40 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;King Ravine to Chemin des Dames (.7 miles; 40 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chemin des Dames to Air Line Junction (.4 miles,  40 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Air Line to Adams Summit (1.1 miles; 1 hr, 10 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adams Summit to Madison Hut (.6 miles; 45 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;---Kate's Tentative Return Route - --&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Madison Hut to Summit of Madison (round trip to the hut) (.8 miles; 40 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Madison Hut up to Air Line via Air Line Cutoff  (.2 miles, 10 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Air Line to Scar Trail (1.4 miles; 1 hr, 15 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scar Trail to Valley Way (1 mile; 1hr)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Valley Way to Appalachia (approx 2.5 miles)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book time is approximately:  6 hours 5 min (Ascent) 4.5 hours (Descent) = Roughly 11 hours excluding stops&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Distance is: 5.9 miles (Ascent) 5.9 (Descent) = Roughly 12 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). WHILE I HAVE CLIMBED THIS PEAK BEFORE, I HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic with a bumper sticker in the back window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1350911152000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348424610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>King Ravine, Adams, Madison Hut and Optional Ascent of Madison (VERY ADVANCED)</name><id>83721962</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350822600000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/83721962/</event_url></item>