<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Music begins @ 9:30pm &lt;br /&gt;COVER CHARGE: $10.00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Classic American Soul Revue Funk/Dance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHECK OUT: www.chickenslacks.com&lt;br /&gt;                   &lt;br /&gt;The Chicken Slacks are dedicated to the re-creation of an authentic soul revue show featuring a larger-than-average band. A tight rhythm section, gritty horns, and a stirring star vocalist combine to create a powerful stage presence and big sound to which audiences immediately respond. The band delivers high-energy music for people to dance, romance, bump, grind, sway, stumble, sing along, reminisce, celebrate, and get down to. The Chicken Slacks are Boston area musicians who have toured nationally and internationally. They make an immediate impression on their audiences and clients with their young look, professional work ethic and dedication to the live show. What is SOUL music, you ask? There are many definitions, but it began with Ray Charles and Sam Cooke, spread in Memphis with STAX records and Otis Redding, Sam and Dave, Rufus Thomas, and the gang. It made its way to MUSCLE SHOALS with Wilson Picket and Aretha Franklin. The MOTOWN sound has a soul thing, with Stevie Wonder and Marvin Gaye. James Brown and Sly and the Family Stone took soul and made it into FUNK, paving the way for Tower of Power and Blood Sweat and Tears. Soul also morphed into R&amp;amp;B and disco, with Michael Jackson and the Bee Gees among the champions. Within this musical milieu are the names and songs we all know and love, but also hundreds of forgotten tunes by forgotten soulsters just as worthy to be performed and just as great to dance to. Its all about the groove. This is SOUL. This is what we do. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*&lt;b&gt;NOTE: &lt;/b&gt;I have tried several times to schedule a night at Gilrein's on a Friday night! but had to cancel due to snowstorms...So, no matter what, tonight is a go!  &lt;b&gt;Anyone want to get together earlier for dinner? Please add it to your RSVP.. we can decide on when &amp;amp; where. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_Jo&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tables ahve been reserved and there will be a meetup sign on our table(s). When you enter just ask for " George" or the meetup group. You will be directed to where we are all seated. .</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208738320000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>It's all about the GROOVE... THE FUNK... THE SOUL! Let's get out... listen &amp; dance to all the songs we all know and love.  Gilrein's is a great place to go out! * They have VALET parking.</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205716383000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHICKEN SLACKS @ Gilrein's Home of The Blues</name><id>7546684</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208565000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7546684/</event_url></item>