<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to everyone intrigued by neuro-linguistic programming (NLP). Here are the details of the February meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First off, a reminder: we start the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP, those who want a review, and those who want to come early to socialize/network.  At 7pm we will jump into the main event for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main event: Superhero Training (aka Using NLP without calling it NLP)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NLP is amazingly effective, but is sometimes limited by its very name. When people hear NLP, or the full name, Neuro-Linguistic Programming, or even worse, some of our jargon (well-formed outcomes, trans-derivational search, nominalizations, etc) they can go running for the exits. It is very useful to be able to use NLP with calling it NLP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this month's meetup, I will take you through a personal development workshop I created called Superhero Training (see the description at the end of this message). It will take between 60 and 90 minutes, and then we will review the workshop to show how NLP is at the core. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've been wanting to introduce friends, neighbors, family or colleagues to NLP, this would be a good session to bring them to. I've given the Superhero workshop to many audiences, and they unanimously found it both fun and useful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular. I will stay for a while after the meetup, if you want to discuss specific issues that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Workshop: Discovering the Superhero in You&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Superheroes! They save lives, promote justice, right wrongs, and protect the weak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, beyond their obvious powers like great strength, flight and invulnerability there is something &lt;br /&gt;more that defines a superhero - their determination to make the world a better place through the use of &lt;br /&gt;their special gifts. This means that any of us, through the exploration of our own special gifts, can &lt;br /&gt;discover the &amp;quot;superhero within&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through a series of exercises, you will choose the superpowers you've dreamed of having, and bring &lt;br /&gt;them into your everyday life. You will gain clarity on your life goals, find the internal motivation needed to &lt;br /&gt;achieve those goals, and have a deeper appreciation for the gifts you bring to the world. &lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;We meet on the first floor of Sturtevant Hall, 197 Herrick Road, which is near the library on the central quad of Andover Newton. &lt;br /&gt;Andover Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk straight ahead into the meeting room.  I'll probably be the one talking.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237499682000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232670855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP February Meetup - Superhero Training!</name><id>9581437</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235086200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/9581437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/8/global_3512920.jpeg</photo_url></item>