<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Humphrey St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.313480</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Carissa's Cafe</name><city>New Haven</city><id>7593572</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.909500</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Happy Hour/Dinner at Carissa’s Café &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday, July 7, 5 to 8 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;

175 Humphrey St., New Haven &lt;br /&gt;

203-498-9400&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebrate the July Fourth weekend with a happy hour/dinner among friends at the latest addition to New Haven’s dining out scene, Carissa’s Café on Humphrey St. If any of you remember the former Humphrey’s restaurant, it is in that location, but has been completed renovated to fit the 21st century and it is beautiful! Play tunes on their electronic Juke Box, watch your favorite games on TVs above the bar, and see the chef prepare meals in the open-view kitchen. Come for drinks, stay for dinner!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The owner, Brian Badamo, is offering the group the following specials: &lt;br /&gt;

 Complimentary happy hour food: 3 different types of chicken wings (barbecue, buffalo, and Jack Daniels), nachos, and house made potato chips with chipotle sauce. &lt;br /&gt;

 Discounted drinks: &lt;br /&gt;

 Draft domestic beers ($2) or draft imported beers for ($3). The bar has a wide selection, from Bud to Samuel Adams, Shock Top, Optical Illusion, and Guinness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the July 4th holiday, he'll have the bartender offer some special red, white, or blue martinis for $5 each. Other well martinis will also be $5, top shelf liquors for $7. A martini menu is available. There’s also a good selection of flavorful wines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other drinks will be discounted $1 off the regular price. &lt;br /&gt;

 Discounted food: &lt;br /&gt;

 10% off the regular menu if people want to order food or appetizers from the regular menu. &lt;br /&gt;

 The menu is extensive and reasonably priced. Apps range from Fried Calamari to Angus Sliders and Crab Cakes. Creative sandwiches for under ten dollars, with sides, such as the Black &amp;amp; Blue Angus Burger (gorgonzola and caramelized onions with a bourbon barbecue sauce), Lump Crab Cake Burger (with chipotle sauce), Portobello Stacker (with grilled seasonal vegetables topped with provolone cheese with pesto mayo), and wraps such as Pulled Pork. Soups, salads, and full dinners include delicious Angus Rib Eye Steaks, Chilean Sea Bass, Pasta Primavera, Cavatelli with Broccoli Rabe and Sausage, and a huge serving of Chicken Parmigiana. Dishes are created and prepared by a chef who trained at the Culinary Institute in New York . Full dessert menu as well. Carissa's is open 7 days a week for lunch and dinner, and happy hour on weekdays. &lt;br /&gt;

 Brian is a friendly guy who will treat you like family and his staff is also friendly and attentive. Give Carissa’s Café a try for the July Fourth weekend, you won’t be disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit carissascafe.com or on Facebook &lt;br /&gt;

Parking is available in a lot next to the building, there’s plenty of free, on-street parking directly in front of the building, and there’s a lot across the street if needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342212311000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339804090000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour and Dinner at Carissa's Cafe</name><id>69373282</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341694800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/69373282/</event_url></item>