<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft  NERD New England Research &amp; Development Center </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1626763</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Philippe Le Hegaret from the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) to hear about HTML5 and other good things from our friends and neighbors at W3C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Open Web Platform is expanding its reach and scope. More industries are looking to adopt HTML5, latest one being the automotive industry. More use cases are also being brought to the W3C and it recently created the System Applications Working Group to define a runtime environment for building Web applications with comparable capabilities to native applications and are in the process of creating a group adding speech recognition and synthesis to web contexts like HTML.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From video conferencing to performance APIs, this presentation will give a general update on the latest technologies being standardized at the W3C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Philippe:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Philippe Le Hegaret is Interaction Domain Lead at the World Wide Web Consortium, responsible for one of the 4 technical domains of the W3C. In this role, he provides technical leadership about Web technologies, organizes and manages W3C Activities to reach their goals, and communicates with the W3C Members and the public about the Web and W3C technologies. The Interaction Domain, which contains 18 Working Groups, standardizes frontend Web technologies including HTML, CSS, SVG, fonts, audio, or touch device support. He is currently a participant in the Web Performance Working Group. Philippe wrote the first version of the CSS Validator back in 1997 and is based at MIT, in Cambridge, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a great event. We hope to see you there. Our last event with Philippe was very popular so please remember to RSVP as soon as possible. We will be meeting in the first floor conference space at NERD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 6:00 -7:00  Free pizza and networking &lt;br /&gt;

 7:00 -7:10 Announcements  &lt;br /&gt;

 7:10 - 8:30 Main presentation &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30 - 9:00  Q &amp;amp; A &lt;br /&gt;

 9:00 - ?? Beers somewhere?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Murphy</member_name><member_id>4790321</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philippe Le Hegaret</member_name><member_id>10875499</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364492784000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>209</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360188052000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>W3C at Boston PHP presented by Philippe Le Hegaret</name><id>103381842</id><duration>10800000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364421600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/103381842/</event_url></item>