<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Cliff St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.333027</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edgerton Park</name><city>New Haven</city><id>333949</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.915660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>******UPDATE: the weather is a bit iffy for Saturday now. Last year it was raining but stopped about 15 minutes before the show and the play was able to go on without any problems. As long as it has stopped by 7, I (Andrea) am planning to be there. Also, I will be off email/meetup most of the day on Saturday so my cell phone will be the best way to reach me with questions. ******* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is summer, it must be time for Shakespeare in the Park (Edgerton Park). After a couple of years of comedies, it is time for a classic drama -- Hamlet. We’ve had a good size group get together for past shows and I hope that we can again this year! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case you need a brush up on the plot or are interested in the history:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sparknotes.com/shakespeare/hamlet/" target="_blank"&gt;Synopsis of Hamlet&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hamlet#Synopsis" target="_blank"&gt;Wikipedia page about Hamlet&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The play starts at 7:30. I’ll be there at 7 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Possible post party in downtown New Haven if there is interest?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show is at Edgerton Park in New Haven (off of Whitney, near the New Haven/Hamden line). Entrances to the park are on Cliff Street and Edgehill Road and there is parking on the street.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If Please mention in your RSVP if you can come around 7 too so I have an idea of how many people are coming and when. The amount of space we can save depends on how crowded the performance is. Last year it wasn’t crowded because of bad weather, but two years ago was a very popular night with a lot of Yale student groups.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things to bring: a blanket or lawn chair, bug spray, food or drink (for yourself or to share). The event is free, but they suggest a donation of $10.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is too early to know how the weather is going to be that night. Check back for updates when it gets closer. If it rains, I’ll try to reschedule the event for another night.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact is Andrea. I'll send my cell phone info to the people who reply YES or MAYBE a few days before the event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.elmshakespeare.org" target="_blank"&gt;Elm Shakespeare Company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call my (Andrea's) cell to find the group i f you don't recognize us.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>23</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219100880000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217360120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Aug 16 – Shakespeare in the Park “Hamlet”</name><id>8436410</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218927600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8436410/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>