<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Norman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.407853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-387-7625</phone><name>MetroRock Everett</name><city>Everett</city><id>669182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>MetroRock Everett is having another climbing shoe demo. This is a good chance to test out a bunch of different styles and manufactures. There is also a 20% discount for shoes in stock in the gym. If you need new shoes or just feel like getting some climbing in please join us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be at the picnic table at 6pm. After that find us on the walls. There's a dry-erase board between the two locker rooms, I will post a description of what I'm wearing on it so you can find us more easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boilerplate:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: you will need to pass a belay test if you are an experienced climber but new to the gym. You can take a belay test when you get there. If you have never climbed before, you should take a class at Metrorock. Please call the gym in advance to make arrangements to take the class. You can use the message board on this meetup to find other people that want to take the class. Metrorock will charge you $16 for a daypass if you are not already a member or a punch card holder. Ladies get a 50% discount on Monday nights! &lt;br /&gt;The Monday night belay classes are filling up quickly, so sign up early.&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.metrorock.com/e-directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metrorock....&lt;/a&gt; for directions. &lt;br /&gt;The gym also has a shuttle to the gym from the T - Wellington Station if you don't have a car. &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339547011000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268012025000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MetroRock Climing and Shoe Demo. </name><id>12812281</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268175600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/12812281/</event_url></item>