<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/9/9/4/event_82162932.jpeg" width="161" height="193" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;From boardgamegeek.com:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Out of the Box calls it "The Game Where Movie Fans Connect!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Can you name a film taking place over the holidays AND features a character in a uniform? Then Cineplexity may be the movie game for you!" Players try to be the first to name a movie that meets the criteria on two different Cineplexity cards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each of the 315 cards has a description from one of nine categories: Actors, Characters, Critiques, Genre, Production, Props, Scenes, Setting and Theme. Two cards are shown at a time. Who will be the first to think of a movie set In the Future that Contains Foreshadowing? If you come up with a name that players agree satisfies both cards, you win the oldest of the two cards, and a new card is added. So now the challenge might be to find a title that Contains Foreshadowing and has a Dance Sequence. And so on. If everyone is stumped you add a third card, and they must find a title that satisfies two of the three cards. Six to ten points (cards) are needed to win, depending on the number of players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send out my house number the day before the event to those who have RSVPed 'Yes'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nidal</member_name><member_id>8949503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331511526000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325084959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Night: Cineplexity</name><id>45705202</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326760200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/45705202/</event_url></item>