<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>100.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;SUNDAY,&amp;nbsp; MARCH 4, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Please read everything below. &lt;br /&gt;

 YOU MUST PREPAY TO COME TO THIS EVENT. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Photographers - $100. &lt;br /&gt;

 Pre-pay Studio members receive a discounted price of $80. &lt;br /&gt;

 Models and hair/MUA are free. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Model releases, food &amp;amp; drinks will be provided. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; There will be a limited number of spots for Photographers and it will be first come first served. To secure your space please pre-pay for your seat by Paypal or stopping down at the studio with check/credit card. Our Paypal address is payment@worcesterphotostudios.com &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will have approximately a dozen models and we will work in small groups. Sharing time and working with the lighting is one of the key concepts for this. We want to make sure everyone learns a bit more about directing models and also the main reason is to take great pictures from this shoot. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This will be a more private shoot, more relaxed and classy. First model out of makeup and hair gets pictures done first. We will keep you on a rotating schedule as long as you want to be shot. Once everyone has got their shots of the model we will switch to another model. If you have a light set-up you are willing to share for the day, that would be greatly appreciated (email the Studio Manager to let them know). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;This is not a Great Model Shoot event and will not be run like one, so feel free to message us with any ideas or comments. Please feel free to contact the Studio Manager, Jenn Owen at jenn@worcesterphotostudios&lt;/span&gt;.com with any concerns. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 CODE OF CONDUCT: &lt;br /&gt;

 We expect everyone to be professional and courteous. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 All models MUST wear a robe between sets and during breaks. While we realize that some people are more comfortable being au natural than others, please remember that it is a point of professionalism more than anything. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Alcohol and drugs are strictly prohibited at all times. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Inappropriate behavior will result in a verbal warning by a WPS staff member. If such behavior continues, you will be asked to leave.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>https://www.facebook.com/events/118061934981645/</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330874395000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327696359000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Classy Nude Shoot v2</name><id>49898652</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330869600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/49898652/</event_url></item>