<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>230 Atlantic Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.360644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greenway Conservancy Tent</name><city>Boston</city><id>760581</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052529</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come out for the &lt;a href="http://www.hellogreenway.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Greenway block party&lt;/a&gt; and get acquainted with this new space. Boston By Foot guides will be leading tours of the Rose Kennedy Greenway from the North End parks through Chinatown. On this 1.5 hour tour, you'll learn of the transition of this public space from its elevated highway days to its present day configuration including plans for future development. You'll see the varying themes among the parcels and learn of their origins. You may also see some of the historical easter eggs planted in the landscape.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't had the opportunity to walk the Greenway, this is a great opportunity to do it. There will be a ton of events going on throughout the day including a ferris wheel in the waterfront district. Check out the calendar on &lt;a href="http://www.hellogreenway.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.hellogreenway.org&lt;/a&gt; for a listing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no cost for this guided tour (&lt;b&gt;FREE&lt;/b&gt;). This tour starts at 11am from the &lt;a href="http://www.rosekennedygreenway.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Rose Fitzgerald Kennedy Greenway&lt;/a&gt; Conservancy tent that will be located on the Greenway across from Columbus park behind Quincy Market (the street number listed is an approximation to get you to the right area).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following this tour, Boston By Foot members will be taking a private tour of &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/member/#CESS" target="_blank"&gt;South Station&lt;/a&gt;. Here is information on becoming a &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot member&lt;/a&gt; that also helps keep this little non-profit going.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find the Conservancy Tent across from Columbus Park. Look for BBF/meetup signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary Fichtner</member_name><member_id>7616136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228053967000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221157309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greenway Block Party &amp; Tour</name><id>8738130</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223132400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/8738130/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/7/global_4722647.jpeg</photo_url></item>