<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Ferncroft Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.595863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>CoCo Key Water Resort</name><city>Danvers</city><id>5174592</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.969078</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello NSBSN, Use coupon code: NSBS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you tired of trying to figure out the secrets to a winning social media strategy? Good news! We have rounded up 6 of the most respected experts in Social Media to help YOU put together the pieces of the social media puzzle. These experts are award winning, best-selling authors, speakers and trainers who have helped their clients achieve huge success using Blogging, Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Linkedin and Pinterest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is coming to you LIVE on October 25 in Danvers a the CoCo Key Hotel and if you sign up by 9/30 NorthShore Business Support Network members will receive $50 off the early bird rate and attend for just $97! &lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/3849796846/BIG/41874010510" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.eventbrite.com/event/3849796846/BIG/41874010510&lt;/a&gt; (use coupon code NSBS)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day is an information packed social media intensive from 8am - 5pm and in addition to the day of great speakers and valuable information, each participant will receive:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A digital copy of the best-selling book Solving the Social Media Puzzle: 7 Simple Steps to Planning a Social Media Strategy for your Business, PLUS the complementary workbook (a combined $40 value). &lt;br /&gt;

 A blog and social media content calendar planner to help you organize your social media efforts &lt;br /&gt;

 Top 50 blog ideas e-book to help get you on the way to writing a great blog for your business &lt;br /&gt;

 365 Twitter Quotes, famous quotes on friendship, inspiration, success written in 140 characters or less, easily placed in Twitter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And MANY MORE worth over $200 -- all included in your ticket price!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea is that you leave that day with a workable and effective social media plan! So if you are a business owner, entrepreneur or marketer who:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is tired of all the hype and wants REAL RESULTS &lt;br /&gt;

 Wants to attract QUALIFIED customers using social media &lt;br /&gt;

 Could use some guidance and FRESH ideas &lt;br /&gt;

 Wants to make social media work FOR you rather than you working AT it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for this amazing event--you will be happy you did! &lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/3849796846/BIG/41874010510" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.eventbrite.com/event/3849796846/BIG/41874010510&lt;/a&gt; (use coupon code NSBS) To attend at the $97 price use coupon code NSBS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you and we look forward to seeing you all there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Use coupon code: NSBS</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn Rose</member_name><member_id>23974902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351202208000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs,Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1824</urlname><id>1133728</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>The NorthShore Business Support Network meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348515471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Media Mastery Tour Presents:...</name><id>83887702</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>32400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351166400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1824/events/83887702/</event_url></item>