<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Broadway/Route 28 </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.733993</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 687-7453</phone><name>MSPCA/Nevins Farm</name><city>Methuen</city><id>419637</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192105</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We invite the public to join us in creating a feast for our horses, by bringing fresh carrots, apples, oats, and peppermints to share with our horses. We'll gather at the MSPCA at Nevins Farm outdoor arena (adjacent to the Noble Family Adoption Center) to meet a few of the dozens of horses in our care. Visitors may also tour the Equine Center barn and place treats in the Christmas Stockings of our horses awaiting adoption. Holiday Tree Lighting &amp;amp; Open House Saturday, December 3, at 5:00pm-6:30pm Immediately following the Christmas Feast for the Horses, join us as we light our 2011 Holiday Tree, decorated with photo-personalized ornaments bearing your pet's names!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy festive holiday music, and light refreshments as we kick off a joyous holiday season. For more information on the Holiday Tree and the Christmas Feast for the Horses, contact Heather Robertson at (978) 687-7453 x6118, or via email at hrobertson@mspca.org. Photos with Santa Saturday, December 3, during the Open House Immediately following our Holiday Tree Lighting, during our Open House in the Noble Family Adoption Center, Santa will be available for photos with your family (including your canine members, on a leash please). This is a BYOC (Bring Your Own Camera), and there is no photo fee, although donations are suggested to help us care for our animals. Due to the expected crowds, we cannot accommodate photos with cats, rabbits, and our other furry friends. Please visit our Boston Adoption Center's Santa Days to have your other furry friends photographed with Santa.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Tobie holding a sign that says "Tobie" at the Outdoor Arena (adjacent to the Adoption Center) at 4:30 and bring carrots, apples, oats, peppermints for the horses! If you miss us at 4:30 at 5:00 look for the tree.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tobie</member_name><member_id>10498367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324671832000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>travel-575</urlname><id>418980</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Old and Not so Old Ladies Travel</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321909182000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Tree Lighting &amp; Open House at Nevins Farm</name><id>41965782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322947800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/travel-575/events/41965782/</event_url></item>