<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>118 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.377995</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-3866</phone><name>EVOO</name><city>Somerville</city><id>224913</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106030</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I've been waiting for this day for nearly a year. This is our chance again to enjoy an amazing brunch at &lt;a href="http://evoorestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;EVOO&lt;/a&gt; and support &lt;a href="http://www.gbfb.org/SHM/brunch.html" target="_blank"&gt; Greater Boston Food Bank (GBFB)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this special occasion only, EVOO is opening on a Sunday and will donate 100% of their $35 prix fixe cost to the GBFB.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the bargain price of $35 per person you receive three courses, tea, coffee, or juice along with a special mimosa. Anything you order from the bar has an additional cost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GBFB will collect your $35 prix fixe cost prior to our seating. You may pay the $35 with your credit card however please bring enough cash to pay for anything you order from the bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVOO only offers brunch during the Super Hunger weekend, so there isn't a menu. &lt;br /&gt;Specific menu items will be identified a couple of days before the brunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Directions From MA Pike: &lt;br /&gt;Take MA Pike to Cambridge/Allston/Brighton exit. Follow signs to Cambridge/Somerville, which puts you onto River Street. Follow River Street straight through Central Square, where River Street will become Prospect Street. From Prospect Street, make a left onto Hampshire Street (there is a Hess Gas Station at the light). Hampshire Street (in Cambridge) becomes Beacon Street (in Somerville). EVOO is located at 118 Beacon Street, approximately one mile down on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From Boston: &lt;br /&gt;Tale Route 93 to Storrow Drive. Take the Kendall Square exit. At the end of the ramp, take a right and go over the Longfellow Bridge. After the bridge, take a right at the fourth light onto Hampshire Street. Hampshire Street (in Cambridge) becomes Beacon Street (in Somerville). EVOO is located at 118 Beacon Street, approximately one mile down on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;There is a lot on Beacon Street 50 yards from EVOO. Street parking is also available on Beacon and Washington Streets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Station on the Red Line, ten minute walk. After exiting the T-station, walk through Harvard Yard to Kirkland Street. Walk down Kirkland Street towards Somerville. At the intersection with Beacon Street, take a right and look for EVOO right away. (118 Beacon Street). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rules for Engagement:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP. *If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it will count as if you NO-SHOWED for THREE (3) events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied by final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as if you NO-SHOWED for THREE (3) events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it will count as if you NO-SHOWED for THREE (3) events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for THREE (3) events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation. In this circumstance it impactS the GBFB fundraising efforts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at 617 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1235322785000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231026432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EVOO Annual Super Hunger Brunch</name><id>9436541</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232901000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/9436541/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/a/global_6818730.jpeg</photo_url></item>