<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 High St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06073</zip><lat>41.667657</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South Glastonbury Library</name><city>South Glastonbury</city><id>738126</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.605847</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;I know this is more of a writer's event than a singles event, BUT...&lt;br /&gt;I'm constantly getting emails from Meetup members, telling me they are interested in writing a book and would like to talk to me about it!  So...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;CONFESSIONS OF A CONTEST JUDGE: The 5 most common mistakes made by beginning writers, and how to fix them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When several writers’ organizations all happened to run contests for unpublished authors simultaneously, Toni Andrews found herself committed to judging over thirty entries in a single month.  She soon noticed a pattern—almost all of the manuscripts had some or all of the same five problems.   Remembering how frustrated she had been back in her own contest days by judges' comments such as &amp;quot;Fix point of view,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Show, don't tell&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Problem with voice,&amp;quot;  Toni decided to figure out ways to present the contestants with simple solutions instead of just pointing out the problems.  Responses to her feedback were so positive that she created this workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About this workshop:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your characters are unique, your plot is tight and your dialogue sparkles.  So why isn't anyone requesting a full manuscript?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the movie Bull Durham, there's a scene when Ebby Calvin &amp;quot;Nuke&amp;quot; LaLoosh has just pitched his first game.  The team's coach is in the manager's office, enumerating the rookie player's mistakes:  He's walked eighteen players, hit a sportswriter, a public announcer and the Bulls' mascot--twice.    After this recitation, the coach throws himself into a chair and grins widely.  &amp;quot;Joe,&amp;quot; he says, &amp;quot;this guy's got some serious &lt;i&gt;stuff!&lt;/i&gt; &amp;quot;  (Okay, he used a different word, but you get the picture.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, editors and agents don’t have the luxury of looking past the problems in a submission to find the raw talent underneath.  With an ever-growing slush pile next to their desk, they just don't have time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will teach you a series of simple steps to identify and eliminate the most common issues editors see over and over again in manuscripts from new authors and replace them with easy techniques that will enhance your talents and let your &lt;i&gt;stuff&lt;/i&gt; shine through.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is sponsored by the Charter Oak Romance Writers, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;a href="http://toniandrews.bravejournal.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Toni's Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;FOLLOWED BY LUNCH AT CHILI'S IN GLASTONBURY.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one with the flip chart...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Toni</member_name><member_id>4890008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220882731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218841687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Toni's giving a FREE Workshop!</name><id>8553816</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220709600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8553816/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>