<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>129 South St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351192</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-861-4940</phone><name>WorkBar Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>1009167</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057367</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In this session Rick Blain, a Certified Fund Raising Executive will lead us through a review of giving trends over the past 40 years, and discuss what makes this year different. We will explore what motivates people to give and discuss successful strategies to secure essential support today, while appropriately positioning our organizations to take advantage of the better times that are to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm excited to be hosting Rick who is Principal of Richard R. Blain &amp;amp; Associates, LLC located in North Andover, as our guest speaker.  Rick has almost thirty years of professional experience, including approximately twenty five years as a consultant to not-for-profit institutions and organizations of various types and sizes.  Rick currently serves on a number of not-for-profit Boards including the North Andover Scholarship Foundation, Family Service, Exchange Club of Lawrence, and the Essex County Community Foundation Grants Management Committee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there!  Invite your development directors and E.D.'s, too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monique&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monique Morimoto Flaherty</member_name><member_id>8025083</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256686667000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252078030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Development Strategies in a Down Economy</name><id>11289360</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253660400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/11289360/</event_url></item>