<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 and 224 Anderson Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zero Station / The Resilience Hub</name><city>Portland</city><id>11570052</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256172</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/4/c/event_64845132.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;You're invited to our April potluck with special guest &lt;strong&gt;Mark Fulford of Teltane Farm in Monroe Maine.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark is a longtime friend and ally of the permaculture community with decades of experience as a grower of mixed annual and perennial crops (and more! see below).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of us already know about increasing organic matter and biological activity in our soils, but what if we build a vibrant soil food web and "the cupboard is still bare?" The idea of re-mineralizing our soils with rock dusts has been gaining ground in our region and, due in large part to Mark, here in Maine.  In this evening session, Mark focuses on the issue of rock dusts and will...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Discuss the importance of rock dusts in our farm and garden soils&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Explain how re-mineralized soils interact with the soil food web and healthy plants and &lt;strong&gt;healthy food&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Talk about what kind of rock dusts we can use and &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;how&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Discuss sources of rock dust for the do-it-yourselfer, home gardener and small farmer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preliminary Agenda&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 Potluck Supper (bring a dish or beverage to share and your own potluck kit plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 Announcements &amp;amp; Presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 Q&amp;amp;A and discussion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:00 Close of program&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a notebook!  This is a &lt;strong&gt;family-friendly event&lt;/strong&gt; with supervised little folk having space to hang out in the new Resilience Hub offices attached to Zero Station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please use the comments area below ONLY for communicating to the entire attendance list.  Every comment and reply generates a new email and overuse of this feature has caused members to leave the group in the past.  If you have specific questions about this event, please send a message to the event host (right column).  Thanks for you help!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Mark Fulford&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mark has been operating Teltane Farm in Monroe Maine with his wife, Paula Fulford, since 1979.  He is a well-known&lt;strong&gt;independent farm consultant and educator&lt;/strong&gt; whose expertise includes transitioning from conventional to organic and biological agriculture; soil, crop and forage nutrition; preparing agriculture and growers for peak oil, climate change and economic drift.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mark also teaches combinations of &lt;strong&gt;minimum tillage techniques, permaculture principles, intensive cropping skills and simultaneous soil-building&lt;/strong&gt; with practical experience.  He facilitates learning on other specialties such as non-electric water technologies, organic orcharding, organic no-till methods, biological crop production, commercial and small-scale composting as well as fundamental rural skills and small farm food preservation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mark's current work also includes developing &lt;strong&gt;custom-blended and field-specific soil amendment recipes&lt;/strong&gt; for organic and nutritionally-focused farm operations.  These customized recipes are meant to simplify and improve the cooperation between consultant, farmer, supplier and organic certifier.  Mark draws on recent discoveries and new understandings of the soil and plant worlds combined with improved methods in order to allow for the widest variety of inputs and skills to meet client goals.  In this way farmers and consumers are assured of the best quality possible in their custom blends.  The service is made possible in cooperation with Lancaster Ag Products due to their wide range of abilities to service the ag communities of the Eastern US.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mark's work in Mexico, China, Australia and the Philippines has &lt;strong&gt;enhanced the scope of his&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;soil and crop insights and has contributed to the evolution of techniques that can be applied to agricultural challenges here in the US.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Selected consulting and/or educational clients:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;MOFGA, NOFA MASS, NOFA NH, NRCS, University of Maine Extension, New Forest Institute, Portland Permaculture Group, Lancaster Ag Products of PA, Biomatrix Water- Forres, Scotland, Heart of Maine RC&amp;amp;D, DownEast RC&amp;amp;D, City of Rockland ME, Troy Howard Middle School, Belfast, ME, North Branford High School (CT), Washington County Soil &amp;amp; Water Conservation Service, Inland Fisheries &amp;amp; Wildlife plus dozens of private farm and orchard clients throughout New England, the US and abroad.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Fulford</member_name><member_id>75294962</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>10</waitlist_count><updated>1367090994000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360857210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Potluck + The Magic of Rock Dust with Mark Fulford</name><id>104593352</id><duration>9000000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366756200000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/104593352/</event_url></item>