<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I'm trying something new.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday April 19th I am hosting a meetup of my Creative Peoples group and I thought it would be fun to ask if some of you would like to join us - we always have a great time talking about our creative interests, be it photography, digital art, sculpture, jewelry making, quilting etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's a new space that's become available on Newbury street for Meetups, the Digital Lounge at Tech Superpowers and I think it bodes well for this group as there are a whole bunch of Macs for viewing slideshows, machines with Aperture, Lightroom, Photoshop, free wifi, cold sodas and a great stereo system and large flat screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tech Superpowers Digital Lounge holds about 15 people comfortably so I need to cap the RSVP's at 10 from each group, and get a few extra chairs and we should do fine. Plan on picking something up to munch on (there are many places nearby as well as a great new organic coffee place next door) We will have the Lounge from 5-8 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The space is being offered free by Tech Superpowers for a limited time and there will be a TSP staff person on hand for the event who I'd like to tip, so I'm asking for $3 per person which includes a free cold soda/water from their cooler if you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So burn a CD and show off your work! Don't forget your business cards!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have the place to ourselves!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240676157000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239161938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet, Greet, Show &amp; Tell</name><id>10141446</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240174800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/10141446/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/5/3/global_8050947.jpeg</photo_url></item>