<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>364 Central Ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.195200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Central Wave</name><city>Dover</city><id>671404</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.874550</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>These &amp;quot;3rd Thursday&amp;quot; meetings (4th Thursday for November) are mostly social, to meet with like-minded others for intriguing conversation and relaxation.  Come and see what's what and who's who!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more focused events, watch the schedule for specific meetings, or check the other Group Links (&amp;quot;Welcome&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;About Us&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Messages&amp;quot;, etc.).  This is a new group, so we're adding content, members, and functions all the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Note regarding location:  Dover Soul went out of business in September, but the new owner (of what is now called the Central Wave), is very &amp;quot;paranormal friendly&amp;quot;.  It's the same location, but a very different environment - so if you have any ideas for alternate locations, I'm up to hear them.  Regarding these &amp;quot;social Thursdays,&amp;quot; I'd prefer to keep them in public establishments, as it keeps them very informal and friendly.  Also, we have another member form Maine... and I'm thinking it might be do-able to have these socials every other week, with the 1st Thursday of the month taking place in or near Portland, and the 3rd Thursday remaining in the NH Seacoast area.  &amp;quot;Events,&amp;quot; however, will always take place wherever they occur...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>andy</member_name><member_id>5342211</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227265478000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193357083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group November Meetup</name><id>6618045</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196380800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/6618045/</event_url></item>