<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"You're traveling through another dimension, a dimension not only of sight and sound but of mind." So said Rod Serling in 1960. Our next Meetup will explore hypnagogic visioning. What do you see when you close your eyes before falling asleep at night? What do you see before you open your eyes in the morning when you first wake up? Have you ever seen or heard strange things when you were half asleep? The hypnagogic zone is that fuzzy area somewhere between being fully awake and fully asleep, when the conscious mind is in touch with the unconscious, intuitive mind. Many people experience quite vivid images and even sounds, voices, or other sensations in this twilight zone of the mind. Some experience lucid dreaming and out of body experiences. Some experience the presence of beings. Others experience fantastic scenes or movies or 3 dimensional animated patterns dancing on their eyelids. Deerheart will share with you his techniques for inducing hypnagogia. You are encouraged to bring your own visionary experiences to share, if you want. Come and explore with us the fascinating world of twilight consciousness. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This Meetup will be led by Deerheart who has had many years of dreams and hypnagogic visions. He will share some of these and talk about them with the group. Deerheart is a &lt;a href="http://www.visionarydreamguide.com/"&gt;dream guide&lt;/a&gt; and a dream artist. He is the founder of &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/"&gt;Boston Dreamers&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/36258693723/"&gt;Dream Blog Network&lt;/a&gt; on Facebook. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left through angel doorway, into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326341339000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325624432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Twilight Zone of the Mind</name><id>46496662</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326240000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/46496662/</event_url></item>