<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online</address_1><state>VA</state><lat>37.431572</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>Online</city><id>1180298</id><country>us</country><lon>-78.656891</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Free Teleseminar with Robyn Thompson&lt;br /&gt;Running your real estate business like a business not a hobby&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, March 31. 8:00 - 9:00pm EST&lt;br /&gt;Register at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=251" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to check your email after registering.&lt;br /&gt;We'll email you the phone number and pin access code for this Teleseminar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Queen of Rehab,&amp;quot; is back with brand new ideas and strategies that she cannot wait to share with you. Now is the time to buy real estate. America is on sale - a 2 for 1 sale. If you want to take advantage of buying real estate at historically low prices, and you want to build a business... then be sure to attend this teleseminar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn Thompson has rehabbed over 278 houses to date. She did this in up markets and down markets just like today. Why did she prosper when others failed? Because she treated Real Estate Investing like a business, no just a hobby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are committed to being in business and being profitable for the next 1, 3, 5 and even 10 years, you definitely want to attend this special teleseminar with Robyn Thompson. This is all new information that you have not heard before. She will share with you:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; How to reinvest your time and money&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; How to work ON your business instead of IN your business&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; How to turn foreclosures into &amp;quot;gravy&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; How to turn your past lessons into a future of profit&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; And so much more&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This call is designed for new investors and experienced investors alike. Will you make money in 2010? Will you be around 10 years from now? Be sure to learn Robyn's strategy for building your successful real estate investing business.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270253741000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269611347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Teleseminar with Robyn Thompson: Running your REI business like a business.</name><id>12998603</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270080000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/12998603/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/9/b/global_12053275.jpeg</photo_url></item>