<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Holiday party for Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also have this event listed on my Forever Young Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://friends.meetup.com/545/"&gt;http://friends.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its a Visit, Bring some food, bring a Fun Grab Bag Gift if you want (OK NO MORE THAN 10 BUCK LIMIT) it can be fun stuff , gag, or whatever.. If you want to participate, about 6:30 or so..&lt;br /&gt;NO GRAB ASSING though..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some Pot Luck Dish, its always good to surprize than fill some lit's thing..we are gonna eat it anyway, even if its similar to someone else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its an event to enjoy time with friends and not let the cold weather stop our fun times, but give us a time and place to enjoy conversing and maybe adding the new things on the list of different things that's forthcoming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details:&lt;br /&gt;From Tina:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Okay, now that the NEW YEARS PARTY is settled, I'd like to post a Holiday Open House&lt;br /&gt;at my place on December 20. Don't have definite time yet, but probably&lt;br /&gt;towards later afternoon (4 ish). People can come and go as they please and&lt;br /&gt;then maybe we'll do a grab bag at a designated time for those that want to&lt;br /&gt;participate. You can post the following for now and we'll add details&lt;br /&gt;later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Holiday Open House at a Private home in Meriden on Saturday,&lt;br /&gt;December 20. More details to follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But also check out the other site, i update that one more frequently&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will send out driving Directions and other stuff the day before and on the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;Check back for updates.&lt;br /&gt;Its not really that far, Hint :&lt;br /&gt;its Near 91 and Rte 15 split.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see you all soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will mail out the info the day before and day of the event, check back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237836228000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229462444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Party At Tina's in Meriden  ADDRESS ALREADY MAILED OUT</name><id>9348776</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229806800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/9348776/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/6/global_3541542.jpeg</photo_url></item>