<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>257 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 629 8717</phone><name>Diesel Cafe</name><city>Somerville</city><id>705077</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121750</lon></venue><fee><label>Suggested Donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston? Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Socializing for Justice at Diesel Cafe for Game Night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program. No speaker. &lt;br /&gt;Just bring your favorite board game and enjoy yourself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP yes, maybe or no - what board game(s) are you bringing or want to play?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Socializing for Justice (SoJust) is for feminists, people working against racism, queer pioneers, genderbenders, environmental agitators, class activists, lefty artists and all people across Greater Boston working for justice in our neighborhoods, in our nation and beyond. But it's not work! Instead, we're building a strong cross-issue network through fun social events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the Socializing for Justice Meetup Board and you'll be able to view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, print &amp;amp; on-line resources - and you'll be able to suggest/coordinate future SoJust events like this one!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.socializingforjustice.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.socializingforjustice.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.socializin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1161116082000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1158335841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scrabblerousers for Justice! (Game Night @ Diesel)</name><id>5132647</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1160337600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5132647/</event_url></item>