<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Marginal St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02128</zip><lat>42.366150</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-204-2052</phone><name>Piers Park</name><city>East Boston</city><id>969281</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.037895</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Don't you wish you could take a little vacation after a long day at work? Now it's possible! Come to a beautiful Piers Park in East Boston for an outdoor relaxation. The park offers spectacular views of downtown Boston and a direct access to waterfront. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborwalk.com/placestogo/location.php?nid=4&amp;amp;sid=24" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let the rhythmic sound of the waves soothe your mind and body...There is no agenda other than relaxation. We will do a 20-30 min sitting relaxation exercise followed by a 30-40 minute walk. Bring a blanket or something to sit on and comfortable shoes. &lt;br /&gt;If there is interest we could also have a picnic afterwards or check out one of the restaurants/bars in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Piers Park is easily accessible by subway or car.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there by subway:&lt;br /&gt;Take the Blue Line to Maverick Square. &lt;br /&gt;Take a left on Sumner Street, walk two blocks and take a right on Orleans Street. After two blocks make a left on Marginal Street. Piers Park is two blocks up on the right (7-10 minute walk).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By car:&lt;br /&gt;Take 1A south towards Logan airport/ East Boston. As soon as you get out of the tunnel, bear right towards East Boston. Stay straight on Porter St, you will pass Santarpio's Pizza on your right. Go till the end of the street and turn right onto Cottage St. Go till the end of the street (about 5 blocks) untill you see the entrance to Piers Park in front of you. Turn left and pull into a parking lot on your right or look for a place to park anywhere on the street (both free).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting by the main gate /entrance to the park (near Cottage St.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilia</member_name><member_id>1728643</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250956984000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>whole-living-center</urlname><id>1384267</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Whole Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248892121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Outdoor Relaxation</name><id>10986540</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250206200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/whole-living-center/events/10986540/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/5/global_7333733.jpeg</photo_url></item>