<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sunset Ln</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.327626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Maria College</name><city>Paxton</city><id>725813</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.918336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. is welcoming all the members of the Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group to a great event it will host on the campus of Anna Maria College in Paxton, MA in the Science Building starting at 7PM. The members of the Aldrich Society routinely offer guidance to its membership about starhopping techniques you can use to find objects in the night sky with. There will be indoor telescope displays, hands on demonstrations and outdoor public sky watching if the weather permits.  You will be taken on a guided tour of the night sky with members who use green lasers to point out constellations, asterism and objects of interest so you will never find yourself lost in our local part of the Universe again! We will guarantee that you can find at least three constellations, a bright planet and a double star after leaving the event!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Munchies and beverages will be served - bring your telescope and binoculars if you have them! We have complete control of all the lighting behind the Science Building so the skies can get pretty dark in Paxton! I plan to send a pdf file with detailed directions to all who respond to this meetup message so do not worry about finding your way or getting a great parking space! There will also be a small group of scouts attending so you can also see how the Aldrich Community Outreach Program ( ACOP ) extends throughout the local communities in New England! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is scheduled no matter what the weather brings since we will offer a full indoor presentation! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Aldrich website url with a link to Anna Maria College : &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aldrichastro.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aldrichast...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;-Jim J. Zebrowski &lt;br /&gt;Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group Organizer &lt;br /&gt;President Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A map will be sent to all who rsvp to the event!  If you have friends or family who would like to attend, please bring them but let us know a headcount!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258416521000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257622682000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Backyard Astronomy : Telescopes 101!</name><id>11820320</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258243200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/11820320/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/4/global_7975572.jpeg</photo_url></item>