<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Kendall Square </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.367496</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>495181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The true story of Salomon Sorowitsch (Karl Markovics), counterfeiter extraordinaire and bohemian. After getting arrested and thrown in a German concentration camp in 1944, he agrees to help the Nazis in an organized counterfeit operation set up to help finance the war effort. It was the biggest counterfeit money scam of all times: over £130 million in British currency was printed, under conditions that couldn't have been more tragic or spectacular. During the last years of the war, as the German Reich saw that the end was near, the authorities decided to produce their own banknotes in the currencies of their major war enemies. At the Sachsenhausen concentration camp, two barracks were separated from the rest of the camp and transformed into a fully equipped counterfeiters workshop. "Operation Bernhard" was born. Kendall Description

NOTE: This movie is in GERMAN with English subtitles.

I will tweak the meeting time as the date approaches.

&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/Y9UlKXYpzxc" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be just inside the door to the right</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 2936604</member_name><member_id>2936604</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207482670000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>From an historical perspective, the Stefan Ruzowitzky?s meshing of plot with debate is impressive. His film is compelling and clever.    Time Out</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204312099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Counterfeiters</name><id>7434260</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206829800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7434260/</event_url></item>