<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;read the entire event description&lt;/span&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;answer all of the questions&lt;/span&gt; that are part of the RSVP process. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - in that case update your RSVP from a computer to generate them again so you can answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your safety and the safety of the group is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be conducting our first official Random SledFest of the 2011-2012 Winter Season at an old nemesis.&amp;nbsp;Cannon Mountain (#36 @ 4,100 feet) is also known as Profile Mountain, referring to the magnificent profile of the Old Man of the Mountain, an infamous formation of three ledges on the east cliff that collapsed in May 2003.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The tower at the summit provides stunning views of Lafayette and the rest of the Franconia Ridge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will climb the Kinsman Ridge Trail to the summit, relax in the summit lodge for a bit, and then sled the ski trails to get back to the trailhead. The plan is to start late - this will allow people some time to recover from New Year's Eve. It will also ensure we arrive at the summit close to the time they close the ski area (4:00 PM). That way we can use the ski trails after the lifts have stopped for the day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don&amp;rsquo;t bring a sled you will miss out on the fun. The most popular choices are:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://zipfy.com/"&gt;Click here for more information about the Zipfy Sled&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a&gt;Click here for more information about the Slidy Sled&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Be sure to have a way to secure your sled to your pack for the snow shoe up and your snow shoes to your pack for the sled down.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you want to sled on this trip you should bring a helmet - the slopes are steep so the speeds will be fast.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The US Consumer Product Safety Commission publishes a pamphlet titled "Which Helmet for Which Activity" which provides useful information covering a broad range of helmets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While there isn't a helmet specifically designed for sledding, they recommend that wearing a ski helmet (ASTM F2040; CEN 1077; Snell RS-98 or S-98), a bicycle helmet (ASTM F1447; Snell B-90/95 or N-94), or a skateboard helmet (ASTM F1492; Snell N-94) is preferable to wearing no helmet at all.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are NOT allowed on this trip&lt;/strong&gt;. All participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are NOT allowed on this trip.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #000000"&gt;moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;hike-up-sled-down trip we will use Kinsman Ridge Trail to climb to the summit and then the Cannon Mountain Ski Trails to return to the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about 2.2 miles (the sled down is about the same distance)&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb about 2,300 feet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;It should take an average hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;about 2 hours 45 minutes to reach the summit (the sled down should take about 45 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;this estimate allows for slower travel during winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip is considered to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;MODERATE&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&amp;nbsp;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's&amp;nbsp;"White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards&amp;nbsp;since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click below&amp;nbsp;for more information about each peak:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6895"&gt;Cannon&lt;/a&gt; (peakbagger.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/NH-4000.php"&gt;Current hiking trail conditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(TrailsNH.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cannonmt.com/snowreport.html"&gt;Current snow conditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Cannon Mountain)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time.&amp;nbsp;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the snow out of your boots. Mountaineering snowshoes with aggressive teeth for traction while climbing. Kahtoola Microspikes or Hillsound Crampons are acceptable for this hike. &amp;nbsp;Mountaineering crampons with 10-12 teeth are optional. Since we won't be using these items all of the time either have space in your pack or a way to secure them to the outside of it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clot&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;hing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly draws heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket. Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants. Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners. Windproof/waterproof&amp;nbsp;over-mittens.&amp;nbsp;Goggles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead of a hydration bladder since the mouthpiece/tube can freeze.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Be prepared to&amp;nbsp;spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket which packs small and weighs just ounces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries - lithium work best in colder temperatures. Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket. Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be meeting at the parking area on the west side of&amp;nbsp;Route 93&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;near near the Cannon Tramway Station. When you enter the parking lot from Route 93 stay to the left - the trailhead parking area is on the left.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Google Maps this spot is about 140 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 22 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.169388,-71.686849(Kinsman+Ridge+Trailhead+%5Bnorth%5D)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.169388,-71.686849&amp;amp;sspn=0.007988,0.022702&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFaz4oQIdPyW6-w&amp;amp;vpsrc=0&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;here&amp;nbsp;for customizable driving directions to the meeting spot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate&amp;nbsp;in this activity; you know and will follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in either my white or Monica's green Toyota Highlander - both have MA license plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325738572000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323558534000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K Cannon SledFest (MODERATE)</name><id>44056112</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325439000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/44056112/</event_url></item>