<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A lovely Fall &lt;b&gt;2-day&lt;/b&gt; hike on the Appalachian Trail (AT) starting at Bear Mtn. State Park and heading southbound into Harriman State Park to East Mombasha Rd. for a total of about 17.6 miles. This is the next segment of the AT southbound for the group. We'll spend the night at a shelter or tenting area near the trail (you need a tent just in case or must arrange to share with someone). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK, third time offered is the charm and I will do this hike! ;-) I just need at least one other person to go which a vehicle so we can place a vehicle at the end. Come on people, this is Fall, lovely leaves and weather! :-) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first day we would start out on Seven Lakes Drive on the south side of Bear Mtn. We would hike 10 miles to the Fingerboard Shelter on Fingerboard Mtn. If there is room we'd stay in the shelter. If there isn't, we must tent for the night at the shelter. The second day is easier with only 7.6 miles of hiking. Should be done by about 2 or 3 PM at East Mombasha Rd. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonably fit, experienced, and equipped we should come in earlier than I estimated.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Full pack &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, and broken in &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Avoid cotton as it stays wet (this includes underwear). Plus second day's clothing. &lt;br /&gt;* Hat &lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/jacket or rain poncho-Just in case &lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag - 3 season (good down to 20 F at least) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Headlamp or flashlight -LED version best -essential!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking tent -Or share &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* 3 quarts water -No defined safe water source&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* 4 meals for on the trail -DAY-1: lunch, supper; DAY-2: breakfast, lunch (all trash to be packed out!). High energy meals should be planned. Only supper may be cooked but if getting up early (6:00 AM) then breakfast can be cooked too. &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Insect repellant&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Toiletries and Toiletpaper -essential!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* Water filter -To restock water, strongly suggested &lt;br /&gt;* Camera and extra batteries &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking first aid kit -For blisters and such &lt;br /&gt;* Bear bag and 15' min. light weight rope -Hang food at night &lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping pad &lt;br /&gt;* Pocket knife &lt;br /&gt;* Compass &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproof matches -For cooking, campfire, emergency fire (warm up, signal) &lt;br /&gt;* Mess kit -If needed &lt;br /&gt;* Camping utensils -If needed &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking stove and fuel -If cooking &lt;br /&gt;* Game(s) to play in camp -cards, Jenga, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/directions to hike &lt;b&gt;meetup location&lt;/b&gt; and hike ending point (146 E. Mombasha Rd., Southfields, NY) &lt;b&gt;MEET HERE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Southfields&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;address=146+E+Mombasha+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=10975&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.266788&amp;amp;longitude=-74.193763&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Lat.=41.266788, Lon.=-74.193763)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/directions to hike starting location (Seven Lakes Parkway, Highland Falls, NY)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Highland+Falls&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;address=Seven+Lakes+Pkwy&amp;amp;zipcode=10928&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.304637&amp;amp;longitude=-74.015235&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Lat.=41.304637, Lon.=-74.015235)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;MAPS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bear Mountain State Park&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/attachments/BearMountainTrailMap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Harriman State Park&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;(No map online, purchase AT maps for NY or purchase Harriman State Park maps from NY/NJ Trail Conf.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;INFORMATION&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on Bear Mountain State Park&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/13/details.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on Harriman State Park&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/145/details.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287804787000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285037333000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT from Bear Mtn. State Park into Harriman State Park, NY</name><id>14840875</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287234000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/14840875/</event_url></item>