<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is one in a series of presentations that Phillip Werner, a co-organizer with the random group, will be making this summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;While you can use our site to coordinate with other randomites you MUST register for this event with REI by &lt;a href="http://networkedblogs.com/iREhb"&gt;clicking here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking The Long Trail in Vermont (educational series)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Time:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;7:00 p.m. - 8:30 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Presenter:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Philip Werner&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;REI Reading &lt;br /&gt;279 Salem Street &lt;br /&gt;(exit 40 off Route 128) &lt;br /&gt;Reading, MA 01867&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone: (781) 944-5103&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built by the Green Mountain Club between 1910 and 1930, The Long Trail is the oldest long-distance trail in the United States. With its 273-mile footpath and nearly 70 primitive shelters, it was the inspiration for the Appalachian Trail, and offers pristine backcountry hiking opportunities for day hikers, weekend, and long distance backpackers. In this talk, Philip Werner will describe the special challenges of hiking The Long Trail, which is notorious for its mud and rainy weather, and will display photos of landscape, animals, mountains, and sights along this wilderness trail. Philip completed an End-to-End hike of The Long Trail in 2008 and volunteers as a Green Mountain Club Mentor for backpackers preparing to hike the Long Trail.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip</member_name><member_id>5187997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312935548000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307571831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking The Long Trail in Vermont (educational series)</name><id>21512151</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312930800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/21512151/</event_url></item>