<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Old River Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.692941</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-975-3600</phone><name>Wyndham Hotel </name><city>Andover</city><id>809493</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.204044</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us this month when Linda Holt of New Light Redesign and Susan Seifer from MadPatter Art Designs share with us "3 Different Design and Color Trends for 2011".&amp;nbsp; Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BIO For Linda Holt &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Light Redesign transforms spaces through the use of color and  what the client already owns . Owner Linda Holt has had a life long passion for art and design. For 26 years she was a professional&amp;nbsp; photographer and the owner of Linda Holt Photography in Boston. Throughout her photography career she maintained an active interest in Interior Design decorating her own home and those of her friends. In 2006 she closed her photography studio and enrolled in&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;North Shore Community College &lt;/strong&gt;Interior Design program. She is also a graduate of &lt;strong&gt;The School of Redesign and Home Staging&lt;/strong&gt; as well as having earned 2 different &lt;strong&gt;Color Consulting Certifications&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp; In 2008 she opened New Light Redesign to be an affordable alternative to traditional Interior Design. She works with Home Owners and Realtors from North of Boston to Southern NH.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Linda's&amp;nbsp; passion is creating&amp;nbsp; warm and welcoming spaces that you'll&amp;nbsp; love coming home to.Visit www.newlightredesign.com/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BIO For Susan Siefer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MadPatter ArtDesign develops and produces innovative artisan decorative finish surfaces on walls, ceilings and canvas.&amp;nbsp; Owner Susan Siefer is an established decorative surface designer creating beautiful environments in residential homes and commercial establishments throughout the New England area.  With a formal education in fine arts and design, Susan stays current with new decorative finishing products and techniques through workshops, contacts and collaboration with other designers. When not working on site, Susan works out of a beautifully renovated mill building in Lawrence, MA.Visit &lt;a href="http://www.madpatter.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen Campaiola</member_name><member_id>6037081</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299768339000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Join us this month when Linda Holt of New Light Redesign and Susan Seifer from MadPatter Art Designs share with us "3 Different Design and Color Trends for 2011".  Hope to see you there!</why><group><who>Daring Women!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup</urlname><id>1412014</id><group_lat>42.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Dare To Be Phenomenal's Success Minded Women's Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281553462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DARE Networking Luncheon</name><id>dqzfpypfbmb</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299688200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup/events/16612687/</event_url></item>