<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Possibilities 13 Session Group Coaching Program&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday evenings, March 24th through June 16th, 7:15 -9:15pm&lt;br /&gt;Roots and Wings, Natick, MA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;(Do not rsvp through this site. Registration and payment directly with Ann is required to participate in this program.)&lt;br /&gt;(Since registrations are directly with me, they won't show on this site.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Has trying to resolve your problems and find greater happiness on your own been as successful as you’d like? Are you reading this book and that book, or listening to this CD or watching that DVD, or listening to large impersonal teleseminars that essentially leave you on your own? &lt;i&gt;Somehow, these aren’t as effective as really engaging and learning with others.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly meetups are great for a little of this and a little of that, getting a boost, and staying in the learning game. But if you’re still not getting the results and changes you desire, then maybe it’s time to consider more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you relate to any of these questions?&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Have you settled for resigned acceptance or complacency for how things are, even though you’re not fully happy about it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you practice Law of Attraction principles, do you feel like you’ve been doing everything you “should” to get results you want, yet still find yourself frustrated, wondering, “Why is this so hard?” or “Why isn’t this working?”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Or maybe you know how you’re holding yourself back, but you still can’t seem to make the necessary changes on your own, no matter what you try.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would you like to expand in new ways for continued growth and personal evolution, and to open up new possibilities in your life? Life can get better and better!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can relate to any of these, we invite you to join us in our &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;13 session New Possibilities Group Coaching Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to immerse yourself in a dedicated, comprehensive, over-time learning program led by experts in personal change, combined with the caring support of a consistent, intimate group of peers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;If you've been to any of our meetups, you've heard us say many times that the way to manifest what you want is to find inner harmony and happiness first. And, being happy is the point of it all, anyway!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Our New Possibilities Group Coaching Program is a comprehensive program that is guaranteed to provide you with proven beliefs and skills for leading a life with harmony, happiness and success.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We use the powerful model and processes of NLP (Neurolinguistic Programming) to create deep changes you don't have to keep working at, and we integrate it with Law of Attraction principles. You'll get personal changes and growth in the areas of your life that matter most to you (work, self-esteem, family, relationships, health, etc.). As Mark likes to put it, it will allow you to easily flow into the future you care about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participating in an in-depth personal growth program like this could be one of the most stimulating, happy, fulfilling, expanding times of your life! It has certainly always turned out that way for us. Little compares to the in-person, experiential, embodied learning and changes that can take place for you in this kind of environment. This is what we are offering you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;It has been SO fulfilling to see the positive changes people have made in this program:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Like the two women who firmly believed (and thus experienced) that there were no more good men in their age range or that any man worth wanting wouldn’t be interested in them. By the end of the program they were both going out on dates with desirable men and having a great time. Last I heard, one of them was getting serious with one man.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;People began to experience greater peace – with themselves, in their relationships, and even within potentially very stressful times (like house and money problems).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;They began to get more of what they wanted because they learned how to ask more effectively!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;They made easy behavioral changes, like eating habits, when they learned how to easily reveal and release resistance to change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;People busted through limiting beliefs, like I don’t have what it takes, that were holding them back in their careers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;One woman said that how she was when she began the program felt like a different lifetime. She could barely express how much better and freer she felt at the end of the program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;So what would you like? Really like. Don’t be afraid to ask, and don’t think too small. Mark and I believe you can have all the harmony, happiness and success that you desire; and we would love to partner with you on that path.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more curriculum details, logistics and current rates (discounts and bonuses for early sign-ups), go here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com/programs.html" target="_blank"&gt;Group Coaching Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested, contact Ann at &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com&lt;/span&gt; to arrange for a quick phone call and to register directly through her. She will then send you the appropriate paypal link and forms. You must make the 13 session program commitment to participate; and people will not be allowed to join once we begin. This is part of what will allow the results you desire!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you'll join us to create lasting new possibilities for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301013306000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294762876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Possibilities Group Coaching Program</name><id>16007917</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301008500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/16007917/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>