<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We've reserved the Screening room at 360 State Street for another Movie Night! Come see a film for free at this great location!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees: I will need your &lt;strong&gt;FULL NAME (and that of any +1) for the Concierge&lt;/strong&gt; to let you in. Please Provide when you RSVP. (Event Comment, Email, or Text me.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP's are limited to 18 due to theater size, there should be &lt;em&gt;NO&lt;/em&gt; Maybe's for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Events Film Is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Prestige&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (2006 Drama / Mystery)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0482571/"&gt;IMDB Description:&lt;/a&gt; The rivalry between two magicians is exacerbated when one of them performs the ultimate illusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directed and Written by: Christopher Nolan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Staring: Hugh Jackman, Christian Bale, Scarlett Johansson, Michael Caine, Rebecca Hall, Andy Serkis, David Bowie&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AJ's Comments:&amp;nbsp; Two popular magicians in the 1800's spark a fierce rivalry between their acts.&amp;nbsp; This is in my current top 10 favorite movies.&amp;nbsp; By my interpretation the Theme and Symbolism in this film is well hidden, but very well done, very interesting philosophically, and seasonally appropriate for mid-February.&amp;nbsp; You'll have to look for &lt;em&gt;the secrete&lt;/em&gt; while you watch, but I will be willing to discuss after.&amp;nbsp; (Pay particular attention to Michael Caine's opening and closing monologues.) As an Engineering Nerd/Geek, I also get a chuckle out of the appearance of Nikola Tesla (played by David Bowie.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event start time is 7:00 for the social portion, so you can start showing up then &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;but please no earlier.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; We will not &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;start the film until 7:30 or shortly there after&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, but don't plan to be any later.&amp;nbsp; (There are now restrictions on room time.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list. If someone else backs out you can be automatically added, just provide your full&amp;nbsp;name for the concierge as a contingency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Snacks:&lt;/span&gt; Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just Please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Getting in:&lt;/span&gt; Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are &lt;span&gt;instructions with a phone number on the door and&lt;/span&gt; a call box with bell button. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call/text AJ at 315-345-9348&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt; There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street (some with Credit Card slot available.), obey the posted limits on the meter.&amp;nbsp; If you don't mind the longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evening/weekends. (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street.) 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only, the entrance is on State Street just to the Right of the buildings main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ring the Bell Button or Call the concierge on the cell phone number on the door, they will Direct you. If you have added problems, call AJ at 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328917476000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327001318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie:  The Prestige</name><id>48786552</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328832000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/48786552/</event_url></item>