<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight we feature author Gary Stamper, co-founder and former leader of SeattleIntegral, to discuss the release of his new book, “&lt;a href="http://www.awakeningthenewmasculine.com"&gt;Awakening the New Masculine&lt;/a&gt;.” The book is based on Gary’s experiences of The Integral Warrior men's workshop series he created and has facilitated for the past 5 years, synthesizing multi-dimensional processes that ignites men's passion for who they truly are and the gifts they are capable of bringing to their lives, the lives of their loved ones, and the planet. His work is a bridge from the first wave of the mythopoetic men’s movement of the last twenty-five years to what is only now beginning to emerge. Gary's talk will combine cutting edge integral and developmental systems with ancient shamanic wisdom technologies and practices.  Moreover, this work will also allow us to balance the masculine and the feminine in Sacred Union, and to see the role of Sacred Activism in the life of the Integral Warrior. (Please note: This evening's event is open to all genders and people of all sexual orientations.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341971980000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327521020000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Awakening the New Masculine: The Path of the Integral Warrior</name><id>49605572</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340753400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/49605572/</event_url></item>