<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(100 yards south of route 140)</address_2><address_1>Thomas St, </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01583</zip><lat>42.379810</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Central Mass Rail Trail</name><city>West Boylston</city><id>637242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.794205</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The rail trail is right outside of Worcester - less than an hour's drive from Boston.  There is a parking lot right near the rail trail.  Please bring a hybrid or mountain bike.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Mass Central Rail Trail is one short part of a hoped-for Waltham to Northampton trail.  This part of the trail begins on the shore of the Wachusett Reservior in West Boylston, just south of the intersection of Thomas St and Rt 140.  The rail trail connects directly to a collection of Holden trails that are pure off-road, grippy tires terrain.  The two types of trail make this a fun and interesting ride.  Afterward, if there's interest, we could head to Finder's Pub or Meola's in West Boylston for some ice cream. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rail trail leads away from the reservoir alongside the Quinapoxet river, mostly under the forest canopy.  The trail goes under I-190 and crosses the river.  This trail is only about 3 miles long, with a stone dust or pea gravel surface.  There are usually plenty of pedestrians to dodge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the rail trail section, through the parking lot, we'll continue on the Town of Holden trails.  These trails are dirt, with rough, rocky, and/or sandy surfaces, with some short but very steep inclines.  You'll want stubby tires.  The trails are mostly under the forest canopy, but there's some open areas.  I've rarely met other people on these trails, other than an occasional mountain biker. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Plan on an hour to an hour and a half for the ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a map of the trails, maintained by Wachusett Greenways, see their website, &lt;a href="http://www.wachusettgreenways.org/Trail%20map%20Info.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wachusett Greenways Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248706294000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Leisure Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-235</urlname><id>527341</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Boston Leisure Bicycling</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228673415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Biking the Central Mass Rail Trail</name><id>9296490</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248030000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-235/events/9296490/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/1/global_1549089.jpeg</photo_url></item>