<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>80.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;How Much?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Min of 5 paid members, Max of 12 members&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Guests: None.  Members Only.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: Annual Members - FREE; Members - $2/event or $5 for all 4 sessions payable at the first session&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each lesson is $20 pp per lesson for a total of $80 pp for clinic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Option #1 - pay entire clinic cost by RSVP July 8th - $80’s (mail check)&lt;br /&gt;Option #2 - pay half by RSVP date July 8th and remaining ½ at 1st meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP to the clinic you are committing to entire 4 weeks of classes or $80’s&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Details:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After reviewing the poll results and coordinating with the golf course, we will begin our golf lessons over a 4 week period, every Tuesday evening, 6:00 pm at the Braintree Municipal Golf Course.   Each lesson will be 50 – 60 minutes and we’ll need a minimum group of 4-6 members for the discounted lessons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lessons are ideal for beginner/intermediate/advanced golfers.  The lesson strategy will be based upon each individuals skill set and goals and will be taught by the course golf professional.  Golf clubs and balls will be supplied to any member if needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is open to both those who own clubs and anyone who would like to use the ones offered by the golf course. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Meetup promptly at 5:45pm each Tuesday for 4 weeks&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Tentative Lesson Plan&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;• Lesson #1 July 14th – Putting and Chipping&lt;br /&gt;• Lesson #2 July 21st – Pitching, working on short game&lt;br /&gt;• Lesson #3 July 28th – Working with Irons&lt;br /&gt;• Lesson #4 Aug. 4th – Woods, driving, T off&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;How many?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a minimum of 4 Participants (Non-organizers) by noon on Wednesday, July 8th. No Guests for this meet-up as demand is high and space is limited to 12 attendees total. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Organizers:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Susan (AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Deadlines&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/b&gt; The Final &lt;b&gt;Deadline is Noon on Wednesday, July 8th&lt;/b&gt;.  Please be mindful if you may change your RSVP to NO at the last minute as you may be taking a spot away from someone else that is serious about participating. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan arrive at least 15 minutes before the class begins each week or 5:45pm to get everyone organized.  The lesson will begin promptly at 6:00 pm on the course.  SSFMG and its organizers are not responsible for any injuries to participants or damage to equipment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Weather Alternative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;None. This event will be canceled if it is raining or too foggy. We will do our best to cancel at least 6 hours in advance but we cannot control Mother Nature so we will do our best to notify everyone at least 3 hours prior to the event. Please do not change your RSVP based on weather forecasts. We check weather forecasts the night before and use those to determine if the event is canceled.  Check emails Monday night or Tuesday morning to determine event status.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Carpool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;  There is no carpool for this event. Members should meet at the Braintree Municipal Golf Course at 5:45 pm.  If you would like to carpool you may note where from in your RSVP comment and someone else may choose to contact you if they are also interested in carpooling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The course is conveniently located just minutes from four major highways &lt;a href="http://www.braintreegolf.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;(Directions)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meeting area at front of Club House</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>8338847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247781979000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246290420000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GOLF CLINIC - 4 WK LESSONS </name><id>10760168</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247608800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/10760168/</event_url></item>