<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Long Wharf</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359940</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>1 Long Wharf</name><city>Boston</city><id>2664911</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051033</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jacquie W. &amp;amp; Vale D. are hosting this event&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cast off for a perfect summer day on and by the water in the beautiful Boston Harbor Islands, exploring, relaxing on Spectacle Island, with music!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;10:30am ferry&lt;/span&gt; for a brief ride from Long Wharf North on the Boston waterfront to the beautiful Boston Harbor Islands (&lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborislands.org/"&gt;http://www.bostonharborislands.org/&lt;/a&gt;)(&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/boha/historyculture/facts-intro.htm"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/boha/historyculture/facts-intro.htm&lt;/a&gt;), where we will disembark on Spectacle Island.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arriving on the island about 10:50am, we’ll stop at the Visitor Center (restrooms, food available), and then walk (a gradual incline) to the top of the Island, where we’ll have lunch (bring or purchase there) and enjoy the sweeping vistas of blue water, the Boston Harbor Islands, and the Boston skyline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll then wander back down to relax on the Spectacle Island porch (covered) and listen to guitarist, David Ehle, and the sounds of big bands, folk music, swing, and jazz ensembles, playing from 12-4pm. Or, wander around the island some more, or do a little of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We’ll depart from Spectacle Island on the 3:50pm ferry back to Long Wharf.&lt;/span&gt; The ferry leaves Spectacle Island at 50 minutes past the hour throughout the day; last ferry is 5:50pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Lunch&lt;/span&gt;: Pack a lunch, beverages, and snacks, or purchase at Jasper White’s Summer Shack on the Island: &lt;a href="http://www.summershackrestaurant.com/uploadDocs/2012%20snack%20shack.pdf"&gt;http://www.summershackrestaurant.com/uploadDocs/2012%20snack%20shack.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Suggested gear&lt;/span&gt;: Bring water, sunglasses, sunblock, bug repellent, hat, beach towel/blanket, jacket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Limited to 12 attendees&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registration &amp;amp; Ferry Ticket Purchase - deadline: Fri 7/13 noon (Please see two steps below)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;To Register&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; (See section below to purchase ferry ticket.) Please email (preferred): Jacquie Wheeler, event Co-host: &lt;a href="mailto:Jacquelyn_Wheeler@yahoo.com"&gt;Jacquelyn_Wheeler@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt; ; 617-388-3390 (cell)/text); please include your email address and your cell phone #. Co-host: Vale; 508-361-0385 (cell).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To Purchase Ferry Ticket(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Purchase and print your own ticke&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;t in advance&lt;/span&gt; from Boston’s Best Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonsbestcruises.com/2012-bos-spec-spec"&gt;http://www.bostonsbestcruises.com/2012-bos-spec-spec&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10:30am departure from Long Wharf ; 3:50pm return from Spectacle Island&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket prices: $15.00; $11.00 for seniors (65+)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please note&lt;/span&gt;: Purchase of the ferry ticket is your responsibility. In the case of heavy rain/bad weather, the Event Co-chairs may choose to cancel the event, even if the ferry is still running. Event Co-chairs will notify Sitz members via email or telephone by 7:30am on 7/15. if this is the case. Non-Sitz members will be notified via Meet-up.com. Or, please contact Vale or Jacquie, if you have questions. Neither Sitzundjibers, nor the Event Co-hosts are responsible for ticket refunds or rescheduling.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Convening Time &amp;amp; Place&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: 10:00am – Boston Islands Ferry Center (Boston’s Best Cruises Ferry) – Long Wharf North (between the Marriott Long Wharf Hotel and Christopher Columbus Park – not the Aquarium side), next to the Chart House (60 Long Wharf, Boston).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discounted Parking ($2.00 off for a total of $7.00) at One International Place (address: 1 International Place) when you present your parking garage ticket at the Ferry Center at time of purchase. Or, look for on-the-street parking in the financial district; parking is free in metered spaces on Sundays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS BY CAR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM THE NORTH: Take I-93 South to exit 24A/Government Center. Left onto Surface Rd; Left on Milk St; Left on Atlantic Ave, Long Wharf North on right past Marriott OR stay straight on Milk St, to park in Harbor Garage at the New England Aquarium, which will be on your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM THE SOUTH: Take I-93 North to exit 23 in the Thomas P O’Neill tunnel; Left on Surface Rd; Left on Milk St; Left on Atlantic Ave; Long Wharf North on right past Marriott OR stay straight on Milk St, to park in Harbor Garage at the New England Aquarium, which will be on your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM THE WEST: Take the Mass Pike (I-90) to I-93 North. Take Exit 23 (Government Center). Follow signs to the New England Aquarium which will require you to make a 180 degree loop onto Atlantic Avenue. There are parking facilities at the New England Aquarium Harbor Garage and the Boston Harbor Hotel, both on the right. When you exit the parking garages walk north along Atlantic Ave. Stay on Atlantic Ave. until you pass the Marriott Hotel. Then turn Right; the Ferry Center is about halfway down the wharf beside the docks, past Tia’s restaurant and the Marriott Hotel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BY PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BY T&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Take MBTA Blue Line to Aquarium Station. Follow the exit signs for the New England Aquarium. Upon exiting the station onto Atlantic Ave. turn around and walk towards the waterfront, walk through the Long Wharf Marriott Hotel. When you exit the hotel, turn Right, the docks are located ahead along with Boston’s Best Cruises&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342488769000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341332268000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Harbor Islands Excursion – Ferry to Spectacle Island, Lunch, Music &amp; More</name><id>71801672</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342360800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/71801672/</event_url></item>