<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 W 44th St</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10036  </zip><lat>40.758275</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>212-239-6200</phone><name>Broadhurst Theater</name><city>New York</city><id>738169</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.987604</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wanda, one of our members, suggested a trip to Broadway to see the new production of Equus and has graciously agreed to co-organize this event.  I think it's a great idea but will take a little early planning.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The date is December 6th and we'll be attending the matinee (2:00 pm).  It should be a great time of year to be in NYC.  The plan is to take the train into NYC from New Haven.  We'll arrange carpools to New Haven from the Hartford area.  We're still working out the details, but it will definitely include lunch, the play, a trip to Rockefeller Center to see the tree and probably other sites in the area.  We're also planning on dinner in the city.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;I have purchased 8 tickets.  There are TWO tickets left.   &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  I have put the other two tickets up for sale but if you're interested, call me at 203-812-0705.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is $126 for orchestra seats.  The cost breaks down as $115 ticket, $1.50 facility fee, $7 service charge, $2.50 handling fee.  None of this money goes to me or the meetup group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you cannot commit by the time the 8 tickets sell out, you are welcome to purchase your tickets on your own at a later date.  Just let me know you've done that so we can include you in the coordination details.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the play:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.equusonbroadway.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.equusonbroadway.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.equusonbro...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EQUUS by the Oscar Award winning Peter Shaffer opened at the National Theatre, London in 1973 and became a worldwide sensation. In 2007, a new production opened in London starring Richard Griffiths (History Boys) and Daniel Radcliffe (now making his Broadway debut), and it became one of the biggest hits ever seen in London's West End at the Gielgud Theatre. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now the same production comes to Broadway this Fall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Psychiatrist Martin Dysart (Richard Griffiths) is brought the most challenging case of his career by magistrate Hesther Saloman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alan Strang (Daniel Radcliffe) seems like a normal seventeen year old. His life appears routine and his family loving. However, Alan’s passion for horses and an encounter with stablehand Jill has led him to behave in the most devastating way.  Only Dysart seems able to grasp the answer to this psychological puzzle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Audience:  Equus may be inappropriate for audiences aged 18 and younger (strong language and nudity) .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, give me a call at 203-812-0705.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will coordinate a meeting spot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228763622000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218846014000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Equus</name><id>8554218</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228590000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/8554218/</event_url></item>