<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for an array of Japanese, Chinese, and Vietnamese food as we dine out for Dinner at Dalat along Nantasket Beach in Hull.  They offer a wide variety of food from appetizers to entrees which range in price from $3-$20.  This will be a great night for sharing and tasting new foods.  Some of the dishes they offer include soups, salads, rice and noodle dishes, veggie dishes, and specialty dishes including sushi, and sashimi.  Tables seat up to 10.  The restaurant can accommodate us at two tables for a total of 20 attendees.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time/Date:  5pm Saturday, May 12th, 2007&lt;br /&gt;Location:  Dalat, 181 Nantasket Avenue, Hull, MA 02045&lt;br /&gt;Minimum/Maximum: There is a maximum of 20 people.  &lt;br /&gt;Guests: One guest per person is allowed up until we have 18 confirmed attendees, then it will become members only.  Please RSVP for a guest only if they will definitely be attending.  If your guest can no longer attend please update your RSVP immediately so someone else may attend in their place.&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place:  5pm outside (inside if inclement weather) the restaurant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $3-$20 for dishes plus drinks, tax, and tip (We expect some dishes will be shared.)  &lt;br /&gt;Event Fees:  $ 2.00 pp&lt;br /&gt;Deadline: 4pm, Friday May 11th as we need to confirm with the restaurant that night&lt;br /&gt;Organized by:  Jen E.&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather:  Event takes place rain or shine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;From Route 3A: Follow to Route 228 and then pick up at the intersection of Route 3A and 228 below.&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 14 to Route 228 North towards Hingham.  Follow throiugh Hingham.  Cross over Route 3A, and follow into Hull.  When you get into Hull you will pass DiNero's, then Nantasket Beach Inn on your left and The Frosty Claw on your right.  After you pass The Frosty Claw, take your first right into the parking lot, and then a left into the 2nd parking lot on the left.  Dalat is across the street.  Please note: It is approximately 7 miles from Route 3/Route 228 to the Restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 3:  Lost?:  Call restaurant at 781-925-4587.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******PLEASE NOTE: REGISTRATIONS FOR THIS EVENT CLOSED AT 3:15PM.  IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO ATTEND AND DID NOT HAVE A CHANCE TO RSVP YES PLEASE CALL THE RESTAURANT TO LET US KNOW AND PLAN TO ARRIVE AT THE RESTAURANT A FEW MINUTES EARLY.******&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179177013000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177792672000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dalat Dinner!</name><id>5719861</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179003600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5719861/</event_url></item>