<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a repeat meetup to accommodate the demand for Aug 31st Zakim shoot.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have already signed up or are on the waiting list for August 31 and are switching to this Friday, please remove your self from the other event after you RSVP for this event&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the date&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August has two full Moon days: Aug 1st @11:30pm and on the 31st at 9:59am. &lt;br /&gt;

 Friday the 3rd is close enough to a full Moon and has the benefit of being followed by a weekend day - for you late night shooters. I hope the weather holds out, of course, however there is shelter nearby, just in case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;According to the US Naval Observatory, Moonrise/Sunset data for Boston is as follows:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Moon will be 97-98% illuminated on Aug 3rd - which is good enough to appear full in photos. Sunset is at 8:03 (Civil Twilight lasts until 8:32pm). The Moon will begin to rise (on the horizon) at 8:34pm. We won't likely not see the Moon until an hour later. It will transit (highest point) around at 1:39 am - that gives more than enough time to experiment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why did I limit this to 12 attendees?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have limited these 2 shoots to a dozen spots to minimize getting in each other's field, and to give everyone a chance to get at "favorite" locations and one-flash-per-scene rear-curtain effects on moving illuminated objects. This will make a lot more sense on location. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Models and Guests (that will model):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Photographers will be experimenting with balancing long-exposure for  night scenes with a flash fill for portraiture. You can expect to get somewhat exotic photos with dramatic lighting effects. We may optionally experiment with motion and LED's (if I can find what I need) so come and discover something different for your portfolio. Any questions, call or email me: Dom@ChannelOne.us 781-866-1597&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment reminder:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Remember to bring camera, wide-angle lens, tripod and external flash. &lt;br /&gt;

 Optional: off-camera cord and/or remote 2nd flash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email RSVP's with complete details</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Domenico</member_name><member_id>9296355</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1344782799000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers, Models &amp; MUA</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonportraitphotographers</urlname><id>830833</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Portrait Photographers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343652634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zakim Bridge Shoot Aug 3rd, THIS FRIDAY</name><id>75505642</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344038400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/events/75505642/</event_url></item>