<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Short Sale Process got you rippin' your hair out???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, glue it back on and find out how to smooth the process. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Short sales are a hot topic these days -- most of the motivated sellers that you speak to are upside down with their lenders. The borrowers can't afford to make payments, but the banks don't seem to be in any hurry to cut a deal, even though they have thousands of these upside down loans on their books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why the banks aren't calling you back &lt;br /&gt;How to speak the bank's language so they want to deal with you &lt;br /&gt;How to streamline the negotiation process so you don't sit on hold for hours &lt;br /&gt;How to package the deal for the best and quickest response from the bank &lt;br /&gt;How to structure the deal with no cash out of pocket &lt;br /&gt;How to get the buyer's lender to agree to a simultaneous close &lt;br /&gt;The tax impact for both you and your seller &lt;br /&gt;Learn from Short Sale Expert Kim Harrington from Profitable-Partnerships New England about negotiating with banks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn from Funding Expert Ann Bellamy about simultaneous closing . . . how to get your transaction funded without using your own money.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn from Tax Expert Joe Craft, CFO of Financial Destination, Inc., about the tax ramifications to sellers and to the investors working the deal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:15 PM - POWER HOUR - For Members Only  &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting  &lt;br /&gt;Location: Best Western, 380 Winter Street, Waltham, MA &lt;br /&gt;Free to BostonAREIA members, visitors and meetup members $25 at the door&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249418376000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245364591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association July Meetup</name><id>10683627</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247779800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/10683627/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/global_6774288.jpeg</photo_url></item>