<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Description&lt;br /&gt;This trail begins at the Sabbaday Falls Picnic Area and ascends to the saddle between North Tripyramid and Middle Tripyramid. There are numerous brook crossings, some of which may be difficult at high water. Except for the very steep, rough section just below the main ridge crest, grades are easy to moderate and the footing is mostly good. The upper part of the trail is in the Sandwich Range Wilderness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total distance is approximately 11.40 miles and estimated time is 9 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees are responsible for reading, understanding and agreeing to the hikers responsibility code and waiver which can be found on this site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Itinerary &lt;br /&gt;starting at Sabbaday Brook Trailhead&lt;br /&gt; entering wilderness area&lt;br /&gt;hike 0.30 mi/12 min/+101 ft on the Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt; From the parking area, follow a gravel tourist path along the brook. A side path bears left and passes several viewpoints over Sabbaday Falls, rejoining where the gravel path ends, and from there the trail continues on an old logging road with easy grades.&lt;br /&gt;to Sabbaday Falls&lt;br /&gt;hike 4.60 mi/3 hr 34 min/+2428 ft on the Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt; Shortly beyond the falls, footways diverge on either side of a rocky brook bed and then rejoin. The trail makes the first of three crossings of Sabbaday Brook. (All three may be difficult in high water, but the first two can be avoided by bushwhacking along the west bank.) The trail follows the old logging road on the east bank of Sabbaday Brook, entering the Sandwich Range Wilderness (about halfway through this section), and then it turns sharp right, descends briefly, and makes a fourth crossing of the brook. Above this point, both the brook and trail swing to the west, then northwest, up the narrow valley between Tripyramid and the Fool Killer, climbing more steadily and crossing the brook twice more. The trail passes the base of a small slide on the Fool Killer, crosses the brook for the seventh and last time (last water) at the head of the ravine, then swings back to the south, passes a restricted outlook to Mt. Passaconaway, and soon reenters the old route of the trail above the slide on the east slope of Tripyramid. It turns sharp right here and climbs steeply up slabs and broken rock, then becomes less steep but remains rough, with many rocks and roots. Finally, it levels off and meets the Pine Bend Brook Trail and the Mt. Tripyramid Trail just north of the saddle between North and Middle Tripyramid; turn right for North Peak or left for Middle Peak.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mount Tripyramid Trail and Pine Bend Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt; Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt; Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt; Download to GPS&lt;br /&gt;Current Route &lt;br /&gt;Saved Routes &lt;br /&gt; Continue your hike: Use the Select Custom Route tool to select the next destination on the map -or- specify the next destination below.&lt;br /&gt;within this area  &lt;br /&gt;find A nameD &lt;br /&gt; starting at Sabbaday Brook Trailhead&lt;br /&gt;Back to here  &lt;br /&gt; entering wilderness area&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.30 mi/12 min/+101 ft on the Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;to Sabbaday Falls&lt;br /&gt;Back to here  &lt;br /&gt;hike 4.60 mi/3 hr 34 min/+2428 ft on the Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mount Tripyramid Trail and Pine Bend Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;hike 0.50 mi/15 min/+288 ft on the Mount Tripyramid Trail&lt;br /&gt;to North Tripyramid&lt;br /&gt;Back to here  &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.50 mi/15 min/-288 ft on the Mount Tripyramid Trail&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Pine Bend Brook Trail and Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;hike 0.30 mi/17 min/+251 ft on the Mount Tripyramid Trail&lt;br /&gt;to Middle TripyramidBack to here  &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.30 mi/17 min/-251 ft on the Mount Tripyramid Trail&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Pine Bend Brook Trail and Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;hike 4.60 mi/3 hr 34 min/-2428 ft on the Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;to Sabbaday Falls&lt;br /&gt;hike 0.30 mi/12 min/-101 ft on the Sabbaday Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;to Sabbaday Brook Trailhead&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance 11.40 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time 8 hr 36 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3295 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -3295 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change 0 ft&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>DIANNE AND I WILL BE IN A BLACK FOUR DOOR ECHO WITH MAINE LICENSE PLATES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248144505000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245951070000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Tripyramid and Middle Tripyramid.</name><id>10734504</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247920200000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10734504/</event_url></item>