<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1250 Burnside Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.783460</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Marco Polo Restaurant</name><city>East Hartford</city><id>664262</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.583560</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey all,&lt;br /&gt;    I feel so bad for not organizing any events lately.  I have just been swamped!  I am planning on going to Marco Polo with some friends this Saturday night and I invite all of you to join us.  The more the merrier!!!  I hope to be there earlier than 9:30pm but I wouldn't want anyone to show up and not see me and then leave.  You are welcome to come earlier and hopefully, I will be arriving early as well.  I probably won't be there before 9pm though.  For those of you who have never experienced the sites and sounds of Marco Polo before, you are in for a real treat!  Their website is &lt;a href="http://www.marcopoloct.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.marcopoloct.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.marcopoloc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I know it's not a &amp;quot;dining&amp;quot; event since the time is way after dinnertime but I figured I would post this anyway in case anyone else was home during the holiday weekend.  I will not be making a reservation since it is so late in the evening.  We will be sitting in the bar area at the front of the restaurant.  Considering the loose nature of this event, you may want to come with a friend as well since we may not all be able to sit together unless you are comfortable with that.  Although karaoke starts at 9:30pm, things don't really get kickin' in this place until at least 10:30 or 11:00ish so don't rush to judge too early.  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>MP is not that big. Look at my profile pic. Hair is a bit longer &amp; wear glasses</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215481184000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214965126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Karaoke at Marco Polo</name><id>8259713</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215307800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/8259713/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/c/global_2456236.jpeg</photo_url></item>