<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Frozen River&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rated R&lt;br /&gt;Directed By: Courtney Hunt &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Melissa Leo, Misty Upham &lt;br /&gt;Running Time: 97 min. &lt;br /&gt;Location(s): Hartford, CT - Trinity College Cinestudio Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two days before Christmas in rural upstate New York, Ray Eddy's husband has left her in an impossible situation--not only is he gone, but he has gambled away all of the family's meager savings. Ray's single wage at the Yankee One Dollar Store can't make the house payment, and the situation forces Ray to feed her two sons popcorn and Tang every day. When Ray strikes out to search for her husband, she encounters Lila Littlewolf, a tough, street-smart Mohawk woman who is dealing with her own struggle to make ends meet. But Lila has found a way to do it--smuggling illegal immigrants into the States. The tribal elders disapprove and attempt to stop Lila by forbidding anyone to sell her a car. Ray has a car, and although the two women don't trust each other, they team up and share Ray's Dodge Spirit to make a run across the frozen St. Lawrence River. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.sonyclassics.com/frozenriver/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sonyclassi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send email to Yes RSVPs. Possibly at Alchemy Cafe 6:30 or the theater 7:15.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225064239000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222639851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Frozen River</name><id>8852423</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224891000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/8852423/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/4/global_5677460.jpeg</photo_url></item>