<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Rowe Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.615200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-283-6776</phone><name>Cruiseport Gloucester</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1225971</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.654700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Empty Bowl Dinner 2011 &lt;br /&gt;Cruiseport Gloucester   &lt;br /&gt;6 Rowe Square   &lt;br /&gt;Thursday, May 12 &lt;br /&gt;4 p.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join  us for an evening of food and hospitality. Park your car at  Good Harbor  Beach and enjoy a complimentary trolley car ride along the  backshore to  the event site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a minimum donation of $15.00 you may choose a  handmade bowl  (maybe you will see the one you may have painted on March 12th?) crafted  by artisans from the community, and fill it with  delicious soup. The  meal is simple soup, bread and a cookie, but the  message goes home with  your bowl as a reminder that somewhere someone's  bowl is always empty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Empty Bowl Dinner raises both hunger  awareness and money to  support our services to these families, which  include an after-school  snack program, a Summer Food Service Program,  and Food Stamp  application assistance, as well as our hot meals and free  groceries at  The Cape Ann Food Pantry. This year we are using proceeds  from the  event to support our summer lunch programs and Mobile markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We  will be meeting at Good Harbor Beach parking lot (free parking),   Thatcher Road, Gloucester (in front of the entrance to the Snack Bar   building) and taking the free trolley to the event.  Please include in   your RSVP whether you will be meeting us at Good Harbor Beach parking   lot or at the event location.  We will only wait 15 minutes after the   meeting time prior to leaving for the event, if you are meeting us at   Good Harbor lot and are running late, please call the meetup phone at   978-304-2811.  Note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we get into Cruiseport and get a table, we may not all be  sitting at 1 table together if this doesn't work for you please take  note when RSVPing for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Please remember that if you  have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this  event.&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your  profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your  Organizer&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Remember to  change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&amp;nbsp; Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget  after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a  good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!  &lt;br /&gt;Donna, Janet &amp;amp; Vicki&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vicki</member_name><member_id>4058114</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305306107000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>It is a great way to help another community.</why><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298243020000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Empty Bowl Dinner.</name><id>16637806</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305241200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/16637806/</event_url></item>