<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Entry fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>14.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This isn't a hike but come join in on the nightime Christmas holiday celebration called &amp;quot;Christmas by Candlelight&amp;quot; at Old Sturbridge Village (OSV). The village will be all decked out for the holiday in a country Victorian Christmas theme. It will be lovely as we will arrive after dark and everything will be lit by candlelight, oil lamp, and hearth fire. Bring back the glory of an old fashioned Christmas with this adventure. There is a liberal amount of walking from building to building so that may &amp;quot;qualify&amp;quot; as our hike. ;-) Let's hope for snow on the ground to add to the beauty and to have actual horse drawn sleigh rides!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The text from the OSV event posting:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Escape the frenzy of a modern Christmas with an enchanted evening of gingergbread, roasted chestnuts, music, dance, and a sleigh ride (weather permitting). Meet Father Christmas and chat with Santa Claus (bring your camera!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover the history of Christmas cards, exchanging gifts, hanging stockings, Christmas trees, mistletoe, holly, poinsettias, and candy canes. You'll learn about these traditions and more! Taste samples of foods long associated with the holiday and hear sounds of the season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy dinner at the &lt;b&gt;Oliver Wight Tavern&lt;/b&gt; during Christmas by Candlelight evenings. Menu:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.osv.org/docs/Christmas_by_Candlelight_Menu_2010.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.osv.org/do...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Highlights and displays&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.osv.org/docs/CBCHighlights" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.osv.org/do...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Performances anticipated by&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;Worcester Men of Song&lt;br /&gt;Elm Street Handbells&lt;br /&gt;Leicester Town Band&lt;br /&gt;Tantasqua Brass Quintet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets for this program are on sale online NOW (at the OSV site)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;u&gt;Please note on your RSVP after you have purchased your tickets&lt;/u&gt;.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will close at 9:00 PM. I will likely stay to the end as I love Christmas! Gates actually open at 4:00 PM but I think it is best to arrive in the dark for best effect. :-) Meet outside just before the ticket building just off of the parking area so we can enter together. We can stay as a group or wander off if you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$14 admission ($12 for OSV members); children under 3 are free. Order on the OSV event page (below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children are very welcome for the event. No pets are allowed. Arrive in a festive spirit! :-D&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; to Old Sturbridge Village (1 Stallion Hill Rd., Sturbridge, MA):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Old+Sturbridge+Village&amp;amp;city=Sturbridge%2C+Town+Of&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=Stallion+Hill+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=01518&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.11003&amp;amp;longitude=-72.09961&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=1027328963" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat=42.11003, Long=-72.09961]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information (&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;and to order tickets online for 12/18/10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;)&lt;/b&gt; for Christmas by Candlelight:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.osv.org/orders/listprograms.html?ID=8" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.osv.org/or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;(scroll to the bottom of the OSV page for ticket purchase.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Video of past Christmas by Candlelight celebration:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=46muDMuBFzg&amp;amp;feature=player_embedded" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information&lt;/b&gt; about Old Sturbridge Village:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Old_Sturbridge_Village" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Old Sturbridge Village website&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.osv.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.osv.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet in ticket building off of parking area. I'll look like my picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292883034000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289773777000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Christmas by Candlelight at Old Sturbridge Village in Sturbridge MA</name><id>15445720</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292709600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15445720/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/4/global_10748196.jpeg</photo_url></item>