<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From the Coolidge Corner website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;World Cinema - Croatia&lt;br /&gt;With a long tradition of strong cinema, Croatia has recently emerged as a popular travel destination with a burgeoning art and film culture, including several film festivals. This series reflects the best from all genres in recent years. From drama to comedy, from features to documentaries ? all films showcase passion and creativity recognized by the worlds? critics with numerous awards at international festivals, including a recent Academy Award nomination. This unique project is a result of a creative collaboration between The Coolidge Corner Theater, The Doors Art Foundation, The New England Friends of Croatia, the Croatian author and film critic Jurica Pavicic, and the featured distribution companies and Croatian filmmakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films at 12pm in Moviehouse 2 unless otherwise noted. Programs subject to change.&lt;br /&gt;Films are in Croatian with English subtitles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket Price: $10/$7.50 Seniors (62+) and Children&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Here's a description of the film also from the website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BORDER POST (Karaula)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, February 24, 2008 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At a small border-post on the Yugoslav-Albanian border, yet another generation of soldiers suffering the usual amount of boredom awaits the end of their service. It is the spring of 1987 and these are the last days of the country called Yugoslavia. Yet no one knew at the time. Daily routine of the army is disrupted by unusual circumstances. Frustrated and always drunk, lieutenant Safet Pasic feels a strange pain in his groins. He seeks help from the only doctor among the soldiers, Sinisa Sircevic, who finds out, very discretely, that it's a sexually transmitted disease. Not wishing his wife to know about it and trying to find excuses not to go home, Pasic declares a state of emergency, claiming that the Albanian army is preparing an attack against Yugoslavia. A joke transforms into war hysteria: soldiers dig trenches, Pasic grows wilder as days go by, Sinisa embarks on a dangerous liaison, and his best friend Ljuba Paunovic makes an unconditional decision to leave the army. The situation slowly runs out of control...Speaking about not so distant past with no nostalgia and no hatred, Border Post is a comedy about people on the verge of tragedy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Rajko Grili&amp;#263;, 1h45m, In Croatian w/ English subtitles&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll  be standing near the front with my Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We'll have a good time conversing afterwards at a local restaurant about what we thought of the movie.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201912519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Border Post at the Coolidge Corner Theatre</name><id>7244391</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203872400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7244391/</event_url></item>