<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Exchange St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01901</zip><lat>42.463640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>LynnArts</name><city>Lynn</city><id>1063251</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.943257</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We're having a Halloween-themed shoot with models, costumes, and unique face painting by &lt;a href="http://www.modelmayhem.com/roustan" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Roustan&lt;/a&gt;.  Shooting will be from 3-5 pm in the Neal Rantoul Vault Theater at LynnArts.  Studio lighting will be provided.  Some sets will be lit with (non-strobe) stage lighting; feel free to bring your on-camera strobes if you will prefer strobe lighting for those sets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are expecting the following models at the shoot:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/home.php#/eleanor.taormina" target="_blank"&gt;Eleanor Taormina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.modelmayhem.com/jojo76" target="_blank"&gt;Jo-Jo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Luz Batista&lt;br /&gt;Ida&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.modelmayhem.com/888108" target="_blank"&gt;Charlie&lt;/a&gt; (tentative)&lt;br /&gt;A couple of other models may also be present; watch this space for updates!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costumes will include a sexy pirate costume, sheer black kimono, Japanese wedding kimono, and Japanese swords, all complemented with matching faces by Roustan.  This will be a good shoot to get those unusual images that make your portfolio stand out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All photographers, models, &lt;b&gt;and&lt;/b&gt; makeup artists from this group are welcome and invited to attend.  You're welcome to arrive any time after 2pm, and indeed we could use a couple of hands before the shoot to help set up, so please do come early if you can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographers will be asked to pay a $40 fee.  If you just want to stop by and meet people, there is no charge, but in that case please sign up for the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/calendar/11655073/"&gt;Meet and Greet&lt;/a&gt; meetup description so we know what to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP now so we can gauge the interest in this event and know what mix of talented individuals from this group would like to attend.  As a comment on your RSVP, please indicate whether you want to attend as a photographer, a model, makeup artist, just to meet people, or in some other capacity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ichi</member_name><member_id>6271486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266081917000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers, Models &amp; MUA</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonportraitphotographers</urlname><id>830833</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Portrait Photographers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252723885000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halloween Theme Shoot</name><id>11351927</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256410800000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/events/11351927/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/9/a/global_11007738.jpeg</photo_url></item>