<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>580 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350250</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>553775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You may have heard of a monthly ride called &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Critical&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Mass.  Critical Mass is a leaderless bike ride that wanders through the streets of Boston and the surrounding neighborhoods.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many people feel that the Critical Mass bike ride does more harm than good for the cycling community because the mass will cork motorist traffic, and not obey the laws of the road...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A brand new group ride is being created called COURTEOUS MASS!  It will essentially be the same principal as Critical Mass (lots of fun, safety in numbers, party on two wheels, etc) except that we will stop at red lights and not cause any unnecessary tension between cars and riders.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You now have a chance to help make this idea take flight, because the very first ride will be Friday August 8th @ 5:30pm (ride leaves at 6) meet in Copley Square near the big fountain.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to be creative with your bike, attire, boombox, etc... I have seen riders of Critical Mass strap an upside down bucket to their bike and jam on it with some drumsticks.  Just because we are following the rules doesn't mean it cant be fun.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see you there!  &lt;br /&gt;- Jon&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Orange Messenger Bag / Brown Bike with Blue Wheels</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Ramos</member_name><member_id>4466935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218423309000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217506527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*Courteous* Mass</name><id>8447439</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218231000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/8447439/</event_url></item>