<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>road is on the east side of Rt. 116 in Easton. </address_2><address_1>Reel Brook Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03580</zip><lat>44.128406</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Reel Brook Trailhead</name><city>Easton</city><id>1101621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.786071</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a AT section hike to Mount Wolf (NH52 with a view list 3478'&lt;br /&gt;)...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; which provides good views to Franconia Ridge, brooks, and rock scrambles. It follows Reel Brook Trail all the way to its end and then turns right to follow Kinsman Ridge Trail to Mount Wolf. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The return trip is via the same route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trails:&lt;/b&gt; Reel Brook Trail, Kinsman Ridge Trail, Appalachian Trail&lt;br /&gt; Central West White Mountain National Forest,  Cannon-Kinsman Region&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hike distance&lt;/b&gt; 9.6 miles,   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation Gain&lt;/b&gt; 2200 Feet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book time Average:&lt;/b&gt;  6 hrs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rating:&lt;/b&gt;  Moderate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route Summary    &lt;br /&gt;• Start on Reel Brook Trail and follow it for 1.3 miles, crossing a few small streams en route.&lt;br /&gt;• The trail will then turn left to join a wide logging road which emerges beneath some power lines after 100 yards. On the way back be careful not to miss this turn off the logging road and back onto the trail - it is marked by a small faded brown sign with a yellow arrow - but you may still be tempted to keep on hiking down the wide logging road if you're not paying attention.&lt;br /&gt;• Cross the power line clearing at a diagonal beneath the lines on a wide, mowed/flattened path to hook up with another woods path on the other side. &lt;br /&gt;• Continue on Reel Brook Trail for another 0.6 mile. You will cross a tributary once and Reel Brook three times. After the third crossing follow the trail to the right on a logging road.&lt;br /&gt;• A half-mile beyond the third brook crossing, go straight while the logging road veers off to the left; and then 100 yards later bear right at another logging road intersection.&lt;br /&gt;• One more mile of climbing up Reel Brook Trail will bring you to a T-junction with Kinsman Ridge Trail which is also the Appalachian Trail (AT).&lt;br /&gt;• Turn right onto Kinsman Ridge Trail/Appalachian Trail and follow it for 1.9 miles. At this point the path widens a bit and there's a white &amp;quot;Kinsman Ridge Trail&amp;quot; sign with arrows pointing in both directions. Opposite this sign, is the barely noticeable and unsigned spur path to the Mount Wolf outlook.&lt;br /&gt;• Turn left onto the spur path and follow it for 60 yards to reach the east knob of Mount Wolf.&lt;br /&gt;• Return via the same route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Driving Directions &lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Reel Brook Trailhead is located in Easton, New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 116:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn onto Reel Brook Road which is on the east side of Rt. 116 in Easton. This turn-off is marked by a hiker sign and is on the right, 3.7 miles north of the junction of Routes 112 and 116; or on the left 1.1 miles south of Easton's town hall.&lt;br /&gt;    * Reel Brook Road isn't plowed in the winter and is rough even in the summer.&lt;br /&gt;    * Follow Reel Brook Road for 0.6 mile, until you see another hiker sign, then take a left  into a small field that serves as a parking area. WATCH FOR ROCKS This will probably be no problem for SUV's, but cars with low underbodies need to be very careful of all the rocks popping out of the ground. Once you get past the entry way, the field itself is much smoother.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow Reel Brook Road for 0.6 mile, until you see another hiker sign, then take a left  into a small field that serves as a parking area. Look For our bumber stickers.  Diane 603-477-5116</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258816152000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256341711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Wolf   NH52 with a view list    3478'...</name><id>11697415</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258291800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11697415/</event_url></item>