<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Situated on 24 acres of woods and meadows in central Massachusetts, Cornerstone Ranch allows riders to savor the colors and smells of New England with a two-hour guided trail ride led by farm owner Sue Connell. From the commanding view afforded by long-legged steeds, riders journey along the meandering trails traversing the ranch, taking in sweeping pastures and dense foliage while receiving instruction on mare-maneuvering basics from the guide and the guide's talking horse. Cornerstone Ranch houses an assortment of safe, tranquil horses fit for riders of any age, experience level, or cowboy-hat fluid capacity. Please note that the weight limit for their trail rides is 260 lbs and is limited to one rider per horse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trail ride is approximately two hours long and costs $70 per person (unless you have a Groupon that will cut that price in half to $35.)  Typical trail ride gratuity is 15%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;To sign up for the ride:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Go to their website: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://cornerstoneranch.org" class="linkified"&gt;http://cornerstoneranch.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Click on the 'Check Availability/Make a Reservation' button&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Press the Book button for the 'Beautiful Two Hour Guided Trail Ride'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Select &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Sunday, May 6th&lt;/span&gt; on the calendar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Select the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;1:00PM&lt;/span&gt; slot and press the Continue button at bottom of page&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Continue past the Options page&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-On the Rates Detail page, enter your Groupon number (without dashes) into the Discount box if you are using a Groupon. (This is very important because this is the only page to enter it. Your amount should then be reduced to 0.00).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Press the Continue button to advance to the Customer Information page. Fill in information and press Continue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-You should get a confirmation once all done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; If you are paying by Groupon please remember to bring your Groupon paper with you to the ranch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you have any problems in signing up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at ranch.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam</member_name><member_id>8861556</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336435469000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333204455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Horseback Riding in Princeton, MA</name><id>58648822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336323600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/58648822/</event_url></item>