<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1019 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06405</zip><lat>41.281631</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Branford Green </name><city>Branford</city><id>963428</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.811409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Branford is once again hosting several talented and staged Jazz evenings for the next nine Thursdays&lt;br /&gt;following opening night of Thursday July 1st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The music is always good, the weather will change but can be so delicious when you catch one of those perfect balmy summer evenings . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your pic-i-nic basket or grab some take out on the way over,  your cooler ( discreet alcohol consumption is permitted), your chair, a friend or two and lets all laugh and breathe and enjoy . ..despite the stresses of the day . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starts at 6;30pm and does not go very late, but should be very fun and relaxing night,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you here!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glennn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info for this weeks scheduled performance ( subject to change)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Marshak - Smooth Jazz - August 5!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Marshak’s live shows overflow with passion, energy, crowd interaction and intensity, as the guitarist throws a series of blues, rock, soul and jazz licks. Now, one of the freshest faces on the contemporary jazz scene has captured the flavor of his popular live shows with his fourth major release, The Family Funktion.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A native of Long Island, Marshak grew up on rock ‘n’ roll music in a home full of musicians. Passing guitarists inspired his muse, and in high school he honed his chops with three well-respected teachers: Joseph “Joey” Casciano, Mike Orioles and Richard Rabatin. They all inspired in him a lifelong commitment to his craft, while Rabatin in particular turned him on to the contemporary jazz and blues guitar sounds of Larry Carlton, George Benson and Robben Ford. While attending college at SUNY Geneseo, Matt had the opportunity to play with a blues and R&amp;amp;B group, as well as connecting and improvising with straight-ahead jazz saxophonist Joseph Yoon. Once out of college, Marshak performed a variety of musical styles with New York’s top original bands and artists, even drawing praise from Deep Purple’s legendary guitarist Ritchie Blackmore.  We can't wait to hear him on the Branford Green!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also hear Matt Marshak's tracks on Blue Plate Radio!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>probably some type of purple balloon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glennn</member_name><member_id>8036405</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281050877000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275506526000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday night JAZZ series on the Branford Green</name><id>jnwsnynlbhb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281046500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/13674408/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_3095463.jpeg</photo_url></item>