<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06415</zip><lat>41.574399</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-537-5755</phone><name>Cafe on Main</name><city>Colchester</city><id>1064448</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.332402</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I typically don't like to stay out late on a weeknight but for THIS, I'm making an exception! I recently saw Bruce Jacques perform and he had everyone on their feet, singing, dancing and laughing all at the same time! Not only is Bruce a great musician, he's hysterical and a riot to watch. If you love music and laughter as much as I do, consider going into work late on Friday ~ trust me, it's worth it! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's plan on meeting there for dinner at 8:00 and Bruce will perform from 9:30 - 12:30. (I know, it's late, but step out of the box and live a little!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce's career started in 1977. He played in several bands until going out on his own as a solo artist at age 19. Using the latest synthesizers and computers along with his guitar and live vocals he produces the sound of a four or five piece band. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce incorporates comedy spoofs on artists such as Devo, Guns and Roses, Britney Spears and many more. His repertoire is a mix of songs everyone knows by heart from the sixties to today's top hits. He also involves the audience with a six foot L.E.D. light board that displays the words for sing-a-longs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce's ability to connect with audiences of all ages, through all moods and in all types of settings, is something that comes only with years of experience. He also possesses the natural ability to make people feel comfortable - to make them laugh, sing, and dance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out his website at: www.brucejacques.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews: &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...Bruce was captivating - he had the whole audience laughing and singing music from the 60s to today... 3 hours later we were ready to take up a collection to keep in playing longer!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll email my cell # to all "Yes" RSVP's the day before</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254525824000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253447810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner &amp; Live Entertainment w/Bruce Jacques</name><id>11418150</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253836800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/11418150/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/5/global_10794837.jpeg</photo_url></item>