<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Real Estate Investor,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you one of the millions of wanna be investors that are afraid to death to buy a house in this terrible market because you think you can’t sell it?   Have you shut down your buying machine because selling with sub prime financing was you exit strategy?  Is first time buyer financing a mystery to you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you answered yes to any of the three questions above then you are in luck. On Monday night February 28th, 2008, from 9am to 4pm, the nations leading expert, Robyn Thompson and her top selling realtor Lena de Matos will be teaching Robyn’s students, The 9 Marketing Strategies to Sell a House in a Depressed Real Estate Economy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who don’t know this dynamic team, Robyn invested in Waterbury and Meridan for over 13 years and has bought, renovated and sold 276 houses. She made millions in CT when Waterbury went through the tough times, two mayors arrested, huge tax hikes, and a near bankruptcy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The good news is Robyn knows how to sell houses when times are tough and she plans on giving you all the strategies to get your phone ringing off the hook with qualified buyers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn has asked her top selling realtor, Lena de Matos to join her on the teleconference call. Lena has been a top producing selling realtor for over a decade and has sold over 500 homes.  She knows how to sell houses at lightening speed in a down market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=127" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=127" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctreia.com/eve...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234820769000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230530075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>All Day Seminar with Robyn Thompson</name><id>9400405</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233151200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/9400405/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/4/global_6764372.jpeg</photo_url></item>