<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>91 Shelton Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.404.5166</phone><name>CT Rock Gym</name><city>New Haven</city><id>441780</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919998</lon></venue><fee><label>Daily climbing pass</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>13.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come and enjoy some rock climbing at the &lt;a href="http://www.ctrockgym.com/membership.php" target="_blank"&gt;CT Rock Gym&lt;/a&gt; in New Haven.  An all day pass is $13, and equipment rental is $7.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Saturday December 1st, 2007&lt;br /&gt;Where: CT Rock Gym in New Haven (&lt;a href="http://www.ctrockgym.com/directions.php" target="_blank"&gt;directions&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be starting bright and early at 9am, and climbing until lunch time, and perhaps circling back after grabbing something to eat (New Haven pizza, perhaps?).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear clothing you can be flexible in and thin socks (for the climbing shoes).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't know how to climb, that's no big deal (we all have to learn some time!).  However, if you've never belayed before (held the rope for someone), we'll work some instruction in.  If you need instruction belaying, CT Rock Gym will have certified instructors teach you, show you some basic climbing techniques, and let you loose in the gym with rented equipment for $35 and about an hour and a half of your time.  They will allow people to climb (but not belay) without being belay certified.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to meetup location via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=19+Shelton+Ave.&amp;amp;city=New+Haven&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leader on this one is &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/4429379/"&gt;Adam Skinner&lt;/a&gt;, so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196690813000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196336968000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT Rock Gym visit in New Haven CT</name><id>6823952</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196517600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6823952/</event_url></item>