<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rte 185</address_2><address_1>130 hartford rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06070</zip><lat>41.842920</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>Hike to top</phone><name>Heubelin Tower/Talcott Mountain</name><city>Simsbury</city><id>333458</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.792090</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summer is getting shorter..&lt;br /&gt;Ok if you are not into hiking, its about 30 minutes to the top and staying till a bit after sunset then going to a interesting location afterward by the fire pit.. Please concider Betsy's Movie event..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its almost impossible to get me inside on a nice night while its summer out..its half over..remember that...&lt;br /&gt;Then i do inside things..as i will guess you will too.. but its good to have options here at Meetup.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO, wouldn't it be nice to have a short hike to a nice flat area near the first set of open area at the top path of the Heublin Tower (Talcott Mountain) for a small dinner, snacks and wine (other beverage too for non wino's) for a sunset socializing event? &lt;br /&gt;If we want we can go to all the way to the tower and sit on real picknick benches...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can't stay up there too much past sunset since there is the trip to the bottom..its still ok as the light drops though..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;Look for the signs for Talcott Mountain/Hebulin Tower State Park area (south side of rte 185), its right across from Penwood State Forest if you missed it.. &lt;br /&gt;Go up the entrance way for a short distance, you will see the parking area off to the right across from the trail head on the left. I will have the blue Toyota Avalon.with a orange traffic cone ner the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since there are many different routs to here.. &lt;br /&gt;Please check your maps. &lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest, GPS or others, 130 Hartford Road (rte 185), Simsbury, CT will get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warning...at most of our events someone complains that we are enjoying ourselves at the end location..so either the fire department, police or other people show up..but when they see people their parents age..we just say &amp;quot;you dont have enough room for our canes , walkers , and heart attack pains, etc.to even think of arresting senior citezens and causing a death in that patroll car..we bruize easily and police brutality is a hot issue now a days..&amp;quot;cops beat seniours to death over little peaceful gathering&amp;quot; and the fire is an appliance thats fed by propane..&amp;quot; yep..that will make the news alright...&lt;br /&gt;are you ready for some enjoyment ???&lt;br /&gt;We usually are left alone or they feel sorry for us geezers...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186095275000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185672143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>&lt;Winoe's on the Mountain&gt; a Sunset at Talcott Mountain/Heubelin Tower</name><id>6091892</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185921900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6091892/</event_url></item>