<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>450 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363593</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-9278</phone><name>Central Square Theater</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1044961</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100953</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Before Orchids to Octopi: An Evolutionary Love Story &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/12689227/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; there will be a Pre-Performance Symposium for all ticket holders starting at 7:00 pm with the co-author who literally wrote the book on Biology, Joe Levine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Orchids to Octopi site:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://centralsquaretheater.org/season/09-10/orchidsoctopi_auxiliary.html"&gt;http://centralsquaret...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Resistance to Darwin&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;How do we explain and respond to denials in history and science?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With Joseph Levine, Co-author of [Prentice Hall's] &lt;i&gt;Biology&lt;/i&gt;; Science educator &amp;amp; consultant John Durant, Director, MIT Museum [moderating]&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at Central Square Theater &lt;br /&gt;450 Massachusetts Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA 02139 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's grab seats at 6:40 pm. T.J. Maher should be waiting outside the theater by 6:30 pm. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Joe Levine, from his Bio at Pearson Training:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mypearsontraining.com/pdfs/TG_MLBio_AboutAuthors.pdf"&gt;http://www.mypearsont...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Joe Levine earned his PhD at Harvard University. His research has been published in scientific journals ranging from Science to Scientific American, as well as in several academic books. He has taught introductory biology, ecology, marine biology, neurobiology, and coral reef biology at Boston College and the Boston University Marine Biology Program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Also a broadcast journalist, Joe has dedicated himself to improving the public understanding of science. He has written for magazines such as Smithsonian, GEO, and Natural History. He has produced radio segments for National Public Radio and has acted as a scientific advisor for public broadcasting at WGBH in Boston. At WGBH, he has worked on NOVA and other PBS series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joe Levine, About Writing Miller &amp;amp; Levine &lt;i&gt;Biology&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'Every now and then somebody will ask me, ‘Tell me the truth. Did you guys really write this book?’ And I look them straight in the eye, and I say ‘Yes we did; Ken Miller and I wrote every word that is in this textbook.’ We have worked for more hours than either we, or our families, would actually care to tell you about, to get this right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'The reason we do that is because we started out in the process of writing these biology programs because we firmly believe that biology is the most exciting discipline in the sciences, and that there has never been a more exciting time, or a more important time, to study biology than right now.' &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Central Square Theater&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.goldstar.com/events/cambridge-ma/from-orchids-to-octopi-an-evolutionary-love-story.html"&gt;http://www.goldstar.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Central Square Theater is home to Underground Railway Theater (URT) and The Nora Theatre Company, two professional theater companies with a combined track record of over 48 years of excellence. URT has a 29 year history of connecting high quality professional theater with communities, performing new plays for young audiences, families and adults, and teaching through its rigorous education programming. Combining actors, puppetry and music, URT reaches out to and engages diverse audiences with performances of great beauty and compelling social content. During The Nora's 19 years, audiences and the media have recognized it for its exceptionally high quality work. Mission-driven to bring cutting-edge, thought- provoking, and contemporary productions to New England audiences, The Nora has introduced local audiences to Boston, New England, and/or world premieres. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271113373000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270139473000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joe Levine, writer of Biology,Pre-Performance Symposium @ Central Square Theater</name><id>13058943</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270940400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13058943/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/2/6/global_14063926.jpeg</photo_url></item>