<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>48 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.358219</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kresge Little Theater (W16-35)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1244639</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094804</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come to MIT's Stratton Student Center, grabbing something to eat on the first floor and join us at the tables on the second floor! See &amp;quot;Where to Meet&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update:&lt;/b&gt;: Tickets are $15.00 each, unless you are a student, and according to Stacy Rahaim who saw the show earlier, the box office is CASH ONLY. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Didn't reserve your ticket yet? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Evil Dead: The Musical's Ticket Reservation page, &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/mtg/www/TicketReservations.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mt...&lt;/a&gt; the Friday performance is sold out, but don't despair if you have not yet reserved your ticket because... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[A] number of tickets are held for purchase at the door only, and in addition, many reservations are made that are never picked up. Therefore, we have a waiting list for these tickets. Usually, everyone on the waiting list is able to get into the show, some of them in very good seats. While we can make no guarantees, we hope to once again accommodate everyone interested in the show. To put your name on the waiting list, please send e-mail to our box office manager. Please let us know which performance you are interested in attending, and how many tickets you will need. Arrive at the performance at least 15 minutes before curtain and check in at the box office mtg-tickets@mit.edu . We will begin releasing seats that have not been picked up to the waiting list, in order, 10 minutes prior to the performance&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From MIT's Musical Theater Guild (MTG) website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/mtg/www/CurrentShow.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mt...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What the F@#k Was That? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;That's was people all over the world have been saying after seeing &lt;b&gt;Evil Dead: The Musical&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This hilarious live stage show takes all the elements of the cult classic horror films, Evil Dead 1, Evil Dead 2, and Army of Darkness then combines them to make one of the craziest theatrical experiences of all time. Five college students go to an abandoned cabin in the woods, and accidentally unleash an evil force that turns them all into demons. It's all up to Ash (a housewares employee, turned demon killing hero), and his trusty chainsaw to save the day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Blood flies. Limbs are dismembered. Demons are telling bad jokes... and all to music. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;You don't need to be a fan of Evil Dead to love this show. You don't need to be a fan of horror to love this show. You don't even need to be a fan of musicals to love this show. As long as you like having fun... this show is for you. [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Note - This show contains blood, gore, sex, violence, bad language, and very bad puns&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Most of the cast in this production appear to be MIT students and alumni &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/mtg/www/ProdStaff.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mt...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;To reserve your ticket&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Go to &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/mtg/www/TicketReservations.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mt...&lt;/a&gt; and fill out the reservation form&lt;br /&gt;* Fill out the information, placing the words &amp;quot;No Splash Zone&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;Special Needs&amp;quot; if you do not want to sit in the splash zone.  &lt;br /&gt;* Add &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;I am with Nerd Fun&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;Special Needs&amp;quot; and they will seat us together in the Assigned Seating. Heh. This cracks me up! ;) &lt;br /&gt;* Select the Friday April 30th 8:00 pm show&lt;br /&gt;* We will need to bring a printed copy of the confirmation letter to the box office and purchase the tickets at least 15 minutes ahead of time. If we get 10 or more Nerd Fun people maybe we can get the group discount (whatever it is) and not pay the $15.00 for the general public. &lt;br /&gt;* Update your Nerd Fun RSVP so we know who is definitely coming. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Warning: Splash zone ahead!&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever sit in the first row of a Gallagher concert, featuring the amazing sledge-o-matic? Or in the first few rows of a Blue Man Group concert with paint splashing about? Buckets and buckets and buckets of fake blood will be sprayed all over you if you sit in the &amp;quot;Splash Zone&amp;quot;. Go ahead. Sit there. You will be doing a great duty and will be the human shield for the rest of us. Me, I'll be sitting a few rows in the back. There seems to be a LOT of fake blood according to the YouTube video, not a one time occurance. Zombies will stagger to you and purposefully spray blood on you. Take a look at the Calgary production of the musical &lt;a href="http://www.evildeadthemusical.com/site/splatter-zone" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.evildeadth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grab food on the first floor of the Stratton Student Center and come up to the second floor to join T.J. Maher before the show! He should be there by 5:45 pm. Feel free to drop by at any time. We should probably leave by 7:15 pm since we should be getting to the box office to pick up tickets by 7:30 pm. Red Meetup signs will be on the table. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Stratton Student Center is at 84 Massachusetts Ave in Cambridge, MA &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/campus-activities/www/html/studentcenterinformation.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/ca...&lt;/a&gt; and has many places to grab food on the first floor. See &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=W20" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt; and select &amp;quot;More&amp;quot; to see the places to eat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. is 5 foot 7 with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Official Evil Dead: The Musical Site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.evildeadthemusical.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.evildeadth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the official site of &lt;b&gt;Evil Dead: The Musical&lt;/b&gt; you can listen to music (such as those all time classics &amp;quot;Cabin in the Woods&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Housewares Employee&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;What the F was that?&amp;quot;), watch videos of performances, and see little promo clip about the media talking about the show. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evil Dead: The Musical even had it's own Youtube page featuring the amazing Bruce Campbell (who was the star of the original Evil Dead series, for those who never saw these funny B rated films directed by Sam Raimi). &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/evildeadvideos?gl=CA&amp;amp;hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;History of the Show:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.evildeadthemusical.com/site/history" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.evildeadth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Many musicals nowadays are based on movies. But Evil Dead The Musical is the only musical in history to be based on a series of movies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dating back to 1981, the Evil Dead films combined to make one of the most beloved cult franchises in the history of cinema. Directed by Sam Raimi (Spiderman), and starring cult icon Bruce Campbell, these movies used comedy, gore, slapstick, blood, one-liners, and some of the most creative camera techniques ever seen to revolutionize the horror genre. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Some might have looked at these films, and never thought they could be combined into a musical... but that didn’t stop a group of ambitious young people in Toronto from giving it a try. And in August, 2003, in the back room of a small bar called the Tranzac Club, Evil Dead The Musical made its debut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] in November, 2006, Evil Dead The Musical made its Off-Broadway debut in New York City where it was praised by both the fans and critics alike. The cast album from the show even debuted at #4 on the Billboard Show Charts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] With the success of the show in Toronto, productions began springing up all over the world. Seoul, Tokyo, Cleveland, Calgary, California, Kalimazoo, and so many more locations... wherever there were theatre fans twisted enough to want some blood with their musicals, there was bound to be a production&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This might be Christian Hegg's (Ash, in this production) website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newenglandfilm.com/user/39992?mini=events/calendar/2010/05/all" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newengland...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Kresge building (W16):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The building itself, with it's rear entrance at 48 Massachusetts Ave., Cambridge, MA is 1/8th of a sphere. To me, it looks like Lex Luthor and the Legion of Doom is planning a nefarious plot vs the Superfriends. The Kresge Little Theater (W16-35) has a maximum of 130 seats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Musical Theatre Guild:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://theaterarts.mit.edu/home.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://theaterarts.mi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The MIT Musical Theatre Guild is the oldest and largest theatre organization at MIT, and we are entirely student-run! Formed from the merger of the MIT Gilbert and Sullivan Society, the Classical Musical Society, and the Tech Show Society in 1971, we produce a wide variety of Musical Theatre. We perform four shows a year so there is plenty of opportunity to act, sing, dance, tech, design, direct, and produce. So, if you want to be part of a great art form, come investigate MTG!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;MIT makes some lots available for visitors after 5pm, and lists them on an MIT Parking and Transportation web page &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/facilities/transportation/parking/visitors/public_parking.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/fa...&lt;/a&gt; . Your best possibilities are either the West Annex, located on Vassar just west of the garage, or East Lot, located at the corner of Vassar and Main. There is also a small for-pay lot at the corner of Mass Ave and Vassar St, and a garage next to the University Park Hotel just off of Mass Ave about four blocks north of MIT&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map to the Kresge Auditorium, where the Little Theater is located:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?selection=W16" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272935837000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271178599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Evil Dead: The Musical @ Kresge Little Theater, MIT</name><id>13170968</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272672000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13170968/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/global_14358269.jpeg</photo_url></item>