<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>268 Park Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.310808</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-772-3210</phone><name>The Thomas E. Golden , Jr. Center</name><city>New Haven</city><id>915430</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.932195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event is an open invitation from fellow NHC member Michael about an upcoming charity event.  See details below (from Michael)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I would like to invite all of you to the annual Songs For Soup benefit taking place at The Thomas E. Golden, Jr. Center of Saint Thomas More Chapel, the Catholic Chapel &amp;amp; Center at Yale University. The Golden Center is located in downtown New Haven at 268 Park Street betwen Chapel and Broadway. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the past 25 years the church has run a soup kitchen for some of the neediest residents of New Haven.  Currently, the soup kitchen feeds on average of 250 adults, children, and families every Wednesday.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;On Wednesday April 1st, St. Thomas More will be holding its annual &amp;quot;Songs for Soup&amp;quot; benefit which is the yearly fundraiser to support the operating expenses of the soup kitchen, as well as the Social Justice ministry program of the Chapel.  All of the money raised through the sale of soup, baked goods, and the silent auctions will go to the soup kitchen and Social Justice curriculum.  Through the curriculum Yale students volunteer in service trips to communities in need, build houses for Habitat for Humanity, and tutor children in New Haven schools.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The schedule for the benefit is listed below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00pm Simple Soup Dinner and Benefit Auction Preview&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm-8:00pm Concert and Benefit Auction w/ Intermission&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On hand will be a variety of items to bid on if you are interested, many of which are donated by local businesses from New Haven.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entertainment will be provided by a number of the performing groups from Yale University.  In the past, it has been a wonderful event,  and I hope that you will consider attending in support of some of New Haven neediest residents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is free, though they are asking for a good will donation at the door.&lt;br /&gt;There is a small fee for the soup dinner and/or if you wish to bid on any of the auction items&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further information, see this link &lt;a href="http://www.yale.edu/stm/documents/s4s2009poster.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to call Michael with any questions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see some of you there.  It will be a kid friendly event!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Contact for this event is : Michael Joyce  (203) 675-1179&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238796846000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238183858000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Songs for Soup Benefit Concert</name><id>10051315</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238623200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/10051315/</event_url></item>