<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>DETAILS FOR THE MEETUP ON FRIDAY - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at Troquet at 8:30pm to get the group together and to have drinks before the show.  Troquet is a French restaurant located at 140 Boylston St, nearby the Estate.  There is a bar area right when you walk into Troquet, and we will meet in this bar area.  We will leave for the Estate by 9:30pm for the Oakenfold show.  Please meet us at Troquet as you may not be able to find us at the Estate - that place gets very crowded!  My picture is located on the left side of the nightlife website, and my cell phone is 646.541.0708.  Give me a call if you problems finding the group.  See you on Friday!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Looks like tickets are sold out for Friday's show.  If you did not get one, you may want to call The Estate directly.  They MIGHT be selling tickets at the door, but it will be expen$ive.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the great house DJs of our time will be in Boston on Friday, March 14, at The Estate.  This is a rare event as world famous international DJs do not visit Boston that often!  Tickets are already $40 each, and the prices will be going up every week, so buy your tix now!  More details about the meetup will follow soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do not know Paul Oakenfold, I encourage you to visit youtube.com and type in his name and listen to some tracks.  His music has been used in countless movies, commercials, etc.  If you are into electronic music and house, this is your night, so break out the dancing shoes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are balking at the ticket price, think about it this way:  The Estate normally charges $20 cover to get in anyway.  It is also the newest and largest venue in town.  For an extra $20 more, you get to experience a legendary, world-renowned DJ.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: Link to buy tickets - Looks like tickets are sold out for this show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as this is an upscale venue.  If traveling by T, Boylston T is the closest stop on the green line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**On a side note, please look on the message board for Meetup Etiquette and other thoughts about the group**&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the site.  Call my cell if you have questions or trouble finding the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205806138000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><why>The best ticket in town that night!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204005181000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paul Oakenfold @ The Estate! Friday, Mar 14th!!</name><id>7409740</id><headcount>42</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205542800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/7409740/</event_url></item>