<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>North Pier at Christopher Columbus Park</address_2><address_1>66 Long Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359885</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston's Best Cruises</name><city>Boston</city><id>1270679</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050082</lon></venue><fee><label>administrative Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;ISLAND BACKGROUND&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Georges Island is dominated by historic Fort Warren, a Civil War-era fort known for its graceful granite archways and reputed ghost, the Lady in Black. The fort and its grassy parade ground are a popular place for a scenic low-stress walk. Take a ranger-guided tour. Picnic under a shade tree. See the ramparts or fish off the pier. Get exceptional views of the surrounding islands and Boston Light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Georges Island has toilet facilities, drinking water, food service and refreshments, and cooking grills. It’s a popular site for group events. We can help plan your company outing, wedding, or other event. As the central transportation hub to the islands, Georges Island is a frequent stop for the island ferries. And it provides a jumping-off point for other islands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few travel and meetup notes before we go: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Check the weather and dress appropriately for being out on the ocean and trekking around on the island. The forecast is calling for mostly cloudy and highs in the upper 70s but out on the ocean, it could get a little cool if it's windy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Bring a flashlight. We can go inside the fort and word is that there are some pretty DARK areas which actually could be fun to shoot in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Bring a tripod and flash for shooting inside the fort. Also bring extra batteries and cards. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; There are &amp;quot;facilities&amp;quot; on Georges and Spectacle island but there are no refreshment options on Georges due to the construction. Bring water and a light snack if you feel the need. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; We're going to start out on Georges Island but due to construction, we're going to spend part of the day there then transfer over to Spectacle Island for lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; There are several parking options in the area.  The garage closest to the Aquarium may not be the cheapest.  You can Google parking to find the best option for you.  Please be sure to leave a little extra travel time to deal with parking.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Travel On Saturday*** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Long Wharf North at 8:30 near the ticket booth. I believe that's on the Columbus Park side of the Marriott Hotel. Please leave time to park and find the ticket booth. You will have to check in at the booth to get on the boat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boat leaves at 9:00 AM sharp and we arrive at Georges Island at 9:20. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet back at the dock to take the *free* transfer boat over to Spectacle Island. We're going over on the 11:45 shuttle boat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have lunch and spend a little time on Spectacle Island then head back to Boston on the 2:15 boat to arrive at 2:40. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***IMPORTANT NOTE*** &lt;br /&gt;The boat company tells me all morning boats have been selling out. They recommend that we call in before Saturday to make a reservation. You will have to tell them what time you're going over, what time you're coming back and from which island. If for some reason you cannot get a booking on the 9:00 AM boat, drop me an email or call me to let me know so we'll know what time you're heading over. If you call tomorrow, you shouldn't have a problem. Remember: 9:00 AM to Georges Island and 2:15 from Spectacle Island. Adult tickets are $14.00 - the transfer ferry is free &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***IMPORTANT NUMBERS AND LINKS*** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Call the ranger line for island information: 617-223-8666 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Visit or call Boston’s Best Cruises—Harbor Islands Express for detailed inquiries about boat service: harborexpress.com or 617-222-6999 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Ferry Schedule... &lt;a href="http://www.bostonislands.com/ferry-schedule" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonisla...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Tickets: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonislands.com/tickets" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonisla...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Georges Island: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonislands.com/georges" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonisla...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Spectacle Island: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonislands.com/spectacle" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonisla...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;li&gt; My cell phone number is 617 794 8711. I will be available via email as well. On Saturday morning, I'll check it once around 7:00 AM for any updates from you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe RSVPs.... &lt;br /&gt;I will be printing a roster of folks who have confirmed that they're coming on Friday night. Please change your rsvp so I'll know your coming and so we can keep an eye out for you at the docks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to contact me if you have questions. Looking forward to Saturday's outing and seeing everyone! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take care... Dianne &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet near the ticket booth or check in gate.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>5274985</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277954431000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273693707000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Harbor:  Georges Island (formerly Peddocks Island)</name><id>13463985</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277555400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/13463985/</event_url></item>