<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Private Residence</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.362500</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Private </name><city>Wayland</city><id>12177072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.361946</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Buonasera....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I am pleased to announce that we have reached our limit of 12 participants for tomorrow's unique cooking lesson "Cucina e parla italiano".  We will be learning how to prepare and we will be making several typical Italian dishes with our hands, we will be enjoying 4 distinct wines selected to be paired with our "piatti"; we will be speaking, learning and practicing Italian through organized games and activities; and we will be treated to a live performance by a very talented jazz pianist who will be performing this summer at Umbria Jazz.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Most of the participants of this event are students in the Italian Program with a couple Meetup Members added to the mix.  Keep an eye out for future announcements for such events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;italianprogram@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Buonasera a tutti....&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;This is going out to all participants and "possible" participants for&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Saturday's Cooking Lesson/Event in Wayland.  There are now about 18 participants. They are mostly students in my Italian Program, but there is still room for more Meetup Members.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Thanks to all of the hard work that my wife does, you can all now pay&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;in advance for Saturday's Cooking Lesson to be held at a private&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;residence in Wayland.  I would really appreciate if you would&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;follow-up your initial verbal and written commitment to attending this&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;lesson/event with an actual advanced payment.  This would ensure us&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;and helps us prepare better for this event, knowing ahead of time that&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;there are committed participants.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;This is what you have to do:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;1. Go to my website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.italianprogram.com/Home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.italianprogram.com/Home.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;2. Click on the 'Italian Cooking Lessons' link:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.italianprogram.com/Italian_Cooking_Lessons.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.italianprogram.com/Italian_Cooking_Lessons.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;3. Click on the 'Upcoming Lessons' link:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.italianprogram.com/Upcoming_Lessons.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.italianprogram.com/Upcoming_Lessons.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;You will see a link to PayPal, where you can pay for the lesson&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;online.  Just choose either Group 1 (11:00-2:00 or Group 2 (4:00-7:00)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;and continue with your credit card payment.  I will be notified via&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;PayPal that you have signed-up and paid.  I would also appreciate an&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;email from you telling me that you have in fact gone ahead and made a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;payment for the event.  I will then in turn confirm with you that I&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;have in fact received it.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Once we have the minimum number of paid participants (we fully expect&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;to meet that number), you will be notified along with everybody else.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;I ask that you pay for this cooking lesson/event by Thursday, March 14&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;at the very latest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img src="https://mail.google.com/mail/u/0/images/cleardot.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #888888"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 John Jordan &lt;br /&gt;

 Language, Travel and Culture Exchange, LLC &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a&gt;(617) 233-9876&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="mailto:jjordan@italianprogram.com"&gt;jjordan@italianprogram.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://italianprogram.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://italianprogram.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buonasera a tutti...(or Buongiorno)....depends on when you read this....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had made an initial announcement 2-3 weeks ago about this very unique event that we would like to offer all of you. On Saturday, March 16th, my friend Federico Zampieri, Enrico Costa and I are going to be performing a unique cooking exhibition and Italian language lesson at a lovely private residence in Wayland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Federico, with whom I am working closely now, is a chef who now lives in the area with his wife and 2 children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Federico has worked as a chef for many years now, has had his own restaurant, and has also worked under the tutelage of some very important people in that field in Italy. I'll spare you his biography and resumè for another time. If you are interested in what he has done and where he has worked, I can probably ask him to put together a list for you. In any case, once he gets established here, he will be running his own "food" company and will be importing Italian products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His cooking style basically involves utilizing a special type of paper that wraps the food and minimizes cooking time while keeping the food tasty, healthy and nutritious. This technique also minimizes the need for cleaning, among other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enrico is a journalist and writer who is here in Boston for at least one year as his wife works at Boston University. Enrico also teaches Italian with me in the North End. All three of us are joining forces to help launch and establish a type of collaboration that runs deep and that will be long-lasting. Our other friend, and my primary assistant in the Italian Program, Sara Arduino, is also working with us. She is in the area because her husband works at MIT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, March 16th we are offering the following menu:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;antipasto: pepata di cozze &lt;br /&gt;

 primo: gnocchi burro e salvia &lt;br /&gt;

 secondo: pollo alla cacciatora &lt;br /&gt;

 contorno: peperonata &lt;br /&gt;

 dolce: tiramisù&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will learn and practice with your hands how to prepare all of these dishes, and you will obviously eat everything you make. There will be an abundance of wine included in the price. While you prepare food, sip wine, and learn about the technique, you will be involved in fun activities using the Italian language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am also hoping that one of my private Italian students, and Australian pianist named Sarah will be joining us and perform some songs for us live. She was invited to perform at the Umbria Jazz Fest in Italy this July. She has given me an initial YES about coming to the cooking lesson, but I will confirm that with you once I know for sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course/event will last no more than 3 hours and the cost will be $75.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are planning on having two shifts on Saturday. Shift #1 will be from 11:00-2:00 (lunch), while the second shift will be from 4:00-7:00 (dinner).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The limit for participants will be 12 for each shift.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in attending, I need to know asap, and I need to know which shift you would rather attend. I will need your name, email address and cell phone number. I will then add your name to an email list. There are already 7-8 students that have expressed an interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you are ready to commit and want to sign up, you will need to make a payment. You will be able to do that on my website, once I get that set up for you for this particular event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, if you want to get an initial look at what this is all about, you can go to my website: italianprogram.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on the tab that says: 'Italian Cooking Lessons' - &lt;a href="http://italianprogram.com/Italian_Cooking_Lessons.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://italianprogram.com/Italian_Cooking_Lessons.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the part that says: 'Cucina e parla Italiano' (don't mind the spelling errors, and don't pay attention to the price)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then click on the part to the right under 'Courses' that says 'Cucina e Parla Italiano': - &lt;a href="http://italianprogram.com/Cucina_e_Parla_Italiano.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://italianprogram.com/Cucina_e_Parla_Italiano.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of that should give you enough information about what to expect from a cooking lesson such as this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any immediate questions, please call/text/email me asap!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;cell - 617-233-9876&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 John Jordan &lt;br /&gt;

 Language, Travel and Culture Exchange, LLC &lt;br /&gt;

 (617) 233-9876 | jjordan@italianprogram.com &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://italianprogram.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://italianprogram.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>john jordan</member_name><member_id>3198507</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363475830000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members of this group</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>italian-374</urlname><id>288923</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Italian Language Meetup Group &amp; Lunedì Italiano</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362894247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EVENT IS SOLD OUT 'Cucina e parla italiano' - Italian Cooking Lesson - Sat, 3/16</name><id>108511132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363464000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-374/events/108511132/</event_url></item>