<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>An after work looping hike of 3 miles and roughly 2.25 hr. at Hubbard Park in Meriden, CT. We'll stop at Merrimere Resevoir, ascend East Peak via a steep trail and then try to catch the sunset (6:58 PM) at Castle Craig with its commanding views on the cliffs of East Peak. A small portion of the hike will be on the Metacomet Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the parking lot and we'll hike from there via about a half mile of road (Notch Rd. to Reservoir Rd.) to the reservoir, then about a mile by trail to Castle Craig on East Peak (about last 700 ft. are steep). The return trip of about 1.5 mi. is by trail including a footbridge over I-691. It will be dark for a portion of the return trip so your own light is necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive on time (by 5:45 PM) as we have a short amount of sunlight to do the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must bring a quart of water and a flashlight or headlamp (for return trip). A small backpack would be advised to carry water and lamp so hands are free for the steep trail. LED flashlights or headlamps are strongly advised as they are lighter and last longer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children and dogs are not advised due to the steep paths and cliffs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; (Notch Rd., Meriden, CT):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Meriden&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=95+Notch+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat.=41.5499, Long.=-72.8321]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map&lt;/b&gt; (2nd page) &amp;amp; general information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.scrcog.org/Trails_files/TrailMapHubbardPark.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.scrcog.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information&lt;/b&gt; about Hubbard Park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cityofmeriden.org/CMS/default.asp?CMS_PageID=426" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cityofmeri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253396988000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252559887000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Hubbard Park &amp; Castle Craig in Meriden CT</name><id>11335900</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253223900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11335900/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/f/global_705503.jpeg</photo_url></item>