<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Cochituate Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.305604</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 626-3636</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Framingham</city><id>703515</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.397715</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hola Todos,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going to try to have a weeknight  Framingham Spanish Meetup. Some members have stated that they cannot make the weekend day, so we are going to attempt a weeknight meetup in addition to Saturday's meetings. Everyone is invited to attend. In the future, if there is an interest I will try to schedule the meeting in between the Saturday meetings. For the summer it appears we will have a Saturday meeting every three weeks, during the winter probably every other Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we have the support we will continue with a weekday meeting. I find these Meetup venues an excellent way to practice speaking the languages we are studying. I am a member of several French and Spanish meetups. Hopefully, we will have an interest in the weeknight meetings and moderate attendance, especially among those who have specifically stated they would prefer a weeknight meeting. The day and week of the month is flexible now, although once we figure it out, I would like to keep to the same location, same day and same week of the month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is kind of an exciting expansion of what I have found to be an excellent, informative, fun and great group. If you have any questions contact myself or Peter.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Melencio</member_name><member_id>2726681</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182466868000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Castellano Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-581</urlname><id>232171</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>The MetroWest-Greater Boston Castellano Speakers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181568989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weeknight Framingham Spanish Meetup</name><id>5878248</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182294000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-581/events/5878248/</event_url></item>