<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Welcome local permaculture designers, teachers and world travellers Charles &amp;amp; Julia Yelton home to Maine by joining them at their permaculture home and gardens in Whitefield, Maine (about 1h 15m from Portland).  Charles &amp;amp; Julia have invited all who are interested to join them in seeing Humustacia (the name of their home), enjoying a potluck lunch and helping out a bit in reviving the gardens for the season.  The Yeltons have been busy travelling and permaculturing:) in Australia, Sicily, the Bahamas and Cyprus since December and will have only just returned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The site includes extensive permaculture gardens, several ponds, a passive solar home with integrated thermally massive greenhouse, a cool cupboard, humanure system and more.  Although no has been living there for a few months, &lt;i&gt;this remains one of the best examples of applied permaculture in Maine&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Help out in the gardens &lt;i&gt;before lunch, after lunch or both&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;10:00 arrival for &lt;b&gt;morning&lt;/b&gt; work party session&lt;br /&gt;1:00 break to share potluck lunch (bring your own potluck kit and a dish to share) and informal touring/Q&amp;amp;A about the site&lt;br /&gt;3:00 start an afternoon work party session&lt;br /&gt;5:00 wind down and depart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to your potluck kit and a food item to share, bring work shoes/boots, gloves and clothes that can get a bit dirty.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242171103000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239299372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Permaculture Site Visit and Work Party</name><id>10152712</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241877600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/10152712/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/a/global_8069562.jpeg</photo_url></item>