<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I will be at the theater by 7, the movie time is 8:10.   It is showing in the large downstairs theater, which means things are going to be crazy.   I will be near the ropes by the concession stand until they decide to let us line up.    Last time this happened, for the Harry Potter show,  they suddenly stopped letting people get in line inside and blocked them in the lobby.   So try to be there as close to 7 as possible.    Look for me in line, I will be wearing a meetup pin and holding a meetup sign.   Once they let us inside we can grab seats and take turns going to the restroom and/or concession stand.  I strongly suggest buying your tickets ahead of time.  If they are showing this downstairs it means that they anticipate it selling lots of tickets.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't find us before the movie, look for us after.  I will try to stop right outside the movie theater to allow for restroom breaks, discussion and a head count for going out for drinks and munchies after.   I will also stop again for a few minutes right outside of the building in case some members get separated.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rockbottom is closed for renovations, so I thought we would try something different.  Montien a Thai place nearby for the after movie gathering.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Details:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Season of the Witch   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: January 7, 2011    &lt;br /&gt;Studio: Relativity Media    &lt;br /&gt;Director: Dominic Sena    &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Bragi Schut    &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Nicolas Cage, Ron Perlman, Stephen Campbell Moore, Robert Sheehan, Claire Foy, Ulrich Thomsen, Stephen Graham, Christopher Lee    &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Action, Adventure, Supernatural    &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG-13 (for thematic elements, violence and disturbing content)    &lt;br /&gt;Official Website:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seasonofthewitchmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.seasonofth...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary:Oscar winner Nicolas Cage(&amp;quot;National Treasure,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Ghost Rider&amp;quot;) and Ron Perlman (&amp;quot;Hellboy,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Hellboy II: The Golden Army,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Sons of Anarchy&amp;quot;) star in this supernatural action adventure about a heroic Crusader and his closest friend who return home after decades of fierce fighting, only to find their world destroyed by the Plague. The church elders, convinced that a girl accused of being a witch is responsible for the devastation, command the two to transport the strange girl to a remote monastery where monks will perform an ancient ritual to rid the land of her curse. They embark on a harrowing, action-filled journey that will test their strength and courage as they discover the girl's dark secret and find themselves battling a terrifyingly powerful force that will determine the fate of the world. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin and will also have a meetup sign.  The movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand until they let us line up, then look for me in line.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294634402000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292009230000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Season of the Witch</name><id>15699283</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294531200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/15699283/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/e/f/global_20146591.jpeg</photo_url></item>