<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Lansdowne Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347182</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.247.1222</phone><name>The Lansdowne Pub</name><city>Boston</city><id>1088408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094957</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday September 18th, come on down to the Lansdowne Pub to watch the Red Sox take on the Tampa Bay Rays!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission is free (although you must be over 21). We have a private, large room reserved in the back of the pub where you can hang out with fellow Red Sox fans and take in a game in a fun atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the event will be three writers from the baseball analysis website ‘FanGraphs’, and two from the Red Sox blog ‘Over the Monster’. If you have any Red Sox or baseball-related questions for these writers, we’ll be hosting an informal Q&amp;amp;A early on that evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is being hosted by Partners for Youth with Disabilities, a one-to-one mentoring program that serves youth with disabilities in the Boston area. PYD currently has nearly 100 youth on its waitlist, and they are looking for any adult volunteers potentially interested in becoming a mentor. There are many male youth that are simply looking for a friend to talk sports with, to have a catch with them, or to take them to sports games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the event, PYD will be providing free appetizers for all, and they will also be raffling off two Red Sox tickets to anyone that signs up to receive more information on our program and becoming a mentor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can sign up to enter the raffle at the event, or by filling out the form here: &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/U6oNN2"&gt;http://bit.ly/U6oNN2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Slowinski</member_name><member_id>61455252</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348024321000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347381401000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Sox Pub Night: Free Food, Free Ticket Raffle, And For A Good Cause!</name><id>81896232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348007400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/81896232/</event_url></item>