<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a joint event organized by Social Fun&lt;br /&gt;If you have already RSVPed for this even with another group, please do not RSVP for more than one group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kitty O'Sheas is an awesome spot to host another Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party for 150 members on Saturday October 17 2008! This is not a Singles party. Anyone can come which means couples and singles are welcome so all can get to know one another and socialize.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kitty O'Sheas is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100 Website &lt;a href="http://www.kittyosheasboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kittyoshea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2nd floor can hold 185 people. There are 2 Bars upstairs, 4 huge comfy couches, AC, its own DJ area with light machine and dance floor, plus its own bathroom upstairs so we would truly have our own private party. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: this time the Musicc will be half as loud. The Music will be tuned very low or off in the back room so members can have a seperate area to chat!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Biagio has a commitment from Kitty OSheas for 2 Bartenders at the upfront 2nd floor Bar and one Bartender in the back area 2nd floor Bar. Biagio is ordering $150-200 worth of appetizers (Wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) because their Kitchen is small and we will never get enough food for 200 members. Biagio will ask if you eat any of the appetizers then he will need to ask people please to throw in $5 or so if they have some ( So if you do not have any its still voluntary and a free event).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This cost gets us the whole 2nd floor, 3 bartenders and the DJ so its not all just to cover the food!&lt;br /&gt;I will ask all if you ate or do NOT eat any of the appetizers to please to throw in $5 to help cover the cost of this event. Please find me or Biagio at the party and please give me or Biagio the $5. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for all this fun Friday October 17, 2008 starting at 7 till the cows come home. &lt;br /&gt;Please note : After 9PM the bar charges a mandatory $10 cover just to get in so we need to make sure members come before 9PM. &lt;br /&gt;After 9PM if we still have over 100 people upstairs we can keep the 2nd floor to ourselves all night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 7 Meetup Groups that are invited to come :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Social Fun &lt;a href="http://socialnetwork.meetup.com/887/"&gt;http://socialnetwork....&lt;/a&gt; (Confimred)&lt;br /&gt;Single in the &amp;quot;City&amp;quot; Women's Social Group &lt;a href="http://women.meetup.com/514/"&gt;http://women.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; (Still TBD)&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Happy Hour &lt;a href="http://nightlife.meetup.com/421/"&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt; (Still TBD)&lt;br /&gt;Boston Night Life Meetup &lt;a href="http://nightlife.meetup.com/29/calendar/8479069"&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt; (Still TBD)&lt;br /&gt;Chestnut Hill Social Networking Meetup &lt;a href="http://socialnetwork.meetup.com/1175/"&gt;http://socialnetwork....&lt;/a&gt; (Confimred by Elana)&lt;br /&gt;Beantown and Beyond 20-40 Singles &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1169/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt; (Confimred byTim)&lt;br /&gt;Metro West 30's to 40's Singles &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1555/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt; (Confimred byTim)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Maybe RSVPs will be moved to NO RSVPs 1 week before the event with no exception. We hit the target to get 250 YES RSVPs to hoprfully get 150 members to actually show up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had over 185 members at last Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party plus there were a few members hat could not get in because they came too late and it was full., so keep that in mind.&lt;br /&gt;It should be fun and I hope you can all join us for this blast of a party!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be out front until around 7:15.  If you come later, look for me inside.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225041193000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222107645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mix and Mingle (Joint Event)</name><id>8809188</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224284400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/8809188/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/3/global_1218899.jpeg</photo_url></item>