<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group and their Guests for a hibachi-style dinner at the &amp;quot;A&amp;quot; Restaurant we all voted to try!  Save your appetite for this delicious dinner!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quotes from &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/aoyama-japanese-steakhouse-marshfield#hrid:2iP_lUknVFWcrT0sc00Cig" target="_blank"&gt;reviews on Yelp&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amy C.: &amp;quot;FINALLY Marshfield gets blessed with an amazing Japanese Steakhouse, dare I say, to rival any Japanese I've had in Boston. *Aoyama is sort of hidden in Webster Square in the center of Marshfield, but it is so worth the trip!* The hibachi-style experience is totally delicious, with really fresh ingredients, and it's completely entertaining. I've been here on numerous occasions, and enjoyed the steak, chicken and shrimp options with delicious made-to-order fried rice. Yummy yummy.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate H.: &amp;quot;The filet mignon was grilled to a true medium rare perfection. Fresh, well-prepared food and kind help have won me over. (Sushi lovers take note: there is an extensive selection of items on both the luncheon and dinner menus!)&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prices range from $6-$17.  Our entire party must be present to be seated.  Due to the set-up of the table (if I remember correctly) you will generally be socializing with those seated in your immediate proximity (up to 2, possibly 3, seats away).  Therefore, we have decided to meet a little bit earlier to give everyone the opportunity to meet and socialize while we are waiting for our table.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aoyama Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;14 Snow Road&lt;br /&gt;Webster Square&lt;br /&gt;Marshfield, MA 02050&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp / First Time Guests are FREE!&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max:  Max of 20 attendees.&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome!  First-Time Guests are FREE!&lt;br /&gt;Accessibility: This is handicap-accessible.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, February 22nd @ 4pm&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizers: Estella and Kathy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember:  Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Route 3 to Exit 12/Route 139 East.&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 139 East/Church Street approximately 3.6 miles.&lt;br /&gt;Take a Right onto Webster Street.&lt;br /&gt;Turn Right onto Snow Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please use maps.google.com or mapquest.com for door-to-door directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will do our best to update the directions with landmarks prior to the RSVP Deadline.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the Lobby area.  All of us Organizers have our pictures posted so you will know who to look for.  We'll probably have a clipboard for signing in as well.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathy</member_name><member_id>339609</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205368956000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><why>It's the "A" Restaurant you voted for and the first time we have dined out for this type of cuisine.</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202337134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"A" Restaurant Dinner @ Aoyama</name><id>7278736</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203805800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7278736/</event_url></item>