<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trinity College</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.748314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio</name><city>Hartford</city><id>291370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690384</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Here is an opportunity to see a French film with your French friends!  It is on a Monday evening, and we welcome those who cannot attend our usual Wednesday Meetups.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Il y a longtemps que je t'aime&amp;quot; (I've Loved You so Long) will be showing at Trinity College's Cinestudio.&lt;br /&gt;Cinestudio is a grand traditional cinema, complete with a curtain that rises at the beginning! See Dianne for discount card&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional: pizza dinner beforehand First &amp;amp; Last on Maple Avenue&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description(France, 2008) Written and directed by Philippe Claudel. Cast: Kristin Scott Thomas, Elsa Zylberstein, Serge Hazanavicius, Laurent Grevill. Kristin Scott Thomas is the first British actress to win a Golden Globe nomination for Best Actress while appearing in a French language film (for her first experiment in French cinema, see Tell No One on the Cinestudio schedule). In any language, her performance is unforgettable, as a fortysomething woman named Juliette who mysteriously shows up at her sister’s home after fifteen years. While her nervous family would like to lock up whatever dark secret or crime lies in her past, Juliette’s tentative path to redemption is impossible without understanding. This haunting mystery is the first film directed by award-winning author Philippe Claudel (Grey Souls). “Scott Thomas's performance, easily the best of her career [it's] the centre of a deeply involving, beautifully acted and expertly constructed human drama by and for grown-ups.” Peter Bradshaw, The Guardian UK) 115 min. &lt;a href="http://www.son" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.son...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in lobby or at pizza before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235602748000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French</urlname><id>459167</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Groupe de French</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233201621000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French film trip Deux</name><id>9625297</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234830600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French/events/9625297/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/7/global_1365207.jpeg</photo_url></item>