<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Union Station</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.825216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>351-1400</phone><name>Ardeo</name><city>Providence</city><id>1077944</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.414199</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Providence Collective Monday Meetup series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant/bar scenes in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Ardeo - next to Waterplace Park (next to the Capital Grille and diagonal from Lux Burger)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ardeo is the newest edition to the Waterplace Park restaurant scene and specializes in Mediterranean cuisine (and yes, this is where Raphael's &amp;quot;used to be&amp;quot; - *sniff*). The newest restaurant in a small chain that has several popular locations on the Cape, THIS location is decidedly more upscale and elegant befitting the Providence nightlife. Oddly,  I have actually been in the one in Yarmouth - so you can only imagine my suprise at realizing the connection to the one in Providence - they've done a great job! The restaurant is also located next to the tunnel that connects to the skating rink so its a great place for an après-skate drink or bite to eat. It's a versatile place that becomes a nightclub after the weekend dinner crowd leaves and I've heard the food is great to boot! It's one to know about, so let's check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ken is hosting this one - please look at his picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263424215000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262873916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Ardeo!</name><id>12250336</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263250800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/12250336/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>