<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are planning a weekend of fun and adventure at the Ridin-Hy dude ranch in the Adirondack's in NY.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a complete weekend including all activities and food the cost is $250.00.  The activities for this Adirondack weekend will include hiking, horse back riding and so much more.  Check out the ranch at &lt;a href="http://www.ridinhy.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ridinhy.co...&lt;/a&gt; .  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to get everyone from our group placed together in cabins we will need to know if you would like to attend by the end of March.  Once we get all of our responses we will determine the room assignments and then everyone will be able to call the ranch and pay for your reservation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to plan to car pool to the ranch since the drive will be around 4 hours.  If you would like to carpool please let use know.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope you will be able to join us for this fun weekend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*** UPDATE*****&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I just called the ranch and it is now full for the weekend.  I have put the people who responded maybe on a waiting list.  If any space opens up before the weekend, I will notify the people on the waiting list.  If you would also like to be notified, please put yourself on the waiting list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judie</member_name><member_id>5431837</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1281130664000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Ma-NH-Singles-Club</urlname><id>1356935</id><group_lat>43.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Trailblazers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267410166000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ridin-Hy Dude Ranch</name><id>12738636</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275652800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Ma-NH-Singles-Club/events/12738636/</event_url></item>