<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>727 Marrett Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02421</zip><lat>42.445094</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 761-1700</phone><name>Aloft Lexington</name><city>Lexington</city><id>849027</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.259875</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Stuart L is organizing this event, thanks Stuart!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first Afterwork Cocktail Party in November is on the day following Election Day! Come and join us as we reflect on the outcome of the hard-fought campaign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The venue is the Aloft hotel in Lexington. Located adjacent to Route 128, The Aloft is easy to find, and parking is both plentiful and free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet your Sitz friends and bring a guest to the new Aloft Hotel’s “w xyz” bar. The atmosphere is modern and hip. Light appetizers will be served compliments of Sitzundjibers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Aloft Hotel is conveniently located at the intersection of Rte. 128 (I-95) and Rte. 2A (Marrett Road).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming from the north or south on Rte. 128 (1-95), take Exit 30B and head west briefly to the first stoplight (about 0.2 mile down). Turn right at this stoplight into the hotel driveway (across from Forbes Business Center).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Boston: take Rte. 2 West to Rte. 128 North to Rte. 2A West (Exit 30B). Head west briefly to the first stoplight (about 0.2 mile down). Turn right at this stoplight into the hotel driveway (across from Forbes Business Center).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You cannot miss us; we will be the ones with the smiles and laughter!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352657486000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348705398000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Afterwork at The Aloft in Lexington</name><id>84270532</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352329200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/84270532/</event_url></item>