<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>C'mon, let's get back in the air... A Saturday out morning breakfast run! and then some.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who has Blueberry Pancakes and Lighthouses? Only Maine... well, anyhow, let's go there....Have you been to Sanford (SFM) Lately? They have a great breakfast at the Cockpit Cafe located on the field. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We did this last year and it was a lot of fun. SFM for breakfast, then off the coast. The controller even gave us all the 5 cent tour!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and I quote Gary Archer...&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...If I remember correctly there are about five or six light houses along the coast within a few miles of each other. From here we contact Portland Apc. and request flight following with the light house tour. These guys do a great job and I found it very easy to do. Portland actually vectors you at a set altitude towards and around all the light houses, they even spin you around if you want to view them all over again in the other direction.  &amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So don't forget to ask your loved one or a friend to join you. Your not going to want to miss this one and don't forget that camera...HOW BOUT THAT.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.airnav.com/airport/KSFM" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.airnav.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284212411000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282655434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blueberry Pancakes and Lighthouses!  Saturday at Sanford The Light House tour.</name><id>14523299</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284208200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/14523299/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/4/6/global_8632678.jpeg</photo_url></item>