<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 High Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01951</zip><lat>42.799458</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Church of Newbury</name><city>United States</city><id>1547353</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.862633</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sharon Astyk, a North Shore native and nationally known energy and environmental writer, will speak about local food resilience on Thursday, June 2 at 7:00 PM.  She will talk about the importance of developing a strong local food system and how we can work toward individual and community food resilience, including eating local food year-round. This is the second event of a local food series organized by Transition Newburyport. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;The structure of our globalized industrial food system is not sustainable or healthy for us or the planet.&amp;rdquo; says Elizabeth Marcus of Transition Newburyport, &amp;ldquo;Sharon Astyk is a leader in creating a new approach by showing how we can create sustainable food systems and a vibrant local economy through buying, growing, preparing and eating local food.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sharon Astyk is a farmer near Albany, NY, and an expert on building individual and community resilience in the face of an uncertain future. She has authored several books including A Nation of Farmers: Defeating the Food Crisis on American Soil (co-author Aaron Newton), Depletion and Abundance: Life on the New Homefront, and Independence Days: A Guide to Sustainable Food Storage and Preservation. Ms. Astyk is a member of the Board of Directors for ASPO-USA (Association for the Study of Peak Oil and Gas-USA) and is a prolific, insightful blogger whose posts regularly appear in the Energy Bulletin and at Science Blogs.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This program to be held at the First Parish Church of Newbury at 20 High Road is sponsored by the Central Congregational Church (UCC), First Parish Church, First Religious Society of Newburyport (UU), New Eden Collaborative, Northshore Permaculture, Pennies for Poverty: 2 Cents for Change, Newburyport Farmers Market and Transition Newburyport.  The program is free and open to the public. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter the side or rear door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Dion</member_name><member_id>6134374</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307060177000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>The structure of our globalized industrial food system is not sustainable or healthy for us or the planet.</why><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303917539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sharon Astyk Talk:  Healthy, Resilient &amp; Equitable Regional Food Systems</name><id>17452944</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307055600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/17452944/</event_url></item>