<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Argilla Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.685432</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Castle Hill</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>2237751</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.779739</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Check our site for event updates. Changes and cancellations will be posted no later than 1 day ahead barring any unforeseen issues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Place:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Castle Hill, in the upper parking lot by the main house. (regardless of where you end up parking) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Date/Time:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Saturday, November 12 at 9:00AM&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Parking Fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;$5/per car at Castle Hill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was going to schedule this further out, but the weather is looking lovely for this Saturday. Sorry for the short notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're going to do something a little different this month.&amp;nbsp;Many of you have been requesting a portrait event for updated photos to use on Facebook/Online Dating/Etc. So... With such a variety of architectural and landscape backgrounds at Castle Hill--let's give it a try!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is welcome to participate as photographer and/or subject. No worries about unflattering photos being posted on the internet :), I'll ask participating photographers to agree that the "subject" gets final say. We'll shoot "round robin" style to keep things sane and to get the best results.&amp;nbsp;This should be a lot of fun and great practice!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the "comments/notes" section of our site. I'll update with suggestions for equipment and clothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who aren't interested in participating in the portrait session can&amp;nbsp;photograph the beautiful grounds surrounding the Great House at Castle Hill. There's plenty to shoot here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The grounds immediately surrounding the Great House may be closed during an event. If that should happen, notice of event changes are posted here and an e-mail sent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Castle Hill is home to a wide diversity of wildlife typical of northeast Massachusetts forests. Deer, fox, turkey, and a multitude of songbirds can be observed from the many trails and roads on Castle Hill. In addition, it is home to several pairs of nesting great horned owls and red-tailed hawks. Due to its location on the Atlantic Ocean and adjacent Crane Beach, unusual species such as turkey vultures, migratory hawks, and even an occasional bald eagle can be seen soaring above the landscape. Castle Hill is also a link in the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.baycircuit.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Bay Circuit Trail&lt;/a&gt;, offering four miles of moderate hiking trails and roads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS (from the Crane Estate website):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

From Route 128 north (towards Gloucester), take exit 20A (Route 1A north) and follow for 8 miles to Ipswich. Turn right onto Route 133 east and follow for 1.5 miles. Turn left onto Northgate Road and follow for .5 mi. Turn right onto Argilla Road and follow for 2.3 miles to entrance on left. Gatehouse attendant will direct you to parking area (20 cars) behind Farm Building Complex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321129237000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320678935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portraits (for use online) and autumn shoot at Castle Hill on the Crane Estate</name><id>40261632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321106400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/40261632/</event_url></item>