<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Tanager St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.421910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-648-3737</phone><name>Herb Pearce's</name><city>Arlington</city><id>899371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188564</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Herb Pearce has done a wonderful job teaching us about personality type systems such as The Enneagram of Personality and Myers-Briggs. Tonight he is going to teach us about the Zodiac.  Here is a description from Herb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Have you ever been lost at a party when people are talking about Astrology. Learn more about the differences between Taurus and Scorpio, Pisces and Leo, and see what you relate to the most. Whether you believe in astrology or not, learn the language and the psychological differences between each sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7 to 10pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sliding scale of $15-40. Pay whatever you can afford if you can't pay $15.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. You are also welcome to bring vegetarian appetizers and drinks, including wine.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce ******&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce, M.Ed., has been teaching personality systems for 20 years and has been a psychotherapist for 30 years, having worked with thousands of individuals, couples and families, as well as teams in corporations and agencies. Author of The Idiot's Guide to the Enneagram, he has also taught the Enneagram and Myers Briggs to unlock keys to the mystery of our uniqueness. He has been studying astrology for over 30 years and finds it a valuable system to understand the complexities of inner and outer reality.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256570078000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252710921000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 12 Signs of the Zodiac</name><id>11350730</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256338800000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/11350730/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/9/global_7697593.jpeg</photo_url></item>