<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>You should be dressed business casual. No T shirts. Even a &lt;br /&gt;sport Jacket would be nice. The better you look the better &lt;br /&gt;you''ll look&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you tomorrow, Spread the word&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Singles Meetups &amp;gt; Affluent Single Men &amp;amp; Fabulous Women&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MAJOR UPDATE: We were going to have a band. But circumstances beyond our control have forced us to increase it to 3 bands. Hesse posse (an inprov group from NY &amp;amp; CT) and  Suburban demographics (A blues &amp;amp; Jazz band) And of course as always Ben Noir will be here with his band) These men are not AFSM&amp;amp;FW group members (Yet), but have demanded entrance to the party to meet our lovely female attendees. They made me an offer I couldn't refuse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So:&lt;br /&gt;Announcing a NEW and UPDATED ASM&amp;amp;FW &amp;amp; SUPER SPEED DATING event and party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: SUPER SPEED DATING Grand Opening Party&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: August 23, 2008 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: See above location. Call if you get lost 203 746 2240&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MeetupDescription: The Grand Opening SUPER SPEED DATING Event and party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be having our first Meetup SUPER SPEED DATING event and before and after party all in one fabulous night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be from 20 to 50 speed daters as well as up to 150 other party guests to mingle with. Plus there willbe about 20 or so single male band members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've got an instrument, bring it and jam with the bands. If you can sing, well, you know whatto do. If you play the piano, we have two grands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two bars will operating and we could use some volunteer bartenders. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a FREE EVENT and you're asked to BOYB and/or a delicious treat for all to enjoy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AS ALWAYS, ABSOLUTELY NO DRUGS WILL BE TOLERATED. PERIOD!!!!PLEASE DRINK RESPONSIBLY. Anyone over the limit will be either asked to stay over or makealternate transportation arrangements if they are driving&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ladies &amp;amp; Gentlemen, we would like you to also bring a single male friend (not someone you are involved with. Guys definitely not someone you're involved with) to help even the odds. Experience tells us that it's hard to get the men to put down the remote, basket or bowling ball and come out to a social event in any great numbers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's where you come in. You all have male singlefriends, brothers, co-workers, your mechanic, tennis pro, personal trainer, pool boy, hair dresser (you may wanna be careful there) even your &amp;quot;Ex&amp;quot;. Hey, some of us still talk to our ex's.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drag him/them kicking and screaming if you have to. I guarantee they'll have a blast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DISCLAIMER: No men will be harmed in the making of this party. Men who still have the remote attached to their hands when they show up will have it removed byapplying lipstick to their lips while still attached to a female guest andin extreme cases, alcohol will be applied directly to their lips and tongue until their grip loosens. Frowns, excess baggage, grumpy dispositions and sullen looks must be checked at the door. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Left over smiles will be given to all guests to take home in doggie bags.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPECIAL NOTICE TO MEN: World Famous Dance Instructor MARIA FIORA will be giving some dancelessons as well as participating in the SPEED DATING. She is VERY HOT, Very single and she is an Assistant Organizer and will be having SUPER SPEED DATING PARTIES at her famous dance studio in Stamford. Check your calendar, one is already booked.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's Maria: &lt;a href="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/member/3/f/c/1/highres_736321.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;http://photos1.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP ASAP so you won't be LOITC*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, stay late, bring a smile and I guarantee you a date (or maybe 20)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to join our other group: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/2177/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Left Out In The Cold&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/2317/calendar/8391521/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Fairfield, CT  06812 - USA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, August 23 at 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photo: &lt;a href="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/5/d/event_4351581.jpeg"&gt;http://photos3.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attending: 0&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details: &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/2177/calendar/8370251/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be the tall guy with red hair</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John </member_name><member_id>6728192</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310132463000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219120294000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bruce's Big Party!!!</name><id>8574512</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219532400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/8574512/</event_url></item>