<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Globe Corner Bookstores is thrilled to host author Steven Kazlowski in a talk and presentation of photographs from his book “The Last Polar Bear: Facing the Truth of a Warming World”. He'll talk about his travel over an eight-year period to the Beaufort and Chukcki Seas, from Point Hope in western Alaska to Herschel Island in the Yukon and give his thoughts the impact of climate change on the Arctic habitat. .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Last Polar Bear includes anecdotes about life among the bears, relayed by the photographer, Alaskan natives, and Inupiaq elders. Essays written by conservationist Theodore Roosevelt IV, Natural Resources Defense Council President Frances Beinecke, cultural anthropologist Richard Nelson, environmental journalist Daniel Glick, Alaskan residents, and writers Nick Jans and Charles Wohlforth provide a more in-depth understanding of the scientific, political, and social issues that surround climate change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This will be a ticketed event. Reservations are recommended. Please call (617-649-5700 x21) or email (events@gcb.com) to have tickets reserved or mailed to you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be out of town. Hope you meet up.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223959407000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219189076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Polar Bears</name><id>8579711</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221688800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/8579711/</event_url></item>