<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-245-1525</phone><name>Harrington's Pub</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>733190</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a joint meetup with the Red Sox Natives. Please RSVP early if you plan to attend as we have a limit of 35 guests between the 2 groups due to space limitations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harrington's Food and Spirits in downtown Wakefield is a cozy Irish Restaurant and Pub with two floors. We have been there before. The food is great and the full menu will be available for purchase.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive early&amp;nbsp;by 6:00 PM and get yourself a prime seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing. Stop by for drinks, stay for dinner and stick around&amp;nbsp;to watch the Bruins game.&amp;nbsp; Or arrive&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;later and stay until when ever.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game Time is 7:05 PM for the Bruins vs the New Jersey Devils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking in downtown Wakefield in the public lot across from Harrington's in front of Bank of America and along Water and Main Streets. The location is T accessible by the 136 and 137 Bus from the Orange Line in Malden Center. And Commuter Rail accessible from North Station&amp;nbsp;via the&amp;nbsp;Reading and Haverhill Trains stopping at Wakefield Station&amp;nbsp;with a less than 10 minute walk up Albion&amp;nbsp;Street, right on&amp;nbsp;to Main Street and 1 block to Water Street. If you are joining us from the City this is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the Scoreboard hostess to direct you to our groups in the bar area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327033507000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325120553000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour followed by Bruins Game Viewing at Harrington's Irish Pub</name><id>45785222</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327014000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/45785222/</event_url></item>