<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>161 Brighton Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.353202</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-782-8100</phone><name>Tavern in the Square Allston</name><city>Allston</city><id>1479967</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132668</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's like the saying goes: &amp;quot;Extraordinary claims require extraordinary brunch.&amp;quot; We'll be gathering for our first monthly brunch of the year, at the new Tavern in the Square location in Allston. The all-you-can-eat buffet is about $14/person: &lt;a href="http://taverninthesquare.com/tavallston/content/brunch" target="_blank"&gt;http://taverninthesqu...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New members are encouraged to come out and make some friends; all members are invited to bring interesting atheist paraphernalia -- books, articles, FSM figurines, and so on. These brunches are a great way to 1) find something to do on Sunday morning, when all your friends are in church; and 2) strike up a conversation with some of the most curious and intellectually wide-ranging crowd you can find. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before we break, members will have the chance to make any announcements they'd like, about new developments in their life, interesting happenings coming up, and the like. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A SPECIAL NOTE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As part of our ongoing efforts to pair our gluttony with charity, we are inviting anyone in attendance to make a small cash donation to the Michela Harriman Memorial Fund, to support the construction of a community center, kitchen and dining hall for Ganako Secondary School in Tanzania. We'll have a donor sheet in case you'd like to make a named donation personally; otherwise, your donation will be part of a lump donation from the Members and Friends of the Boston Atheists. We'll be adding the proceeds from this event, to the money we raised at our earlier holiday party, and sending a check in to the organization in February on behalf of the BA organization. For more information about the Fund, visit &lt;a href="http://www.fotzc.org/projects/current-projects/ganako-secondary-school" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fotzc.org/...&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://blog.thomsonsafaris.com/safari/family-supports-tanzanian-community" target="_blank"&gt;http://blog.thomsonsa...&lt;/a&gt;. Our webmaster Calvin will list any donors who wish their names be known, in the Altruism section of our group website at &lt;a href="http://bostonatheists.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonatheists...&lt;/a&gt;. Because we'd like people to know we aren't just a bunch of bah-humbug anti-religionists. We ARE that, but we are also so much more!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Meetup group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297559614000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295888202000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BA Brunch</name><id>16165160</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297008000000</time><rsvp_limit>29</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/16165160/</event_url></item>