<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1300 South main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.524809</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-347-7773</phone><name>Haveli India Restaurant</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1383199</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.665074</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Havelis developed in India in ancient times as royal houses where Royal guests would stay and be entertained. In later eras they would also become merchant homes or homes of the wealthy. But, their initial evolution was where the royal families and selected ministers got together in a congenial environment to discuss affairs of state, as they dined and were entertained. The custom was for hundreds of the best cooks and entertainers to be brought from around the state to serve the royal families and their guests. The entertainment and the food was always the best the state had to offer. And because of the number of cooks they were known to try new and creative dishes to distinguish themselves before the royal family.  It is because of this beginning that Haveli's over time became known as keepers of Indian traditions and cuisines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laxman Sharma (owner/chef) has continued this tradition of serving the King and Queen at Haveli India in Middletown Connecticut. As, Laxman states : his new King and Queen are the guests, who come to Haveli India to be dined and pampered by his always polite and attentive staff. Here you will find food fit for a King or a Queen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone who has dined here can attest to the wonderfully tasteful and aromatic dishes...all served at your request. From the time you are seated, you will be spoiled by the superb foods and impeccable service. You will be seated in an atmosphere of serenity and will mingle with friends, enjoying this unique dining experience and great conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for  Terri or the Meetup Sign...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286753236000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285195468000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HAVELI  INDIA...The Best In Indian Cuisine...</name><id>14863678</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286667000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/14863678/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/e/global_18167214.jpeg</photo_url></item>