<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you carry a compass and map in your hiking backpack? When was the last time you used your compass?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Up North Orienteers will hold another one of its great workshops on Sunday, May 5, 2013 to teach compass skills and give an opportunity to practice them in the woods at UNH Durham. The event will be held rain or shine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to the public. This means, I am not running the program, but am a participant. It will be my third time at UNH for this workshop with UP North Orienteering. The first time I took one of the workshops, followed by practice on the easy course. Last year, I enjoyed practice on the intermediate course. It always is great fun, and I regain confidence in knowing how to use my compass should I ever need to. And it is even more fun with a great group of people navigating together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need to register at the event. According to the website, optional classes will be held outdoors at 10:30 am, 11:15 am, and 12 noon to teach the following skills: &lt;br /&gt;

 reading a map for scale, declination, climb, and features &lt;br /&gt;

 understanding the parts of your compass and how to use them &lt;br /&gt;

 using your compass to navigate &lt;br /&gt;

 ways to determine distance traveled &lt;br /&gt;

 using your map and compass to determine where you are&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After your class, you can practice the same skills on one or more orienteering courses in the woods ranging from 2 to 6 miles. All participants must check out by 2:30 pm. You choose which course to try out. (You can also do more than one; they just provide you with a different map once you finished your first course; e.g. you may start with an easy course but decide that it is too easy or too short and switch to/add an intermediate one thereafter): &lt;br /&gt;

 Easy Navigation: White: 1.8 km; Yellow: 2.7 km &lt;br /&gt;

 Advanced Navigation: Brown: 3.5 km; Green: 5.5 km &lt;br /&gt;

 Intermediate Navigation: Long Orange: 8.5 km&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From previous experience, to the best of my knowledge the cost is $5.00 for the map, compass workshop and the practice courses in the woods (or only practice; you pay for using their set up trails; workshop in a way is complementary as it is the same fee, whether you take it or not) . You will be asked to register and sign a waiver form. There are no restroom facilities at the site. Bring your own compass, or you can borrow one on site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check www.upnoor.org for updates or additional information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions to the workshop as provided on UpNoor.org site--they are more accurate than the google map: From NH Route 4, exit at Route 155A (UNH - Whittemore Center). Turn towards Durham and travel 1.2 miles on that road to the UNH Campus. Go straight through the traffic circle and at the first traffic light take a right onto College Road and travel 0.3 miles. Turn right onto South Drive, go under the RR overpass, and make an immediate right onto Waterworks Road. Take your first left into the parking at the Gregg Hall lot. If that lot is full, go back to Waterworks Road, turn left onto Colovos Road, and right into the parking for Chase and Ritzman Labs. Do not park your car in anything that isn't a legal parking space since UNH has stiff parking fines. Registration will be outdoors in front of Gregg Hall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you rsvp, please clarify whether you plan on taking the workshop.&lt;/strong&gt; I recommend taking the workshop if you have never been trained in how to use a compass.  &lt;strong&gt;I do NOT plan on taking the workshop, but start on a course at 10am&lt;/strong&gt;.  Depending on rsvp's we could split into two or more groups: those first taking a workshop and then practicing; and those who start on a course right away. (Depending how many of us there are, we may decide to split into smaller groups and use different courses to properly practice with the compass and not follow a group who is just ahead of us.) It is a lot of fun thinking you just navigated correctly to a flag, only to find out that the flag is not part of your course... and eventually you get it right and find the correct flags and become more confident throughout the day &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; This is like an 'Easter egg hunt' without the calories of chocolate eggs. &lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/614102232183174521616/img/smileys/wink.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica</member_name><member_id>10925522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367793839000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367162274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Compass Workshop and Practice</name><id>116589472</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367762400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/116589472/</event_url></item>