<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 122a</address_2><address_1>Causeway Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01522</zip><lat>42.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-399-4001</phone><name>Eagle Lake Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Jefferson</city><id>321444</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.870003</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>One quick change about where to meet and park for this event!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you could just change the parking info in the event description, that would be great! Is there some way for me to make sure that everyone sees the info I posted to the message board?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After some poking around, I found this map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/images/maps/eagle_trails.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massaudubo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It shows the parking lot on Causeway Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello All! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP to this event - even if it's a no. We want to be sure we know who is coming out!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time for another click and shoot for you nature lovers! JB Sweeney (cell phone: 978-399-4001) has graciously offered to lead this one to the Eagle Lake Wildlife Sanctuary in Holden/Jefferson MA. Here is some info about the place...and I heard a rumor that there may be someone there who will share brownies...anyone need more incentive than that to go!!! If anyone gets lost be sure to give JB a call on her cell phone-she'll do what she can to get you there! 978-399-4001.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We plan on meeting at the trail head off of 122 A - there are directions below, but if you have any questions please just post them on the message board and someone will get back to you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be fun! Please come on out and join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eagle Lake Wildlife Sanctuary &lt;br /&gt;From its mammoth red oaks to its extensive wetlands, this sanctuary?s many habitats support a wealth of wildlife. Its 175 acres of wildland are home to hundreds of species, including fishers, pileated woodpeckers, river otters, barred owls, muskrats, and many types of waterfowl. A three-mile marked trail loops through forests of oak, pine, and hemlock and skirts meandering Asnebumskit Brook. The trail also helps visitors discover some of the sanctuary?s prime attractions like its pleasant overlooks of Eagle Lake and great masses of blooming mountain laurel in the spring and summer. Public programs are scheduled for the property each season through Broad Meadow Brook Wildlife Sanctuary in Worcester.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Holden, MA&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;The sanctuary is located on Causeway Street off Route 122A in the village of Jefferson. Visitors may park in a pull-off at the trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/Eagle_Lake/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massaudubo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Hours:&lt;br /&gt;Trails: Open every day, dawn to dusk.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For Your Safety&lt;br /&gt;Do not feed any animals&lt;br /&gt;Stay on trails to avoid ticks and poison ivy&lt;br /&gt;Do not smoke anywhere on the sanctuary&lt;br /&gt;Do not pick or collect plants or crops without permission&lt;br /&gt;Avoid Conflicts with Wildlife&lt;br /&gt;Do not bring pets, leashed or unleashed, on to the site&lt;br /&gt;Picnic only in designated areas&lt;br /&gt;Do not bring motorized vehicles or bicycles onto the site&lt;br /&gt;Hunting, fishing, or trapping are not permitted&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;$3 for nonmember adults;&lt;br /&gt;$2 for nonmember children (3-12) and seniors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember sunblock, bug spray, snack, water, comfy walking shoes, and your camera gear!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186620101000</updated><rating><average>4.63000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184240916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot:  Eagle Lake Wildlife Sanctuary</name><id>6012504</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186333200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/6012504/</event_url></item>