<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Cambridge Innovation Center, 1 Broadway St</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>5th floor Havana Room </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>11480952</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109734</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/9/4/8/event_218766472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever caught yourself wondering what is the bigger "why" beyond what you do? Is there a way of finding one's purpose? Will you find it, or will your purpose find you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and join us for an intimate, interactive and insightful conversation to learn more about the role of purpose in one's self-development, how we shape and craft our purpose, and how it may fundamentally define who we are as individuals. This session will have many interactive processes and we will experience the role the breath plays in supporting our understanding of our purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The talk will be presented by Bill Herman - Founder &amp;amp; Director, International Association for Human Values. He has developed programs for young teens, adults and educators that help them manage their mind and emotions, and has facilitated workshops in schools, communities and organizations in Texas, New Orleans, Chicago, Haiti, Mexico, Argentina &amp;amp; Pakistan. &lt;span&gt;Bill has personally trained 7,000 middle and high school students in managing their minds and emotions, and 670 facilitators who have taught in the barrios of Mexico, Belize and Brownsville Texas; Hurricane affected areas in New Orleans, and in slums and villages of Haiti and Pakistan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a picture ID and check in at the desk on the 1st floor to get a visitor's badge. The registration fees for this event is $10 and can be paid at purposefulindividual.eventbrite.com or via. Meetup's Paypal portal.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anuj Madan</member_name><member_id>6404070</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vidur</member_name><member_id>9973871</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366077712000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonmeditates</urlname><id>1257412</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>"Boston Meditates" Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364511801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Purposeful Individual</name><id>111567172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366066800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonmeditates/events/111567172/</event_url></item>