<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention: Actual screening time to be posted the week of the movie. Kendall evening screenings typically start around 7 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like back to back weekends of Werner Herzog-one old and one new! The great director of Fitzcarraldo, Aguirre, and Grizzlly Man has a new one and from what I've read, this is the German director's most accessible movie in years, maybe ever. Werner goes mainstream- I think not! Then again, this movie does star Batman's Christian Bale, who is no Klaus Kinski, but maybe that's a good thing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The film recounts the true story of Dieter Dengler (Bale), who grew up in bombed out, post-war Germany, dreaming of becoming a pilot. He eventually made his way to the United States, where he joined the military during the Vietnam War. Forty minutes into his first mission he was shot down and captured. Surviving untold tortures at the hands of the Vietcong, he eventually escaped?only to face the most unforgiving enemy of all: the jungle&amp;quot; Kendall description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herzog is definitely intrigued by this man's story having previously filmed the  1997 documentary, Little Dieter Needs to Fly based on the same material, and is a continuation of the director's ongoing exploration of the relationship between man and nature. Here is a link to a full review: &lt;a href="http://www.shadowsonthewall.co.uk/07/rescdawn.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.shadowsont...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film opens on the 13th and  because of its  subject matter, I did not want to host it on a Sunday afternoon ( not exactly what I had in mind when thinking of leisurely al fresco discussions on a Sunday). A new Herzog movie has got to get a least a month run at the Kendall and so I'm posting if for the following  Saturday night, the 21st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the custom, Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185231812000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183228286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Herzog's Latest!  Rescue Dawn</name><id>5957003</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185058800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5957003/</event_url></item>