<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1721 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.336548</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bark Place</name><city>Boston</city><id>6651362</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hi Everyone!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join us for a Sunday Meetup at BARK PLACE! Come and play Sunday, December 9 from 11 AM – 1 PM in our new, fun location.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Bark Place is a dog spa, DIY wash and boutique that is all PLAY! They have a “Playcare Studio” filled with toys and playground equipment. Bark Place will provide us with a big, private indoor space for all our little white fluffballs to run round around and play!! Kathi and the staff are super nice and you can’t beat the Bark Place location on Washington Street in the South End. Only 7/10 mile down Washington Street from Peter’s Park Dog Park. Check out Bark Place at &lt;a href="http://www.barkplacesouthend.com/"&gt;http://www.barkplacesouthend.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;We even get 20% off all products during that time!! So stock up on your HOLIDAY GIFTS!!  Treats, toys, coats, collars, harnesses, leashes and so much more!! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;From Bark Place:&lt;/strong&gt; For the safety of all guests, Bark Place requires that all dogs have up-to-date vaccinations. A Bark Place Open Playground Waiver Form must be filled out prior to each dog participating in the Meetup. Please either fill-out the application in advance of the Meetup or Bark Place will have applications on-hand on the day of the Meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Here’s a link to the Bark Place Open Playground Waiver Form: &lt;a href="http://www.barkplacesouthend.com/pdf/Bark%20place%20waiver%20open%20playground.pdf"&gt;http://www.barkplacesouthend.com/pdf/Bark%20place%20waiver%20open%20playground.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Mandatory Dues:&lt;/strong&gt; $5 per household for each Bark Place meetup. $30 goes to the Bark Place hosting fee for renting the space and clean up. If Meetup attendance does not cover the $30 hosting fee, then the organizer will pay the difference. Anything in excess will be banked for future months when we are short on the hosting fee. At the end of the year any additional excess will be donated to a charity of our choice (Friends of Peter’s Park, Animal Rescue League of Boston, or your favorite Maltese rescue group) in the name of The Downtown Boston Maltese Meetup Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Bark Place is located at 1721 Washington Street in the South End. Bark Place is located on the street level in historic Minot Hall, close to the corner of Washington and Mass Ave.  For your reference, Bark Place is 7/10 of a mile down Washington Street from Peter’s Park Dog Park (our outdoors Meetup location).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; There is metered parking (free on Sundays) in front of Bark Place and on most of Washington Street. Mass Ave has non-metered parking (free). Most side streets are generally marked for South End residents only with one space(s) reserved for Visitors.  Shawmut Street offers many non-resident, non-metered spaces but check the signs for the few blocks that are South End resident parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Public Transportation:&lt;/strong&gt; The Silver Line Bus drops you off right in front of Bark Place at Minot Hall. Or the Orange Line Massachusetts Avenue Train Station is 3 blocks away; walk down Mass. Ave past Columbus, Tremont, and take the left on Washington Street. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Thanks so much! See you there! Janine and Coco!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janine</member_name><member_id>9399538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358811263000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Maltese Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-115</urlname><id>215542</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Downtown Boston Maltese Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354369791000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The December Downtown Boston Maltese Meetup</name><id>93606582</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355068800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-115/events/93606582/</event_url></item>