<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Martin Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01929</zip><lat>42.630955</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Essex Town Hall</name><city>Essex</city><id>1032121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.782369</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Essex Clamfest&lt;br /&gt;October 24, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Memorial Park&lt;br /&gt;Downtown Essex&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE: As you may have seen in the previous email that I sent out this event was on Saturday but we changed it to Sunday, because of the rain on Saturday Essex changed the event to Sunday.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little history about Essex:&lt;br /&gt;Before European settlers arrived in 1634, the area, which was one of the earliest settlements in Massachusetts, was inhabited by Native Americans of the Agawam Tribe but soon became known as Chebacco Parish, Ipswich's eighth parish, until 1819 when it was incorporated as the Town of Essex.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essex Clamfest - In its 27th year, the Essex Clamfest celebrates the most famous food of Essex. This festival takes place in October at Memorial Park and is organized and run by the Essex Division of the Cape Ann Chamber of Commerce. Featured activities include a clam chowder competition among area restaurants with public voting; 40 to 50 local vendors selling everything from handmade products, packaged foods, jewelry and Essex garb; Essex Police and Fire Department Safety Day; Essex Board of Health Fair; Non-Profit Groups doing fundraising activities and local music.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;center&gt;Health and Wellness Fair&lt;br /&gt;October 24, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Essex Fire Station&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Health and Wellness Fair - The Essex Board of Health is sponsoring our 2nd Health Fair held in conjunction with the Cape Ann Chamber of Commerce’s Annual Clam Festival. Our goal is to offer education, information, and entertainment for the whole family on health and wellness topics of importance. All Health Fair activities and information are free! Bring your family and friends and enjoy the day, get health screenings and gather important information!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a pay as you go event, you are responsible for paying your own way through the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;TIME&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note we will only wait for 15 minutes after scheduled meetup time to head out to where we will be sitting, if you think that you will be running late, please email me before hand so we can make other arrangements.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The clamfest is right next to the Town Hall with LOTS of free parking in the field.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take 128North to Exit 18, Route 22:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Turn left at Essex St/&lt;br /&gt;2. Turn right at Grapevine Rd/ MA-22MA-22 &lt;br /&gt;3. Turn left at MA-22/ Rubbly Rd/ Woodbury St&lt;br /&gt;4. Turn right at Essex St/ MA-22, Continue to follow MA-22&lt;br /&gt;5. Slight right at MA-22/ Martin St&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 128North:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take MA-128 N (signs for MA-128/ Gloucester)&lt;br /&gt;2. Take exit 15 for School St toward Essex&lt;br /&gt;3. Turn left at School St&lt;br /&gt;4. Continue on Southern Ave&lt;br /&gt;5. Turn left at MA-133/ Main St&lt;br /&gt;6. Turn left at MA-22/ Martin St&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In front of the Town Hall!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256770957000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254070898000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clamfest in Essex</name><id>11478581</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256486400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/11478581/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/c/global_10923500.jpeg</photo_url></item>