<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a *free* meetup organized by our Cultural Kitchen classes.  A number of the youth in this winter's classes are from Haiti, and everyone wanted to find a way to support Haiti earthquake relief.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, they will be baking all afternoon and then will host a bake sale with cookies and sweets from many nations at the Boston Hostel from 4-5 PM on February 6th.  Proceeds from the sale will go to the American Red Cross.  Additionally, there will be a cultural presentation on Haiti.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since Cultural Cafe is a fundraiser for our Cultural Kitchen programs, I thought you might like the chance to get to meet some of the youth that you are generously supporting...and I'm sure they'd be delighted to have you buying their international sweets!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a flyer if you'd like a copy to hang up at work - let me know!&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for being part of the Cultural Cafe meetup group, and I hope to meet you at an event soon.&lt;br /&gt;Warm regards,&lt;br /&gt;Karin Turer&lt;br /&gt;617-718-7990 ext 23&lt;br /&gt;kturer@usahostels.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS: The February 2nd Estragon Tapas Bar meetup is sold out; the next meetup after that is at Annapurna (Himalayan food) Restaurant in Cambridge on March 2nd.  It is amazingly delicious food and spaces are filling up briskly, so please go to &lt;a href="http://culturalcafemarch.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://culturalcafema...&lt;/a&gt;  :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265663426000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Culturalcafe</urlname><id>1554280</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Cultural Café - Dine Out for a Cause</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264699715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Extra-special *free* meetup: A bake-off for Haiti!</name><id>12450121</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265490000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Culturalcafe/events/12450121/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/7/global_12833367.jpeg</photo_url></item>