<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>162 Shield Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06110</zip><lat>41.729337</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cora Cora</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>860879</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.720123</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; Spanish Meet Up de Diciembre 2011 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

El Meet Up de diciembre sera el 8 de diciembre en el Restaurante Cora Cora, 162 Shield St., West Hartford, CT.&amp;nbsp; El reunion comenzara a las 6 de la noche y sera una cena con todo incluido por $25.00.&amp;nbsp; El precio de $25.00 es para una cena completo, impuestos y propina.&amp;nbsp; El unico que no esta incluido&amp;nbsp;es una&amp;nbsp;bebida alcoholica.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

Para reservar tiene que mandar un giro (check) de $25.00 por persona.&amp;nbsp; Por favor haga el giro al nombre de Karen Dworski o Kurt Weingartner &amp;nbsp; Los giros puede ser mandado a los sigiente direciones:&amp;nbsp; Karen Dworski, 28 Circle Dr., Unionville, CT 06085 o Kurt Weingartner, 1426 Trout Brook Drive, West Hartford, CT 06117.&amp;nbsp; El ultimo dia para recibir los giros sera el 3 de Diciembre 2011. 
&lt;p&gt;El unico posibilidad de un reembolso de su dinero sera si llamas a Karen @ 860-922-7997 (cellular) o Kurt @ 860-978-0851 un dia antes (7 de Diciembre 2011).&amp;nbsp; Esperamos que todos pueden asistir esta noche para buena conversacion y comida.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The December meet up will take place December 8, 2011 at Cora Cora Restaurant, 162 Shield St, West Hartford, CT 06110.&amp;nbsp; The meet up will begin at 6pm and will include a complete dinner for $25.00.&amp;nbsp; The $25.00 cost will include a complete dinner with a non alcoholic drink and dessert tax and tip included.&amp;nbsp; Alcoholic drinks can be purchase that evening from your server. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To reserve your spot you will need to send a check for $25.00 per person.&amp;nbsp; You can make the check out to either Karen Dworski or Kurt Weingartner.&amp;nbsp; The checks should be sent to either of the following addresses:&amp;nbsp; Karen Dworski, 28 Circle Dr., Unionville, CT 06085 or Kurt Weingartner, 1426 Trout Brook Drive, West Hartford, CT 06117.&amp;nbsp; The checks must be received by December 3, 2011.&amp;nbsp; Refunds will only be given if you call Karen @ 860-922-7997 (cell)&amp;nbsp;or Kurt @ 860-978-0851 by December 7, 2011.&amp;nbsp; No refunds will be given for no shows. We hope everyone will be able to come that night for an evening of conversation and food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;- Mostrar texto citado -&lt;/span&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The restaurant is in the Shield St Plaza off of New Britain Avenue West Hartford CT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Dworski</member_name><member_id>2589505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Weingartner</member_name><member_id>8679708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326330101000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321483573000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fiesta de diciembre 2011</name><id>41441502</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323385200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/41441502/</event_url></item>