<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's spend the 3 day holiday weekend together at an All-Inclusive Resort designed exclusively for adults! There's nothing better than 300 wooded acres nestled in the foothills of the Berkshire Mountains set on a sparkling lake in Kent, CT (www.clubgetaway.com) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Club Getaway, you'll find almost every sport/activity you can imagine including: Tennis, Mt. Biking, Water Skiing, Volleyball, Archery, Zip Lines, Rock Climbing, Softball, Yoga, Dancing, Wine Tasting, Arts &amp;amp; Crafts, Dodgeball and the Flying Trapeze just to name a few!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All your meals, entertainment, activities, equipment and instructions with the pros are included as well as overnight accommodations in air-conditioned cabins and unlimited wine at dinner. Choose from dozens of fun sports and adventures to cool parties and entertainment or just kick back, relax in the sun and make new friends! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fun starts as early as 5:30 p.m. on Friday, September 3rd (or whenever you're able to get there) and continues through Monday, September 6th at 4:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The cost for this AMAZING weekend is $459/person plus tax and service fee. Say you're with Sheri's group and save $25! (Note: Price is based on 4 people/cabin. Smaller cabins may be available at an additional cost.)&lt;/b&gt; (The only things NOT included in this price are: Transportation to/from the resort, refreshments and cocktails at the bar, T-shirts, hats, etc. at the boutique.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;You must pre-register and pay ASAP because we're getting a discounted rate and they sell out very quickly!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click here to for more info: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.clubgetaway.com/affil/default.asp?AffiliateMicroSiteID=749" target="_blank"&gt;Club Getaway&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've gone to Club Getaway at least once a year for the past 10 years and every time I go I never want to leave! Trust me when I say that you'll have the time of your life! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By clicking &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for agreeing to attend this event, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Steppin' Out... A Social Group! for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event or sports/physical activity associated with this event and grant the Steppin' Out... A Social Group! the authority to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll email my cell # to the "Yes" RSVP's a few days before</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283857656000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279892717000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Labor Day Weekend at All Inclusive Resort (9/3 - 9/6/10)</name><id>14189869</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283549400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/14189869/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/global_16638131.jpeg</photo_url></item>