<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4848 Monument Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.460968</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>978/369-9200</phone><name>The Colonial Inn</name><city>Concord</city><id>520639</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.349020</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join citizens interested in restoring our liberties and freedom at this exciting meeting on Sunday, Feb. 24 from 12:00 - 3:00. The featured speaker is Bob Schulz, Chairman of We the People Congress. The agenda is informational and inspirational to those of us who want our freedoms and liberties back! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come learn about the profound legal tool provided by our Founders that can restore Constitutional Order without electing a single politician or firing a single musket. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn the historical context and original intent of the little-known &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Right to Petition for Redress of Grievances&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; that could quickly force our government to fix virtually every violation against the Constitution. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time to stand in defense of the Constitution and learn what the last ten words of the First &lt;br /&gt;Amendment really mean. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Right to Petition is not about Free Speech. It's not about protesting everyday political questions. It's the most powerful weapon in law the People possess to enforce our Constitution and secure our unalienable Rights. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ron Paul activists are encouraged to stay on after the mtg for a planning session to discuss delegates and caucuses for MA.&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time to organize to exercise this Right!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"Look for We the People Congress and fellow Ron Paul volunteers!"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joan M Donahue</member_name><member_id>4236394</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204045436000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Come join us because you haven't given up fighting for our country or for Congressman Ron Paul! Learn how to make a difference, share ideas with other citizens!</why><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203687431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Revolution: Phase II</name><id>7385642</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203872400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/7385642/</event_url></item>