<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Parking fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per car (CT resident)</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>*** Note 9/6/07: Change in leadership for this hike from Kevin S. to Adam Skinner (due to flight change for Kevin)***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a roughly 6.2 mile looping hike in Peoples State Forest. Some portions will be steep. Established in 1924, the forest includes over 11 miles of trails as well as the west branch of the Farmington River which was designated as a Wild and Scenic River by the National Park Service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet by 9 AM at the state forest main parking area on the west side of East River Rd. This paved parking area will be roughly across the street (a little more north) from the main entrance (see the map, the southern gray block near the entrance). We'll start the hike at 9:15 AM after getting bug spray and such set and any last minute arrivals. We'll hike a short distance to the Nature Center and pick up the blue blazed trail on the west side of Greenwoods Rd. We'll follow the Robert Ross Trail north and then get onto the blue w/yellow dot Jesse Gerard Trail and eventually intersect with Greenwoods Rd. again at the northernmost point of this hike. then hike a little south on the road and then pick up the yellow blaze Charles Pack Trail on the left and head generally south-east. We'll then finish up the hike on the eastern half of the orange blaze Agnes Brown Trail where we'll end near the Nature Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike should last no more than about 3.5 hrs. at a leasurly pace depending on heat/humidity and be over by about 12:45 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one is Adam Skinner (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/4429379/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions on this event to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will likely be a parking fee of $7 per car and is $10 for non-CT residents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Water is a must on the hike -1 Qt. Bug spray strongly advised. Food (e.g. trail mix) optional but a good energy boost. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pets on a leash are permitted on hiking trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/peoples.pdf"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Hartford (about 45 min.):&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 44 west&lt;br /&gt;* Take right onto Route 181, RIVER RD., about 1 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Go across the steel bridge&lt;br /&gt;* Take an immediate left onto East River Road&lt;br /&gt;* The parking area is approximately 1 mile up on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the parking area can be found via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;address=%5b100%2d109%5d%20E%20River%20Rd&amp;amp;city=Barkhamsted&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06063&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;location=1SQnVj2M956m56ubJXeg%2bk04z0uUP2laFE%2fs9mMspX1Jrkjs6AS7Ztl0svM2v1uchjVHWLTFQABAF6C24B8CygUeQ%2bZUxhenrkv9QiF0aNpO8DEqHlnlbOn3czLRyMDVvFh6m%2fseyi2KmSy17Qbe9ALHotoU15N%2b&amp;amp;ambiguity=1"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the state park, see:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325054&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189429302000</updated><rating><average>4.55999994278</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187297086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Peoples SF in Barkhamsted CT</name><id>6193010</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189256400000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6193010/</event_url></item>