<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>DeCiccio Family Auditorium / Room 1</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02912</zip><lat>41.826191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 863-3650</phone><name>Salomon Center for Teaching at Brown University</name><city>Providence</city><id>1116631</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.402848</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;LOVE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Tavis Smiley!!!! If you've never watched late night PBS, then you might have missed him, and if you have, then then you &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt;.  If you've never heard of him and you're missing his hour-long broadcast this week with Hilary Clinton, then this is your opportunity to see him in person!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is at Brown at 5pm, and from what I understand the auditoruim is small, so get there EARLY!!! I really wish that Brown would put these things in larger auditoriums and make them at times that working people can get to. I hope I can make it! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Smiley is the host of the late-night television talk show Tavis Smiley on PBS and The Tavis Smiley Show from Public Radio International. He has written 14 books, including his memoir, What I Know for Sure: My Story of Growing Up in America, which was a New York Times best-seller. His most recent book, Accountable: Making America As Good As Its Promise, published last year, examines issues America faces and addresses how political leaders, corporations and, finally, American citizens themselves can enforce accountability and cause change. The lecture, free and open to the public, begins at 5 p.m. in the De Ciccio Family Auditorium, Salomon Center for Teaching. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://news.brown.edu/pressreleases/2010/01/smiley" target="_blank"&gt;http://news.brown.edu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Posted as an FYI - You are on your own if you want to go, or post a message on the message board if you're looking for someone to go with</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265494109000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264602064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Martin Luther King Jr. Lecture: Tavis Smiley at Brown!!!!</name><id>12438023</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265320800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/12438023/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/8/global_12822616.jpeg</photo_url></item>