<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On July 25, 2006, the CCRI Roleplayer's Guild is going to host the second weekly Dungeons and Dragons campaign day, beginning at 12 noon and ending at 6-7PM. Players can expect to find adventure throughout the Elsir Vale, fight vicious goblinoids and dragonspawn, and roleplay with a myriad of supporting characters and players. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the title indicates, we're following the WotC published adventure: &amp;quot;The Red Hand of Doom&amp;quot;. As it stands, the party is close to finishing the first part of five. After arriving in the Elsir Vale, the group was ambushed by a small warband of hobgoblins, supported by a pair of summoned hellhounds. Quickly dispatching the raiders, the group arrived in Drellen's Ferry, and were speedily recruited to stop the continuing raids on the town. After hiring a guide, they made their way to Vraath Keep. Scouting ahead, they identified and killed the bugbear leader of the local warbands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can bring a 6th or 7th level character, using resources from the following rulebooks:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All 3.5 Core Rulebooks&lt;br /&gt;Players Handbook 2&lt;br /&gt;Dungeon Masters Guide 2&lt;br /&gt;Forgotten Realms Campaign Setting&lt;br /&gt;Magic of Faerun&lt;br /&gt;Silver Marches&lt;br /&gt;Spell Compendium&lt;br /&gt;Eberron Campaign Setting&lt;br /&gt;Sharn: The City of Towers&lt;br /&gt;Races of Eberron&lt;br /&gt;Complete Warrior&lt;br /&gt;Complete Divine&lt;br /&gt;Complete Arcane&lt;br /&gt;Complete Adventurer&lt;br /&gt;Heroes of Battle&lt;br /&gt;Unearthed Arcana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to play a unique or rare race, make sure to contact me beforehand. Otherwise, only things from the above books can be used. NO EXCEPTIONS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is normally found in the student lot, to the left of the main building. There is a guest parking area, but it's limited to 30 minutes only. RIPTA serves CCRI Warwick on the 22 and 30 routes from Kennedy Plaza in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ripta.com/schedules/view.php?route=22&amp;amp;direction=2" target="_blank"&gt;http://ripta.com/sche...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ripta.com/schedules/view.php?route=30&amp;amp;direction=20" target="_blank"&gt;http://ripta.com/sche...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is on the first floor, in room 1128. A map of the campus can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.ccri.edu/floorplans/warwick/01.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ccri.edu/f...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2295622</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540375000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1152882932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CCRI Roleplayer's Guild DnD Game- Red Hand of Doom</name><id>5023917</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1153843200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/5023917/</event_url></item>