<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>CT REIA Monthly Meeting - J.T. Foxx&lt;br /&gt;October 19th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm-9:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Crowne Plaza Hotel&lt;br /&gt;100 Berlin Road.&lt;br /&gt;Cromwell, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guest Speaker&lt;/b&gt;: J.T. Foxx (Entrepreneur, Teacher &amp;amp; Internationally Syndicated Radio Personality)&lt;br /&gt;How to Partner, Brand, Network and Market your Way to Millions when Banks are NOT Lending&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;J.T Foxx embodies the American Dream. Departing Canada in 2003 with nothing but a rusted out Ford pick up truck, he arrived to America with 940 dollars and the clothes on his back.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now just 5 years later, he has bought and sold over 500 real estate properties, started several very successful entrepreneurial businesses ventures and become a Internationally recognized speaker, all by mastering investing principles that are current with today’s market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J.T. is most recognized as very successful investor and a popular internationally syndicated weekend radio personality of the J.T. Foxx Show and the Canadian Wealth Show. His radio program features such celebrity guests as Senator McCain, Secretary of State, William Cohen, Jesse Jackson, Trump, and George Ross (Donald Trump’s right hand man), and celebrated authors like Robert Kiyosaki, author of Rich Dad, Poor Dad and Bob Proctor, author of The Secret and Mark Victor Hanson &amp;amp; Jack Canfield from the Chicken Soup for the Soul series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even though his recognition and success in business and radio continues to rise, J.T.’s true passion is teaching and reaching out to those who dream of achieving their goals. J.T. teaches the same practical real estate ideals he utilizes daily himself and that actually get results in today’s rapidly changing marketplace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J.T.’s goal is to change the business and investing landscape by teaching powerful up to date partnering, marketing, branding and networking techniques which beginner and advanced entrepreneurs will be able to take their game to the next level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;A few of his topics include:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• How to Network like and with Millionaires &amp;amp; Multi-Millionaires&lt;br /&gt;• How to find partners to fund your business ventures&lt;br /&gt;• How to break the ice with partners with 1 specific question that works every time.&lt;br /&gt;• How to develop an impactful 29 second presentation&lt;br /&gt;• Learn how to brand yourself and your business&lt;br /&gt;• How to network with the rich, the famous and tycoons of industry.&lt;br /&gt;• How to multiply your partners so you never have to look for funding ever again&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J.T. is beloved by his audiences for his results oriented, no-nonsense approach to business and to life but most importantly because he gives them the tools, both to make more money in today’s market and make a powerful impact in this world for the better. Partners are the key to successful, profitable, investing and fun in today's market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register now for this meeting at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=205" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256248268000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253572583000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA October Monthly Meeting with J.T. Foxx</name><id>lvqfjymnbzb</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255987800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/11430756/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/1/global_10975025.jpeg</photo_url></item>