<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>381 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.394272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rosebud Bar &amp; Lounge</name><city>Somerville</city><id>4400732</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Girls -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MARCH 9 UPDATE:MEETING PLACE IS ROSEBUD...I'LL BE WEARING GREEN/WHITE JESTER HAT. CELL IS 617-645-7272...GISELLE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is more "fun" than "run". Please join me on my first foray into running with this 5K through Davis Square on Sunday March 10 at 11 am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to come watch, cheer, participate. Runners vary from complete newbies who walk to competitive runners. Many dress in green and St. Patrick's themed costumes...I plan on doing so also. There is plenty of drinking and partying afterwards, as the local bars co-sponsor the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details can be found on the website at: &lt;a href="http://www.baevents.com/rasnaheireann/info1.php"&gt;http://www.baevents.com/rasnaheireann/info1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll plan on meeting in front of the Rose Bud diner both pre and post race. I'll send out my info closer to race day. Again, this is meant to be FUN. But also, for anyone who embarked on a New Year's resolution to get in shape or do more, this would be great incentive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Update: Feb 10, 2013.  I admit that I've done zero training and am now totally focussing on the "fun" side of this run...ie. will be in costume and more looking forward to the bar afterwards.  There are bands playing in the area - anyone have a suggestion for which of the bars will be big enough to accomodate all of us afterwards?  Our options are: The Burren, The Sligo, The Foundry, Joshua Tree, Orleans Bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, do me a favor and put in your RSVP whether you will be there to run or to just cheer on/party.  I'm hoping someone from the cheering group will be kind enough to hold the bags and personal items for the runners...  Please also be updated about your RSVP...we'll be gathering before the run and after and I don't want to leave anyone behind but also don't want to be waiting around for no-shows.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362937905000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357746365000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>St. Paddy's Day 5K Fun Run/Walk in Somerville (and subsequent Bar crawl)</name><id>98728982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1362925800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/98728982/</event_url></item>