<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>623 Trapelo Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.404760</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John M. Sullivan Post #10334 - VFW</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1114517</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.217073</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Cost: $10 in advance, $12 at the door&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s been some time since the BBTC hosted a dance. Well, due to popular demand, we are having a fall Harvest Dance! Greet your fellow Beanstalks and members of the public while dancing to great tunes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This brand-new, beautifully appointed hall has hardwood floors throughout for dancing, a full bar, and plenty of parking. It has the distinction of being the first VFW post in Massachusetts to be named for a Vietnam veteran. Their bartender will take care of all your beverage needs, there will be plenty of munchies, and a DJ will provide tunes to keep your feet happy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tell a friend--bring a friend--and BE THERE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To register in advance, please send a check for $10 per person to Susan Huffman, BBTC Registrar, 27 Indiana Terrace, Newton, MA   02464-1314.  OR pay via Paypal via the option when you RSVP to this posting, and enter your payment as a &amp;quot;donation&amp;quot; along with your credit card information. (It’s not really a donation, but that’s the language Paypal uses, so we humor them.) Forward your emailed payment receipt to registrar@hubtall.org along with the names of those registering. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 95: Take exit 28, Trapelo Road, east toward Waltham/Belmont. Continue eastward on Trapelo. The building is on the corner of Trapelo Road and Marguerite Ave. Parking is behind the building as well as on Marguerite Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 2: Take exit 54, Waltham Street, and follow southward, crossing Route 2. Waltham Street will change to Lexington Street. At junction with Trapelo Road, turn left and continue on Trapelo. The building is on the corner of Trapelo Road and Marguerite Ave. Parking is behind the building as well as on Marguerite Ave.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sylvia</member_name><member_id>4519074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marie A</member_name><member_id>4623326</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259969603000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257651391000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harvest Dance</name><id>11822662</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258849800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/11822662/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/b/global_3153499.jpeg</photo_url></item>