<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>171 Newbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350754</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pucker Gallery</name><city>Boston</city><id>802377</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079131</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Naftali Bezem: Miracles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is I: Ceramics by Kang hyo Lee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;In the Bible the most important experience was a miracle, in our time it is energy. What kind of energy do we need to have an idea? I think a color, a spot or a line and how they come together &lt;i&gt;is a fusion of many ideas. That is what gives us pleasure, like in a play. This play of joy which is different and common for each visitor and which makes us all partners of creation. This could bring us closer again to a miracle.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Naftali Bezem&lt;br /&gt;May 2008 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kang Hyo Lee works from the punchong approach of putting white slip over dark stoneware clay and embellishes with strong, vigorous brushstrokes and finger wiping. Kang Hyo Lee studied ceramics at the College of Fine Arts at Hongik University, in Korea. After receiving his degree, he spent three years studying the making of Onggi ware. Onggi are traditional Korean clay vessels which have developed throughout Korean history and are an important part of Korean culture. His current pieces, ranging from small vase forms to gorgeous platters and larger traditional jars, are energetic and wonderful examples of the punchong technique.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Kang Hyo Lee's works are represented in numerous international museums, including the British Museum, the Musée Royal De Mariemont (Belgium), the Victoria &amp;amp; Albert Museum (United Kingdom), the Asian Art Museum of San Francisco, the International Ceramic Art Museum (France), Art Complex Museum (Massachusetts), and the Art Institute of Chicago (Illinois).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 20th of May, 2006 was the opening of Kang Hyo Lee's first exhibition at Pucker Gallery, The Beauty of Imperfection. As Phil Rogers wrote for the exhibition catalogue of Kang Hyo Lee's work, &amp;quot;here is a piece of ceramic, made by man, that is so close to the earth, so close to nature that it has become the same thing.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a purple flower pin.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cristin</member_name><member_id>603739</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229643669000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225464741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opening Reception for 2 New Exhibitions at Pucker Gallery on Newbury St.</name><id>9066965</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228593600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/9066965/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/7/global_6114631.jpeg</photo_url></item>