<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*** &lt;b&gt;Weather 2/6/09 update&lt;/b&gt;: We have snow on the ground but temperatures will be up to 52 F! So things will be wet and warm weather. Temperature starts at 43 F and heads up. Will be partly cloudy with light winds and only 10% chance of any rain. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A moderate Hike of 7 to 8 miles in no more than 5 hours on the Chatfield Trail which is partially in the Cockaponset State Forest south of Rte. 80 and Chatfield Hollow State Park.  Some climbs, some views, some caves too! Length of hike will be adjusted to ensure we return to cars in no more than 5 hours. We go slower, we don't go out as far on the Chatfield Trail. This means we are back to the cars no later than 3 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well meet at 10 AM at the parking area in Chatfield Hollow State Park just inside the park entrance (see park hiking map below). There should also be parking for 6 cars on the south side of Rte.80 at the trailhead. We will walk across Rte. 80 to one fine trailhead and begin our adventure. We will follow the blue trail (Chatfield Trail), descend to base of 40' cliff which should have ice falls, scramble through glacial boulders and crevasses and under overhangs. we'll then loop around on the alternate orange/blue trail and then back to the blue trail. Then we hike by and over various ledges, cliffs, and boulders to no further than River Rd. and return staying completely on the blue trail. How far we go towards River Rd. depends on how we are doing for time (turning point is no later than 2.5 hours out). We'll have some different sights on the way back as we won't use the alternate trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a &lt;b&gt;potluck&lt;/b&gt; at a members home (Barbara's) right after the hike. Those who come on the hike will get directions to her place then. Please get together your offering and it might be a good idea to coordinate with Barbara. We'll be combining with another meetup for the potluck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Things you should bring:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Wear layers -for warmth (avoid cotton material)&lt;br /&gt;* Gloves -cold, may need hands for climbing&lt;br /&gt;* Warm hat&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproof and warm boots&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Strongly advised to bring traction footgear like MICROspikes&lt;/b&gt; -for icy conditions&lt;br /&gt;* Quart or two of water&lt;br /&gt;* Some trail food/lunch&lt;br /&gt;* Daypack -to carry stuff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we get snow before the hike, be advised to dress appropriately (e.g. gators, snow pants, maybe even snowshoes if a lot)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In pre-Colonial times, Indians frequented the valley in considerable numbers for purposes of fishing and hunting. Many artifacts found in the vicinity of Indian Council Caves indicated that Native Americans sought refuge in the jagged ledges and held tribal gatherings amid the rock recesses and overhangs. An Indian trail paralleled the brook, winding through the trees and along what is now the park road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/l=41.365;g=-72.5845" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(approximate lat=41.365, long=-72.5845)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Partial hiking map&lt;/b&gt; (shows only park trails and north end of Chatfield Trail at Rte. 80)&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/chatfieldhollow.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chatfield Trail map&lt;/b&gt; can be found on &lt;b&gt;page 87&lt;/b&gt; in the current 19th ed. &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Connecticut Walk Book East&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; by the Connecticute Forest and Parks Association.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on Chatfield Hollow State Park&lt;/b&gt; (includes general directions)&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325182&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dogs on the hike?:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs on a leash are permitted. Health regulations require that pets be kept off the beach and out of the water in the swimming pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this hike is Kevin S so please direct questions on the hike to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237043542000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235504027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike of Chatfield Trail in Killingworth CT</name><id>9813261</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236438000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/9813261/</event_url></item>