<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Maltese lovers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to everyone for attending today's Meet.  We had a good turnout despite the absolutely gorgeous weather outside!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We welcome new participants Barbara and Joe Murphy, and their absolutely adorable three Malts, Finian, Alex and Andy.  we also enjoyed meeting Michelle Overhulser and her daughters, Christy and Holly, along with their cutie, little Beamer (BMR).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was  good to see Maureen and Reno again, the latter fresh from his neutering operation, but frisky as anything.  Also, congratulations to Ali and Mike for sponsoring a successful heart operation for their Lexi, the tiny Maltese they own, along with Tasha and Penny.  Done at Tufts, this amazing state-of-the-art operation involves ridding Lexi of a heart murmur with a new coil procedure.  Tufts pronounced the operation a total success and now Lexi is full of energy and running her household!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ANGELS GLOW was once again a topic of discussion, because several owners have been trying it out.  Karen Dilando brought her lovely Maya and Haley, whose tear stains are totally gone, due to this product.  The link is below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.angelsglow.com/success.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.angelsglow...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next Maltese Meet will be May 14th, the second Sunday of the month.  Please note that this is different from our usual routine, but was necessary because Especially for Pets has a microchip session scheduled the afternoon of the 7th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maltese best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1147194126000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1144001227000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Maltese May Meetup</name><id>4891036</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1147021200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/4891036/</event_url></item>