<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1996 Park Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.750000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 523-5477</phone><name>Brazil Grill Churrascaria</name><city>Hartford</city><id>409919</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.699997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You can go to the 'other one'. You know, the churrascaria in West Hartford that gives you a little light you turn over to red when you want them to walk by and slice off a tiny piece of meat. They're also the ones that charge you an arm and leg when you walk out too. But if you're looking for the 'real deal', you'll love Brazil Grill. Here's how it works: Walk in and grab a plate. To your left are your sides which change daily: rice, beans, polenta, collard greens, squash, yucca floured squash, fried potatoes, codfish casserole, fried bananas, okra, etc. Once you've piled on a little bit of everything, you walk to the fire pit and order your meat. The 'pit master' (I'm sure there's a real word for his position, but I don't know it) piles on as much lamb, sirloin, chicken wrapped in bacon, chicken hearts, wings, and chicken sausage, pork loin, beef ribs, as you want. Just tell him how you like it - rare, medium, or well done. By this time, your dish is pretty full and you're ready to weigh it. The total? $7.00 - $8.00 for a supersized plate. Take your receipt, but don't pay yet, because you'll want to go back for some flan, rice pudding, corn pudding, coconut pudding with plum, or passion fruit mousse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brazilgrillhartford.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Brazil Grill Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer, Judy&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195579427000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193222843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brazil Grill Churrascaria</name><id>6607908</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195344000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/6607908/</event_url></item>