<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Both of our kayaks are rented for this trip. You can rent a boat from EMS in Portsmouth (or some other place) and still come with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paddle up Chauncey Creek - Then enjoy the freshest lobster in the world!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/3/5/event_9794645.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We'll launch from Kittery Point harbor with amazing views of islands, lighthouses, and the sea. We'll paddle up scenic and protected Chauncey Creek, under bridges and through a tunnel, entering Rachel Carson Wildlife Refuge.  Within the refuge, we'll continue through a beautiful salt marsh and into the romantically named, &lt;strong&gt;Brave Boat Harbor&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/e/d/0/event_120444272.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the creek passes into &lt;strong&gt;Rachel Carson Refuge&lt;/strong&gt;, it begins to twist and turn back on itself through the salt marsh, finally opening up into a small, protected bay where the remnants of an old railroad bridge can be seen.  There will be plenty of birds and other wildlife to spot along the way, and a great place to eat once we return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/e/2/event_120440962.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;After our trip, we'll stop at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chaunceycreek.com/"&gt;Chauncey Creek Lobster Pier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to eat, drink, and celebrate our return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As far as I'm concerned, Chauncey Creek is the &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; place in the area to eat fresh lobster, which are kept in tanks continuously circulating with fresh ocean water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/1/d/c/event_120445052.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may bring your own alcohol, salads, and anything else not on their menu. (Enoteca has a good selection of wine and beer.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;~Ask Larry about rental kayaks if you need one.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;~Boats shorter than 12 feet: you can use them but they're not recommended.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~This will be a mostly calm water paddle and the current shouldn't be strong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~Beginners are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boat Ramp Etiquette&lt;/strong&gt;: Park and unload your boat away from the main ramp area.  Then, carry your kayak down to the water and place it off to the side until ready to launch.  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Keep access to the boat ramp open at all times&lt;/span&gt;.  Kittery Town Launch Fee: $5 additional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/6/e/event_120441102.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Parking: There is some parking at the town dock. More parking is available across the street in the lot owned by Enoteca Market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fee is for planning and administrative expenses only. We will not have a registered Maine kayak guide on this trip and each participant is responsible for his or her own safety. (Wear a PFD at all times!)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/d/0/event_12951920.jpeg" width="148" height="194" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Unless otherwise specified, refunds for timely cancellations will be processed the day after the event.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Photo is of Enoteca when it was Frisbee's Market.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/messages/boards/thread/13601461/0/#48171231"&gt;PS - Click here for an explanation of fees.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338254471000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316180472000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Voyage to Brave Boat Harbor (&amp; Lobster)!</name><id>33791462</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338046200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/33791462/</event_url></item>