<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>158 South Bend Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.873936</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Galway Bay Irish Pub</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>8483282</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.372131</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Happy Hour series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the events and restaurant scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Galway Bay Irish Pub &lt;br /&gt;

 Located in Pawtucket next to the Pawsox Stadium on South Bend St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;" Galway Bay Irish Pub is located in Pawtucket next to McCoy Stadium. Perfect place to start and end baseball games, concerts and more. You'll find friends you never realized you had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pub has 2 dart boards, and they host Karaoke from 9 to 12 on Mondays according to the interwebs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pawsox game starts at 7:05, Some of us will be heading to the game around that time.  Everyone is welcome to stay at the pub, or come join us at the Pawsox game.  We'll make sure to keep our location at the game posted in the Meetup comments.  &lt;span&gt;This game is the last of a 4 game series over the weekend with the Leighigh Valley IronPigs (Phillies farm team?)&lt;/span&gt; The Pawsox are having a great year. They are 1/2 game back in their division and currently the IronPigs are 2 games behind them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If don't want to go to the game, and can help out hosting please let us know.  As we'd like to have someone "host" at the pub until at least 8.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John'll be wearing a "Hokies" jersey and VT hat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8642703</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher</member_name><member_id>10240270</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344391721000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343756479000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Galway Bay Irish Pub &amp; the Pawsox vs IronPigs</name><id>75705452</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344290400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/75705452/</event_url></item>