<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Corner of Church and Elm Streets</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.308235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Haven Green</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1049257</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.924166</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Cheer for our own Party Express member Richard as he takes on the challenge of the 2009 New Haven Labor Day 20k Road Race.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2009, approximately fourteen bands (including bag pipes and DJs) will line the 20K course. 5K runners will enjoy the music of four bands. Runners, in the past, have enjoyed the bands and more bands are planned in the future. A &amp;quot;spirit&amp;quot; contest encourages the runners' enjoyment of the race. The large crowds, posters and music generated by the contest are greatly appreciated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting on the picturesque New Haven Green, all three courses are flat and fast. The 20 kilometer course winds its way past Yale University, residential neighborhoods, scenic waterfront areas and large city parks. The 20K course has 2 hills and the rest of the course is flat with few turns. The 5K and 1/2 mile races have no hills. Khalid Khannouchi's and Collen De Reuck's World Records set in 1998 race attest to the ease of the course. Carol McLatchie and Paul Pilkington set American 20K Masters Records in New Haven. Trina Painter set an American record winning the 1995 race. In 1997, Keith Andersen ran the fastest 20K ever by a man in the Master's division.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids Fun Run Start&lt;br /&gt;8:15 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5K and 20K Start&lt;br /&gt;8:40 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post-race party with live music&lt;br /&gt;9:00 - 11:30 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5K awards&lt;br /&gt;10:30 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;20K awards&lt;br /&gt;11:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Runners that I know will be attending and their bib numbers: &lt;br /&gt;#1211 Richard (Party Express member) &lt;br /&gt;#766 My cousin Kim &lt;br /&gt;#56 My good friend Peter Halsey &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you know any runners? Are you a Party Express member that's running? Please respond and tell us your bib number so we can cheer you on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newhavenroadrace.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newhavenro...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Leave comments or suggestions as to whether you'd like to be along the route or at the finish line.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joanne</member_name><member_id>9085331</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252721311000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251424903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Haven Road Race-- Labor Day, September 7,  2009</name><id>11220929</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252324800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/11220929/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/0/9/global_10421385.jpeg</photo_url></item>