<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It has been a rough few months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am going to have some time off in August, so at the Meet Up Monthly &lt;br /&gt;Meeting on July 19 we decided that we will take a weekend trip to &lt;br /&gt;Salem during my time off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is still interest in going in October, then we might also go in &lt;br /&gt;October. &lt;br /&gt;If there is no interest in October, then I will cancel that trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be staying at the Comfort Inn in Danvers. &lt;br /&gt;(978) 777-1700 &lt;br /&gt;If you have AAA, then you can get a discount through them. &lt;br /&gt;You have to make your own reservation.&lt;br /&gt;I will be meeting Maribeth and her group at the hotel later Friday night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be later updates and reminders of the Salem Trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bestmaps.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bestmaps.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.bestmaps.com/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will park either in front of the Salem Mall or in the &lt;br /&gt;Parking lot between the Mall and the Visitors Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will try to fit in three or four attractions for the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We might need to break off into different groups &lt;br /&gt;Depending on who wants to go where.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will arraign to meet each other at the Visitors Center &lt;br /&gt;at a certain time later in the afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of us might stay late enough to go on a Ghost Tour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you have any comments or questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A lot of us need a break with everything that has been &lt;br /&gt;happening. This is my break for a couple of days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions that I will be taking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(This depends on traffic, if I - 95 is busy then I will take back roads &lt;br /&gt;to I - 91.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I - 95 N to I - 91 N &lt;br /&gt;to I - 84 to &lt;br /&gt;Mass Pike 90 &lt;br /&gt;to Exit 22 &lt;br /&gt;I-495 &lt;br /&gt;to Exit 24 to &lt;br /&gt;(back roads to avoid the highways) &lt;br /&gt;Rt 20 Main Street &lt;br /&gt;(Massachusetts has hard to see signs so becare &lt;br /&gt;when trying to look for Rts.) &lt;br /&gt;To Rt 60 Linden Street &lt;br /&gt;to Rt 1 &lt;br /&gt;to Rt 114 &lt;br /&gt;To Hotel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rt 114 goes into Salem. &lt;br /&gt;I avoid Rt 114 in October because of the traffic going into Salem. &lt;br /&gt;I do not know if it will have traffic in August?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B &lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have my purple backpack with me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>maribeth</member_name><member_id>2893690</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251567624000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Coffee Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>coffee-397</urlname><id>570343</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Coffee Talk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248137626000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coffee Talk's Salem Trip on August 14 to16 </name><id>10919975</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250344800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/coffee-397/events/10919975/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/c/3/global_1719779.jpeg</photo_url></item>