<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Soldiers Field Road</address_2><address_1>Room: Aldrich 107</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02163</zip><lat>42.283400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>http://www.hbs.edu/about/visit.h</phone><name>Harvard Business School</name><city>Boston</city><id>875063</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.142700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event will feature a presentation by Dr. Ory Zik at Harvard Business School (Aldrich 107).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Zik is the Co-founder and CEO of &lt;a href="http://www.heliofocus.com" target="_blank"&gt;HelioFocus&lt;/a&gt;, an Israel-based startup developing and commercializing modular highly-efficient solar thermal solutions.  In January 2008, HelioFocus received its first round of investment from &lt;a href="http://www.israelcorp.com/Holdings/Energy/ICGreenEnergy.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;IC Green Energy&lt;/a&gt;.  Its technology is the result of 2 decades of research at the Weizmann Institute of Science and is exclusively licensed to HelioFocus. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Zik will discuss: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The challenge of building a solar startup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * commodity markets and cost reduction&lt;br /&gt;    * the dilemma of selling to utilities&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tech transfer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * from academic paper to commercialization&lt;br /&gt;    * compare and contrast life sciences and cleantech&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Israel's solar legacy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Israel's entrepreneurial and tech capabilities applied to cleantech&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Harvard Business School and a campus map are available at &lt;a href="http://www.hbs.edu/about/visit.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hbs.edu/ab...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is sponsored by Combined Jewish Philanthropies (CJP), in collaboration with the HBS Business &amp;amp; Environment Club, Harvard Kennedy School's Israel Caucus, MISTI MIT-Israel, and the New England Israel Business Council.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ory Zik&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Zik is Co-founder and CEO of HelioFocus.  From 2001 to 2006 Ory was the Founder and CEO of QuantomiX Ltd. The company solved the problem of imaging live samples with an electron microscope. Prior to that Ory led a spinoff of El-Mul technologies where he developed a nanotube- based electron source. In 1998, he developed a solar thermal technology at the Weizmann Institute of Science. This was done while consulting to international environmental organizations on clean technologies. Ory holds B.Sc. (cum laude) in Physics and Mathematics from Tel Aviv University as well as M.Sc. (cum laude) and Ph.D. in Physics from the Weizmann Institute of Science, in Israel, where he received the Feinberg physics award and the Amos De Shalit physics prize. Among his not for profit activities, Ory was the scientific director of Israel’s National Museum of Science.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Shapira</member_name><member_id>6110717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235693278000</updated><rating><average>3.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-israel</urlname><id>1175193</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>100</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230145784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Solar Energy Startups - the Israeli Perspective </name><id>9384939</id><headcount>103</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234306800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-israel/events/9384939/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/2/e/global_6736654.jpeg</photo_url></item>