<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>730 Centre St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.310830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 983-5177</phone><name>JP Seafood</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>831692</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114622</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Getting rained on doesn't sound fun (especially with a chance of thunderstorms) - so we're skipping Recess and heading to JP for brunch! Join us even if you weren't planning to be at&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/events/17521346/"&gt;Recess for Justice&lt;/a&gt;. Arrive by yourself or bring your hungry friends!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP so we have an accurate head count for the restaurant.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

JP Seafood serves traditional American breakfast dishes PLUS you can choose from their sushi menu. Including lots of vegan/vegetarian options. From personal experience and based on reviews like &lt;a href="http://bostonist.com/2008/12/05/brunch-jp-seafood-cafe.php"&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt; we know you're going to enjoy it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look no further if you're seeking like-minded folks to share a side of pancakes with, want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while enjoying omelets or savoring sushi, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in. If you want to build a strong cross-issue social justice movement, SoJust is for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free parking is available behind the restaurant or across the street in the lot behind the liquor store. Nearest T stop is Green Street on the Orange line. Bus route: 39&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 SoJust is all about building a cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston. We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. We focus on creating welcoming spaces that foster relationship-building across issue silos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SoJust isn't a non-profit 501(c)(3).&lt;/strong&gt; We're a grassroots volunteer-run member-supported cross-issue progressive community that's been growing steadily since August 2006. We have over 1750 members, we've hosted 95+ events and we manage an online hub of progressive events and resources at www.sojust.org. If you've benefited from this cross-issue progressive network please contribute the suggested annual membership fee of $25. You may do this &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/dues/" target="_blank"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; or at any of our events. Thank you for helping us continue to provide a space for like-minded progressives of all stripes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309018814000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308876062000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch for Justice (Recess Cancelled)</name><id>23322101</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309014000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/23322101/</event_url></item>