<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Public Library - at Copley</name><city>Boston</city><id>872472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A race for...LOVE?!?!  YES!  Because every day is Valentine's Day, we are celebrating together, the day after V-day, with the first-ever ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;LOVE RUN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt;and Mixer at Lir Pub!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Sunday, February 15th &lt;br /&gt;Run start time: 3:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Run start location: Boston Public Library main steps (facing Dartmouth Street)&lt;br /&gt;***Run end location: &lt;a href="http://lironboy.ipower.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Lir Irish Pub and Restaurant &lt;/a&gt;(903 Boylston Street, Boston 02116)&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the library steps, we'll run 2.5 miles together through the city and the Common.  If you want to run longer, you can choose to do a loop about 4 mi along the Charles.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***The run will end at Lir Pub, where they will provide all us runners with FREE APPETIZERS!!!  Drinks are there for us too, but on you:)  To really do this shin-dig right, we will do a &amp;quot;green-light/red-light&amp;quot; theme, which means, upon entering Lir, we'll give you a green ribbon to wear if you are single, and a red ribbon to wear if you are taken.  You might even fall in L.O.V.E :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to ALL RUNNERS, no matter what club you run with or who you are attracted to (ha ha)...just come run and hang out afterwards!  Spread the word to other clubs, people, and the entire city of Boston.  If you can't run, please come meet us at Lir around 4pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE OTHER COOL THING about this event is that all proceeds will go towards &lt;a href="http://www.paveyourlane.com" target="_blank"&gt;Katie Visco's Run Across America &lt;/a&gt;(to inspire people to pursue their passion) and the charity she is supporting, &lt;a href="http://www.girlsontherun.org" target="_blank"&gt;Girls on the Run&lt;/a&gt;.  We'll have raffle prizes and silent auction as well.  Cool.  Katie's run will leave from Boston at the end of March, and needs your support.  If you want to support this cause but cannot make it on the 15th, you can donate &lt;a href="http://www.paveyourlane.com" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on the 15th!  Contact us if you have questions, and invite other running clubs too!  Oh, baby!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Love and Peace,&lt;br /&gt;Your Super-Stellar event planners who love you,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Katie Visco and Katrina &amp;quot;Tree&amp;quot; Bernstein&lt;br /&gt;(Proud members of The Most Informal Running Club Ever)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tree&lt;br /&gt;(617)447-1026                                &lt;br /&gt;bernsteinkatrina@hotmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Katie                                                                                                              &lt;br /&gt;(630)660-4597                                                   &lt;br /&gt;Katie.Visco@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet on main library steps facing Dartmouth street, and run from there!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tree</member_name><member_id>7444643</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235232242000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233985388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LOVE RUN and multi-running club MIXER at Lir Pub</name><id>9691896</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234729800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/9691896/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/9/3/global_7210755.jpeg</photo_url></item>