<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-325</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>447074</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP early!&lt;/b&gt; This meeting has only Joe Burns on the agenda.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For an IBD group there is no bigger star to have than Joe Burns.&lt;/b&gt; The New York IBD Group brings him back repeatedly and every time he is a huge draw. The last time was in February and he drew an audience of 165 members. They described his talk as &amp;quot;This is a not-to-miss presentation!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Advanced Charting by Joe Burns of Burns Investment Group&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Talk Description:&lt;/b&gt; Joe will cover Advanced Charting Techniques. He will review not only traditional buy points but also secondary buy points and teach early entry strategies to get you an edge by buying within the base.  We will also cover key aspects of fundamental analysis that can help an investor hold a potential big winner without getting shaken out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Joe Burns, the president of Burns Investment Group, is a dynamic young leader in the field of investor education. He spent the past ten years traveling the world for his former employer, Investor's Business Daily, giving seminars and workshops to investors of all skill levels. His innovative and informative teaching style has helped empower tens of thousands of individuals to take control of their own investing future by giving them proven rules for stock selection and precise strategies for buying and selling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe is a regular speaker at many international forums including The Money Show and The Traders Expo. Mr. Burns has been a frequent guest on CNN, CNNfn, Fox News channel, CNBC, and BusinessWeek TV, and he conducts interviews on nationally syndicated radio outlets year-round. You can also now find him as a featured on-air personality at moneyshow.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joe's Seminar:&lt;/b&gt; Joe Burns will be in Boston to deliver his paid investor seminar. A description of the same seminar delivered in New York City this month is viewable at this link: &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/web/Joe+Burns+NY+2008+Wkshop+Early+Reg+Flier.doc" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(If you have trouble accessing this description it is probably because you are not registered with our Google Group - BostonIBD. If so, go to &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt; and register; it is free.) We will update this description when the information is updated to reflect Joe's Boston appearance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208560332000</updated><rating><average>4.42000007629</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>100</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206008728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advanced Charting by Joe Burns of Burns Investment Group</name><id>7568647</id><headcount>99</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208386800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/7568647/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/e/global_938062.jpeg</photo_url></item>