<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>HELLO ALL FELLOW TRUTHERS,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the time has come for this meet up group to step up its efforts up&lt;br /&gt;a notch.  Sunday&lt;br /&gt;at 10 PM we will be hosting our 2nd telephone and internet chat (this feature is on the talkshoe site link below) conference call&lt;br /&gt;meeting.  This virtual meeting will be the 2nd test drive for a regularly&lt;br /&gt;scheduled meeting of the 911 Meet Up Group.  Please join us. This is an attempt at organizing the group to form a&lt;br /&gt;collective and diverse active group.  We are looking for 911 Truthers&lt;br /&gt;and Freedom Loving Individuals to step up and do more than complain on&lt;br /&gt;the internet! Each of us have the potential to create the changes that&lt;br /&gt;we want to see around us... But as a group we can utilize each other&lt;br /&gt;as resources to have that much more of an impact!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight's discussion will be covering the topics below and open format.  This is the test drive where we&lt;br /&gt;will be able to feel out the process and discuss how we will be moving&lt;br /&gt;forward.  What a great opportunity for us all to connect without having to&lt;br /&gt;take time out of our schedules and pay for a place to meet up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What:  2nd Weekly/Bi-Weely/Monthly 911 Meet Up Group Teleconference&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:  10 PM Sunday 02-15-09&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Wherever you are.  Take an hour/half hour/fifteen minutes of your&lt;br /&gt;time.  From your phone or computer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How:  Go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.talkshoe.com/talkshoe/web/userCreate1.jsp?pushNav=1&amp;amp;cmd=signup" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.talkshoe.c...&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;br /&gt;sign in.&lt;br /&gt;(Dont worry it is free.)&lt;br /&gt;Then go to this page where our call will take place:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.talkshoe.com/talkshoe/web/talkCast.jsp?masterId=38129&amp;amp;cmd=tc" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.talkshoe.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or call Phone Number: (724) 444-7444&lt;br /&gt;Call ID: 38129 from 10PM to 11 PM.  It's that simple&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us tonight for this important discussion and contribute your&lt;br /&gt;ideas and plans for the group.  Or just chime in briefly to express your&lt;br /&gt;support. You can also just listen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THANK YOU ALL AND HOPE TO SPEAK WITH YOU TONIGHT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This site has the ability to save a recording of the teleconference&lt;br /&gt;for people that have missed what has transpired BUT we will not be&lt;br /&gt;using this feature or authorizing any recording of tonight's&lt;br /&gt;conversations. If we collectively agree that this will be a helpful&lt;br /&gt;tool we will utilize this feature in the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have set the settings of the call for people to be able to use&lt;br /&gt;whatever colorful language they feel like using if the mood strikes&lt;br /&gt;you to do so. Although it would be best to not over indulge in that&lt;br /&gt;behavior so that we can have a productive meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your phone number will remain private to people on the call. We will work out the bugs again this Sunday. Join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris Hemenway&lt;br /&gt;781-588-6632&lt;br /&gt;hemenwayc@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark O&lt;br /&gt;1800capone@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;617 201 3334&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some topics that we would like to cover:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;1.  Meet Ups:  This is a meet up group and we are not meeting up.  What are the actions being posted?  Why are people not attending the proposed actions?  What types of actions would people be more interested in?  (I personally would like to initiate localized actions with no venue; like going door to door in your town, or from business to business, or street actions etc...  These obviously would employ different members of the group to meet up with other members locally.  Just a thought for the topic.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;2.  Interests and Goals:  911 Truth compared to everything else.  Where do we all fit into the equation?  How do we feel 911 Truth fits in with other topics, issues, and actions in waking people up and creating change in our community?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. I have contacted a local free paper about getting an advertisement in the paper. This may also enable us to partake in there email blast system. We will need a add layout and people to help pay for the add. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. I am considering contacting the organizers of the upcoming Roller Derby Saturday Feb. 28, 2009 (women only contestants... it is a fun event!) to pay for a table at the event. I think we should give away info and sell stuff with the intent of giving all of the profits to the fealgoodfoundation.com. We could also help publicize the upcoming  Dr. David Ray Griffin event. Details here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/290/messages/boards/thread/6152666"&gt;http://9-11.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5.  Lets see what else people suggest.  I am sure that I will come up with more as well by Wednesday.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236040134000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234381664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday free telephone + internet chat conference call 2/15/09 @ 10pm</name><id>9722095</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234753200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9722095/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/5/global_7275445.jpeg</photo_url></item>