<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>113 Goodnow Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.455643</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass Audubon's Wachusett Meadow Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Princeton</city><id>3918582</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.905052</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Bill will lead the group on an autumn shoot through the Wachusett Meadow Wildlife Sanctuary. There should be great color by then, and plenty to shoot through this Audubon property..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twelve miles of trails at Wachusett Meadow traverse vast meadows, woodlands, and wetlands. Brown Hill Summit, South Wachusett Brook, and Glacial Boulder are highlights among many other features. Wildlife is abundant in all seasons, and visitors may take advantage of opportunities to snowshoe, cross-country ski, and canoe in addition to hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$4 entrance fee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;From Rt 2:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Take exit 28 (Rt 31, Fitchburg/Princeton). Follow Rt 31 south for 3.9 miles to a blinking red light. Turn left at the light and follow Rt 31 and Rt 140 south for 1.8 miles to a blinking yellow light. Turn right and follow Rt 31 south for 2.8 miles to a steep hill and a blinking yellow light (center of Princeton). At the light, follow signs for Rt 62 west by crossing the intersection and bearing right (follow the road as it curves right on the far side of the common after the light). Follow Rt 62 west for 0.6 miles, and you will see the sanctuary sign on the right at Goodnow Road. Turn right on Goodnow Road, and the parking lot is 1 mile ahead on the left.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Rt I-190:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Take exit 5 (Rt 140, Sterling/W. Boylston). Follow Rt 140 north for 2.4 miles to the intersection of Rt 62 (blinking yellow light). Take a left onto Rt 62 west and follow it for 4.2 miles to a stop sign. Turn left on Rt 31 and go up the hill to a flashing yellow light (center of Princeton). Follow directions above from the "center of Princeton."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wachusett Meadow Wildlife Sanctuary&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

113 Goodnow Road &lt;br /&gt;

Princeton, MA 01541.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the entrance, 113 Goodnow Road.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill </member_name><member_id>8415746</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319482367000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318296470000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wachusett Meadow Wildlife Sanctuary Fall Shoot</name><id>36909732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319382000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/36909732/</event_url></item>