<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;    I would like to invite you all to a class that is being offered now for the first time to members of the meetup group. It is a more intensive class than our regular monthly Guided Meditation class, and would probably be of interest only for those who are seriously wanting to find a real spiritual path. The class is called Introduction to Christian Mysticism and Meditation. It meets every Tuesday evening for six weeks. There may be an opportunity for more advanced classes for those who complete the whole series and are interested in more. It is an intense and deep class, incorporating guided meditation at each meeting and a lesson and discussion of a topic from the ancient wisdom teachings that have been practiced by mystics through the ages. The class is designed to give an in-depth look at the Inner Mystical Path, which exists in every major religion and is the true path to finding God within, here shown as practiced in the Christian tradition. The class also provides instruction and opportunities to begin to experience first-hand the real presence of God inside oneself. It is a powerful, relevant, and potentially life-changing class. We are beginning the series this week. The class is free, but RSVP is required if you wish to attend. If you are highly interested in attending but cannot make the first class due to the short notice, send me an email or call me and we can talk about what arrangement may be made. Also, feel free to email me if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;Blessings to you all in this new year,&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233364024000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231001971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Class series: Introduction to Christian Mysticism and Meditation</name><id>9433730</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231288200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/9433730/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/f/global_1078639.jpeg</photo_url></item>