<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Sumner St # A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.151306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lucky Dogs Daycare</name><city>Milford</city><id>3738622</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.518684</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A step further - and better! - than Basic Obedience! All PIT BULL Basic Obedience!....... This is a formal class beginning Saturday, October 22nd (National Pit Bull Awareness Day!) at 11:00a at Lucky Dogs Day Care in Milford, MA to run 7 weeks (week one: handlers ONLY. Bring your dog to all consecutive classes)............. Topics to include ALL of your basic obedience cues - loose-leash walking, focus, sit, down, wait, stay, drop it, leave it, come - PLUS coursework geared toward these very special breeds, including ways (and TRICKS!) to make you and your bully better breed ambassadors (say that three times fast!)................ Cost is $225, paid up front, and space is limited. Price includes access to private practice workshops............... Open to dogs 16 weeks and up. Whether they have never been in a formal class before or are brushing up on their obedience/distraction work, if you have a pit bull, this is the class for you.............. Call April at (508) 634-3037 to sign up. Email justcassie101@gmail.com with any questions......................... See my listing here: &lt;a href="http://www.thumbtack.com/ma/bellingham/dog-training/dog-training" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thumbtack....&lt;/a&gt;. Also available for private in-home training and other group classes. Barbara Jean Crehan, our director of public relations, is also an experienced, GIFTED, NEBBC-endorsed dog trainer and can be reached at bjcrehan88@hotmail.com for private in-home consultations/training. Find her on facebook here: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100002032581804....................................." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;. We are also preparing to welcome our very own Lorena Lacasse, Vice President of the NEBBC to our training staff! She can be reached at newenglandbullybreedclub@gmail.com......................... Hope to see some of you on October 22nd! Happy Training!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319374517000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317261054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>All Pit Bull Basics Class w/Cassie-Leigh Stock, ABCDT at Lucky Dogs Day Care</name><id>35407392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319295600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/35407392/</event_url></item>