<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>October in Salem?! Are we insane?!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After learning of our group's desire to hit Salem right in the heart of the season, I decided we clearly needed outside help and an interesting way for both new and old Beyond Beantowner's to explore this mecca of Halloween in NE.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watson Adventures is offering a Scavenger Hunt in Salem the night of October 27th.  No, unlike most of the scavenger hunts of our youth, we will not be stealing articles of clothing or public property (the gravestones stay in the ground, people!!).  Instead we will be dividing into teams of six to answer questions about the history (fact and fiction) of Salem.  There are winners, and depending on turnout and the number of teams we contribute, we may have to have a little inner B &amp;amp; B competition complete with prizes.  Not to bribe you into signing up or anything:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to a lack of interest, we'll be just meeting for dinner and the hunt.  Folks interested in dinner should meet in front of the visitor center b/w 4:45 and 5 p.m. (closer to 5 for all us commuter rail takers:-).  Hunt only folks should plan to meet there at 6:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The visitor center is near Salem Commons, across 1A (Hawthorne Blvd) and next to the Museum Place Mall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To check out Watson Adventures and all of their Scavenger Hunt offerings in Boston, seek out the link below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://watsonadventures.com/schedule_boston.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://watsonadventur...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note this is the Secrets of Salem hunt (adults only), not the Witches of Salem Family Hunt held that afternoon at 2 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20 and must be ordered on your own, in advance.  I honestly, have no idea how popular these hunts are, or how many tix are available, but many have sold out in the past.  Hence, I'm posting early to give folks some planning time.  They are available online at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ovationtix.com/trs/performance.html;jsessionid=8D5B7E12524A432E678110885FEB0094?method=showPerformance&amp;amp;reset=user&amp;amp;perfId=77543&amp;amp;code=" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.ovationti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or if you're having trouble with that link, click on the time of the hunt (7 pm) off this site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ovationtix.com/trs/pr/6027" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.ovationti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is reported to be a disaster, so check out the MBTA schedule at www.mbta.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions?  Contact Lisa (vetchick)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beantown and Beyond</member_name><member_id>4494456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194375528000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188403785000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Secrets of Salem Scavenger Hunt</name><id>6263218</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193524200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/6263218/</event_url></item>