<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey folks -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leah said I should post this event here even though there is a Drupal meetup that night. If you're a Drupal person, well, go to that one. :) But, if you're not, here's an alternative, and developers/hackers/those who want to put heads together about freemium business models are encouraged to attend...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we don't have any Hidden Tech programs in the summer I've organized an interactive discussion on a topic that never loses importance for me: how creative types can use new digital tools to create new business models, often with "freemium" approaches.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; The event is this coming Wednesday the 17th at the Media Education Foundation room in Northampton, MA.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; It starts at 5:30, and it's a fundraiser for the Independent Music Conference so if you're so included you can bring a $10 donation for that. Noel Ramos of the IMC will be facilitating this discussion with me.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; The program itself will be a variation on ones I have done in the past including one at the IMC for musicians, but it's open to creative folks of all types (including developers and code hackers!) who want to share their successes with new "freemium" approaches and digital distribution methods. Of course we can talk social media tactics as well, but the goal of this talk is to cut a bit deeper into the issues, take an honest look at the obstacles as well as the opportunities, and come out with some practical ideas we can put to use. Noel will be presenting on crowdfunding tactics specifically.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; I'll paste in some more program information below from our event page. I'm travelling the next couple of days so if you have any questions about the program the best thing to do is to call me.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; Here's a link to the Facebook version of the event: 
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/?eid=263505557009514#%21/event.php"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/#!/event.php?eid=263505557009514&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; Hope to see some of you Wednesday...
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; Jon Reed
 &lt;br /&gt; 413 586 4590
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; "Artists across many fields are concerned about the future of intellectual property in an era of online content proliferation. However, with new digital distribution methods also come new opportunities, especially those who aspire to build their own brand or community. Please join us for a freewheeling discussion on how artists - including musicians, writers, and yes, code hackers - can respond to these trends and tap into new audiences.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; On Wednesay, August 17 at the Media Education Foundation in downtown Northampton, join Jon Reed, author of Free From Corporate America, and Noel Ramos, mastermind behind the Independent Music Conferences, for an interactive discussion on "making the most of free." We'll talk about the obstacles to monetizing, and also share our successes through creating kickass content and/or "freemium" business models, where some digital content is given away in order to increase audience and generate interest in paid products. We'll also talk about how socialized media and online communities can help to spark a creative person's career, with a focus on real-life examples. We're hoping to broadcast this event live as well, but to make sure to get in on the discussion, definitely come to the MEF in person!"
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; ---&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Jon Reed: Jon Reed is an independent analyst and podcaster in the SAP software marketplace. He advises clients on community-based marketing and organic search. In his free moments, he advises artists on how to better finance their own subversive projects. The author of Free From Corporate America: A Tactical Guide to Success on Your Own Terms and two other books, Jon is an expert in Print on Demand publishing. He is a founding Hidden-Tech Board Member.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the MEF discussion room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Reed</member_name><member_id>9974627</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313701982000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313354317000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open discussion on "Freemium" business models and digital media for business</name><id>29467421</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313616600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/29467421/</event_url></item>