<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1200 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.340000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-277-1200</phone><name>Holiday Inn</name><city>Brookline</city><id>311713</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120003</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>3 Visions. 3 Voices Monday, March 12, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(***Note: Pre-registration is required for this program- you must register through the CIPNE web site NOT the meetup site. If you would like to join CIPNE and attend FREE, download a membership form Non-members, students &amp;amp; assistants can register using PayPal &lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cipne.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to register...)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;John Earl has been shooting portraiture and people-driven images for the graphic design, advertising, and publishing industries since 1977. His experience encompasses news photography for major publications like Time, Newsweek, and the New York Times, as well as corporate assignments for Fortune 500 companies. The common denominator in John?s images is a delight in photographing ?subject matter that actually talks back.? www.johnearlephoto.com&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bruce Martin specializes in photography, multi-media, and installation art. In addition to widespread acclaim for his fine art creations, Bruce has become one of New England?s leading architectural and interior design photographers. His work can be seen in national and international magazines, as well as numerous books and collections. Among his passions is the use of photography to help put endangered buildings on the National Register of Historic Places.  www.brucetmartin.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tim Gray of Furnald Gray Photography is one of the premier magazine photographers in the Boston area, with his images frequently appearing in publications like Boston, Inc., Health, CIO, and Fast Company. His work runs the gamut: executive portraiture, lifestyle, and studio photography. A born free agent, Tom is philosophical about the uncertainties of freelancing. ?No matter what happens,? Tim says, ?it?s better than a desk job.? www.furnaldgray.com&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When: Monday, March 12, 2007&lt;br /&gt;Where: Holiday Inn 1200 Beacon Street Brookline, MA&lt;br /&gt;Times: 6:30pm: Social ~ 7:00pm: Program&lt;br /&gt;Cost:&lt;br /&gt;CIPNE members FREE&lt;br /&gt;Non-members $35&lt;br /&gt;Students/assistants $15&lt;br /&gt;(Note: Pre-registration is required for this program&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to join CIPNE and attend FREE, download a membership form&lt;br /&gt;Non-members, students &amp;amp; assistants can register using PayPal &lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cipne.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to register...)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go To:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cipne.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to register&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173910129000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172670670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3 Visions. 3 Voices Presented by CIPNE</name><id>5521751</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1173736800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/5521751/</event_url></item>