<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1187 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.343877</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Temple Ohabei Shalom</name><city>Brookline</city><id>831141</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114520</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most important aspects of the rich Indian culture is food. Growing up in India in a close-knit extended family, both food and more importantly cooking, were important aspects of my life. The kitchen was always busy and there were always unexpected guests at the dinner table, partly because my mother is such a phenomenal cook.  To her, cooking was never a chore, it was something she loved to do.  Nothing made her happier than creating delicious, healthy food for her family.  Growing up, I always wanted to be part of the commotion and activity in the kitchen, and seeing the reaction of guests tasting the food inspired me to learn to cook the same meals, so that I could share them with others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have always been a huge advocate of cooking healthy meals without compromising on flavor.  The rich spices and ingredient set used in Indian cuisine are perfect tools to do just that! A staggering 31% of Indians are vegetarian. They can be that way because even healthy food can be transformed into delicious dishes using the right techniques and spices.  In this session we are going to learn a few such dishes - that are healthy yet packed with flavors!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First we are going to start with a delicious mango yogurt smoothie called Lassi. This will go perfectly with our healthy mouthwatering appetizer - chicken kebabs.  The kebabs will be made using lean chicken breasts marinated with mint, ginger garlic, sour cream and spices. For our main course we are going to make a flavor-packed vegetable korma, made from an assortment of vegetables, nuts and exotic spices, to be server over steamed rice. We will finish off with a healthy but hearty rice pudding that can be served warm in winter and chilled in summer.  It’s going to be a healthy meal you won’t want to miss!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This celebration is $40. Mastercard and Visa are accepted. Must buy by 1/20 so we can prepare for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The money goes to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Renting the kitchen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buying the food&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Helping with our nonprofits yearly Meetup fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This healthy eating fundraiser will also provide:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future volunteer events like the Pet2K charity walk to benefit a local animal shelter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;create jobs (one of our goals is to create two jobs this year)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the limited size of the kitchen this celebration is exclusive for the first twenty people who buy tickets. Don't miss this celebration!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extraordinary value: Bring 4 family/friends with you and YOU get in for free!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a $70 dollar value at the Boston School of Adult Education. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;We stand behind your total satisfaction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Don't miss this celebration!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We anticipate cooking with you,  &lt;br /&gt;

 Priyanka and Josh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.S. There will be a special Indian FREE gift for you to bring home! :)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;The Boston Volunteers &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Big Enough to deliver, small enough to care &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Learn more: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonvolunteer.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.BostonVolunteer.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the popular group standing next to the door. I'll provide my cell for your convenience.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Priya</member_name><member_id>13210803</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1359510000000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Boston Volunteers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BigEnoughtoDeliver</urlname><id>1343564</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Volunteers. Big enough 2 deliver, small enough 2 care</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357606696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Popular Indian Cooking class. Bonus: special FREE gift for you! :)</name><id>98470212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359315000000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigEnoughtoDeliver/events/98470212/</event_url></item>