<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 S Water St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822195</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 621-5644</phone><name>The Wild Colonial Tavern</name><city>Providence</city><id>801946</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405316</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Happy Hour series! This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in Providence.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: &lt;strong&gt;Wild Colonial until 7:15 then heading a block over to the RISD Artisan's Cafe for Pecha Kucha! &lt;/strong&gt;Here's some Providence trivia - the RISD Artisan's Cafe is where Rafael's "used" to be before it "used" to be where the Capital Grille is! LOL! ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this week we're doing&amp;nbsp; twist on the 'ol MNM. Lucky for us, the PechaKucha that was scheduled for last Wednesday was postponed due to snow for this Monday! If you've never been, this is your chance! PechaKucha is a world wide phenomena with its roots in Japan, but our Providence PechaKucha has been the the only one world-wide to run consecutively without missing a month! For those that don't know, PechaKucha is a series of short presentations by anyone on any subject. Put simply: 6 minutes and 40 seconds of adult-style ...show &amp;amp; tell.  (20 slides every 20 seconds). So for those with short attention spans - its great! To be honest I was skeptical when I first heard about it, but I went to one in the Fall, it was great, and I've been wanting to go back. So I'm so excited that we'll be able to do both this Monday Night! &lt;strong&gt;We'll start at 6PM at the Wild Colonial and then at 7:15, walk up a block on South Water Street to the RISD Artisan's Cafe to mingle some more and watch the Pecha Kucha that begins at 8:20.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Obviously, you can join us for the PechaKucha or stay at the Wild Colonial as your mood suits.&amp;nbsp; For more info on the PechaKucha and the list of presenters click here:&lt;a href="http://www.pecha-kucha.org/night/providence/22"&gt;http://www.pecha-kucha.org/night/providence/22&lt;/a&gt;. So, let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296694540000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>We'll be meeting at 6PM at the Wild Colonial and then heading over a block at 7:15PM to the RISD Artisan's Cafe for the PechaKucha!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296339619000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Wild Colonial &amp; PechaKucha at RISD Artisan's Cafe!</name><id>16361343</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296514800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/16361343/</event_url></item>