<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;it's about friggin' time we hosted again! I can't give you many excuses why we haven't had one in quite awhile but I can best just say I have been exhausting myself fundraising for a charity race/run I'll be doing in July in California.  There. That's my time sucking excuse.  Plus the kid has been in soccer every Saturday, plus plus plus.  Screw it- it's ON- summer time baby, bring out your drinks, snacks, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do have one favor and it's small- we never ask for anyone to pay- we cover the monthly 15 bucks to run the group and we don't mind that one bit but I would ask, if possible, any donation you might want to contribute would be so appreciative- it will all go into my fundraising (for Crohns and Colitis diseases)- Steve, my husband has Crohns and if you didn't know that now you do.  We can discuss it when you come.  And honestly I won't hastle or beg or anything about donation but I will send out a thank you to Jennifer and Jim for their donations, so thanks guys.  Anything anyone else might be able to give will be mucho appreciated.  I'm almost to my half way of raising $4300. btw, my site- if you are able to donate- is  &lt;a href="http://www.active.com/donate/napa12newengland/napaMBolton" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.active.com/donate/napa12newengland/napaMBolton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you wanted to online.  In person cash or check is fine too.  again, no pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;now shall we get our Euchre groove on for this fine early beginning of summer night?? Yes, I believer we shall!! come one come all!! yay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mindy</member_name><member_id>4498017</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339988496000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Euchre Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>euchre-262</urlname><id>1040200</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The North of Boston Euchre Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338519032000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>a LONG OVER DUE meet up, here it comes (finally!)</name><id>67220142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339887600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euchre-262/events/67220142/</event_url></item>