<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 S Washington Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.522995</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-744-4080</phone><name>Hawthorne Hotel</name><city>Salem</city><id>754199</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.890053</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt;Salem Haunted Happenings&lt;br /&gt;Salem, MA, United States&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;10/30 UPDATE: I am sorry to be sending out another email but I got word this morning that Salem is expecting a huge crowds tomorrow they will start to shut down roads as early as 5:00pm (maybe sooner?).  This will put a cramp into our schedule so my thought is to forget about the meeting place in Peabody &amp;amp; take the train directly into Salem!  Here is the link to the website that will give you the train schedule: &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/riding_the_t/whats_new/?id=18417" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/r...&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of us that are in the Newburyport and surrounding we can take the 4:30 train out of Newburyport that will get us into Salem @ 5:02 we can meet at the train station at 4:00 that will get us there early enough for everyone to Meetup w/us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan on meeting at the Newburyport station please send me an email so I know to be looking for you.  If not then you should have my cell # and you can find us when we get into Salem or take a copy of the train schedule and Meetup w/us there.  Other than meeting at the train we are still planning on meeting at The Hawthorne Hotel at 5:30 or there about.&lt;br /&gt;If w/this update changes your plans to join us, please update your RSVP so we aren’t looking for you!&lt;br /&gt;Please send me an email or call my cell if you have any questions!&lt;br /&gt;Donna&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE: 10/29 I have sent out an email to everyone that has a yes RSVP for this event if you have decided to join us and you have RSVP'd after today please send me an email and I will send you the update!  OR if you didn't get my email please send me an email and I will send you the update! &lt;br /&gt;Thanks, Donna&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Nobody celebrates Halloween quite like Salem, Massachusetts. Whether you are seeking the changing leaves and cooler weather New England Autumn brings or the ghosts and goblins that Halloween is known for, you will find it all in Salem this October. We invite you to the most exciting month long Halloween Festival in Salem, Massachusetts!  If you would like to come in costume feel free, there will be a lot of other costumes so you will blend right in.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is A LOT going on in Salem, the city will be buzzing w/lots of interesting people and attractions, let’s meetup at 5:30 in time for us to get into town, avoid the crowds, grab something to eat and then walk around and check everything out.  If you are not able to meetup at 5:30 please contact one of the organizers and we can set up a better time for you to meetup w/us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Seeing that parking will probably be an issue, we will be setting up a car pooling meeting place.  I will update this as the event gets closer, please check back.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Or if you can't make the carpool meetup time/don't want to get a bite to eat, here are some directions to get you directly into town, there is some on street parking, a parking lots and parking garages scattered around the town.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Boston and Surrounding Communities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Take Route 1 North or Route 95 North to Route 129 South. Follow Route 129 South to Route 107 North, &amp;amp; follow into Salem.&lt;br /&gt;• Take Exit 44B to Lynn/129 East. Enter Goodwin Circle (Rotary) &amp;amp; take the Salem St/Peabody exit. Salem St turns into Lynnfield St. Lynnfield St turns into Washington St. At the intersection w/Main St, take a right, &amp;amp; follow signs to Salem.&lt;br /&gt;• Take Route 128 North to Exit 28 (Centennial Drive). Follow Centennial Drive &amp;amp; take right on Summit Street. Follow &amp;amp; take left onto Lynnfield St. Lynnfield St will turn into Washington Street. At intersection w/Main St, take a right, &amp;amp; follow signs to Salem.&lt;br /&gt;• Take Route 128 North to Exit 26. Follow Lowell St through Peabody Sq. Lowell St will turn into Main St. Follow signs into Salem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Cape Ann, New Hampshire, Maine, and all points North&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• Take Route 128 South to Exit 24. Follow Endicott St to intersection w/Route 35 (Water Street). Take Route 35 South to Route 114 East. Follow Route 114 East into Salem.&lt;br /&gt;• Take Route 128 South to Exit 22. Take Route 62 East to Route 1A South. Cross bridge, &amp;amp; follow Route 1A South into Salem.&lt;br /&gt;• Take Route 128 South to Exit 20. Take Route 1A South and follow into Salem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;We look forward to seeing you!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/devilish.gif' border='0' alt='devilish' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will update as the event gets closer</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257197868000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252844641000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go check out Salem!</name><id>11359396</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257024600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11359396/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/c/global_10673804.jpeg</photo_url></item>