<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 Canal Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364371</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-897-1337</phone><name>Boston Beer Works</name><city>Boston</city><id>842989</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060299</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;After the holidays, let's get together to "regift" the worst, tacky, useless holiday gift that we have received...You know you have them! Time to get rid of them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yankee Swap Rules&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It's really not that complicated but when questions arise it's nice to have a common framework.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants bring one wrapped gift (typically within a $20 or more price range) and places the gift in a pile/central location. Doesn't really matter what you bring as long as its costs $20 or more ---so the  good, the bad and ugly are all welcome! ---------Note: Even if you don't have anything to re-gift, pick up something for $20 or more and bring it anyways! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants draw numbers to determine the order in which they go. ( I might use playing cards)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The person who drew #1 goes first and must open a gift from the pile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The person who drew #2 goes next and has the choice of taking the gift opened by #1 or selecting an unopened gift. If #1's gift is taken player #1 must open another gift from the pile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The person who drew #3 goes next and can either take #1's gift, or take #2's gift, or open a gift. If player #3 takes an opened gift from player #1 or #2 then that player who is now giftless has the option of taking the other gift that was opened or opening a wrapped gift (they cannot take player #3's gift -- see rule 8).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play continues as such with players either taking/swapping a gift or opening one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When a gift is opened the round is over (you can't decide you don't like what you opened and decide to swap for something else).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any single gift can only be swapped once per round.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once the round for the highest numbered player has completed player #1 can swap gifts with any other player (for this final round there is no futher swapping after that).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hard core rule additions that can be useful if you have a large group. (Yes we'll use these too!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After taking your turn you &lt;strong&gt;must&lt;/strong&gt; keep your gift out where other players can see it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When it’s your turn if you touch a wrapped gift you &lt;strong&gt;have&lt;/strong&gt; to open it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a participant takes too much time deciding which gift to swap/open the remaining participants &lt;strong&gt;can&lt;/strong&gt; start counting aloud from ten down to zero. If zero is reached the participant must take the wrapped gift closest to them.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will be held upstairs at Boston Beer Works on Canal Street in Boston close to North Station T stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please update your RSVP no later than 24 hours prior to the event. I will be at the Beer Works at 1PM to meet people and we will start drawing numbers at 1:15PM. Please let me know if you will be arriving late.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Upstairs in the private room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Biagio</member_name><member_id>3847345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358181853000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357149016000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bad Gift "Regifting" Yankee Swap at Beer Works Boston (North Station)</name><id>97494892</id><headcount>12</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358100000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/97494892/</event_url></item>