<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Bridge St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02188</zip><lat>42.246058</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-331-0303</phone><name>Margaritas Mexican Restaurant &amp; Watering Hole</name><city>Weymouth</city><id>892407</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.934836</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Members and Guests of the SSDOMG for an Appetizer Social!  Back by popular demand, we had so much fun at our Appetizer Socials last year that we decided to run this type of event again.  Let's start off the month with a relaxed laid-back fun event where you can come and go when it suits your schedule. We'll be meeting at Margaritas on Route 3A in Weymouth on the Hingham line.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Margaritas serves delicious authentic Mexican appetizers, Margaritas and desserts, all made fresh in the restaurant.  It is a fun authentic Mexican restaurant.  They make all of their food from scratch in the restaurant which means it's fresh and can be made to order.  They import all of their Mexican items (from chairs to table decor to wall decor) from Mexican artists.  Some of their appetizers include Nachos, Chicken Baby Chimis (which is their most popular), Avocado Jack Crisp, Queso Fondito, and Roasted Vegetable Zarape.   The quesadilla entrees can be split among a few people.  There is also dessert, including a mouth-watering Fried Ice Cream.  Try a Margarita.....their specialty and the name of the restaurant!  Two types of Margaritas on the menu are Jose Cuervo Tradicional and a Sauza Extra Gold.  Margaritas hosts a monthly full moon party in the lounge in which they donate proceeds to a local charity.  They also have feature nights including Ladies Night on Thursdays which afford the women 40% off their bill and Trivia Night on Tuesdays. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With an appetizer social you can join us whenever you can get there, whether it be 4:30, 5 or 5:15.  If you would let us know approximately when to expect you in your RSVP Comments it would be helpful so we can keep an eye out for you.  Please check-in with an Event Organizer and pay your Event Fee upon arrival.  Since the purpose of an Appetizer Social is to sample different appetizers and socialize with others (as in get up and get on your feet and move around), we are planning to have multiple tables in an area that is all ours.  Arriving at 4:30 will afford us this opportunity as it's just before the dinner rush and we can have more opportunities to socialize and enjoy our appetizers.  As is our policy, you will still have to pay for your drinks, individually ordered food, any shared appetizers that the SSDOMG does not cover as well as tax and tip.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will run for at least a couple of hours from 4:30-6:30pm or later.  We will cash out between 6-6:30pm and start a new tab for those who might want to stay for dinner or to continue the Appetizer Social.  If you leave before we cash out be sure to consult a menu or ask one of the Organizers to help you figure out how much you owe and leave it with us so you can enjoy the rest of your Saturday night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a load off - it's Saturday!  Join us for a fun and relaxing Appetizer Social at Margaritas in Weymouth! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Evening Appetizer Social! &lt;br /&gt;Margaritas Mexican Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;765 Bridge Street &lt;br /&gt;Route 3A &lt;br /&gt;North Weymouth, MA 02191 &lt;br /&gt;P: 781-331-0303 &lt;br /&gt;W: www.margs.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizer(s)&lt;/i&gt;: Angela &amp;amp; Elaine &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Min/Max&lt;/i&gt;: At least 8 Yes RSVP's by 5pm on Wednesday, March 3rd.  / Currently no max. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Guests&lt;/i&gt;: Up to 2 per member! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Cost&lt;/i&gt;: Plan on approximately $8-$15pp for shared appetizers, including tax and tip, plus whatever you order for beverages and indvidually-ordered items plus tax and tip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Event Fee&lt;/i&gt;: Org Team and Annual Members - Free, Members and Guests - $2pp, A portion of the Event Fees will go towards the purchase of a shared appetizer.  (Last chance to become a 2010 Annual Member (AM) till the summer!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Price Range&lt;/i&gt;: Appetizers range from $6.99-$9.59.  Entrees are in the $10-$18 range. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/i&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps us to keep things simpler for everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/i&gt;: Friday, March 5th @ 8pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location Overview: Located in the Riverway Plaza on Route 3A, North Weymouth (southbound side) next to the Dollar Tree and CVS, just north of the Hingham line. Lowe's is also located there. (If you drive from Quincy you will be going over the Fire River Bridge.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Union St Braintree, MA 02184  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Head northeast on Union St toward Middle St  0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;2. Continue onto Commercial St  0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;3. Turn right at MA-53 S/Quincy Ave (This will be your 3rd set of lights.)&lt;br /&gt;4. Continue to follow MA-53 S  0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;5. Turn left at Commercial St  1.3 mi (Sacred Heart Church is on the corner and will be on your right after making the turn.)&lt;br /&gt;6. Turn left at Church St  0.3 mi (blinking light)&lt;br /&gt;7. Turn left at North St  89 ft (set of lights, gas station directly in front of you)&lt;br /&gt;8. Take the 1st right onto Green St  1.2 mi (Follow all the way, going under the bridge, through the lgihts and bending towards the left at the fork in the road.)&lt;br /&gt;9. Turn right at Bridge St/Massachusetts 3A S  0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;10. Margararitas is about 1/2 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;765 Bridge Street, Weymouth, MA 02191-2100 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For directions from other locations, go to the website www.margs.com and use map quest to obtain directions from your location. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at our tables.  Exact seating area TBD.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269812304000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264968249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Evening Appetizer Social!</name><id>12475520</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267911000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/12475520/</event_url></item>