<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Gracey Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06019</zip><lat>41.841767</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-693-0623</phone><name>Roaring Brook Nature Center</name><city>Canton</city><id>1402156</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.881076</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>October 16, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don Sineti&lt;br /&gt;with Steve Roys&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceeds go to the Roaring Brook Nature Center and the CT Cetacean Society,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before leaving for his annual tour of Alaska, Mystic Seaport’s balladeer and shanteyman, Don Sineti will perform a program of maritime music and roots folk songs that will amuse, entertain and educate listeners of all ages. As co-founder and past president of The CT Cetacean Society, now CSI (Cetacean Society International) Don continues to benefit the organization and our state by promoting awareness of whales and dolphins through his music programs, oil paintings and graphite drawings. Don performs globally, backing his superb voice by playing guitar and 5-string banjo. Tonight he’ll be joined by Steve Roys on harmonica, concertina, saw, jaw harp and harmony vocals. Don has performed with The Morgans, Finest Kind, Pure Americana and Chris Morgan. His three CDS are titled A Sailor’s Valentine, Ironmen and Wool Ships and Songs from the Dogwatch. Don will warm your heart with his Appalachian version of “The Cuckoo” and Woody Guthrie’s “Reuben James” and “Hard Travelin’.” He’ll warm up your vocal chords as you sing along on “Rolling Down to Old Maui,” “Farewell to Nova Scotia” and “Leaving of Liverpool.” Proceeds from tonight’s show will benefit the ongoing educational works of both Roaring Brook Nature Center and CSI.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 PM--$15.00 &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287328584000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287004668000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Benefit concert Don Sineti with Steve Roys at the Roaring Brook Nature Center</name><id>15100484</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287271800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/15100484/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_2930168.jpeg</photo_url></item>