<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-345</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>337655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Title: Day Trading Strategies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fausto Pugliese is the founder of Cyber Trading University (CTU), one of the world’s leading providers of online training and education for market traders and investors. This school has educated thousands of individuals in the art of day-trading, swing trading, Forex trading, and options and futures trading. CTU also provide classes on investing, technical analysis, trading psychology and other topics. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fausto was one of the original SOES bandits of the early 1990's, and one of the first independent traders to take advantage of the Direct Access Trading technology boom that started in 1987.  He acquired a wealth of knowledge from years of hands on experience, and working side by side with some of the most experienced successful traders in the industry. Today, Fausto continues to trade his portfolio, in addition to providing training and education to his students.  He has appeared on FOX News, CNBC, and dozens of radio programs in the US and all over the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda/Outline&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Successful Day Trading or Investing requires the Right Education&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Successful trading or investing requires having a winning system, sound money management practices, and the proper mental approach. Without any one of these key elements, you'll ultimately fail in these endeavors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this seminar, Fausto Pugliese covers all these important aspects, along with numerous other factors that can determine how profitable you'll be in the market. No matter if you're a daytrader, swing trader, or investor, this course will help you beat the tough learning curve, and establish a path to your success. Even if you've been trading or investing for a while and are just disappointed with your results, this course is for you.&lt;br /&gt;While receiving valuable information like this is helpful, in order to fully comprehend it, you need to see it in practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's why Fausto allows you to watch him live in action during market hours to reinforce what you've learned. Very few courses offer this important feature, because most professionals are afraid to demonstrate their techniques during real-time conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the presentation, you'll be able to interact with Fausto, ask questions, and receive personalized feedback all through the course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This rare opportunity to watch- and talk to- a highly successful trader will greatly benefit you when you start applying these lessons. &lt;br /&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;br /&gt;Being a profitable trader or investor is demanding work. However, Fausto has helped countless clients become wealthy in the market, and he can help you, too. But, you must be serious about this pursuit, and willing to learn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, if you're ready to maximize your trading or investing potential, enroll today for the free, no-obligation seminar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To put it in market terms, your risk level is nothing, while your reward level is unlimited.&lt;br /&gt;In this seminar you'll discover how to:&lt;br /&gt;• Identify ideal entry and exit points &lt;br /&gt;• Develop winning strategies &lt;br /&gt;• Spot market peaks and bottoms &lt;br /&gt;• Use charts to find potential trades &lt;br /&gt;• Properly deploy your capital &lt;br /&gt;• Determine risk/reward levels &lt;br /&gt;• Limit losses while maximizing gains &lt;br /&gt;• Decipher Level II quotes &lt;br /&gt;• Trade on Direct Access System &lt;br /&gt;• Stay out of market maker traps &lt;br /&gt;• Establish the optimal trading mindset&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google..." target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;or send email to Jeff Orrik at orrik@comcast.net &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to identify people who evidence expertise in particular interests we have virtual trading. &lt;br /&gt;To join in our virtual trading, go to this link for instructions and signup links: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google..." target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273665372000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272973075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Group Speakers Meeting: Fausto Pugliese</name><id>13378748</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273618800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/13378748/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/f/global_14829327.jpeg</photo_url></item>