<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Grove Hall</address_2><address_1>18-24 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02121</zip><lat>42.308500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-445-0324</phone><name>Biff's Lounge</name><city>Dorchester</city><id>1142262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello All! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry this is so last minute, but I have scheduled a meetup for this thursday. this meetup will feature this month's meet-up speaker, &lt;b&gt;Colette Kessler&lt;/b&gt;, part of the Business Development New England Lending Team for &lt;b&gt;ACCION USA&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ms. Kessler will speak about ACCION USA's micro-lending and financial education programs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for this great informational meetings - especially our small/ independent business owners!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Victoria &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ACCION USA is a leader in U.S. microfinance. The group empowers low-to-moderate income business owners through access to capital and financial education. With economic opportunity, these entrepreneurs—often minorities and women—can build assets, better provide for their families, create employment and strengthen their communities. Mico-loans typically range $7,000 - $15, 000.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ACCION is an innovator in financial access, pioneering many of the best practices and emerging standards in the industry. They provide a full range of management services, technical assistance and training, as well as investment and governance support to help financial institutions build institutional capacity and financial strength in order to serve low-income households on a broad scale.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Financial Education Program features financial literacy modules, to help low-income clients better manage their personal and household finances and become informed and effective consumers of financial services. &lt;br /&gt;Business training through our Dialogue on Business program – a set of award-winning modules that focus on building the skills of microentrepreneurs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Awards and honors include: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Presidential Award for Excellence in Microenterprise Development for Program Innovation awarded to the U.S. ACCION Network in 1998  &lt;br /&gt;Four star rating on Charity Navigator awarded in 2008.  &lt;br /&gt;New York City Neighborhood Achievement Award Winner in 2009 for Minority/Women-owned Business Enterprise Advocate of the Year  &lt;br /&gt;2009 Boston Business Journal Corporate Citizenship Partner of the Year honoree  &lt;br /&gt;NOVO Award from the Greater Miami Chamber of Commerce  &lt;br /&gt;Our parent organization, ACCION International, was recognized as a leader in microfinance by Philanthropedia's Microfinance Expert Mutual Fund.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Qiana Christian</member_name><member_id>5933597</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270335779000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270002893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Professionals of Color Business &amp; Social Networking Group March Meetup</name><id>13044175</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270162800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/13044175/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/global_5310243.jpeg</photo_url></item>