<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Final Update - 5:00PM on May 19th...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9 Guests who have said &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;13 Guests who have said &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP'd &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; and your plans have firmed up, now is the time to change your response to &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With 22 potential guests, we should have a really good time taking turns on the microphone.  If you prefer to just listen, that's OK also, there is absolutely no pressure to sing if you aren't ready.  We've sang songs from the Beatles, Billy Joel, Blondie, Fleetwood Mac, Al Green, Elton John and many other artists.  The song selection at the Limelight is terrific with music from the latest artsts.  But we also have oldies, hip-hop, pop, rock, standards, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, so you can get a few songs in.  I'll be there promptly at 8:00PM on Saturday evening.  Let the doorman know that you are there for the &amp;quot;Boston Karaoke Meetup&amp;quot; and he'll direct you to the Private Studio we have reserved.  Our reservation ends at 10:00PM sharp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have trouble finding our group on Saturday night, please call my cell phone at 617-429-6571.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Phil&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Dear Boston Karaoke Members:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been getting messages from many of you asking me to organize a Karaoke Event soon.  Your wait is now over, as I am announcing the next Boston Karaoke Meetup!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be this Saturday evening at the Limelight Studios in Boston.  This is a fantastic place and we have a private studio reserved for us.  Ask for the Boston Karoake Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not sure yet, then RSVP &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot;.  In my experience running many Meetups, I find that everyone else is waiting for others to sign up first, so by signing up yourself, you will create momentum for others to respond.  I thank you in advance for your help in getting things going.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, we've always had a great time singing songs from many different genres.  Everyone gets multiple opportunities to sing and everyone else provides encouragement.  Our Karaoke Studio is booked from 8:00-10:00PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come early to enjoy the full two hours we have booked.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Your Meetup Coordinator,&lt;br /&gt;Phil&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip L</member_name><member_id>1522860</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179792076000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonkaraoke</urlname><id>212993</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Karaoke Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179150819000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Karaoke Meetup - Saturday May 19, 2007</name><id>5775989</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179619200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonkaraoke/events/5775989/</event_url></item>