<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On the first Tuesday of each month, join Hostelling International for Cultural Café, an exploration of the food and culture of the Boston area. It's also a delicious fundraiser for our Cultural Kitchen program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On May 4th, we'll be visiting Sabur Restaurant in Somerville for an exciting Bosnian feast.  Sabur is a fascinating place, serving multi-ethnic cuisine inspired by the rustic fare of the Mediterranean region.  Owner Haris Jusufbegovic will be hosting us with a feast featuring food from his native Bosnia.  He will also share the strong coffee tradition of his country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by April 28th for this affordable and fun event. You may do so online at &lt;a href="http://culturalcafemay.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://culturalcafema...&lt;/a&gt; or by signing up with Karin directly by e-mailing kturer@usahostels.org or calling 617-718-7990 ext 23. REMEMBER, YOU MUST PRE-PAY IN ORDER TO SECURE YOUR SPACE AT THE MEETUP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***more about Cultural Kitchen and Cultural Café***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an afterschool activity, Cultural Kitchen teaches Boston and Somerville youth about culture and diversity using cooking as the primary vehicle - just like travelers at our hostels learn about one another while cooking together in the hostel kitchen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cultural Café gives us a chance to experience something similar to what the students experience in our program. The setting is informal as we gather to build community, share a delicious meal, learn a bit about Bosnian culture, and support a great cause.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our group will be seated in the Lounge area</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1273187133000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Culturalcafe</urlname><id>1554280</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Cultural Café - Dine Out for a Cause</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265907246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May meetup: A Bosnian feast at Sabur!</name><id>12580498</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273014000000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Culturalcafe/events/12580498/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/e/global_13047102.jpeg</photo_url></item>