<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>State House</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.225640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>State House</name><city>Concord</city><id>386899</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.554750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;The following message is from &lt;a href="http://nhcommonsense.org/" target="_blank"&gt;NH Common Sense&lt;/a&gt; released on April 9th.&lt;/i&gt;  For additional information please contact &lt;a href="mailto:info@nhcommonsense.org" target="_blank"&gt;info@nhcommonsense.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friends,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The whole state has been buzzing about &lt;a href="http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/legislation/2008/HB1623.html" target="_blank"&gt;HB1623&lt;/a&gt;, and we've been receiving great coverage in all the papers. The fiercest critic who came out against us, Manchester Mayor Frank Guinta, took a lot of heat and suddenly (coincidence?) announced he wouldn't be running for governor.  Smaller-scale attacks like the one Guinta leveled against Rep. David Scannell have been backfiring in Rochester and other towns across the state.  When you consider that for much of the last few decades, all a politician had to do was accuse his opponent of being &amp;quot;soft on drugs&amp;quot; to win a lot of elections, this demonstrates that a sea change in public opinion is in progress.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's our job to help that sea change along, and we're having a lot of success.  It has been said that the people are usually way ahead of politicians, and it sure was nice to see some politicians catch up in that 193-141 House vote March 18.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, the Senate and Governor Lynch are a different story altogether.  After all, it's an election year, and regardless of what any of them may privately believe, these individuals are more politically cautious than most House reps.  This is why winning the media war has been so important; we are slowly demonstrating that public support for marijuana reform is on the rise, and politicians are becoming less afraid to admit our current laws don't make sense for the 21st Century. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Senate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HB 1623 has now been scheduled for a hearing by the Senate Judiciary Committee April 22 at 3:00 p.m.  If possible, plan now to take the afternoon off work and visit the state house to show support for this sensible reduction in penalties.  The media is now watching this issue intently, and if we can put 50 or 100 respectable-looking citizens at the state house wearing &amp;quot;Reduce Penalties!&amp;quot; stickers, it will make a tremendous impact. Unlike the boring general session some of you witnessed March 18, the Senate hearing will be very educational and possibly even exciting.  There will be five Senators listening to testimony from both sides, so we'll hear a series of short presentations from legislators and citizens who favor or oppose HB 1623, and the Senators will get to ask questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who are unfamiliar with the state legislature, I can tell you that the Senate is a good bit... well, stuffier than the House.  Part of the reason we've gotten this far is that legislators can see this effort is not &amp;quot;just a bunch of stoners,&amp;quot; and that is the image we must continue to cultivate if we want to succeed in the Senate.  If we can successfully present ourselves as responsible citizens who want to make New Hampshire a better, more sensible place, we will continue to make huge progress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can click here to find your Senator and his or her contact information.  I'll provide more advice for contacting senators in the next email, but for now it would be great to send your senator a quick email saying you think the House did the right thing by voting to reduce marijuana penalties.  Politely ask your Senator to support HB 1623, or to at least consider the issue thoroughly before making up his or her mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(The Judiciary Committee is composed of Senators Foster, Clegg, Reynolds, Letorneau, and Gottesman, but all 24 senators will eventually vote on the bill.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Governor Lynch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you contacted Governor Lynch about HB 1623, you may have received a form letter which essentially parrots the position of the state police chiefs: &amp;quot;While he respects your opinion, Governor Lynch agrees with the law enforcement community in New Hampshire and the House Criminal Justice and Public Safety Committee, which carefully weighed the testimony and thoughtfully voted 13-5 against passage of this bill.&amp;quot; Ugh.  And as you know, the Governor has threatened to veto HB 1623 if it reaches his desk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, at least we know where we stand, I guess...  Despite Governor Lynch's disinterest, we will do our best to educate him and hopefully move him in the right direction.  A strong, respectable showing of public support for HB 1623 will help us get the Governor's attention.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;College Students&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's a petition being circulated at some New Hampshire colleges.  If you are a college student and want to gather some signatures at your school, let me know and I'll forward you a copy of the petition.  A large number of signatures from a large number of colleges across the state would make a good impression on the committee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rocketman</member_name><member_id>3933001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209063966000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>This is the Senate hearing, the house Hearing was last month (http://ronpaul.meetup.com/6/calendar/7535816/).  Show your support for this bill.</why><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207772618000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH Senate Hearing:  HB1623</name><id>7708424</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208890800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/7708424/</event_url></item>