<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>53 Marlborough St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.354078</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.912.0400</phone><name>French Cultural Center</name><city>Boston, </city><id>1451512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.074798</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are a language and culture geek like, uh, some of us, this should be an enjoyable evening. Sorry for the late notice, but I just read about this tonight and thought it was too good to pass up. They list some of the topics as Gastronomie, Géographie, Histoire, Cinéma, Pop Culture, &lt;br /&gt;

Sports, Littérature, Sciences, Musique and Art, and they make vague promises of an "awesome prize". A few notes...This starts early, at 6:30, kind of an after-work event in Back Bay. Admission appears to be $10, unless you're a student (bring ID) or a member of the French Cultural Center where this will be held, in which case it will just be $7. They will be serving beer and wine, and since I know my constituents, I figure you might want to check out the purveyors of the biere here: &lt;a href="http://www.brasseurs-gayant.com/anglais/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.brasseurs-gayant.com/anglais/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please don't hold me to this, but it seems like you get a nice glass of something with your admission. They suggest RSVPing, so I can call in our numbers on Wednesday afternoon or so. Try to RSVP if interested and say if you are a definite yes, a probable yes, etc so I can be pretty accurate. We can either meet at the center or in a nearby coffee shop perhaps, as our schedules allow. OK? I used to take French a pretty long time ago, and it would be nice to have some people with recent or native cultural and language experience, but those with any or no French language knowledge alike are welcome to attend. Details at this site: &lt;a href="http://www.frenchculturalcenter.org/index.cfm/events/scheduled-events/qui-quoi-quand-ou-/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.frenchculturalcenter.org/index.cfm/events/scheduled-events/qui-quoi-quand-ou-/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy Hersh</member_name><member_id>8018901</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359685945000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Trivia Buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Area-Pub-Trivia</urlname><id>1554091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Boston Area Pub Trivia</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359437840000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trivia en français: first-ever Qui? Quoi? Quand? Où?</name><id>101921222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359675000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Area-Pub-Trivia/events/101921222/</event_url></item>