<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 John F. Kennedy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371391</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name> LAND Hall,  Belfer 4th floor , Harvard Kennedy School. </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>5917342</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Gettysburg Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding and Revitalizing Civic Engagement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Harvard University&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontline with Faculty Seminar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All FwF seminars are open to the public&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ARCHON FUNG | Ford Foundation Professor of Democracy and Citizenship, HKS &lt;br /&gt;

MARSHALL GANZ | Senior Lecturer in Public Policy, HKS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, Apr 10 | 3:00 – 4:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Belfer, L-4, Hauser Center Conference Room, Lobby Level, Harvard Kennedy School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For centuries, American democracy has been built by ordinary people standing up in the town square and using the tools available to them—from the printing press to blogs—to build organizations and social movements for change. The work of citizens engaging with each other to organize, debate, struggle, and decide created a politics of common purpose and democratic accountability – a sharp contrast with the market-based approaches that have come to dominate public policy today. As American politics becomes increasingly corrupted by those who command the most money, the only hope for shared prosperity and real democracy lies in mobilizing millions of Americans from all walks of life to be participants in shaping our collective futures on the issues most important to them. Marshall and Archon will convene leading organizers, activists, and academics in the first meeting of The Gettysburg Project, an effort to develop understandings to reinvigorate meaningful and consequential civic engagement for the 21st century.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archon Fung is Ford Foundation Professor of Democracy and Citizenship. His research examines the impacts of civic participation, public deliberation, and transparency upon public and private governance. His Empowered Participation: Reinventing Urban Democracy examines two participatory-democratic reform efforts in low-income Chicago neighborhoods. Current projects also examine initiatives in ecosystem management, toxics reduction, endangered species protection, local governance, and international labor standards. His recent books and edited collections include Deepening Democracy: Institutional Innovations in Empowered Participatory Governance; Can We Eliminate Sweatshops?; Working Capital: The Power of Labors Pensions; and Beyond Backyard Environmentalism. His articles on regulation, rights, and participation appear in Political Theory; Journal of Political Philosophy; Politics and Society; Governance; Environmental Management; American Behavioral Scientist; and Boston Review. Fung received two SBs and a PhD from MIT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marshall Ganz, Senior Lecturer in Public Policy, entered Harvard College in the fall of 1960. In 1964, a year before graduating, he left to volunteer as a civil rights organizer in Mississippi. In 1965, he joined Cesar Chavez and the United Farm Workers; over the next 16 years he gained experience in union, community, issue, and political organizing and became Director of Organizing. During the 1980s, he worked with grassroots groups to develop effective organizing programs, designing innovative voter mobilization strategies for local, state, and national electoral campaigns. In 1991, in order to deepen his intellectual understanding of his work, he returned to Harvard College and, after a 28-year “leave of absence,” completed his undergraduate degree in history and government. He was awarded an MPA by the Kennedy School in 1993 and completed his PhD in sociology in 2000. He teaches, researches, and writes on leadership, organization, and strategy in social movements, civic associations, and politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Frontline with Faculty Series is a venue for Harvard faculty affiliated with the Hauser Center to share their work and research with faculty colleagues, as well as students in an informal setting that will allow for spirited discussion, debate and exchange. The seminars link faculty experts from Harvard Schools and beyond on a wide range of topics.  The Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations at Harvard University seeks to expand understanding and accelerate critical thinking about civil society among scholars, practitioners, policy makers and the general public, by encouraging scholarship, developing curriculum, fostering mutual learning between academics and practitioners, and shaping policies that enhance the sector and its role in society.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365632236000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357591174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Civic Engagement</name><id>98421882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365620400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/98421882/</event_url></item>