<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for our annual fall foliage hike up North. We depart Boston early in the morning. Carpooling is recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leave from Boston @ 8:30 am.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;b&gt; Trail&lt;/b&gt;: Mt. Major Trail&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Mountains&lt;/b&gt;: Mt. Major (1784 ft.)&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;b&gt; Rating&lt;/b&gt;: Easy/Moderate&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Total&lt;/b&gt;: 3.0 miles (round trip hike), approximate time 2:30-3:00 hrs.&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Elevation Gain&lt;/b&gt;: 1180 feet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Date&lt;/b&gt;: Saturday, October 9th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;b&gt; Location&lt;/b&gt;: 11:30am Mt. Major Parking lot. We will leave promptly at 11:45 so don't be late!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;b&gt; RSVP&lt;/b&gt;: Wednesday October 6th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time for our Annual Fall Foliage hiking trip. This should be a relatively easy hike, but of course it's still a hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some excerpts from the Hiker's Guide to the Mounts of NH:&lt;br /&gt;This is a popular, exciting hike to an open summit with sweeping views of Lake Winnipesaukee, central New Hampshire and into Maine. Although it is a short hike and popular with families, the mountain is quite steep with a couple of spots some hikers may find a little difficult. At the outset the trail coincides with a jeep road, branches off it and returns to it. After a brief level section, the trail departs left from the jeep road and climbs steadily to the summit. Rock slabs are ascended and views of the lake begin to open up. There are a few very short sections that require extra caution, especially on the descent and with small children. The wide open summit area is spectacular and the old stone enclosure will provide relief from the cooling breeze. Take the same route back down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: Take 93N to exit 20 in NH. Follow Route 3 to NH 11. The trail head parking is on NH 11. Driving time is approx. 2.0-2.5 hours from Boston. RSVP for further directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP&lt;/b&gt; by Wednesday Oct 6th so you can be kept up to date if any plans change. Transportation is the responsibility of the individual, however we will do our best to accommodate you. Please let me know if you need a ride or can take passengers and where you will be coming from. Please note that when you RSVP. Since it is quite a long drive, we suggest helping out with a carpool fee of $12 or whatever is agreed between driver and passenger -payable directly to the driver.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stuff to bring:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Backpack&lt;br /&gt;Lunch&lt;br /&gt;2 liters of water&lt;br /&gt;Hiking boots&lt;br /&gt;Extra layers like a sweater/sweatshirt &lt;br /&gt;Wear polyester blend clothing or other wicking clothing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO Cotton! (Once it gets wet from sweat, it won't dry and you'll be cold.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the trailhead</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Henry</member_name><member_id>7346155</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286763042000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Asian Professionals</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Asian-Professionals</urlname><id>431528</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Asian Professionals Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285364033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Foliage Hike</name><id>14885994</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286627400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Asian-Professionals/events/14885994/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/9/global_11149161.jpeg</photo_url></item>