<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>943 Namquid Drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02888</zip><lat>41.741898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-572-3390</phone><name>Game On!</name><city>Warwick</city><id>1111698</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405803</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come celebrate the release of the new D&amp;amp;D Essentials line of products and the new Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons Fantasy Roleplaying Game with a classic-style adventure and a retro game experience!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The D&amp;amp;D Essentials product line is designed to give you everything you need to play the classic D&amp;amp;D game experience, and it starts with the new boxed set – the Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons Fantasy Roleplaying Game. Inside the “Red Box,” you’ll find everything you need to begin your adventure. After you’re done exploring the Red Box, you can find all the rules for the 4th Edition game in the Rules Compendium, create the iconic characters you want with Heroes of the Fallen Lands and get ready to expand your campaign with the Dungeon Master’s Kit, Monster Vault, and Dungeon Tiles Master Sets.&lt;br /&gt;Just for participating you’ll take home the pregenerated character sheet of the character you played. If you DM the game, you’ll take home the adventure itself, a poster map of the encounter areas, and the tokens used in the adventure. To satisfy your curiosity, here’s a quick description of the adventure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunderpeak Temple&lt;br /&gt;Long a bastion of good on the edges of the wilderness, Sunderpeak Temple has succumbed to an unknown threat. You have been tasked to journey to the site of the temple and find out what has befallen its residents, as the priests are needed to destroy an enchanted skill imbued with necromantic magic. Will you face down the dark denizens that dwell within and learn the truth of the temple’s fate? A Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons adventure designed for 4-6 pregenerated characters of 2nd level.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanios</member_name><member_id>4187193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284300605000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280376473000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worldwide D&amp;D Gameday:  D&amp;D Essentials Red Box</name><id>14249262</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284224400000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/14249262/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/f/global_6578223.jpeg</photo_url></item>