<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>409 The Hill</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.038895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Mermaid Island Grille</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>7034552</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.829414</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Michael Finger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Austrian School Economics: Your Window to Understanding the Financial Crisis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very few Americans have heard of the Austrian School of economics. In fact, even if you majored in economics in college, chances are you still were never exposed to these thinkers: Carl Menger, Ludwig Von Mises, Friedrich Hayek or Murray Rothbard. But their disciples were the only ones to accurately predict the current financial crisis, back when mainstream economists were forecasting rising housing prices for the foreseeable future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael will explain how the Austrians were able to see that the dot-com and housing bubbles would collapse, and why they see an even greater crisis ahead. Also, Michael will discuss strategies to protect yourself and your family during these difficult times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Finger graduated with honors from Tulane University with a BA in Philosophy. He is principal of Centinel Consulting, a marketing and economic consultancy based in Portsmouth, NH. Michael has worked in real estate development and on Wall Street, through which he developed a keen understanding of economic forecasting, direct marketing, and public relations. Centinel combines these disciplines to identify growing markets and help businesses effectively target them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael's media credits include Al Jazeera English, the Portsmouth Herald, LewRockwell.com, and the Tulane Hullabaloo.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338464870000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337891792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Austrian School Economics expert to speak in Portsmouth</name><id>66206902</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338330600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/66206902/</event_url></item>