<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; Welcome to our second Open House of the year!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; If you plan to come, and would like reminders, feel free to RSVP. It helps us get a sense of who/ how many we're expecting.&amp;nbsp; But the attendance for this one is unlimited, so it's not necessary to RSVP.&amp;nbsp; Anyone who shows up is welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're planning to open the doors at ten a.m. and we'll keep the party going until at least 4 p.m....so try to plan your arrival accordingly.&amp;nbsp; (Some of us may stay later but the sale will be wrapping up at 4.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've got lots of ideas in the works for this, but our main focus is to introduce you to our collaborative art space in Holliston! Come and see our space, where our art is displayed, where we welcome fellow artists to learn and share (we have openings for a few new members) and where we hold workshops and open studio days when we welcome you to come and play and learn new techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the Open House, the Works on the Wall will (mostly) be available for sale as marked.&amp;nbsp; We're also planning to run an Artisans Fair during this time, with art, gifts and decorative items by our members and friends for sale.&amp;nbsp; It's a great time to start your holiday shopping, and support both local artists *and* ArtStudio360!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll also have a couple of make-and-take activities, for adults and for children.&amp;nbsp; There will also be kits available at minimal cost, if you can't take the time to play while you're there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Applegail</member_name><member_id>26569312</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321896826000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317723993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Autumn Open House at ArtStudio360, with Holiday Artisans Fair</name><id>36066812</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321714800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/36066812/</event_url></item>