<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>170 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.556435</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Shadow Room</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1183893</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.646935</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come to the The Shadow Room bar, bring friends, drink, dance, party, AND get to be a background extra as part of an indie comedy feature film, AND see me, Jason, behaving like a complete lunatic...again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All you have to do is show-up, dress like you would any casual night out on the town, have fun, and ignore the cameras. You do not have to stay the whole night (probably ends 11-ish?). At some point the cameras are probably getting packed-away and then it's just a time for pure fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There should be some free food there (likely pizza). The alcohol is not free. Plenty of free street parking, or in nearby plazas (like the Destinta Theater plaza).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The producers are calling on lots of people, so we'll probably have a fair-sized crowd, my Event isn't the only avenue by which we're finding people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHY:&lt;/b&gt; This is being shot as part of a scene in an indie comedy feature film, in which one of the characters (Seppy) has been released from prison and his friends are all celebrating.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE FILMING:&lt;/b&gt; It's &amp;quot;Burial Boys&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Burial-Boys/266458207439" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be actors present from the film, in costume, in character, some odd, saying a few lines, and partying as well. Most likely they will only ever interact with you in-character.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not anxious for attention, just ignore the weirdos and have fun. If you WANT to be caught on camera more, spend more time interacting with the strange folk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AS FOR ME:&lt;/b&gt; I'll be one of the stranger characters there. My character (Kevin) is flamboyantly gay, and lascivious. I will have strange clothes, makeup, &amp;amp; hair, will be behaving like a lunatic, and will only interact with you in-character during the night (as long as the cameras are still out). Be frightened of me on the dance floor. Doubly-so if you're a man.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See Event description</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>2254163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277165288000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276901503000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mon. 6/21 - Drink, dance, party, free food, be in a film, see Jason be a lunatic</name><id>13844040</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277161200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/13844040/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>