<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Church Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06473</zip><lat>41.387018</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Haven Green</name><city>North Haven</city><id>995700</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.861212</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Let's try something different something fun.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;One of our own members Ralph will be working in one of the food booths on Fri &amp;amp; Sat.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Looking for something FREE to do on Friday and Saturday, August 21st and 22nd?  We've got some great ideas for you.  North Haven Sons and Daughters of Italy Lodge #2805 is thrilled to invite you to our 5th Annual &amp;quot;Italian Festival of Angels™&amp;quot; on the North Haven Town Green.  Starting Friday at 3 pm to 10 pm we have lots of interesting and exciting activities to enjoy, such as our Soccer Fest, US Marine Honor Guard at 5:30 pm, Italian cultural exhibits, pasta making demo, Murano Glass demo and multiple craft demos.  At 5 pm, entertainment begins on our Main Stage with Minotti singers.  At 7 pm, Rich DiPalma, a local favorite, who always performs with passion and personality, will be singing.  Crowds of all ages have enjoyed his performances at our past Festivals.  Mario Ciconne &amp;amp; Vision continue on stage at 8:30 pm...and that's just some of what's happening on Friday. &lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;We continue to entertain on Saturday at 10 am to 10 pm with more of our Soccer Fest, Grape Stomp, Author Round Table, Pizza Toss, Garlic Braiding, Herb Drying, Pesto and Pasta Making demos and much more.  Bring your children for crafts and activities from 11 am to 7 pm at our Children's Area (next to the Cultural Tent) and leave your &amp;quot;Angel Print&amp;quot; for future Festivals.  At 2 pm our Main Stage will begin an evening filled with dancing and singing.  At 4 pm is our Procession of Angels, which is especially for the children to participate in with us.  Minotti Music will begin performing at 5 pm.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt; We are pleased to have Aaron Caruso singing at 7 pm, who is a wonderful, operatically trained tenor, deeply devoted to preserving the traditional Italian culture.  Aaron has entertained audiences around the country with his talent.  Finally, Sound Sensations begins at 9 pm on our Main Stage. &lt;/u&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Throughout the duration of the Festival, you may visit our Lodge Marketplace where you can find a wide variety o f homemade crafts, wonderful Italian novelties, t-shirts, soccer balls, baby clothing and much more.  Please be sure to browse our &amp;quot;Everything Italian&amp;quot; Photo Contest entries to see if anyone you know has won.  We'll also be selling raffle tickets for a homemade &amp;quot;Crazy Quilt&amp;quot; and Vespa motor scooter and a 32&amp;quot; TV that will be won at the Festival.  There will also be 18 craft vendors selling many beautiful items and, of course, we can't forget to mention the delicious food available from local restaurants and lots of other tasty treats for you to indulge in at our Food Court.  We truly have something for everyone to enjoy!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you'd like more information about our Festival, please contact our Lodge at 203-234-6725 and visit our website at&lt;a href="http://www.northhavenlodge2805.org/festival_of_angels.htm" target="_blank"&gt; www.northhavenlodge2805.org&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve C</member_name><member_id>6197158</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joanne</member_name><member_id>9085331</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251513814000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250641660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Italian Festival of Angels</name><id>11143517</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250980200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/11143517/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/2/global_10275186.jpeg</photo_url></item>