<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Holiday season is upon us, so I figure I better sneak in my personal favorite Holiday Movie before time gets away from us.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please do not be fooled by the title, this is NOT a sports movie.  &lt;br /&gt;Come visit the 360 State Street Screening Room, for a showing of:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Ref&lt;/b&gt; (1994 - Comedy)  &lt;br /&gt;Description from IMDB: A cat burglar is forced to take a bickering, dysfunctional family hostage on Christmas Eve.  &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Denis Leary, Kevin Spacey, Judy Davis  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0110955/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a bit of a dark comedy, but it takes place on Christmas Eve, and does have relevant humor/messages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I Set the time for 6:30, but we will not start showing the movie until shortly after 7. Don't plan to be any later than 7 though.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Important Notes:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately I have to limit RSVP's to 18 for theater size. Please only respond Yes if you're sure you can make it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're RSVPing Yes, I will need your full names if I don't already have (or remember) them for the Concierge to let you in, and you may need ID. Please either put your name in your RSVP or e-mail it to me. (If you live in the building just let me know instead.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 8 pm and free after.  If you want free with a longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evenings (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street).  360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only.  I'm not sure of the exact cost, entrance is on State street just before the buildings main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The concierge should be able to let you in and direct you, make note of the directions near the call box. I will also try to post signs. My Cell if you have problems is 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291940081000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291054931000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie:  "The Ref"  (This is not a sports movie)</name><id>15584572</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291851000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15584572/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/4/8/global_19959912.jpeg</photo_url></item>