<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Church Street Wharf at Thames Street, </address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02809</zip><lat>41.671589</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Prudence Island Ferry</name><city>bristol</city><id>2117961</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.278450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's go to Prudence Island for the day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My family has a house at the top of the hill near the lighthouse point on the island.  The house is more like a 3 season shack, but the backyard is large and a great place to escape the summer sun.  The house is only minutes away from a small beach that is a great place to swim, and jump off the dock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What else is there to do out there?  Lot's of NOTHING.  Well there is another beach or two, several paths for walking/hiking.  Good bicycling (as long as your bike can handle gravel roads).  You might be able to talk my father into showing you some good fishing spots and take a few casts.  Or perhaps if low tide hits at the right time, we can try our hand a clamming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FYI -there are 2 country stores on the island, but I wouldn't recommend picking up food and drink from them as the cost is high.  Bring whatever you need to drink, and some food to share for Lunch.  (We have filtered water.)  If you would, please let everyone know what you are bringing in the comments for this event.  And if you plan on going to the beach all day, definitely bring a beach chair if you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So you want to know &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Providence,+RI&amp;amp;daddr=41.71255,-71.26744+to:Thames+St&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=41.747325,-71.345025&amp;amp;sspn=0.198515,0.424347&amp;amp;geocode=FfUufgIdnlO--yldc35D4ETkiTEntrNITXzfaQ%3BFaZ7fAIdkIvA-ykj5UM6vFbkiTFnbA0IQjMTBQ%3BFSDQewIdrWTA-w&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;mra=dpe&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=12&amp;amp;via=1&amp;amp;z=12"&gt;how to get there&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is &lt;a href="http://prudenceferry.com/fares.htm"&gt;ferry service&lt;/a&gt; from Bristol.  There are only 2 boats out to the island in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8AM and 10 AM.  I highly recommend you make it to the ferry dock by 7:45 to catch the 8 boat, as there is a Bristol Town daily parking lot available for free across the street from the Ferry dock.  Generally this lot fills up a little after 8 on nice days, so you likely can't park there for the 10 boat.  Seriously folks, if you want to go - catch the 8 boat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adult fare on the ferry is usually under $7 round trip (depending on fuel surcharges), children 5-12 under $3 (under 5 go free), Bikes add $1.10 each bicycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Ferry trip takes about 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When can you go back to the real world:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are only 3 boats back to Bristol in the afternoon, they leave Prudence at 4:05, 5:15, and 6:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Wait, this means I'm stuck on an Island all day" - YES!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Can I bring my car?" - Why do you need it?  I'll arrange to have any heavy gear (coolers, etc) picked up and carted to the house/beach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(This is a sunny day only meetup, if the weather is bad I'll reschedule for another weekend day later this summer)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a VT hat, as usual.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8642703</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344453139000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342302292000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hang out on Prudence Island</name><id>73356392</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342957500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/73356392/</event_url></item>