<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Quality St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06611</zip><lat>41.256035</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203 452 5197</phone><name>Trumbull Library</name><city>Trumbull</city><id>379788</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.217674</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hollywood and the Paranormal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Community Room in the Trumbull Library&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many people over the years have wondered what, if any, truth there is to the way paranormal phenomena is represented in TV and movies. This program uses movie and TV clips , as well as evidence from the presenters' investigations, to compare the two. And you might be surprised to find how much truth there is in fiction!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fun program presented by Smoking Gun Research Agency out of Westport. Time for Q&amp;amp;A and included. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free. &lt;br /&gt;Registration suggested.&lt;br /&gt;I will take care of Registration for the Unknown Zone Meet Up Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; www.trumbullct-library.org/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.sgra-media.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from I 95 South &lt;br /&gt;Take exit 38 towards Ct-15 Merritt and Wilbur Cross Pkwys &lt;br /&gt;Merge onto Milford Pkwy &lt;br /&gt;Take the exit onto CT - 15 S/Merritt Pkwy towards NYC &lt;br /&gt;Take exit 50 for CT-127 towards Trumbull &lt;br /&gt;Slight right at CT-127 / White Plains Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Continue to follow CT-127 &lt;br /&gt;Turn left at Quality St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walk into the Main Entrance facing Quality St.&lt;br /&gt;There is also a side entrance on the side of the fountain&lt;br /&gt;but for these directions you are&lt;br /&gt;Encouraged to use the front main entrance.&lt;br /&gt;Do not go through the Sliding Doors going further into the Library.&lt;br /&gt;Turn left going the direction towards the phone on the wall.&lt;br /&gt;There are rest rooms on the left just before you go into the &lt;br /&gt;Community room where the lecture will be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To give even more of an idea where the Trumbull Library is, there is a Stop and &lt;br /&gt;Shop Shopping Complex across the street up on a hill.  &lt;br /&gt;It is on the same side of the street as the Trumbull Town Hall.&lt;br /&gt;If you go further down the Quality Street and take a left, that will put you on&lt;br /&gt;Rt 111 Newtown Tnpk / Main Street.    Rt 111 will take you to the Trumbull Mall&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of Friday night traffic on October 5, to go to the &lt;br /&gt;Warren lecture, I ended up taking 122 to 34 to 110 to 111&lt;br /&gt;to 127 Quality Street.&lt;br /&gt;For a ride break, there was a McDonalds on 111 not too far&lt;br /&gt;Before the Trumbull Library.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Trumbull Library and SGRA want me to send them a head count&lt;br /&gt;A few days before the lecture.  On 10/7, I did let SGRA know that I found&lt;br /&gt;The conference room to be acceptable for their up coming lecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact me if anyone wants to meet either in West Haven&lt;br /&gt;For a ride or by the Trumbull Mall to follow before the lecture. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybes will be allowed up to October 19. &lt;br /&gt;All Maybes will become No on October 20.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193073175000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190437529000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hollywood and the Paranormal</name><id>6406587</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192899600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/6406587/</event_url></item>