<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>5 minutes from Park Street T</address_2><address_1>42 Province Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-426-3333</phone><name>Kennedy's Midtown</name><city>Boston </city><id>1088491</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060079</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;If you have a life, you have a story.  Bring it.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to Kennedy's Midtown, 42 Province St., Boston, MA.  Doors open 6:30pm; stories start at 7:00pm.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;love objects&amp;quot; co-hosted by massmouth co-founder &amp;amp; storyteller Andrea Lovett and dancer, choreographer, actor Torena Webb.&lt;br /&gt;Admission $7, students $3.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information: stories@massmouth.com; andrea@massmouth.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a play of words, this event invites tellers to bring stories of their love objects and/or what they object to when in love.  A lover accepts the blueberry pie his love has made him despite his allergy and consequent trip to the emergency room.  Perhaps your objection was less physical; perhaps your love object simply created a strong intellectual reaction. Bring these stories to Kennedy’s Midtown as massmouth continues its successful series of story slams.  Names will be drawn at random.  The stories will be judged and prizes awarded to the top two finishers.  “Love Objects” story slam welcomes the Caribbean flair of co-host Torena Webb. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;massmouth is a non-profit organization dedicated to promoting the timeless are of storytelling through social media, education and live performance.  This is massmouth’s second story slam season. &lt;br /&gt;join massmouth.com for FREE and view over 500 videos of 5 minute kickbutt stories!  Over 2500 photos.  &lt;a href="http://www.massmouth.ning.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massmouth....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At a story slam, participants tell five minute personal stories on the theme. Ten lucky tellers have their names drawn at random to tell and be judged by five volunteer judges.  massmouth awards prizes to the top two stories. Listeners will be engaged in story improv games between each five minute feature. On April 26th, 2011 winners will gather for a BIGMOUTHOFF story slam at Rabb Hall at the Copley Square Library. massmouth will award the lucky winner of this contest with a fabulous prize getaway. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Boston Kennedy's Midtown Slams:&lt;br /&gt;MAR 7&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Slams Jamaica Plain's Bella Luna:&lt;br /&gt;FEB 20&lt;br /&gt;MAR 20&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Slam Cambridge Enormous Room:&lt;br /&gt;FEB 13&lt;br /&gt;MAR 13&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297176405000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295358320000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"love objects" massmouth story slam Downtown Boston</name><id>16090926</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297121400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/16090926/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/8/global_20893032.jpeg</photo_url></item>