<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be taking Ted's Trail (in Greenfield NH) to the summit of North Pack Monadnock, a round-trip &lt;b&gt;6 miles with ~1400' elevation gain&lt;/b&gt;, with an option to take Carolyn's Trail for the return for a loop hike.  There should be sufficient water along the trail for the dogs.  Pace will be relaxed for a moderate hike, with plenty of stops for water, snacks, and general play.  Your dogs may be on- or off-leash - your choice.  Weather for Sunday looks good right now - cross your fingers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting *at the trailhead* at 10:15am and will start up the trail at 10:30am.  Please be on-time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring:&lt;br /&gt;- For you: 2 quarts of water, lunch, and some snack items.  &lt;br /&gt;It's chilly this time of year, so dress in layers: couple of long-sleeved shirts, a sweater or sweatshirt, a coat, and a &lt;b&gt;warm hat&lt;/b&gt;.  Gloves/mittens and other cold-weather gear are optional but strongly suggested.  Some of this will probably stay in your backpack on the way up, but you'll be glad to have it at the summit.   Cameras are encouraged.  Hiking boots are recommended, but comfortable (and dirt-friendly) sneakers work as well.  &lt;br /&gt;- For your dog(s): Leash, dog food snack&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details can be found here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;North Pack Monadnock:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6746" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.peakbagger...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/PackMonadnock071103.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions (new and improved - Thanks Norman!):&lt;br /&gt;- From Boston, take route 93 north to route 128 south (a.k.a. route 95 south), towards Burlington.  Please adjust your direction on route 128 depending on the  highway you've taken from Boston.  If you've taken route 2 west, then you'll need to be on route 128 north to get to the next step.&lt;br /&gt;- In Burlington, exit north to route 3.&lt;br /&gt;- Once in NH, you are looking for exit 7W, route 101A Amherst.&lt;br /&gt;- Take route 101 towards Wilton, exit on left.&lt;br /&gt;- Get back on route 101A towards Wilton.&lt;br /&gt;- In Wilton, take route 31 north, a sharp turn to the right.&lt;br /&gt; - Continue on route 31 north until you reach Yankee Farm on the left.  For those of you who joined our hike to NPM in September, you will pass the library we met at last time on the right and drive possibly another 5-10 minutes before reaching the farm.&lt;br /&gt;- Right after the sign for the farm, turn left onto Russell Station Road. &lt;br /&gt;- Proceed .8 mile.  I believe it's the second right that you'll be taking and I'm not sure there's a sign there.  If you have GPS, this is Mountain Rd. &lt;br /&gt; - Proceed 1.6 miles on Mountain Rd.  There is parking, a grassy pullout) on the right side of the road, opposite a small sign for the trailhead.  There is no sign for this parking area.  Start looking for it as soon as you see signs for the Wildlife area on the left side of Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Alternatively, use GPS coordinates for the trailhead:  (42.907500, -71.851111)   OR   (+42° 54' 27.00&amp;quot;, -71° 51' 4.00&amp;quot;)   &lt;i&gt;You can plug these into GoogleMaps, MapQuest etc. to get directions from your house.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact:&lt;br /&gt;Please email me - I'm happy to answer any questions!  My cell number will be sent to all confirmed attendees in case i need to be reached that morning.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>VT license plate 'WISE UP'</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>whichway</member_name><member_id>6713575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259077383000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>trail seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NE-Trail-Dogs</urlname><id>1347727</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>New England Trail Dogs</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258678176000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>time change to 10:30 NE Trail Dogs Hike to North Pack Monadnock </name><id>11915653</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258903800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-Trail-Dogs/events/11915653/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/c/5/global_10626453.jpeg</photo_url></item>