<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pot Luck Lunch Barbie-Q is NEARBY at a restful outside location AFTER this DEMO event, Join me if you want.&lt;br /&gt;The Pot Luck location is at Spring Street Park apx # 200 Spring Street.&lt;br /&gt;When you Leave the Demo event, take a right and head south on rte 75, go apx 1 mile then take a LEFT onto Spring Street, go apx 1 mile and the Spring Street Park sign will be on your right ..its before the cenetary. I will get there as we decide to leave the Demo event, time unknown at this time..&lt;br /&gt;Bring your chairs, food, whatever, i have the grill and fire pit loaded.&lt;br /&gt;Mmmm first Barbie-Q of the year too on a warm sunny day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Sunny, with a high near 71. South wind between 3 and 10 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking perfect to me, not staying inside with this kind of weather..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Someone told me the Rescue Demos are in the morning ??? 9-9:45 ???&lt;br /&gt;This i feel is not when the majority will be there, such as apx 1 pm.. but im not in the real know I NEVER SEEN A SCHEDULE POSTED.&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;If So why list this event again ? but will only post it as an individule FYI.&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;If so im still going at 12 and see no reason to change anything. If there is no rescue demo for us to see,&lt;br /&gt;then we will have our own GROUP DEMO in the first week of May. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;“ The First (non paddling) Kayak event of the season for us to have you in the spirit of being ready when its paddling time.... ” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I simply can not be explaining safety all season long to you especially if you are a beginner when THIS EVENT SAYS IT IN ONE PLACE-AT ONE TIME. For Free.&lt;br /&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;The demos ???????  &lt;br /&gt; you can even purchase some things here too..&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;I know some of you can't or don't want to go, but once the season is underway, we will be also underway somewhat prepared and concentrating more on the  sights to be seen.&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Being surprised with a capsize will sure be a shock to you especially  if you have no idea what its about or what to do.&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Yes we will do &amp;quot;our own self rescue&amp;quot; practice session but that is usually much later in the season ESPECIALLY IF WE DON'T GET TO VIEW THEM HERE.&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; So GO To this safety event It if you can, go to a self rescue class too, and practice self rescue again with us later especially before joining us on the ocean events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the Air Museum next door, The Fire Info and the Kayaks things in one area.&lt;br /&gt;If too early for the Demo's just relax..we will be somewhere nearby..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whats wrong with the picture above of my new GIRLFRIEND ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~`^&lt;br /&gt;Go Ahead and click on it for &lt;br /&gt;MORE DETAIL..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will learn &amp;quot;what&amp;quot; right at this event..&lt;br /&gt;so ya might as well join us...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1, Right, no spray skirt, (might help with the view too).&lt;br /&gt;2, Wrong she already has a BFG on.&lt;br /&gt;4, Right, proper foot ware&lt;br /&gt;6, Right,white water  paddle too long&lt;br /&gt;7, Right, always have a snack on hand if you become stranded..remember Gilligans Island ???&lt;br /&gt;9, Maybe, floatation bags may not be needed in this craft any longer. already beached..and sunk&lt;br /&gt;10, your turn to tell me an few more..&lt;br /&gt;11, Yes, might be at Anglecoes eating all the food before ya get there..LOL&lt;br /&gt;12 Hot dam yes..this is the Theme Song &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=csrPT9ClVUc" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;13..The best lesson i have ever learned..never steal a fat persons bucket of chicken. You will get &lt;br /&gt;wacked by a paddle and hard usually in breaking it in two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...................................................................................................................................&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the info i have so far :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.depdata.ct.gov/calendar/viewev.asp?id=3909" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.depdata.ct...&lt;/a&gt;    updated&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/boating/paddlesmart.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;        Poster&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2222&amp;amp;q=320638&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1620#canoe" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Still waiting for the demonstration times, etc..soon i will get that info ?..if not we go earlier and meet at the site and check out whatever. I may go earlier to check out their museum or whatever, Look for the ORANGE HUNTING HAT..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE MAY HEAD OUT TO THE BARBIE-Q AREA ABOUT 2 PM ????? MAYBE EARLIER ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will be giving out some REDUCED admission tickets for the air museum for those interested&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neam.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neam.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And since its a Fire Training Building there will be fire related things too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ConnYak team will be back again. ??????????????????????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They usually do the  rescues demo and how important they are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its not as easy as it looks when its your turn out on a fast moving river or the surprize storm out on the ocean , its very different and difficult..WE WILL DO WHAT WE CAN TO HELP YOU THOUGH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A demonstration of how &amp;quot;Recreational&amp;quot; class Boats are unsafe is always a chuckel but a serious problem if something occurs in a bad place. Knowing what to expect really helps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't want you to take my word for it, but to see it in real life will influence you to know better and react accordingly when its your turn to try some safety things out in the lake prior to our ocean trips. Or if your boat becomes swamped..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;be ready...LOL..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This I HOPE WILL BE A GOOD event and way to spend a day with new ad old members learning/observing and simply socializing during and of course after the event at our Traditional Pot Luck Barbie-Q.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PADDLE SMART SAFETY EVENT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 20, 2010&lt;br /&gt;CT Fire Academy 34 Perimeter Rd, Windsor Locks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WINDSOR LOCKS, RIGHT NEXT to THE NEW ENGLAND AIR MUSEUM at BRADLEY AIRPORT..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NICE AND CLOSE FOR MOST OF US.. and pot luck after party with our traditional POT LUCK BARBIE-q nearby also. if its nice out then its outside if not then its  inside somewhere or both.&lt;br /&gt;Its also a great incentive to look forward to a safe and enjoyable paddling season with fellow paddlers..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9 am - 5pm       &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(I TEMPORARILY chose 12 pm to show up) If there are no water demo's then just socialize etc, go to the air museum..etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOU CAN GO ANYTIME AND MEET UP WITH US AS WE GO ALONG OR GO AND CHECK OUT WHAT THAY HAVE &lt;br /&gt;INDEPENDANT OF ALL OF US..BUT JOIN US AFTER  for th pot luck lunch..THATS THE SOCIAL PART AND MEET FELLOW PADDLERS IN THE GROUP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE WILL STAY TILL  WE DECIDE WE HAD ENOUGH, AND THEN HEAD OFF TO THE POTLUCK  Barbie Q RIGHT AWAY...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE Admission      ( This is what i like, so no one should complaine )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info to come! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/cfpc/cwp/view.asp?a=829&amp;amp;Q=245552" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/cfp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to CT Fire Academy, 34 Perimeter Road, Windsor Locks are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-91 north or south to exit 40 (Route 20, Bradley Connector).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 20 west 1.7 miles to the exit for Route 75. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a right off the exit onto Route 75 North and follow 2.5 miles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a left onto Perimeter Road (see sign for the CT Fire Academy and the New England Air Museum). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue 1.4 miles to the Academy ( new building with red sand accents) which will be on your right. (its before the controll tower) Parking is available at the rear of the building. &lt;br /&gt;____________________________________________________________________--&lt;br /&gt;How does this sound ? :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe we can even stick Hut dogs and marsh mallows on a long stick or METAL leaf rake and hold them behind the enjins of departing jets while laying in the sun on the runway's Threshold or MARKING NUMBER. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;. When we her the CON-TROLL in the Tower say &amp;quot;SouthWest 514- Taxie into position and HOLD&amp;quot;..that WILL mean &amp;quot;HOLD UP THE HUD DOG RAKE AT THE jets EXHAUST AND WAITE FOR THE RUN UP--- it cooks them South West Style&amp;quot;.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;. Then when the con-troll in the tower says SouthWest 514 Cleared for TAKE OFF..I would say they will be cooked and done ready to take off of the hud dog rake and eat.. Cant get any better than that..Airline food in an instant......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;. Heck the pilots can't see us through them small windows of them big jets, they are so busy pulling all kinds of levers, flipping keys, stomping on pedals making like they are playing a big pipe organ in a big church.... and the flight attendant is blowing up OTTO...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe only a few passengers can see us and by the time thay say anything our Hud Dogs will be cooked. and they will be gone wishing thay had one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Actual Lunch location is at a Nearby location if interested..details at paddling event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok see ya all soon..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing my Bright Orange Hunting Hat checking out the vendors and demo's.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>31</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269709919000</updated><rating><average>4.15000009537</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264108735000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> *FREE KAYAKING SAFETY - EQUIPMENT- WATER DEMO'S  ? EVENT * &amp; Barbie-Q Nearby </name><id>12385619</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269100800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/12385619/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/a/global_13060842.jpeg</photo_url></item>