<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Half Moon&lt;/b&gt;  2007 Iraq / Iran / Austria / France   110 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Kurds may not yet have a country, but as long as Bahman Ghobadi keeps making movies they have a national cinema. The Iranian-born director came to prominence with 2000's &amp;quot;A Time for Drunken Horses&amp;quot; and followed through with 2004's breathtaking &amp;quot;Turtles Can Fly,&amp;quot; set in an Iraqi refugee camp on the eve of the US invasion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With &amp;quot;Half Moon,&amp;quot; Ghobadi's knack for turning statelessness into dark comic poetry continues. Like 2002's &amp;quot;Marooned in Iraq,&amp;quot; this one has a musical bent -- the soundtrack is glorious -- and it follows the travels of a troupe that just wants a place where it can perform. Since Iranian women aren't allowed to perform in public, Mamo tries sneaking a singer (Hedieh Tehrani) into Iraq, hiding her under the floorboards when the border police search the bus. Ghobadi's gift for shaggy magical realism is given full scope during a visit to a village of 1,330 exiled women singers: They stand on rooftops and serenade the musicians en masse. It's an unforgettable sight.  Ty Burr&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the NY Times: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For his poetic fourth feature, “Half Moon,” the Kurdish-Iranian writer and director Bahman Ghobadi returns to the breathtaking desolation of the Kurdish borderlands and the enduring optimism of his people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the fall of Saddam Hussein, Mamo (Ismail Ghaffari), a famed Kurdish musician living in Iran, gathers his many sons for a trip across the border to Iraqi Kurdistan and a long-planned celebratory concert. Despite failing health and his offspring’s fluctuating commitment to the dangerous enterprise, Mamo is resolute; neither callous border guards nor his own recurring premonitions of disaster will derail the performance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fateful and funny, haunting and magical, “Half Moon” balances delicately between the harsh realities of its location and the mystical power of Mamo’s visions. Shooting mainly in Iranian Kurdistan, the cinematographers Nigel Bluck and Crighton Bone find an unearthly beauty amid the gambling frenzy of a cockfight and the silent ranks of exiled female singers lining the rooftops of a mountain village. As the end of the journey draws near, the line between the natural and the supernatural becomes increasingly difficult to discern. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inspired by Mozart’s “Requiem” and commissioned by the New Crowned Hope festival in Vienna, “Half Moon” is an affecting contemplation of resilience in the face of tragedy. When a higher purpose beckons, death itself must take a back seat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is free and is part of the Boston Muslim Film Festival: Art Under Fire &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.muslimfilm.org/films.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.muslimfilm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we will go to a nearby restaurant for our post-film discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a  Meet-up sign near the front row after the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223148787000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kurdish Film -Half Moon</name><id>8896646</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224352800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8896646/</event_url></item>