<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Tuna Warf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01966</zip><lat>42.660433</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-546-5050</phone><name>North Shore Kayak Outdoor Center</name><city>Rockport</city><id>993512</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.614818</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THIS MEETUP HAS BEEN MOVED TO SUNDAY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a tour of beautiful Rockport Harbor and paddle to Thacher Island on Saturday August 29th at 1:30pm (please arrive and check in at least 15min prior to start.) &lt;br /&gt;To sign up you MUST Call North Shor Kayak for your reservations to save your spot with a credit card. The number is (978) 546-5050&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE mention that you are part of the Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors Club Thacher Island Tour&lt;br /&gt;hosted by Michele DeSoto.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the tour we will enjoy dinner and coctails at a local Restaurant. This is a 3 1/2 hrs / 4 miles paddle and No Experience is Necessary Located a half-mile off the eastern shore of Cape Ann, Thacher Island has something for everyone. The 50-acre island contains a National Wildlife Refuge, and birders will love wandering the extensive trails and observing the variety of species that nest on or visit the island. Thacher hosts two lighthouses, the only operating twin lighthouses remaining in America. The North Tower is on the National Register of Historic Places and is open to the public. Visitors who climb the 155 stairs to the catwalk, 166 feet above the sea, are treated to a fantastic view of the Atlantic coast from Boston to Maine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info please check out the cool flyer that Michele put together.  If you are coming please check this for additional info you will need to know. &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/687583/Thacher_Island_Kayak%201.pdf"&gt;Thacher Island Brochure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michele DeSoto is running this trip, you can reach her at 1-978-836-7165 with questions or call North Shore kayak direct.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251842399000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250984732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thacher Island kayak trip</name><id>11175084</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251653400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/11175084/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/0/global_3292112.jpeg</photo_url></item>