<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max: Min of 4, Max of 16 members &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: None. Members Only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: $2 event fee &lt;br /&gt;Annual Members - FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greens Fees - $10 per person &lt;br /&gt;Additional fee of $8.50 to rent clubs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone -   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've been having a great time golfing this season so let's keep it up and play another 9 holes.  Changing it up a bit and trying a different course.  This time we'll play at the Rockand Golf Course - 5:45 pm for a 6:00-6:15 T off meeting outside the pro shop Monday, August 24th. Similar to last week we'll stagger the T times amongst the groups about 10 minutes apart. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone should arrive 10-15 mins before 6:00 so I can assign groups, clubs and get everyone started. &lt;b&gt;However, if there is someone that may have trouble getting there for the 1st T time or intend to borrow/rent clubs - indicate what you need - women/men's, left or right handed in the comment section upon RSVPing.&lt;/b&gt;  The cost to rent clubs is $8.50.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All members are welcome; however, it may be worth noting that the majority of the group are at the beginner level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How many?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a minimum of 4 Participants (Non-organizers) by noon on Thursday, August 20th. No Guests for this meet-up as demand is high and space is limited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Susan (AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadlines: The Final Deadline is Noon on Thursday, August 20th. Please be mindful if you change your RSVP to NO at the last minute that you may be taking a spot away from someone else that is serious about participating. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to arrive 10-15 minutes before 6:00 pm to get everyone organized to play. If for some reason you cannot make it right at 6:00 pm but would still like to play or you need clubs, please indicate it in the comment section when RSVPing to the meetup. PLEASE ALSO NOTE: if you intend to borrow clubs indicate what you need - women/men's, left or right handed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SSFMG and its organizers are not responsible for any injuries to participants or damage to equipment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather Alternative: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;None. This event will be canceled if it is raining or too foggy. We will do our best to cancel at least 6 hours in advance but we cannot control Mother Nature so we will do our best to notify everyone at least 3 hours prior to the event. Please do not change your RSVP based on weather forecasts. We check weather forecasts the night before and use those to determine if the event is canceled. Check emails Sunday night or Monday morning to determine event status.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool: There is no carpool for this event. Members should meet at the Braintree Municipal Golf Course. If you would like to carpool you may note where from in your RSVP comment and someone else may choose to contact you if they are also interested in carpooling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please allow a little extra time due to heavy traffic on Route 18&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rocklandgolfcourse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup outside the Pro-shop</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>8338847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251323332000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249753611000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Golf - 9 Holes at Rockland Golf Course</name><id>11065566</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251150300000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11065566/</event_url></item>