<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>62 Talbot Avenue Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.418430</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tufts University/Pearson Hall RM 104 </name><city>Medford</city><id>1185502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106164</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Saturday, February 27th 7-9pm &lt;br /&gt;A Presentation by Toby Hemenway: What Does Permaculture Look Like?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the Urban Homesteaders' League, the Tufts Food Systems Planning Coalition, and Tufts Slow Food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sliding Scale: $15-25 (Tufts students are free.) &lt;br /&gt;Buy tickets here: &lt;a href="http://www.eventsbot.com/events/eb651647603" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eventsbot....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Tufts University/Pearson Hall RM 104 &lt;br /&gt;62 Talbot Avenue Ave, Medford, MA 02155&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Permaculture is an increasingly popular set of solutions for sustainable living that is based on ecology. This presentation will show how permaculture works, and will give examples and images of permaculture in practice around North America. Whether you are new to permaculture or an experienced practitioner, this lively evening with one of the world's best-known permaculture teachers will offer both principles and practical steps you can take toward living more sustainably.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: &lt;br /&gt;Toby Hemenway is a writer, university professor, and freelance educator based in Portland, Oregon. He is the author of &amp;quot;Gaia's Garden: A Guide to Home-Scale Permaculture&amp;quot;, which for the past seven years has been the world&amp;#8217;s best-selling book on permaculture. Toby is an adjunct professor in the School of Graduate Education at Portland State University, and Scholar-in-Residence at Pacific University. His writing has appeared in publications such as Natural Home, Whole Earth Review, and WorldWatch, and he has taught workshops all over the continent and in many countries. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: You need to buy tickets at the link above or at the door.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to room 104</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Dion</member_name><member_id>6134374</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267488213000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265213935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Presentation by Toby Hemenway: What Does Permaculture Look Like?</name><id>12507453</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267315200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/12507453/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/7/global_7064327.jpeg</photo_url></item>