<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>152 Commonwealth Ave Unit M-1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.458334</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(877) 578-4777</phone><name>Lens Pro To Go</name><city>Concord</city><id>1066094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.396617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry to say, but I'm not likely to make tonight's event. The side wall of a front tire blew out and I'm unable to get it replaced until tomorrow at the earliest. It's apparently not a tire most places keep in stock :-/.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be members of both CAPE Group and Seacoast there tonight, please do look for each other.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm sorry that I won't be able to join you all, and to miss this presentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beth&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note:&lt;/strong&gt; You must &lt;span&gt;register and pay through CIPNE&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Register here&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="https://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/eventReg?oeidk=a07e5frelhtbd602608&amp;amp;oseq"&gt;https://events.r20.constantcontact.com/regi...&lt;/a&gt;=&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you've registered please RSVP here on our site so we know to expect you. &lt;em&gt;We can arrange to meet for a quick dinner beforehand if there's interest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; LensProToGo, 152 Commonwealth Ave, Unit M-1, Concord, MA 01742.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; CIPNE Members, Free; Non-members; $35; Full-time Students, $5.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://events.constantcontact.com/register/event?llr=4zkrpubab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e5frelhtbd602608"&gt;Click here to register&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Non-members may pay by PayPal). Please note: on-line registration closes Jan. 6th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;9th 2012 &lt;em&gt;Tim Tadder On Assignments&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commercial advertising photographer Tim Tadder will walk us through the dynamics of two drastically different styles of brand advertising campaigns shoots. We will first explore an "all hands on deck approach" where budgets are stretched razor thin and crews are pushed to the brink in order to bring great creative to light. Sometimes clients have a desire for more than they can afford. Tadder will explain how to temper unrealistic expectations and deliver great images on thin budgets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tadder will contrast this with a "no stone left unturned" approach, where clients budget for perfect production, every detail is debated, call sheets go on for pages, and pre production meetings run for hours. Sometimes more is less, and while big budgets make productions easier, they also can create overall complications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us as Tadder provides insight into his mistakes and successes and discusses his approach to creating successful shoots not matter what the budget or approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tim Tadder is a visual communicator who produces award-winning campaign work for top consumer brands including Adidas, Budweiser, Coke Zero, Craftsman, Gatorade, and more. He creates highly-stylized action shots that draw viewers into the moment. Tadder has always been active in sports, exploration, and adventure and believes that being familiar with shooting live action makes it easier to recreate the look for advertising shoots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326212257000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325179576000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CIPNE: Commercial Advertising Photographer Tim Tadder On Assignments</name><id>45847872</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326155400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/45847872/</event_url></item>