<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/a/event_236102682.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hey gang...it's our favorite nerd topic again - neuroscience!  Join us at the Middlesex Lounge as sciencecafes.org and NOVA/PBS present the Adolescent Brain Café. Alea Skwara from the Affective Neuroscience and Development Lab at Harvard University will be speaking about her work in understanding the social and neural influences on the human adolescent experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Science Cafes are sponsored by the folks from the NOVA television series on PBS, and feature a scientist speaking and answering questions in an informal format at a local pub over food and refreshments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;As always, getting there early is recommended - your organizers will probably get there around 6:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The Middlesex Lounge is located on Mass Ave, a few blocks from the Central Square Red Line stop in Cambridge. For folks who are driving, parking is available at the following locations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University Park @ MIT garage - 55 Franklin Street ($10 after 5:00 PM)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Green Street Garage - 260 Green Street ($6 after 6:00 PM, up to 4 hours)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cambridge municipal lots along Bishop Allen Drive (parallel to Mass Ave in Central Square)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Metered street parking along Mass Ave and nearby streets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Municipal and metered street parking is free after 6:00 (if you can find any, and watch out for the permit parking only signs on most side streets in Cambridge). Parking rates are from &lt;a href="http://en.parkopedia.com/"&gt;Parkopedia.com&lt;/a&gt; - YMMV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;From sciencecafes.org:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ever wonder why the world seems so different from when you were a teenager? Join us on May 21st for an evening with Alea Skwara from the Affective Neuroscience and Development Lab at Harvard University. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 An artist turned scientist, Alea earned her BA in Theatre from Davidson College in 2009. Since then, she has jumped into the world of psychology and neuroscience, trying on a new lens of understanding the human experience. She is currently the lab manager of the Affective Neuroscience and Development La&lt;/span&gt;b at Harvard University, where she works with Professor Leah Somerville to better understand the complexities of adolescence, from the social to the neural. In her work, Alea maintains a holistic perspective, considering the diverse factors that contribute to individual differences in emotion and cognition, and looking at the brain as a complex system of dynamic networks. A mountain girl at heart, Alea spends her free time meditating, hiking, and singing folk songs with her guitar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sciencecafes.org/"&gt;www.sciencecafes.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.middlesexlounge.us/"&gt;Middlesex Lounge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="http://andl.wjh.harvard.edu/"&gt;Affective Neuroscience and Development Laboratory at Harvard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/401896916584383/"&gt;Sciencecafes.Org Facebook Event Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Your organizers will be wearing Meetup pins.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369325351000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>60</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368571883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Adolescent Brain Café at the Middlesex Lounge</name><id>119405812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369177200000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/119405812/</event_url></item>