<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Atlantic Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.352551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Consulates: Demasi Piero Consul General</name><city>Boston</city><id>5921952</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054588</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Nando Pellegrino was born in Rome, Italy. Nando gives us a view into his world through his paintings of scenes through windows and doors. He connects the organic and architecture through colors and hues in order to develop relationships from the lights and shadow turning them into geometrical forms. The vista from windows and doors becomes a combination of savvy and naive literal abstracts. He practices and lives in Rhode Island. ARTIST'S STATEMENT BY NANDO A painting is a million moments of observation. When I make a painting I am amazed at how the light changes around the subject from moment to moment. The light moves through the object creating multiple illusions of colors. I take my brush from the paint and place the mark on the surface only to see the light has changed. I am intrigued how the colors and hues develop relationship between objects in the painting. I begin to chase the light. The game starts between me and the light of brilliant colors as together we create a literal abstract of depicted landscapes, cityscapes, figures and still lifes. The light moves quickly through the scenery connecting the organic and the architecture. It teases me saying catch me if you can. The painting then becomes connected together through a puzzle of geometric forms created from marks and colors. The end result becomes my magical world of observation. My purpose is to create a threshold that invites everyone into this world.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gianni </member_name><member_id>10523375</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330792763000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330453830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Artist Reception Nando Pellegrino</name><id>54196672</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330729200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/54196672/</event_url></item>