<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizers - Karine and Spruce&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a small group of fast hikers to hike the entire Carter-Moriah Range in a day. This includes six 4K peaks (Moriah, Middle Carter, South Carter, Carter Dome, Wildcat, Wildcat D) and a handful of other peaks we'll hit along the way - Mt. Hight, North Carter, Mt. Lethe, the other Wildcats. This range is known for it's beautiful views of the Presidential range. This isn't really a peak-bagging trip - if you "need" these peaks, there are much easier ways to get them! This hike is geared towards people who enjoy long, fast day hikes and are looking for a physical challenge. Admittedly, this hike is very difficult and is not for everyone - please be sure to answer all RSVP questions in full to demonstrate your preparedness for this hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Monday, May 28th is the rain date*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;On this  &lt;strong&gt;fast-paced&lt;/strong&gt; one-way trip we will&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;hike 19 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 8,500 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. Book time is 14.5 hours - but our plan/goal is to hike faster than book time and finish in 11-12 hours. This trip is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;EXTREME&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain&lt;/strong&gt;. This distance and elevation is comparable to a Presi traverse. Between the hiking and the car spots, this will be a LONG day - and you should be prepared to hike out in the dark if we run behind schedule.  You may want to stay over/camp the night before and/or the night after.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will hike North to South - starting at the Carter Moriah trail head, climb up to Moriah, over the Carters and down to Carter Notch (and the hut if we need to refill water), then we'll take the Wildcat Ridge trail up over the Wildcats and either descend to the Glen Ellis Falls trailhead or go down the Polecat ski trail depending on conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While we are familiar with these trails, we expect all participants to bring a map, and be familiar with the route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who should sign up?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To sign up for this hike, you should be an experienced hiker who has &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;recently&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; completed trips of similar distance (15+ miles) and elevation (6,000+ feet) - and be comfortable moving faster than book time. Please answer all RSVP questions - if we haven't hiked with you before, you may also be contacted by meet up organizers to further elaborate on your preparation/experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Footwear: Sturdy hiking boots/trail runners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater. ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip (2-3 Liters recommended).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Insect Repellant. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional Items: Waterproof/windproof pants. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will meet either at the Glen Ellis Falls trailhead or the Wildcat Ski area parking (both are on Route 16 north of Jackson, NH, near Pinkham Notch) to spot cars before heading north to the Carter-Moriah Trailhead in Gorham.  The exact meeting spot will be confirmed a day or two before the hike depending on conditions.  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;According to Google Maps this spot is about 160 miles from Boston and it should take about 3 hours 15 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=43.5022414,-71.6129185+to:NH-16+N%2FWhite+Mountain+Rd&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=43.326655,-71.02239&amp;amp;sspn=2.553413,5.41626&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFaHKlwIdCka7-ynXcn561EqzTDEugsKlbHNH6A%3BFcz6owIdRzzB-w&amp;amp;vpsrc=0&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=8&amp;amp;via=1"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for the driving directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Once you open Google Maps simply change the generic starting point ("Boston, MA") to your own starting point to get customized directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338238501000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337477517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moriah-Carters-Wildcats Traverse (Extreme)</name><id>65521232</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338114600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/65521232/</event_url></item>