<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>274 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.237621</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Greenside Grille Restaurant</name><city>Hingham</city><id>5956652</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.902130</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Members and Guests of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group as we celebrate our 6th Anniversary! This year we're changing things up - by going to Brunch! We will be heading to The Greenside Grille at the South Shore Country Club in Hingham!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greenside Grille is well known to SSDOMG. We dined there as a group last July, and Angela is also a fairly regular customer on her own. Given our consistently positive experiences there, we were happy to have them as an alternative when we had to change the venue for our Sixth Anniversary Dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The change of venue will in fact allow us to &lt;strong&gt;lower the price&lt;/strong&gt; of the event and even afford us a &lt;strong&gt;broader selection&lt;/strong&gt; of food! Not a bad deal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what exactly are we getting for our money? Here's a partial list from their online buffet menu: an Omelet Station, Waffle Station, Carving Station, Chicken Selection, Seafood Selection, Eggs Benedict, and a Fabulous Sweet Table!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They had us at "Waffle Station!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of this and more will come at the low cost of $22.00 per person, because as our &lt;strong&gt;anniversary gift&lt;/strong&gt; to our members, SSDOMG is &lt;strong&gt;waiving our normal event fee&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;picking up part of the tab!&lt;/strong&gt; (But please note that the base price only includes coffee and juices: If you &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; have soda or a mimosa, be prepared to pay for it!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're hoping that the reduced price and expanded selection will allow at least as many people to come and celebrate with us as we would have had if we hadn't changed the venue. And, of course, we're hoping that you'll be among them. If you'd like to read about how our last event at The Greenside Grille went, you can find it described &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/25903471/"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6th Anniversary Brunch Celebration!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Greenside Grille at the Hingham Country Club &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; Sunday, August 26th, 2012 @ 11:30 PM  &lt;br /&gt;

 274Main Street &lt;br /&gt;

 Hingham, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 (781) 749-1720 &lt;br /&gt;

 Website: &lt;a href="http://www.greensidegrille.com/index.html"&gt;The Greenside Grille&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizers:&lt;/strong&gt; Angela &amp;amp; Mike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/strong&gt; None at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. Up to 2 per Member - Your Guests are FREE today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price:&lt;/strong&gt; Will be $22.00, which will include coffee, tea, juices, tax &amp;amp; tip. &lt;strong&gt;Sodas and alcoholic beverages will be extra.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over five years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; NONE!  You can become a 2012 Annual Member for $5 at today's event, which is $1 off our regular mid-year price of $6.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Saturday, August 25th @ 12:00 PM.&lt;/em&gt; Changes to No after this point will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No-Show Policy on Membership Information Page:&lt;/em&gt; (Please click on the following link to be taken directly to the page.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/strong&gt; This event takes place rain or shine as it's an indoor event.  Please see our Weather policy on the About page. (Simply scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather.")&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview: Located just off Route 3A.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the South&lt;/em&gt;: Take Route 3 North to Exit 14 (Nantasket / Rockland).  Upon exit, take Route 228 North for approximately 6 miles.  Take a left on Central Street (towards Town Hall &amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt; Hingham Historic District).  At second stop sign, take a left on South Street.  Follow for approximately ¼ mile and &lt;span&gt;South Shore&lt;/span&gt; Country Club will be on left prior to &lt;span&gt;West Hingham&lt;/span&gt; Train Station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From &lt;span&gt;Boston&lt;/span&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;span&gt;Points North&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;: From Route 93 South take Exit 12 (Neponset / Quincy).  Follow signs to Route 3A South (beware of construction on &lt;span&gt;Neponset&lt;/span&gt; River Bridge).  Follow 3A South through &lt;span&gt;Quincy&lt;/span&gt;, over the Fore &lt;span&gt;River Bridge&lt;/span&gt; and into Weymouth.  Take a right onto Beal Street (at 99 Restaurant).  Follow straight until 1st set of lights.  Take a left and South Shore Country Club will be on your right.  [Alternatively, you could take Route 93 South to Route 3 South and follow the directions above "From the South."]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346213520000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342189232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>6th Anniversary Brunch Celebration!</name><id>73188862</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345995000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/73188862/</event_url></item>