<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Product Launch Roadmap: What to Do and When to Do It&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 4 P’s of Marketing are critical to the Product Launch. It starts with Market analysis and a Market needs assessment, a competitive analysis and competitive product bench tests, and continues to developing an ROI / Sales Plan, getting launch budget, creating the marketing plan, and managing a cross-functional launch team of Regulatory, Clinical, Quality, R&amp;amp;D, Manufacturing, Supply Chain, Marketing Communications and Legal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sounds like a lot of work? It is, but with good planning, it is all manageable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation is designed for medical device employees that want a thorough overview of the product launch cycle and roadmap. We will review the entire process of getting a product to market, with specific focus on successful product launch, and all the activities it requires. Of special interest to the MDG constituency will be an overview of where R&amp;amp;D and other engineering based functions fit in the product launch process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation covers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Product development cycle overview &lt;br /&gt;the one page marketing plan &lt;br /&gt;Critical success factor review in product launch activities &lt;br /&gt;The Limited Market Release – dos and don’ts &lt;br /&gt;Who should attend?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marketing and product managers &lt;br /&gt;R&amp;amp;D &lt;br /&gt;Project Team Members needing an overview in their part of the product launch process &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maria Shepherd has 20 years of leadership experience in medical device and life sciences marketing in small start-ups and Fortune 100 companies. She founded Data Decision Group after a career in industry that included serving as Vice President of Marketing for Oridion Medical, and Director of Marketing for Philips Medical and senior management at Boston Scientific. She has also served on the corporate board of the American Patient Safety Foundation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maria received her MBA, magna cum laude, from Babson College, cited by USA Today as the top US entrepreneurial program. She also earned a BA in Biology from University of Pennsylvania. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Data Decision Group (www.ddecisiongroup.com) is a full service medical marketing company. We are a healthcare vertical specializing in strategy consulting (White Space Research, Due Diligence, Portfolio Analysis), marketing support and market research for the medical device, pharmaceutical, diagnostics and biotech industries. We are a highly experienced team with unique in-depth clinical and industry knowledge, Data Decision Group synthesizes and transfers clinical findings into product design recommendations that can be rapidly and profitably integrated into client product development.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A meeting fee payable in cash or check (to &amp;quot;MedDev Group, Inc.&amp;quot;) will be collected at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Networking Event Fee &lt;br /&gt;Member $15 &lt;br /&gt;Nonmember $15 first visit&lt;br /&gt;$25 subsequently &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.memberclicks.com/mc/community/eventdetails.do?eventId=288193&amp;amp;orgId=meg&amp;amp;recurringId=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.memberclic...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295481308000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292992501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Product Launch Roadmap: What to Do and When to Do It</name><id>15796364</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295476200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15796364/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>