<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This 2nd meet- up will be at Victory Rd Park.  We've used it before.  There's more grass and space for the pups to run around.  I recognize that some of the pups don't like the gravel at Peter's Park, so this should be a good alternative.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully Sunday afternoon works well for everyone.  I thought a change up in the day and time might let more people attend.  Hopefully by having two meet-ups this month everyone will get to participate!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation procedure: If it is raining, too hot, too cold, etc. a cancellation notice will be sent via email and posted on the meetup website 2 hours prior to the meetup time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Meetup.com charges each group a $15 a month meetup fee. This is a GROUP fee and if not paid, our Boston French Bulldog meetups, would not exist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizer is in charge of paying this fee every month. It would be greatly appreciated if at each meetup, each member can submit a donation that goes towards the monthly $15 fee. Give $1, give $10. If at the end of the meetup, the organizer has not collected enough to meet the $15, she will pay the difference. If she receives more than $15, the extra would go towards the next meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to allow payment by PayPal, I had to put a minimum &amp;quot;Suggested Donation.&amp;quot; This is just to cover the meetup.com fee. You can give whatever you feel is appropriate. The cost is $15 per month, so you don't have to give every month either. Whatever works for you. And you can do it through PayPal or at the MeetUp. Hope this helps!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's more difficult to recognize me from the picture in the winter because my hair is up and I'm usually wearing a hat.  : )  But Lola is a tall, lean, pied Frenchie w/ one eye patch.  So look for her and you'll probably see me.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204053101000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>What better way to spend a Sunday afternoon than with a bunch of Frenchies!</why><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201359512000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd February Meet - Up</name><id>7199391</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203879600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/7199391/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/9/1/global_381217.jpeg</photo_url></item>