<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Easy 4 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 11am &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt; @ dead-end of Old Enfield Road, Belchertown, Mass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/a/6/event_82123942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please park on either side of the road, and do not block the gate. We'll hike down the road to our right, and through Gate 4, which will take us to the shore farthest south before the restricted-access zone. It's a pretty spot, with views of Quabbin Hill and the viewing tower directly across, and Winsor Dam to the south.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we'll backtrack to Gate 5 and follow Old Enfield Road until it goes into the water. It's a really pretty spot, across from the gap between Prescott Penninsula and Quabbin Hill. For lunch/snack break, my choice would be the 2nd spot, but I'll let the group decide. It's not a long hike, so even with a break and picture-taking, it will be less than 2 hours. Great first introduction to Quabbin Reservoir!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No wading nor pets; Quabbin is a public water supply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please remove your trash from the premises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring a drink, and lunch or snack. We'll take a break at the shore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No outhouses at these gates! (Facilities on the way: Route 202...New Salem General Store; Intersection of 9/202...McDonald's)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Northeast and Northwest:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 122 or 2 to Route 202, and go south to Route 9 (about 1/2 hour). Turn right to go east on Route 9. After 1 mile, turn left onto Old Enfield Road. (It's across from Route 21 at a flashing yellow light.) Follow this residential street until it dead-ends in front of a yellow gate. Please park on either side, and don't block the gate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, if Route 31 is convenient, go south to the center of Spencer and turn right onto Route 9 west. Continue as below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from South, West, and East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 east or west.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the west, pass Amherst and enter Belchertown. Pass through the intersection of 202 (McDonald's on right).&amp;nbsp; After 1 mile, Old Enfield Road is on the right, across from Route 21 at a flashing yellow light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from east (Worcester), pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. Pass all 3 Quabbin Reservoir park entrances. Look for Route 21 on the left at a flashing yellow light. Old Enfield Road is on the right. (If you pass Route 202 and McDonald's on the left, you've gone too far.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326219397000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325895159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginner hike: Quabbin Reservoir, Gate 5 to Gate 4 and back</name><id>47013432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326124800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/47013432/</event_url></item>