<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Before signing up for this event, please read and understand the entire Write-Up and the Liability Waiver. By signing up for this event you agree to the terms of the waiver.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rating: Strenuous&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Distance: 9.0 Miles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Time Duration: 5 Hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Orange: Recommended&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This will be a combined pre-hike of the Mt. Tom and JB Hudson trails for those members in the process of completing the Weber 40 hikes. Since this is a pre-hike of these trails and the anticipated trail conditions due to all the rain the number of participants will be kept low and no waiting list will be available.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Mt. Tom trail is a 6.5 mile loop within Exeter which features a variety of attractions. We will cross rushing brooks, climb atop a rocky cliff, pass the remains of an old gristmill and hike through a thriving reforestation project. This should take us about 3.5 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The JB Hudson Trail is a 3 miles trail also in Exeter. This trail passes through a surging pine grove, past a tiny cemetery and a fish ladder near its end. This should take about 1.5 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Portions of this hike will be wet and muddy due to the recent rain; therefore a good pair of hiking boots is recommended.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bring Drinking water (1 Liter per person), Snacks, Hiking Boots and bug spray.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Safety First!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John N</member_name><member_id>11460346</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt</member_name><member_id>37623632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1371436876000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1371229247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Combined Pre-Hike of JB Hudson (Weber #13) and Mt. Tom (Weber #14) Trails</name><id>124647022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1371389400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/124647022/</event_url></item>