<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Lets Revel in Some Holiday Cheer!  Come to my house for a Yankee Swap Christmas Party!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is a Yankee Swap?&lt;/b&gt;  Everyone brings a wrapped gift (no more than $10.00). Everyone draws a number.  The first person picks a gift under the tree, and unwraps it.  When the second person goes, they pick a gift under the tree to unwrap as well, and can either choose to keep it or swap with the first person if they like that gift better.  And so forth and so on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please bring a dish to share, and B.Y.O.B.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can also play Left, Right, Center.  It's a dice game which is hilarious.  The buy in is 3 one dollar bills for each game.  Bring 9 one dollar bills so we can play at least three games.  Whoever wins keeps the pot!  I'll explain the game in more detail when you get here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress is casual, but it would be nice if you wore something festive: something with red, a Santa hat, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.  I do have a dog and cats so if your allergic, don't forget to take your allergy meds!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can come!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sharon&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll Be the One Opening Door Wishing You a Merry Christmas!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharon</member_name><member_id>8235187</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232903538000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228323569000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yankee Swap Christmas Party with Pot Luck!   B.Y.O.B.</name><id>9273210</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231545600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/9273210/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/4/global_5975620.jpeg</photo_url></item>