<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte. 116, South Hadley</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01075</zip><lat>42.215430</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Mount Holyoke College, Gamble Auditorium</name><city>South Hadley</city><id>478993</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.589430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;In a Different Voice&lt;/b&gt;:  What Happens when a famed feminist psychologist turns her hand to fiction?  Find out January 31, when Caroll Gilligan reads from her first novel, a love story titled &lt;i&gt;Kyra&lt;/i&gt; that is due to be released mid-month.  Gilligan is a major figure in gender studies, best known for her book &amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;In a Different Voice: Psychological Theory and Women's Development&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot;, first published in 1982.  Her research pioneered the view that women and girls posses different-but no less worthy-moral values and psychological tendencies than men and boys.  Gilligian taught at Harvard for more than 30 years, and held the University's first position in gender studies.  She now teaches at New York University and lives part-time in the Berkshires.  In her first foray into fiction, Gilligan explores the story of a woman coping with love and loss and navigating pain of betrayal.  Publishers Weekly writes, &amp;quot;The Novel's great strength is Kyra's voice, which Gilligan renders with assurance and lyricism.  The result is a powerful portrait of a complex character&amp;quot;.  Not surprising for a psychologist whose life's work celbrates and amplifies the power of women's voices. A question and answer period and book signing will follow the reading.  The event is co-sponsored by the Odyssey Bookshop.  For info call the Odyssey at 534-7307.  (This excerpt was writtenby the Women's Times and and can be found in their January Edition)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>4671887</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201997028000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1514</urlname><id>824401</id><group_lat>42.0999984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5899963379</group_lon><name>Single Mingle Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200360759000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Carol Gilligan Book Reading</name><id>7116168</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201824000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1514/events/7116168/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/6/b/global_2890459.jpeg</photo_url></item>