<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Applying Law of Attraction to Your Life&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Getting More of What You Want and Less of What You Don’t&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have become aware of this very powerful force at work in your life. It's called the Law of Attraction and right now it is attracting people, jobs, situations, and relationships into your life. The problem is, not all of these things are the way you want. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great news, there's a straightforward way to change that. In this special TELE-Meetup, we are very delighted to have &lt;b&gt;expert Law of Attraction trainer, best-seller author and radio host, Michael Losier,&lt;/b&gt; teach us how to apply the Law of Attraction to our advantage so we can attract more of what we want into our lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You will learn:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Why and how the Law of Attraction works;&lt;br /&gt;    * Why we're not attracting what we desire;&lt;br /&gt;    * How to change our thoughts and words to stop attracting what we don't want;&lt;br /&gt;    * The three-step process for deliberate attraction;&lt;br /&gt;    * &lt;i&gt;and most importantly,&lt;/i&gt; WHY people are NOT attracting what they say they desire&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 8:00 - 9:00 PM EST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, if you're ready to take the next step, join this interactive high-content training TELE-Meetup and expect to learn GREAT tools and information on how to tap into Law of Attraction deliberately -- the art of Deliberate Attraction. There's a science to doing it and Michael Losier provides you with the simple 3-step formula to use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Michael Losier:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lawofattractionbook.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lawofattra...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Visit Michael on Facebook:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Michael-Losier/75475862711" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Losier (Low-zee-eh) lives in beautiful Victoria BC, on Canada’s west coast.  He is the author of the best selling book: Law of Attraction: The Science of Attracting More of What You Want and Less of What You Don’t .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael has been teaching Law of Attraction since 1996, when he had audiences of three people.  His self published book became a word-of-mouth success and sold ¼ million copies since its release in 2003.  His book has now been translated into 21 languages and has been reaching the best seller lists in many countries, including Brazil, Ireland, UK, Japan and Spain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The world-wide release of the movie The Secret, spurred hundreds and hundreds of hungry Law of Attraction seekers, to seek out more information about the Law of Attraction. Michael’s business flourished as many fans of The Secret wondered how to apply the Law of Attraction to their daily lives. Michael was quickly branded as the ‘How-to’ guy for Law of Attraction and his book sales soared!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2007, Michael caught the attention of Oprah Winfrey and was subsequently interviewed 4 times on her radio show Oprah &amp;amp; Friends on XM satellite radio. Michael hosted his own show for 1 year in 1998 with his own weekly radio show on Oprah &amp;amp; Friends called: The Law of Attraction Radio Show with Michael Losier.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>218-486-3850  Pin 33726 #</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256001960000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>23</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>91</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253648936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special TELE-Meetup with Michael Losier, "How To" Guy  for LOA</name><id>11439264</id><headcount>91</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254268800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/11439264/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/3/a/global_10853178.jpeg</photo_url></item>