<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>730 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.365898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 868-8800</phone><name>Tavern in the Square - Central Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>680367</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105103</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come out and meet other Boston area Science Fiction and Fantasy fans in a comfortable setting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the regular social meetup for the Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group, which always happens on the First Tuesday of every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We regularly meet at Tavern in the Square in Central Square (NOTE: NOT THE ONE IN PORTER SQUARE). We have a standing reservation for the private room in the back, so we have a reasonably quiet space to ourselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're taking the T, Central Square is on the Red Line, and Tavern in the Square is about a block away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're driving in, there are a few parking lots nearby. There are two public lots (free after 6 PM) at the intersection of Bishop Allen Drive and Prospect St: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/5fLIL8" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly/5fLIL8...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is also pay parking ($8 for the evening) here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pilgrimparking.com/facilities/central_sq/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pilgrimpar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll probably talk about the books, television, movies, comics and games that we like (and those we don't like, and even those we may be ashamed to admit that we like), but there is no set agenda!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're can't come on time, that's fine, there is usually still a critical mass of people until 9:00 PM (or later). If you want to come early, that is fine too, I usually get there around 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have SciFi/Fantasy Books or DVDs that you don't want anymore? Feel free to bring them to the meetup and give them away (please, no sales here), but be sure that you take home anything that is left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn</member_name><member_id>9373103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280981791000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278516251000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August Social Meetup</name><id>14028287</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280874600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/14028287/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/global_8154265.jpeg</photo_url></item>