<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>How can I use the law of attraction for a great relationship?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe you're looking for a special relationship, or you're interested in learning how to improve a relationship you're in. We invite you to join us in sharing and discussing how to deliberately and effectively use the Law of Attraction to have the relationships you desire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The principles and strategies we discuss will apply to all relationships. Do you have someone at work who's difficult to work with, or a challenging family member? Bring your questions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a part of the evening, we'll be sharing our belief assessment tool to help you reveal any possible limiting beliefs that might be keeping you from being fully aligned with what you're asking for. I'll also be leading you through a beautiful guided meditation to help you strengthen your relationship with yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We believe there's nothing as good as learning in person and developing a community to support each other. There's power in in-person group energy: increased, embodied learning; emotional support; the power of contributing to others; and stronger intentional energies; to name a few. We encourage you to join us as regularly as possible to help us form a strong, rewarding, like-minded community!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, after you RSVP, as always, please let us know if your plans change, so we won’t be waiting for you unnecessarily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266624227000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266267752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How can I use the Law of Attraction for a great relationship?</name><id>12611369</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266451200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/12611369/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/1/9/global_13131865.jpeg</photo_url></item>