<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302990</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center of Light</name><city>Framingham</city><id>7536472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434044</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In June, the Centers of Light will show &lt;a href="http://centersoflight.org/monthly-conscious-movie/" target="_blank"&gt;Farmageddon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Americans’ right to access fresh, healthy foods of their choice is under attack. Farmageddon tells the story of small, family farms that were providing safe, healthy foods to their communities and were forced to stop, sometimes through violent action, by agents of misguided government bureaucracies, and seeks to figure out why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All donations collected will go to support &lt;a href="http://farmandranchfreedom.org/" target="_blank"&gt;The Farm and Ranch Freedom Alliance&lt;/a&gt; which works to save family farms and individuals from expensive and unnecessary government regulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. We are looking forward to sharing this film with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Centers of Light are mystical Christian centers and communities dedicated to consciousness, spiritual growth, and empowerment.  Each of the 10 Centers of Light across the country offer daily meditation, sacraments, seminars, and spiritual classes. Christian Mysticism is the inner, esoteric path of Christianity, comparable to Kabbalah in Judaism, Zen Buddhism, or Sufism in Islam. All Centers of Light work to bring peace to the planet by helping people gain real, deep connection with God and become dynamic forces for positive change.  For more information, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.centersoflight.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.CentersOfLight.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341112384000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340047853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June’s Conscious Movie – Farmageddon: the Unseen War on American Family Farms</name><id>69703472</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341097200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/69703472/</event_url></item>