<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ben is trying to finish his NH&amp;nbsp;48 by Sunday. This Friday is the only day where the weather forecast looks good. If you want to join Ben in his quest, sign up for this hike. There is still snow in the mountains, so you will need to bring traction (microspikes)&amp;nbsp;and snowshoes. This should not be your first hike this season. You should have experience in hiking above treeline.&amp;nbsp; The hike will be ~14 mi. rt. Contact Ben for more information via email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gear List&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Synthetic shirt and pants, including at least one insulating layer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waterproof rain jacket (with hood) and pants. Down jacket, hat, glove liners and gloves for the summit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High-energy snacks, food for lunch and water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Trekking poles. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GO BEN!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303478300000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303249372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Race to finish the NH48 ---Waumbek or Twins and Galehead hike</name><id>17363909</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303473600000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/17363909/</event_url></item>