<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>If you enjoy scenery and wildlife, we will be particularly excited to have you on our walks!&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk will be about 4 to 5 miles long.  We will climb Holt Hill for nice views extending from the surrounding Merrimack Valley to the Boston skyline.  We will also walk along wooded trails and former wood roads with old stone walls to guide us.  Although the elevation only changes by a few hundred feet, there is quite a bit of up and down walking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hiker Code of Conduct&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please try not to get too far ahead of the group.  I go to a lot of effort to organize these walks, and  it's not enjoyable when people run ahead and create their own event.  If you have an emergency, I completely understand. Otherwise, these are designed to be leisurely, social walks, with time to appreciate the critters around us!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can always use more organizers, and if anyone feels that the pace of the walk is not appropriate for their needs, they should consider organizing their own event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;About Ward Reservation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ward Reservation contains hayfields, hilltops, wetlands, creeks, swamps, and woodlands. Colonial era stone walls on the property, when combined, total more than 17 miles (27 km) long.  Trails link three major hills – Shrub, Boston, and Holt.  The “Solstice Stones” mark the grassy summit of Holt Hill, the highest point in Essex County. This compass-like arrangement of stones indicates the cardinal points on the compass, the points of the summer and winter solstices, and the points of the spring and autumnal equinoxes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE THAT THERE ARE NO RESTROOMS ON SITE SO PLEASE USE FACILITIES BEFORE YOUR ARRIVAL!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on Ward Reservation, here is the website: &lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/northeast-ma/ward-reservation.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Trails&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Almost 10 miles of trails, easy-to-moderate hiking, strenuous in places.  &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hiking shoes are strongly recommended&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.  Some of the trails here are part of the Bay Circuit Trail, a regional greenway linking the North Shore and South Shore. The reservation totals 700 acres. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Getting There&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93 Exit 41, take Rt. 125 North 5 mi. Turn right onto Prospect Rd. (which has a blinking yellow light, I believe) and follow for 0.3 mi. to entrance and parking on right. From Rt. I-495 Exit 42, take Rt. 114 East 1.7 mi. You will pass Merrimack College on your right shortly before you need to turn right onto Rt. 125 South or Andover Bypass Street. (It's more like a right fork). Follow Route 125 South for 1.6 mi.  The last time I was here, there was a large patch of dead trees on both sides of the road a 1/2 mile before your next turn.  Turn left onto Prospect Road, which I believe has a yellow blinking light, and follow for 0.3 mi. to entrance and parking on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note, if you are using a GPS, the address for parking is &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;59 Prospect Road in Andover&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. (Things get tricky because the park covers areas of North Andover and Andover- you want Andover. Also, there is a Prospect Street in North Andover that you don't want- you want Prospect Road.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;How the Waiting List Works&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When someone from the hike drops, everyone on the waiting list is automatically emailed.  The first person on the the waiting list to add themselves to the hike will get in.  I realize that this doesn't seem fair for the first person on the waiting list, if someone lower on the list gets in.  However, I found that the automatic waiting list resulted in a very high percentage of no-shows.  A number of people didn't check their email, even days before the hike, and therefore didn't know they had gotten in to the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking area with meetup stickers on.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1288658756000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287927647000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Nature Walk at Ward Reservation-many Stops</name><id>15209828</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288530000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15209828/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/a/global_8053098.jpeg</photo_url></item>