<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Church St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374370</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>888-262-4386</phone><name>AMC Loews Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669120</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE ADVANCED SCREENING &amp;amp; DIRECTOR Q&amp;amp;A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** WHERE IN THE WORLD IS OSAMA BIN LADEN? **&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THURSDAY, APRIL 3RD @ 7:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Square Theater&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;** There will be a brief question and answer session with the film's director, MORGAN SPURLOCK following this special advanced screening. **&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View &lt;a href="http://www.whereisobl.com/" target="_blank"&gt;WHERE IN THE WORLD IS OSAMA BIN LADEN?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please print out the pass located in the group's file for admission, each pass admits two - feel free to print as many as you need.  Just as an FYI: seating is not guaranteed and is available on a first come first served basis, so arrive early!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email advanced.screening@gmail.com with &amp;quot;WHERE IN THE WORLD IS OSAMA BIN LADEN?&amp;quot; as the subject line if you have any further questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Synopsis:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If Morgan Spurlock has learned anything from over 30 years of movie-watching, it?s that if the world needs saving, it?s best done by one lonely guy, willing to face danger head on, and take it down, action hero style.  In WHERE IN THE WORLD IS OSAMA BIN LADEN?, the Oscar nominated filmmaker takes on a franchise even more lethal than McDonald?s?Al Qaeda.  And after this real life action thriller is over, the world may never be the same.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, with no military experience, knowledge or expertise, he sets off to do what the CIA, FBI and U.S. military have all failed to do: find the world?s most wanted man.  Why take on such a seemingly impossible mission?  Simple?he wants to make the world safe for his soon to be born child.  But before he finds bin Laden, he first needs to learn where he came from and the environment and influences that shaped him.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following bin Laden?s trail through some of the most dangerous places in the world, Spurlock encounters both the rational and the radical faces of the Middle East.  He interviews many people who embrace him on the streets and welcome him into their homes, experiencing their cultures in ways that sharply contrast with the conventional media images of the region.  Spurlock finds they?re not that different from American families, sharing the same hopes and fears for their children that he has for his own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE IN THE WORLD IS OSAMA BIN LADEN? goes beyond shedding light on the one man that has shaped the world?s perception of a region and its people.  Spurlock risks life and limb to uncover the truth about bin Laden, and in doing so explores the lines that divide, those that unite, and the countless shades of grey between.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Opening: April 18th&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chelsea</member_name><member_id>3861711</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212077749000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Get an inside look!  There will be a brief Q&amp;A session with director Morgan Spurlock following the film.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207157663000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE ADVANCE SCREENING AND DIRECTOR Q&amp;A - WHERE IN THE WORLD IS OSAMA BIN LADEN?</name><id>7658486</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207265400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7658486/</event_url></item>