<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-325</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>447074</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Note that these talks are intermediate options talks that assume some knowledge of options.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9:00: Trading Index Options by Marty Kearney&lt;/strong&gt;, Director, CBOE and Senior Staff Instructor, The Options Institute&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marty will discuss several intermediate to advanced strategies.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;First, he&amp;rsquo;ll describe planning option trades, explaining option price behavior and the thought process of option traders. Second, he&amp;rsquo;ll discuss trading volatility with options on the CBOE Volatility Index&amp;reg; (VIX&amp;reg;). &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Third, he&amp;rsquo;ll review intermediate to advanced strategies like debit spreads and time spreads that offer traders advantages for specific market forecasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Kearney became an independent Market Maker in early 1981.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Beginning in 1992, he developed and implemented hedging and trading strategies using listed options for a brokerage firm&amp;rsquo;s institutional clients and retail investors.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Currently, at The Options Institute his duties include helping brokers develop new business with conservative option strategies such as covered- writing and portfolio hedging. He contributes regularly to news services including Barrons Fortune, CNBC, and Bloomberg.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Mr. Kearney coauthored&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Understanding LEAPS&lt;/span&gt;&amp;reg;, published by McGraw-Hill, and contributed to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Options: Essential Concepts and Strategies&lt;/span&gt;, edited by The Options Institute, the educational arm of the CBOE.&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trading Options for Income&lt;/strong&gt; by Dan Sheridan&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan Sheridan will show what options spread strategies are appropriate in the current market environment, and the challenges and opportunities the market presents. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;He will base selected strategies on the current market dynamics, particularly the market trend and implied volatility.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Also, he&amp;rsquo;ll show butterfly trades, emphasizing ways to adjust the trade if the market moves against the trade.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan is a veteran options trader, who traded in the CBOE pit for 22 years.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;He worked for Mercury Trading, with Jon and Pete Najarian, making markets in options.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Since 2004, Dan has run Sheridan Options Mentoring, a company which mentors students one-on-one.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Dan offers free monthly webcasts on options strategies for CBOE.com and regularly gives webcasts for options trading brokers including Think or Swim, Options Monster, and Options Xpress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To join our online discussion go to &lt;a href="http://groups.google" class="linkified"&gt;http://groups.google&lt;/a&gt;.... or send email to Jeff Orrik at orrik@comcast.net If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you! Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room. We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone. This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306368283000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>60</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304703282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Speakers Meeting - Marty Kearny (CBOE) and Dan Sheridan -  9am-1pm</name><id>17569608</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305982800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/17569608/</event_url></item>