<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>USNH</name><city>Hamden</city><id>180814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our speaker this month will be &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fred_Edwords" target="_blank"&gt;Fred Edwords&lt;/a&gt; who, as the then executive director of the &lt;a href="http://www.americanhumanist.org/" target="_blank"&gt;American Humanist Association&lt;/a&gt;, was our inaugural speaker at our organizational meeting in the spring of 1989.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting as a local chapter leader in 1977, Fred went on to be executive director at the AHA for fifteen years, and editor of the Humanist for twelve. Most recently he served as director of communications for the AHA and he has just become the leader of a new organization, the United Coalition of Reason, with the purpose of developing coalitions of local humanist, freethought, atheist, Humanistic Jewish, and Ethical Culture organizations all over the country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fred will be presenting a talk entitled “Making Humanism Relevant,” about which he says: “Humanists have gotten good at critiquing traditional religion. But we didn’t become humanists merely to make such debunking our focus. Humanism offers a larger view that takes us in positive new directions. And many of those directions include vigorous activism toward social change. There is, in fact, a long history of humanist and freethought social action to inspire us. Putting our values to work is thus a central part of our tradition. Though we've sometimes had to do this by going against the grain of popular religion, at other times we've been able to leverage our influence through common cause with religious allies.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start with a pot-luck dinner (please bring a dish to share) and cake at 7:30 PM, and Fred's talk will follow brief announcements at 8:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(It is not necessary to RSVP for this event; I'm listing it as a meetup so that you can get e-mail reminders from meetup.com)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will most probably be in the Social Hall near the main entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>richard.s</member_name><member_id>1140524</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241039830000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238518736000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Humanist Association of Connecticut 20th Anniversary Meeting</name><id>10079545</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240270200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/10079545/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/b/7/global_7925815.jpeg</photo_url></item>