<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Mountain Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06032</zip><lat>41.721367</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.677.4787</phone><name>Hill-Stead Museum</name><city>Farmington</city><id>664278</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.827520</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Sunken Garden Poetry and Music Festival&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a spectacular opportunity!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pack your picnic dinner and lawn chair/blanket and join us. Lets get there early to picnic and find good seating. Parking is $10.00 per car, we can plan a meeting spot outside of the Hillstead and drive in as groups if you like.  Driving in yourself, look for the BW piano Scarf, flying on a tall stake on the picnic grounds in the garden to find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 1992, audiences have enjoyed verse and music among the fragrant blooms of  within. Hill-Stead’s Sunken Garden. This performance series has featured the likes of Billy Collins, Yusef Komunyakaa, Maxine Kumin and Grace Paley. Festivities include a plein air café and bookstore and meet-the-poet opportunities. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Featuring:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marie Ponsot; Gabrielle Calvocoressi&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marie Ponsot&lt;/b&gt; Native New Yorker Marie Ponsot was born in 1921. She has published numerous works, including Springing (2002); The Bird Catcher (1998 — winner of the National Book Critics Circle Award and finalist for the 1999 Lenore Marshall Poetry Prize); The Green Dark (1988); Admit Impediment (1981); and True Minds (1957). In addition to the National Book Critics Circle Award, Ms. Ponsot is the recipient of the Delmore Schwartz Memorial Prize, the Shaughnessy Medal of the Modern Language Association, and a creative writing grant from the NEA. She teaches in the graduate writing program at Columbia University, New York City.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gabrielle Calvocoressi's&lt;/b&gt; first collection of poems, The Last Time I Saw Amelia Earhart (2005), won the Connecticut Book Award and was shortlisted for the Northern California Book Award. Recipient of numerous awards and fellowships, Ms. Calvocoressi has been or is soon-to-be published in many journals and online publications including The Paris Review, The New England Review, Gulf Coast, Guernica and The Owls. Born in Central Connecticut, Ms. Calvocoressi lives in Los Angeles and teaches in the MFA program at California College of Arts in San Francisco and in the MFA Program in Creative Writing at Warren Wilson College. In the fall of 2009, she began a visiting professorship at Bennington College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Music:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Common Ground&lt;/b&gt; provides a unique blend of Afro Cuban jazz and world music that takes the listener on an unexpected journey. Common Ground is Obanilu Allende from Puerto Rico on drums, Pawan Benjamin from Nepal on saxophone and bamboo flute, Christian Sands from Orange, CT on piano, Chris Smith on bass, and Jake Goldbas, a Simsbury, CT native and graduate on the Greater Hartford Academy of the Arts, on drums, and Solomon Howard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facts:&lt;br /&gt;Time: Gates open at 4:30 pm. Music begins at 6:30 pm; Poetry begins at 7:30 pm. Books and CDs available for sale 5:30–8:30 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venue: All performances will be at Hill-Stead Museum, &lt;b&gt;rain or shine&lt;/b&gt; (there will be a tent on site in the event of rain).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: Free to the public. On-site parking: $10 per vehicle. Off-site local parking is available on a limited basis, free public parking available on a limited basis at Brickwalk Shops, off High Street, Farmington.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seating: Bring a lawn chair or blanket for seating in and around the garden.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food: Al fresco dining will be allowed on the West Lawn and in the Sunken Garden on performance evenings. Participants are welcome to bring their own picnic suppers or purchase food and beverages on site from Truffles Bakery, Farmington (www.trufflesbakery.com). &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the BW piano Scarf, flying on a tall stake!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277397041000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272376831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunken Garden Poetry and Music Festival</name><id>13305123</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277328600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13305123/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/3/global_14676339.jpeg</photo_url></item>