<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>At the Sturbridge Host Hotel</address_2><address_1>366 Main St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01566</zip><lat>42.112173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-347=7393</phone><name>Oxhead Tavern</name><city>Sturbridge </city><id>967374</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.088543</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>7 pm DINNER RESERVATIONS, come join us!  Live Music Outdoors on the patio.....dance, dance, dance!  Come out and join in on the fun, even if you don't dance, come watch.....relax.............eat, drink (outdoor bar) and laugh!  Oxhead Tavern is located at the Sturbridge Host Hotel and the band will be playing outdoors on the patio with the lake view behind it!  Awesome!  Of course this is if good weather permits so if rainy then they will be indoors for us to enjoy.  Bigtime Band is made up of experienced musicians of the Boston band and music scene. All of the band's members have worked in a wide variety of rock, soul and wedding bands. Located in the Boston, Massachusetts area, the band formed in 1993 and has been making music as a nightclub, party and wedding band in New Hampshire, Rhode Island, Connecticut and Maine, as well as Massachusetts.  The band plays a wide range of fun, danceable songs to please all ages and tastes. From Wedding Standards, Top 40, Oldies, Funk, Rock, and Disco, Bigtime gets you on the dance floor and keep you there with a high energy performance and smooth vocals. You won't want to miss this fun evening! PLEASE STATE IN YOUR 'YES RSVP' IF YOU ARE COMING FOR 7 PM DINNER WITH US, prior to the show starting later that evening. Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask Hostess for LINDA for 7 pm dinner reservations - OR if just coming for the entertainment then meet outside on the patio (it overlooks the water - gorgious!) </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280166597000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275862339000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>'BIGTIME Band' @ Oxhead Tavern</name><id>13717765</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280012400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/13717765/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/4/global_15544836.jpeg</photo_url></item>