<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>131 Dartmouth St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.346790</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Douzo</name><city>Boston</city><id>669006</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's that time of the year again! &lt;a href="http://www.douzosushi.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Douzo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bounenkai literally means &amp;quot;forget the year party&amp;quot;. It's a Japanese tradition where co-workers/classmates/friends get together at the end of year to celebrate the year that's past in order to leave it behind, especially the bad things. A bounenkai usually involves good food, good conversations and heavy drinking-  after all, drinking heavily is one of the best ways to forget things...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, I'm not going to promote excessive drinking this year. That's why we are having the bounenkai on a Tuesday night, at a somewhat fancy restaurant. So we can't afford the time or money to get too drunk, at least for most of us. With that being said, please come out and celebrate this end of year tradition with your fellow meetup members!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Douzo-&lt;br /&gt;This is a fairly new Japanese restaurant in Back Bay/South End. The theme there is modern, chic, New York lounge-style. It has gotten some good reviews by both Japanese and non-Japanese customers. Check their &lt;a href="http://www.douzosushi.com/" target="_blank"&gt;menu&lt;/a&gt; online, you can find some authentic dishes such as ankimo (monk fish liver pate), ohitashi, chawan mushi, etc. For sake lovers, Douzo offers an extensive list of Japanese sake, the best I've seen in town. Just bring enough cash with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, I apologize for those who RSVPed &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; when this event was scheduled for 12/14. I was informed later by Douzo's manager that they can't accommodate large groups on weekends, bummer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to this event ONLY if you are sure you can attend.  RSVP by Monday night, 12/17 as I need to confirm reservation with the restaurant. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198195603000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194841381000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bounenkai @ Douzo</name><id>6724670</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198022400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/6724670/</event_url></item>