<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi again, I stopped by the Sevens last night to check out our meeting spot.  It is a cool pub and only 2 blocks from the Arthur Fiedler bridge into the park for the Hatch Shell. Very convenient. Great recommendation, Thurman! They said it isn't possible for me to reserve space for us there but since it's a weeknight, the manager didn't think it would be a problem. If you can arrive between 6:00-6:15pm or so to get a drink and then we can walk over together.  I'll have blue balloons (even at the pub) so you can find us. Please bring snacks to share (if you feel like it) and something to drink at the park for yourself and definitely something to sit on. My cell phone # is 617-780-0429, in case you need it. I don't know about parking.  You can call the Sevens and ask what they recommend.  I plan to take the T - green line.  It's a 20min or so walk to the Sevens from Arlington Station but the Boyleston or Park street stops should work fine also.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sevens &lt;br /&gt;77 Charles St &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02114-4621 &lt;br /&gt;617-523-9074       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It should be relaxing and summery and the concert should be great. Gov. Deval Patrick is also supposed to be part of the events to do a Lincoln oration.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My cell (617-780-0429) &amp; w/blue balloons at  the Sevens &amp; the Hatch Shell.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan C</member_name><member_id>6899147</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215884519000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213044884000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hatch Shell - Copland Concert </name><id>8110736</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215640800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/8110736/</event_url></item>