<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 112 (the Kanc), at the "hairpin turn". Parking area is at the Hancock OVerlook which is just above the trailhead.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.038010</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hancock Notch Trailhead</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>282423</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.672508</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Hancock Notch Trail and the Hancock's.&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/e/0/event_3090688.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/5/2/7/event_3085895.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/5/0/event_3081328.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Hike the Hancock Notch Trail for a novice hike or tag North and South Hancock Mountains. Two more official winter 4000 ft summits for your list.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;This hike starts out on a flat, easy walk on the Hancock Notch, Cedar Brook, &amp;amp; Hancock Loop Trails to the base of the range, then a moderate climb for .7 mile up to the ridge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;There are spectacular views from both North &amp;amp; South peaks and along the Ridge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The Hancock Loop Trail is the only trail to Mount Hancock, a 4000-footer at the edge of the Pemigewasset Wilderness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/9/5/event_1274485.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;http://photos2.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;It starts with old woods roads to the loop junction, climbs steeply to the N or S peak depending on which fork you took, then follows a wandering path along the ridge to the other peak before descending back to the loop junction. The route up the N peak is rougher and steeper so we plan to go up that way and down the slightly-better route from the S peak.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Two moderate 4000 footers with astounding views to add to your accomplishments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;This round trip loop is 9.8 miles, 7.2 of which are relatively flat, only 2,650 feet of elevation gain, in 7.0 hours AMC booktime.  Slower hikers will add time for more breaks and a slower pace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Winter conditions are still in effect. Dress in synthetic layers and pack a change of clothing should your clothes get wet. Pack water and food for 9 hours. microspikes will be helpful for icy conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Where:Hancock Outlook, Lincoln , NH 03251&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Directions take I-93 Exit 32 at Lincoln and go E on NH Route 112 (Kancamagus Highway) about 11 miles to Hancock Notch Trail. There is a notable hairpin turn on the highway and the parking lot is right after the turn.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Second hike option: A second light hike group can be formed for a intermediate level hike of the beautiful Hancock Notch Trail.&lt;span style="text-align : center ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com/cgi-bin/findweather/getForecast?query=zmw:03251.1.99999&amp;amp;bannertypeclick=wu_clean2day" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://weathersticker.wunderground.com/weathersticker/cgi-bin/banner/ban/wxBanner?bannertype=wu_clean2day_cond&amp;amp;airportcode=K1P1&amp;amp;ForcedCity=Lincoln&amp;amp;ForcedState=NH&amp;amp;zip=03251&amp;amp;language=EN" alt="Find more about Weather in Lincoln, NH" width="300" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com/cgi-bin/findweather/getForecast?query=zmw:03251.1.99999&amp;amp;bannertypeclick=wu_clean2day" target="_blank" style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Click for weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This hike is suitable for dry or snowy conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;We can enjoy after hike festivities at the Common Man Restaurant pub in Lincoln NH. Super fireplace to warm up by!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Detailed itinerary:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;From the Cedar Brook Trail, the Hancock Loop Trail ascends at a gradual grade, soon crossing the North Fork yet again. Beyond the crossing it climbs R away from the brook, then runs parallel well above. At 1.1 miles, the loop junction is reached.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/9/7/event_1274487.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;http://photos4.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;To climb the main (N) peak first, turn L and angle down toward the brook which is crossed at 1.2 miles, a short distance upstream from the base of the Arrow Slide. This brook may be dry in summer. The trail now begins a steep climb of about a thousand feet in half a mile, over rocks and roots with loose gravel, before swinging L toward the summit. At 1.8 miles, a junction is reached at a small ledge outcrop considered the official summit.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;* A spur path L leads 50 yards to a ledge with a 180-degree outlook S from which almost no manmade structures can be seen, although this is the side of the peak away from the Pemigewasset Wilderness&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;The main trail continues ahead to the N nearly level for 50 yards, then swings E and SE, with little elevation loss. Finally it reaches the SE ridge and descends more steeply before reaching a flattish col. Next it climbs over a minor knoll, then passes near the summit of the middle peak at 2.8 miles. The trail now briefly follows near the Pemigewasset-Saco divide, descending quickly to a col and then climbing a narrow ridge to the summit of the S peak at 3.2 miles.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;* A spur path L leads 20 yards to an E outlook&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;* A herd path straight ahead leads to some unofficial camping spots&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;The main trail turns sharply R and descends steeply to the loop junction at 3.7 miles. Turn L to return to the Cedar Brook Trail and NH Route 112.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;[divider]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;You are responsible for yourself, so be prepared:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;1. With knowledge and gear. Become self reliant by learning about the terrain, conditions, local weather and your equipment before you start.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;2. To leave your plans. Tell someone where you are going, the trails you are hiking, when you will return and your emergency plans.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;3. To stay together. When you start as a group, hike as a group, end as a group. Pace your hike to the slowest person.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;4. To turn back. Weather changes quickly in the mountains. Fatigue and unexpected conditions can also affect your hike. Know your limitations and when to postpone your hike. The mountains will be there another day.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;5. For emergencies. Even if you are headed out for just an hour, an injury, severe weather or a wrong turn could become life threatening. Don’t assume you will be rescued; know how to rescue yourself&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;# Be knowledgeable of what to prepare for.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;# Contact the event organizer about any concerns and event challenges.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;# Every participant needs to come fully prepared.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;# Disclose any medical conditions before the event.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;# pack to survive the event and for "what if".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with our Disclaimer. Participation in an event is certifying that you are fit and able to accomplish an event. All hikers will hike at their own pace. By attending events, you and your guests agree to the terms above. Any unqualified participant can be denied participation in the group.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hike soon and hike safe!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the trailhead or suggested carpool:</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363038040000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361476613000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Hike  Cedar Brook Trail and the Hancocks</name><id>qvmmlfyrfbnb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1362918600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/106929782/</event_url></item>