<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;by Lou Ye&lt;/b&gt; (2006, 140 min.). Yu Hong leaves her family and lover behind in a country village to study in Beijing. At university, she discovers an intense world of sexual freedom and forbidden pleasure. Enraptured and compulsive, she falls madly in love with fellow student Zhou Wei. Obsessed by passions they can neither understand nor control, they begin to play dangerous games with betrayal, recrimination, and provocation, while all around them, their fellow students begin to demonstrate, demanding democracy and freedom. In Mandarin with English subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;From the New York Times Critics Pick Review:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Summer Palace,” which was first shown in competition at the &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;2006 Cannes Film Festival&lt;/span&gt;, is remarkable for its candor about politics and sex. &lt;b&gt;Perhaps unsurprisingly, its honesty has not been appreciated by Chinese authorities, who &lt;i&gt;banned Mr. Lou from making movies for five years&lt;/i&gt; after he brought it to Cannes without their permission.&lt;/b&gt; But the film’s ardent, unsentimental embrace of youthful idealism is likely to strike a chord with anyone who can recall — or imagine — such feelings overtaking his or her own life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In mapping the zone in which eros intersects with politics, Mr. Lou shows some affinity with Jia Zhang-ke, another frequently embattled Chinese director (whose new film, “Still Life,” also opens in New York today). “&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Summer Palace&lt;/span&gt;” can be seen as a companion piece, or even a sort of sequel, to Mr. Jia’s “&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Platform&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,”  which followed a group of Chinese young people through an earlier period of cultural and social transition, from the early 1970s into the 1980s. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Summer Palace&lt;/span&gt;” succeeds in finding a cinematic language that does more than summarize the important events of a confusing decade. He distills the inner confusion — the swirl of moods, whims and needs — that is the lived and living essence of history. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we'll dine and discuss at Pho and I, which was quite the palace, this summer, and will hopefully throw us a winter's bone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will gather the group out in the hallway at the close of credits.  Look for him to be holding aloft a Red Meetup sig</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293213697000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292260978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Films of Lou Ye - Summer Palace</name><id>15721107</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293141600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15721107/</event_url></item>