<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>840 Hillside Streen</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.209270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>Houghton's Pond Visitor Center</phone><name>Houghton's Pond Visitor Center</name><city>Milton</city><id>198319</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Blue Hills walk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will participate in a walk conducted by the Blue Hills Adult Walking Club, described as an easy 2 mile stroll around Houghton?s Pond and old Rte. 128. We may have to extend that walk a little to continue on until 12:45.  We will then head to the La Scala restaurant in nearby Randolf for Italian food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is also a holiday toy drive taking place that day, so bring a toy if you can. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10:45 at Houghton's Pond Visitor Center.  People needing a ride may be picked up at the Forest Hills subway station drop-off area at 10:15.&lt;br /&gt;By Car:&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 93 to Exit 3, Houghton's Pond. The exit from 93 puts you on Blue Hill River Rd which is ½ mile long and goes from the 93 to Hillside St. Turn right at the stop sign onto Hillside Street. Houghton's Pond is located approximately 1/4 miles on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Hills Adult Walking Club is a group of adults that meets on a weekly basis for recreational walks.  The purpose of these walks is social exercise.  There is no fee to join and everyone 16 or older is welcome.  Walks are normally 2 to 5 miles.&lt;br /&gt;Walks will be lead by a park ranger or a Walking Club volunteer leader.  Occasionally, the Walking Club meets at other DCR sites or car pools to sites within the Blue Hills Reservation.  The rangers recommend wearing hiking boots and bringing drinking water on all hikes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Holiday Toy Drive &amp;amp; Hike&lt;br /&gt;10 am ? 1 pm  Toy Drop    &lt;br /&gt;11 am   Hike&lt;br /&gt;Join Santa and friends for refreshments in the Houghton?s Pond Visitor Center at 10:00 am.  Then join an easy stroll at 11 am.  Please bring an unwrapped children?s gift as a contribution to Interfaith Social Services which helps families in need during the holidays.  Gifts for children ages 11 ? 16 are most needed and appreciated. Call 617-698-1802 x 310 for more information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located only minutes from the bustle of downtown Boston, the DCR Blue Hills Reservation stretches over 7,000 acres from Quincy to Dedham, Milton to Randolph, providing a green oasis in an urban environment. Rising above the horizon, Great Blue Hill reaches a height of 635 feet, the highest of the 22 hills in the Blue Hills chain. From the rocky summit visitors can see over the entire metropolitan area. With its scenic views, varied terrain and 125 miles of trails, the Blue Hills Reservation offers year-round enjoyment for the outdoor enthusiast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;La Scala Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1070 N Main St&lt;br /&gt;Randolph, MA 02368&lt;br /&gt;781.963.1700 &lt;br /&gt;Sun 1pm-10pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lascalarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lascalares...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165334841000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163723115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills walk, then italian food</name><id>5273304</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165161600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5273304/</event_url></item>