<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>My Personal Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>787702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Friends:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome BestMatchClub members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite a gentleman. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entry fee for this party is $25.00 and includes professionally catered food and one glass of wine. This is more than  a 50% discount as opposed to comparative services. If you want more wine then be proactive like several people did at the last party. They contributed a bottle of wine. I thought that was class and quality combined.( some wine was valued at $15.00 plus) These are the altruistic members I want to attract for you and me to meet. We will find them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our events are evolving to determine if I should offer two or three glasses of wine at a fee of $30.00. Or allow members to bring a bottle. I will get feedback after the next party. It will still be half the fee of comparative dating service offering food and wine at $70.00-$99.00. We will continue to offer the best value and quality. Comparative services offer no food or wine at $35-$45 presently.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notice the quality of people who attended the last party. I'm very happy. You will notice another higher level of quality will be achieved at this party. Nov. 6th.  Surprise! You will witness Continuous improvement. It is a process we will be engaged in daily. More improvements to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This party is for single individuals.(30-65) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mission is to have fun and meet other high integrity single people with common interests. Develop friendships and possibly find a lifetime partner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Values: Be positive, nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and respectful to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite other eligible single men.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***The entry fee is $25.00 &lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location is in a warm, loving, supportive and relaxing environment of my home. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dress code - &amp;quot; professional casual&amp;quot; Comfortable. &lt;br /&gt;First impressions are most meaningful. &lt;br /&gt;7:00PM - 10:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Sat. Nov. 6, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maximum attendees 60 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions &lt;br /&gt;My Home &lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road &lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128-Exit 16B/Route 109 toward Westwood&lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles  left on Pond Street- just past the middle school on left-if you go by Dunkin Donuts on right you missed it.&lt;br /&gt;Go I mile left on Oak St. (google search says go right-this is wrong)&lt;br /&gt;Go 1.5 miles to end-right on Brook St.&lt;br /&gt;100 feet take a  right on Woodridge Road&lt;br /&gt;My home is the 3rd house on the left-cream colored- number 36 Woodridge, Westwood, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on Saturday,  Nov. 6th at 7:00pm----&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7-8 eat and communicate with everyone&lt;br /&gt;8:01-8:10 Welcome speech by myself- sharing our mission/values and objectives &lt;br /&gt;8:11-- Everyone gives a 30 second presentation of who you are and who is your BestMatch. &lt;br /&gt;9:00- approximate communicate with anyone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facebook page is published-Search BestmatchClub or Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is right now! &lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS: Speed dating it coming soon- offering privacy and a touch of class!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289165112000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Curious Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dinner-parties</urlname><id>1245686</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Singles Dinner Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286914089000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Home Party</name><id>15087254</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289084400000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dinner-parties/events/15087254/</event_url></item>