<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366253</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-3721</phone><name>Pandemonium Books &amp; Games</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>875759</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105592</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Time and Temp:  A game of time travel and underemployment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Employed as a temp by Marigold Staffing and working at Browne Chronometric Engineering, Inc., you travel through the ages actualizing solutions for the anomalies and paradoxes that threaten all of existence.  You are reality's only line of defense in the war between the rigidity of causality and free will.  And your only reward is the hard earned satisfaction of a job well done (plus $11.50 an hour and a modest health package including comprehensive immunizations for history's most prolific diseases).  If you fail, all of reality unravels!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Join now and help make anachronism a thing of the past!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the February installment of our series of one-shot RPG experiences to be offered monthly over the course of 2011.  Each month will feature a different GM running a new game.  This month's GM is Tresi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Got a game on your shelf that you've been itching to run, but your regular group just isn't interested?  Why not run it for us at the Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston!  We want to continue running one-shot games throughout 2011, and you can help!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us> Look for the office folder with the yellow warning sticker: CAUTION Temporal Paradox Hazard.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tewhill</member_name><member_id>3431516</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298139525000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295231906000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February One-Shot - Time and Temp</name><id>16073855</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298134800000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/16073855/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/f/global_3081279.jpeg</photo_url></item>