<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parag Khanna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;explains&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to Run the World:&lt;br /&gt;Charting a Course to the Next Renaissance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, February 17, 2011&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM  Harvard Book Store&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: : :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is free; no tickets are required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: : :&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is very pleased to welcome scholar-adventurer PARAG KHANNA as he discusses his vision of future foreign relations, How to Run the World: Charting a Course to the Next Renaissance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to Run the World posits a chaotic modern era that resembles the Middle Ages, with Asian empires, Western militaries, Middle Eastern sheikhdoms, magnetic city-states, wealthy multinational corporations, elite clans, religious zealots, tribal hordes, and potent media seething in an ever more unpredictable and dangerous storm. But just as that initial “dark age” ended with the Renaissance, Khanna believes that our time can become a great and enlightened age as well—only, though, if we harness our technology and connectedness to forge new networks among governments, businesses, and civic interest groups to tackle the crises of today and avert those of tomorrow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Khanna reveals how a new “mega-diplomacy” consisting of coalitions among motivated technocrats, influential executives, super-philanthropists, cause-mopolitan activists, and everyday churchgoers can assemble the talent, pool the money, and deploy the resources to make the global economy fairer, rebuild failed states, combat terrorism, promote good governance, deliver food, water, health care, and education to those in need, and prevent environmental collapse. With examples taken from the smartest capital cities, most progressive boardrooms, and frontline NGOs, Khanna shows how mega-diplomacy is more than an ad hoc approach to running a world where no one is in charge—it is the playbook for creating a stable and self-correcting world for future generations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316505992000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294877811000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Run the World</name><id>16028656</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297987200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/16028656/</event_url></item>