<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Members of the Manchester Buddhism Sangha,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instead of our usual Monday evening meeting in January, I have scheduled a special Saturday get-together at the Millyard Museum in Manchester. This will give us a chance to meet people who are interested in Buddhism, and also an opportunity to learn about different Buddhist organizations in the area. The atmosphere will be informal and friendly. The fee will be $10, and will include a light lunch (vegetarian pizza and salad) and admission to the museum for the day (open 10 a.m.-4 p.m.). Pre-registration is required. Payment may be made at the event. This program should last until around 1 p.m.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will give us a chance to share information about Buddhist resources in the area. I will speak briefly about the Phuoc Dien Temple in Manchester, for example, and other members of the temple are also planning to be present to share information. Please let me know if you would like to let people know about your Buddhist sangha. temple, book group, study group, meditation group, etc. at this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our regular meeting schedule will resume in February, on the second Monday of each month, at Barnes &amp;amp; Nobles in Manchester, at 7 p.m. in the cafe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For details on the Millyard Museum, please visit the website:  www.manchesterhistoric.org. Parking is free in the parking lot next to the building. I happen to work there, so please don't hesitate to let me know of your questions or concerns. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you for being a member of the Manchester Buddhism Sangha. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aurore Eaton&lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;Manchester Buddhism Sangha&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a name tag.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265674097000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257793230000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Manchester Buddhism Sangha Get-Together</name><id>11833821</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263655800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/11833821/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/5/global_1946069.jpeg</photo_url></item>