<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;THE WEATHER IS LOOKING REAL NICE FOR SATURDAY !&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KIJD&amp;amp;state=CT"&gt;http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KIJD&amp;amp;state=CT&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;A Weekend of Friendship at the Lake, Our Traditional Barbeque, &amp;nbsp;assorted activities; hiking, kayaking, lounging around the lake or campfire -- &amp;nbsp;and use of the clubs&amp;nbsp;boats.&amp;nbsp; *kayaks, rowboats, paddleboats, canoes*.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;$11/pp for day picnic,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp;details are below (limited to 25 people)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at this &amp;nbsp;private club with campsites and a pristine lake&amp;nbsp;in a wooded area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;(You can bring your own kayak, canoe,&amp;nbsp;but, due to insurance reasons must use the state launch area.)&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BARBARA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;is HOSTING THIS EVENT.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;please contact her for&amp;nbsp;questions @&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="mailto:bg3step@comcast.net" style="color : #3b74a4"&gt;bg3step@comcast.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;WEATHER: i will add this before the event weekend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please reserve your spot now (SOONER IS BETTER) -- last year&amp;nbsp;the last minute people complained because they were left out.&amp;nbsp; There is a 25 person limit for the day people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Facility:&lt;/strong&gt; Yale Univ. Outdoor Center, East Lyme&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Private pristine lake and picnic area, Nestled on mile long Powers Lake, surrounded by 1500 wooded acres.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Yale Outdoor Education Ctr
 &lt;br /&gt;298 Upper Pattagansett Rd
 &lt;br /&gt;East Lyme, CT 06333&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/4/1/event_21978241.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This SATURDAY ONLY POT LUCK PARTY FEE will cover your entrance to the facility , paper goods, charcoal, some beverages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah bring some pot luck things, most of our stuff will have been at the campsite overnight but preserved in ice..etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OTHER AMMENITIES: Picnic Pavillion, Rowboats, canoes, kayaks. (life jackets are available and must be worn). Blazed hiking trails around a wildlife marsh, pond, clay volleyball court, horse-shoe pit, small basketball court, field office, and recreation cabin with ping pong. A spring water dispenser is located in the Pavilion. Poop Houses, and picanick tables are nearby&amp;nbsp;our site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you care to bring your own yak, then you will need to put in on the state boat ramp (located around the block); Directions: out of the facility, bear sharply right, follow road for about 1-2 miles, boat launch is on the right&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2686&amp;amp;q=384254&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1620" style="color : #3b74a4"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2686&amp;amp;q=384254&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1620&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for insurance reasons Yale can&amp;rsquo;t allow you to put in on their property. The advantage of bringing your own is that you can go for a sunset or moonlight kayak trip and you will not be limited to Yale rules (IE must be in site for life guards; time restraints, and whatever else).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Please send a check for $11.00 per person made out to: Barbara&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Please (include a note with your name, phone and email in case there is some problem and indicate (SATURDAY PARTY ONLY):
   &lt;br /&gt; Mail to:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;YALE MEETUP OUTING
   &lt;br /&gt; c/o B.G.
   &lt;br /&gt; 3 STEPHANIE CT
   &lt;br /&gt; MADISON CT 06443-8112
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;THE SATURDAY GROUP PARTY by the lakeside:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Saturday we will have our Traditional "Pot Luck Lakeside Barbie-Q" so please bring either a desert, side dish to share, some good meat..etc.. (about 8 serving size worth for an idea)..&lt;/strong&gt; Remember to bring a chair or blanket and the usual summer relaxing necessities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Al and Barbara will bring their gas grills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will supply the additional charcoal for the real smoky meat flaviour, paper goods, ice, water and some soft drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(i still have charcoal from 3 years ago, lets use that stuff up too, else i chuck it in our campfire)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;BEHAVIOR:&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;This is a private club reserved and organized by a member who works at Yale, so please be courteous and responsible as this is where she works! Drink responsibly and please keep your space clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;SINCE THIS HAS TO BE A PRE-PAID AND PRE-RESERVED EVENT/FACILITY IF SOMEHOW ITS RAINING and ya already paid, WE WILL STILL PARTY USING THE INSIDE/COVERED FACILITIES.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Hopefully mother nature will cooperate as she did last year!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;So far Saturday is looking OK based on the current prediction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;PLEASE OBTAIN A GPS: I ADD THESE DIRECTIONS AS A CURTISY AND backup data so ITS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO STUDY YOUR &amp;nbsp;MAP BEFORE HEADING OUT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : 18px"&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-County-Rivers-To-Shore-Area-Kayakers-CT/venue/977702/?popup=true" style="color : #3b74a4 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Yale Outdoor Education Ctr&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : 14px"&gt;298 Upper Pattagansett Rd East Lyme, CT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : 14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From I-95 North:
 &lt;br /&gt;to Exit 71 (Four Mile River Rd -- East Lyme), turn right off exit ramp and continue 1-1/2 miles to end of the road. Turn right onto Route 1, continue another 1-1/2 miles, turn left onto Scott Road. (right past the SCOTT&amp;rsquo;s FARM MARKET) Continue straight two miles to front entrance (directly across the road) This is the intersection of Scott road and Pattagansett Road. Enter property and follow dirt road (which bears to the left) by a Hall then go APX A HALF MILE TO THE GATE KEEPER-If you are on the list, then you can come in, if not, well, then you didn't pay up or no special arrangements were made with Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Driving Directions: From HARTFORD:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Yes it kind of confusing..&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take I-84 East apx 0.5 miles to (exit # 55) rte 2 East toward Norwich.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow rte 2 for 24 miles to rte 11 (exit # 19).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take rte 11 for 7.5 miles to (exit # 4) for rte 82.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a right (toward Hadlyme) onto rte 82 THEN TAKE AN IMMEDIATE LEFT onto DARLING Rd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow Darling Rd to its end apx 1 mile Take a Left onto GUNGY rd follow for apx 2.8 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a left at Beaver Brook rd go apx 1 mile and continue strait on Whistletown Rd for 2.1 miles to the intersection of Pattagansett and Scott rd,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE ENTRANCE TO YALE NATURE CENTER IS OPPOSITE SCOTT RD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter property and follow dirt road (which bears to the left) by a Hall then go APX A HALF MILE TO THE GATE KEEPER- If you are on the list, then you can come in, if not, well, then you didn't pay up or no special arrangements were made with Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;look for my Orange 6 foot pole by our BARBIE-Q area when i get there or look for the group since we are a fairly good sized group and look at our pics to make out some of us if you are new..etc...&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;MORE DETAILS WILL BE ADDED LATER if necessary !&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;See you there if you are going.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;AL-R&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>LOOK FOR for other group members, When i arrive after my obligation, i will bring the orange 6 foot pole to find us !</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara</member_name><member_id>5197547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310294558000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>THIS OPTION IS FOR THOSE NOT INTERESTED IN CAMPING BUT TO JOIN US FOR THE SATURDAY PARTY ONLY</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300058922000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>JULY  9 ** LAKESIDE  POT LUCK   PARTY**  @ Powers Lake ( NON Campers listing)</name><id>16908632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310230800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/16908632/</event_url></item>