<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Intersection of Birch Mtn. and Camp Meeting Roads</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.764977</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-643-9776 (Susan B.)</phone><name>Case Mtn --Birch Mtn. Road parking lot</name><city>Manchester</city><id>717878</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.456192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Free after-work Case Mountain Hike at 5:45 p.m. Includes commentary on the history of Highland Park, as well as flora and fauna of Case Mountain. Meet at the Birch Mountain Road trailhead. This approach to the summit of Case Mountain is less steep than others, and we will hike at a moderate pace, but we will nevertheless encounter hills and uneven terrain. Hikers should be fit and wear sturdy shoes, sneakers, or boots. Depending on the weather, we will view the Hartford skyline from the summit. We will walk for about 1-3/4 hours, and view property owned by the Town of Manchester and by the Manchester Land Conservation Trust. Hike starts at parking lot on Birch Mountain Road, close to intersection with Camp Meeting Road, Manchester. From Hartford, take exit 4 off I-384, left off exit ramp, right at traffic light (big grocery store across intersection) onto Highland Street (quickly renamed Camp Meeting Road). Go one-half mile, take right onto Birch Mountain Road. The parking lot is a few feet from the intersection, on the right. Extreme weather cancels.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jeans, red hiking shoes, blue backpack</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan B</member_name><member_id>7644854</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243795265000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242576593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>After work/After school Hike </name><id>10430735</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243028700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10430735/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/4/1/global_8663185.jpeg</photo_url></item>