<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Pleasant St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02367</zip><lat>41.939486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-526-2200</phone><name>Shanti Shala Yoga &amp; Wellness Center</name><city>Plympton</city><id>1084839</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.802394</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/3/8/event_98646712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sat Nam,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come nourish your soul with Kundalini Yoga.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"TheYoga of Awareness"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class is suitable for all. Beginners need not worry: the focus is more on breathing and meditation than on difficult postures. In every posture you have a chance to experience devotion, that's what postures are really all about. Embrace the spirit in you and marvel at the beautiful engineering of your own body. &lt;br /&gt;

 So come and enjoy the results of a Kundalini Yoga Class. &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Classes are 60 minutes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Kundalini Yoga?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kundalini yoga is an ancient science or technology to awaken awareness, it utilizes breathing, mantra (sound and rhythm), mudra (hand postures), asanas (postures) and the beaming power of the mind. All this aids you, the practitioner, to live virtually in harmony with the inner self, the higher self. &lt;br /&gt;

 “Yoga is the union of the individual’s unit consciousness.” ~Yogi Bhajan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kundalini yoga is also a tool to achieve self mastery, and one of the oldest forms of human development. All yoga sets are designed to work on specific body systems, such as the muscular, skeletal, cardiovascular, glandular or reproductive system. Additionally, each set helps to balance emotional as well as mental patterns, and works towards greater awareness and well being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you can expect!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strengthens the body &amp;amp; Calms the mind&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Releases fear &amp;amp; limiting patterns&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enhanced intuition &amp;amp; Emotional balance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sense of well being&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beauty &amp;amp; Strength&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heightened sensory awareness &amp;amp; spiritual sense&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Increased vitality &amp;amp; energy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Kundalini training was at Kundalini Research Institute in Espanola NM. &lt;br /&gt;

 This is where we learned the fundamental principles and practices of Kundalini Yoga as taught by Yogi Bhajan. By completing this stage makes me a certified instructor of Kundalini Yoga. www.kriteachings.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;What Happens During a Yoga Session&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 1. Tuning in with the Adi Mantra while sitting in a crossed-legged position and hands in prayer pose. You chant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ong Namo Guru Dev Namo (3x)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Sanskirt chant means, I bow to the infinite Wisdom of the Universe; I call upon you. I bow to the divine Wisdom within; I call upon you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Warm up exercises a series of exercises or postures to warm up the spine and loosen the body in preparation of performing a Kriya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.Kriya a series of postures (asanas in Sanskirt) with intended results, the purpose of which is to transform your state of consciousness. Different breathing techniques are used to benefit the entire body .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.Relaxation/Meditation There are sometimes opportunities for relaxation between postures providing awareness of the body, sensations, emotions and thoughts. Relaxation is as important as the postures. An extended relaxation and or meditation is done at the end of the kriya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.Class ends with a song - Long Time Sun Song&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May the long time sun shine upon you,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;all love surround you,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and the pure light within you,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;guide your way on...(repeated twice) So come enjoy an evening of yoga. Kundalina Yoga&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Are Beautiful, &lt;br /&gt;

 Darnell / Arjan Deva Kaur&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow the walkway in the back of the house into the studio.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darnell</member_name><member_id>10396246</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1371393447000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightenment Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ShantiShala</urlname><id>1534948</id><group_lat>41.9599990845</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8099975586</group_lon><name>Shanti Shala Yoga &amp; Wellness Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367413411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kundalini Yoga with Darnell</name><id>qsjlwfyrjbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>3600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1371389400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ShantiShala/events/117129982/</event_url></item>