<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>Mass. Ave. &amp; Church St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374420</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Church Meetinghouse</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>274946</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118858</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Cambridge Forum is pleased to welcome LESTER BROWN to discuss his new book &amp;quot;Plan B 3.0: Mobilizing to Save Civilization&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this updated edition of the landmark Plan B, Lester Brown outlines a survival strategy for our early twenty-first-century civilization. The world faces many environmental trends of disruption and decline, including rising temperatures and spreading water shortage. In addition to these looming threats, we face the peaking of oil, annual population growth of 70 million, a widening global economic divide, and a growing list of failing states. The scale and complexity of issues facing our fast-forward world have no precedent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Plan A, business as usual, we have neglected these issues overly long. In Plan B 3.0, Lester R. Brown warns that the only effective response now is a World War II-type mobilization like that in the United States after the attack on Pearl Harbor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lester R. Brown, president of the Earth Policy Institute, is one of the world's most widely published authors, with books in more than forty languages. A MacArthur Fellow, he lives in Washington, DC.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215313905000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202420988000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mobilizing to Save Civilization (?-S.)</name><id>7285919</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203726600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/7285919/</event_url></item>