<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a lovely and interesting 974 acre preserve with water, bridge, cliffs, abandoned railroad tunnel, and a peak surrounded on 3 sides by the Shepaug River (not much view from peak but there is at other points). This hike is about 6 miles in length and moderate in effort due to some steepness and length.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/f/c/event_106838652.jpeg" width="219" height="120" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We will ascend at first and follow the hill above the western side of the Shepaug River in a southerly direction on the Steep Rock Loop trail. We will see a great vantage at the Steep Rock overlook then continue on the loop and descend to cross the river on a suspended trail bridge. From here we break from the Steep Rock loop trail and make a clockwise loop on The Clam Shell feature that is surrounded on three sides by the river. Then we follow a ridge to the south and loop around and get on the abandoned railway and go through the rail tunnel (you may want headlamps/flashlights but not needed). We continue to follow the railway on the east back of the river and heading north until the railway intersects with the Tunnel Road. We roadwalk Tunnel Road the rest of the way back to the parking area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will take up to 4.5 hrs. for this hike as we take deep appreciation for the views from the cliffs, features, and riverside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to go need to have: &lt;br /&gt;

 * A daypack &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1-2 quarts of water &lt;br /&gt;

 * Trail food/lunch &lt;br /&gt;

 * Hiking boots &lt;br /&gt;

 * Dress in layers - So you can take off as you heat up, no cotton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional equipment: &lt;br /&gt;

 * Camera &lt;br /&gt;

 * Hiking pole(s) &lt;br /&gt;

 * &lt;span&gt;Headlamp or flashlight - For railroad tunnel&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Rain shell/jacket/poncho&lt;/span&gt; - Just in case&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking is a dirt/gravel lot with a fair amount of parking. Parking earlier is better for getting a spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs on leash are allowed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; parking area at entrance (Intersection of Lower Church Hill Rd. &amp;amp; River Rd. and just over the river on Tunnel Rd., Washington, CT). &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Be careful, as last I checked there is a road washout (Spring Hill Rd.) near the preserve that may necessitate rerouting your directions to the hiking location so bring a map or be ready to reprogram your GPS&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://mapq.st/H7D5XJ"&gt;http://mapq.st/H7D5XJ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 [Latitude 41.621514, Longitude -73.325007]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking Map&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://steeprockassoc.org/pdf/map_steep_rock.pdf"&gt;http://steeprockassoc.org/pdf/map_steep_rock.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steep Rock Reservation&lt;/strong&gt; - More information &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.trailsoffreedom.com/ct_hike/steep-rock-preserve"&gt;http://www.trailsoffreedom.com/ct_hike/steep-rock-preserve&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://steeprockassoc.org/preserves/steep-rock-reservation/"&gt;http://steeprockassoc.org/preserves/steep-rock-reservation/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steep Rock Association, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; - Preserving this land &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://steeprockassoc.org/"&gt;http://steeprockassoc.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose. I further attest that I, the registrant, am fully and completely responsible for any guests that I bring to the event, whether registered or not.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Ford Escape SUV, CT plates, meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352138120000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350955909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Steep Rock Preserve in Washington CT</name><id>88151262</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352041200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/88151262/</event_url></item>