<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Fat Tuesday has long past but you have yet another chance this Friday March 12th....when the Carnival spirit takes over Ryles with the lively powerful sound of Bloco AfroBrazil.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who haven't been able to make the Sunday shows, now you have a chance to experience the baddest, loudest, funnest indoor carnival around. Last year, each time this group partied, I placed it on the &lt;a href="http://portuguese.meetup.com/316/calendar/12835950/"&gt;Portuguese &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/BostonOnyxbirds/calendar/12835540"&gt;Onyxbirds&lt;/a&gt; Meetup calendars because it always exceeded expectation. Since dinner is an option this time, I've also invited the Meetup dining group, &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/calendar/12835948"&gt;Breakfast Brunch Lunch &amp;amp; Dinner&lt;/a&gt; as well. Let's pack the place because the more the merrier and also your presence will convince Ryles to keep the party on their schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil is a 12-piece percussion ensemble that always puts on a spectacular show combining traditional Brazilian grooves like Samba and Axé with Funk, Rock, Jazz and even Hip Hop; add to this, Ju Marciano's explosive mix of sultry vocals as well as beautiful dancers and you got a recipe for FUN, Brazilian style!! Bring your dance shoes or socks and leave your worries at the door!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your friends....I guarantee a funtastic time, that is if you like your music strong and your party loud. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get there when you can. Don't be shy...Say hi, to the friendly folks seated in the dining area at the tables against the wall, to the right of the stage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rylesjazz.com/dining.cfm"&gt;Ryles Dinner Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You must be at least 21&lt;/b&gt; but you don't have to drink, just enjoy each others company and an AMAZING! show.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn Samba and Brazilian Afro Dance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once the drumming, singing and dancing start, group conversation is difficult. Let's just enjoy the party!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;$10 cash cover charge at the door&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;$12.50 online with credit card at &lt;a href="http://ryles.interticket.com/arrivalorder.php?eid=1943&amp;amp;aid=4&amp;amp;vid=4"&gt;http://ryles.intertic...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.afrobrazil.org/index.php?CLm=10&amp;amp;CLd=11&amp;amp;CLy=2009&amp;amp;c_num=AB"&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil details&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points West:&lt;br /&gt;Take I-90 (Mass Pike) to Exit 18 bearing right toward Allston/Cambridge. At the end of the exit pass through two sets of lights traveling over the Charles River, continue straight onto River Street.&lt;br /&gt;Take River Street through Central Square crossing Over Massachusetts Avenue where River Street turns into Prospect Street.&lt;br /&gt;At Fourth traffic light (Hess Gas Station) take LEFT onto Hampshire Street.&lt;br /&gt;Ryles Jazz Club is located at 212 Hampshire Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points South:&lt;br /&gt;Follow 93 North into Downtown Boston.&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 26, Storrow Drive.&lt;br /&gt;At the bottom of the Exit proceed onto Storrow Drive.• Bear LEFT on Storrow&lt;br /&gt;Drive and take the first LEFT hand exit (Kendall Sq.).&lt;br /&gt;Bear RIGHT on the exit ramp following the signs for Kendall Square Cambridge, 3N.&lt;br /&gt;Pass over the Longfellow Bridge and continue straight onto Main Street.&lt;br /&gt;Follow Main Street straight onto Broadway (The Marriott Hotel will be on your left).&lt;br /&gt;At the Fourth set of lights take a RIGHT onto Hampshire Street.&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Hampshire Street for 0.6 miles.&lt;br /&gt;Ryles Jazz Club is located on 212 Hampshire Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points North:&lt;br /&gt;Follow 93 North into Downtown Boston.&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the exit ramp at the light, take a LEFT following the signs to the&lt;br /&gt;Museum of Science. Take the first RIGHT following Route 28 North (The Museum of Science will be on the left).&lt;br /&gt;Proceed past two sets of lights, at the third light bear LEFT onto Cambridge Street.&lt;br /&gt;Continue approximately 1.1 miles on Cambridge street, take LEFT onto Prospect Street.&lt;br /&gt;Take first RIGHT onto Hampshire Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;1) Free in the two S&amp;amp;S Restaurant lots on Hampshire Street &lt;br /&gt;2) Free behind the 7-11 (store) on Hampshire Street across from Hess Gas Station on Hampshire Street near Prospect Street&lt;br /&gt;3) Municipal lot on Springfield Street off of Cambridge Street behind 1369 Coffee House at 1369 Cambridge Street and Ole Mexican Grill at 11 Springfield Street &lt;u&gt;meter parking in effect 6pm til 10pm at $2/hour max 4 hours buy ticket from machine in lot then place in window&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) Hampshire Street, Beacon Street and Cambridge Street parking &lt;i&gt;READ SIGNS TO AVOID HAVING YOUR VEHICLE TICKETED AND/OR TOWED&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) Last resort Cambridge Hospital garage $7 for 3 hrs $8 for 4 hrs $10 for 5 hrs $13 for 6 hrs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.sandsrestaurant.com/images/map.gif" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Create your route at &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;http://mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;http://www.hopstop.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 69, 83 and 91 buses also run through (or near) Inman Square&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Seated in the dining area at the tables against the wall to the right of the stage.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272924840000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267803481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brazilian Happy Hour Party at Ryles Friday March 12th at 9PM</name><id>12792156</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268445600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/12792156/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/5/global_13469045.jpeg</photo_url></item>