<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Be sure to read the entire event listing before you RSVP - then answer the questions that are part of the RSVP process. While the objective of this event is to enjoy ourselves, your safety, and the safety of the others, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands, overestimate your skills and abilities, or come unprepared you may put yourself and/or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this&amp;nbsp;before&amp;nbsp;you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We are going to visit one of the NH 48 - Garfield (#17 @ 4,500').&amp;nbsp;A trip to Garfield&amp;rsquo;s rocky summit rewards hikers with some of the most impressive panoramic views of the surrounding Franconia Ridge and&amp;nbsp;Pemigewasset Wilderness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This trip is part of the 5th Annual Paddle &amp;amp; Plod - visit our calendar to get a description of other events.&amp;nbsp;Sorry for the early start time but Monica and I have to drive to Maine to host the rafting portion of the Paddle and Plod after we finish the hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, or other situations and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Well-behaved dogs that routinely climb mountains like this one are OK for this hike. Please bring a leash in case you need to use it and a copy of the most recent rabies vaccination.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt; round trip we will use the Garfield Ridge Trail to reach the summit and then we&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;will follow the same route in reverse to return to the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about 10.1 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,200 feet&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;em&gt;for perspective the top floor of the Empire State Building is about 1,250 feet&lt;/em&gt;). &amp;nbsp;Without including time for breaks it should take an average hiker about &lt;strong&gt;7 hours 54 minutes to complete&lt;/strong&gt; this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/photos/2030971/"&gt;Click here for information about&amp;nbsp;our trip ratings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While I have climbed these mountains before I did all of my current research for this trip using the AMC's&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;White Mountain Guide&lt;/em&gt;, a trail map, and the Internet. You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6907"&gt;Click here for information about&amp;nbsp;Garfield (peakbagger.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/?ll=44.187,-71.612&amp;amp;z=13&amp;amp;type=Terrain&amp;amp;label=Garfield"&gt;Click here for information about current trail conditions&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/?ll=44.187,-71.612&amp;amp;z=13&amp;amp;type=Terrain&amp;amp;label=Garfield"&gt;(TrailsNH.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it&amp;nbsp;prior&amp;nbsp;to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Footwear&lt;/span&gt;: Sturdy hiking boots or trail shoes - no sneakers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Clothing&lt;/span&gt;: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater (even in summer). ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when dry it doesn't dry easily and is a great conductor when wet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Outerwear&lt;/span&gt;: Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip. We will be able to resupply our water at the AMC's Lonesome Lake Hut.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Optional Items&lt;/span&gt;: Waterproof/windproof pants. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will begin this hike by meeting in the Garfield Ridge Trail parking area at 7:00 AM. You will need to use North Gale River Road (FR 25) to access the trailhead since South Gale River Road is closed for bridge repairs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 149 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 33 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.228952,-71.633192(Garfield+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.228952,-71.633192&amp;amp;sspn=0.008641,0.018239&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFVjhogId2Pa6-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;Click here for driving directions to the meeting spot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A white or green Toyota Highlander with a Meetup sign in the window.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310413798000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309137233000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Garfield (INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED)</name><id>23620111</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310036400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/23620111/</event_url></item>