<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>274 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371369</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center for Digital Imaging Arts at Boston University</name><city>Waltham</city><id>723446</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236903</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>59.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Bruce and Josh Hudson
Saturday, April 30, 8:30 am&amp;ndash;4:30 pm
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.cipne.org/CC_Postcard/assets/BH_2.jpg" width="220" height="178" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;21 Effective Marketing Strategies for Success in an Economy that Sucks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dynamic father and son team of Bruce and Josh Hudson will give you  the detailed marketing strategies you&amp;rsquo;ve been craving in your business  and a much needed energy boost! During their jam-packed all day  presentation they will be discussing 21 effective ways you can market  your studio and thrive during these challenging times. Here is just a  small handful of what they will be covering: #3- The social media mania  and how to actually make money from it, #7- The lost art of custom thank  you notes as a marketing and referral building tool, #10- Orchestrating  a charity auction program that is a new client generating machine, #13-  Maximizing and optimizing your website so you get Googled more often,  #16- Writing effective marketing and sales copy for your ads, #20-  Implementing an ongoing &amp;ldquo;Portrait Safari&amp;rdquo; marketing campaign. Plus  fifteen more strategies! Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this content rich, no fluff program  created by 27 year veteran Bruce Hudson and one of the most brilliant up  in coming marketing minds in the industry Josh Hudson. Their business  consulting has gained rave reviews, including that of Steve Sheanin, CEO  &amp;amp; Editor Rangefinder Magazine, Founder &amp;amp; CEO WPPI; &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve had  the privilege of knowing Bruce from the beginning of his career 27 years  ago. His studio has always thrived because he is able to evolve and  adapt as the market changes. Studying with Bruce and his son Josh will  drastically improve your business and your life&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://hudsonportraits.com/"&gt;Bruce Hudson&lt;/a&gt; holds a Mastercraftsman degree from the Professional Photographers of  America and is one of only 40 active members in the prestigious  organization Camera Craftsmen of America. A much sought-after speaker to  professional photography organizations, Bruce has lectured on behalf of  Fuji Film USA, H&amp;amp;H Color Lab, Mamiya Cameras, Capri Albums,  Marathon Press, and Excel Frames throughout the United States, New  Zealand, Canada, and Puerto Rico. Over the years he has produced and  authored over 25 instructional video/DVD programs dealing with portrait,  wedding photography and marketing. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe he has  photographed more than a thousand weddings and tens of thousands of  family, children, and high school senior portraits since 1982. He&amp;#65533;s also  had in front of his lens, President Bush (41), future Hall of Fame  pitching great Randy Johnson, and night time radio celebrity Delilah and  her family. Bruce has not only been named a Master Photographer, but  also referred to as a Master Marketer that specializes in Relationship  Marketing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mystudiomentor.com/"&gt;Josh Hudson&lt;/a&gt; has a unique perspective and insight that makes him a valuable asset to  Hudson&amp;rsquo;s Portrait Design. He is currently in charge of some of the  day-to-day operations, client relations, and all of the studio  marketing. As an educator, Josh helped plan and manage his father Bruce  Hudson&amp;#65533;s 50 city lecture tour in 2007, where also had a speaking role  dealing with internet and email marketing. Since then, he has produced  dozens webinars, DVDs, and has spoke to countless local, regional,  national and even international organizations on behalf of H&amp;amp;H Color  Lab, Marathon Press, American Retail Supply, Brown Book It, and  Brucetunz.com. He is considered to be one of the top emerging experts in  social media, internet, and email marketing, as well as helping studios  integrate efficient client follow-up techniques and business management  concepts. As co-founder of MyStudioMentor.com, Josh helps photographers  on a daily basis navigate the trials and tribulations of being a  professional photographer in today&amp;rsquo;s ultra competitive market place. He  was also named host of a new internet TV show called MyMarketingClicks,  which is designed to help photographers make more money with their  craft.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=embed&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=274+Moody+Street,+waltham+ma&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=62.314887,96.855469&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=274+Moody+St,+Waltham,+Middlesex,+Massachusetts+02453&amp;amp;ll=42.371544,-71.236897&amp;amp;spn=0.010146,0.013819&amp;amp;z=14&amp;amp;iwloc=A" style="color : #0000ff ; text-align : left"&gt;View Larger Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LOCATION &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.cdiabu.com/directions.php"&gt;Center for Digital Imaging Arts&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 274 Moody Street &lt;br /&gt; Waltham, MA 02453&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PROGRAM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday, April 29&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Image Competition; 10:00am&amp;ndash;4:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, April 30&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Registration; 9:00&amp;ndash;9:30am &lt;br /&gt; Program; 9:30am&amp;ndash;12:30pm &lt;br /&gt; Lunch break; 12:30&amp;ndash;1:30pm &lt;br /&gt; Program; 1:30pm&amp;ndash;4:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; CIPNE Members, Free; Non-members; $59 ($39 in advance online), Full-time students, $20.&lt;/p&gt;
Pre-registration is required for this program.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://events.constantcontact.com/register/event?llr=4zkrpubab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e3j4fheka7cb559d"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click here to register&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (Non-members may pay by PayPal) &lt;br /&gt; Please note: on-line registration closes April 28th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304373162000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>50th CIPNE Annual Conference
Marketing’s Past, Present, and Future —
21 Effective Marketing Strategies for Success in an Economy that Sucks!</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302813930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bruce and Josh Hudson- Professional Portrait Photographers give all day Seminar!</name><id>17307911</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304209800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/17307911/</event_url></item>