<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Lowell MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.650000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMASS LOWEL</name><city>Lowell</city><id>609723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340000</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>75.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, June 28, 2008, marks our ninth annual Grassroots Use of Technology co&lt;/b&gt;nference!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Registration is Open&lt;br /&gt;This year's event will be held at UMASS Lowell and is just $75 ($35 limited income) which includes coffee and a morning snack, lunch and afternoon refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://organizerscollaborative.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://organizerscoll...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration link: &lt;a href="http://organizers-collaborative.camp7.org/Default.aspx?pageId=134323" target="_blank"&gt;http://organizers-col...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://organizerscollaborative.org/files/ocregistrationfom_08.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://organizerscoll...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can register on-line with a credit card through Wild Apricot.&lt;br /&gt;Or if you would like to register by check, PLEASE CLICK HERE to use the printable form.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connect, Communicate, Collaborate&lt;br /&gt;This year's theme is &amp;quot;Connect, Communicate, and Collaborate&amp;quot;; it focuses on the new technologies and organizing tools available for connecting organizers and their communities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nick Jehlen will be joining us this year with a keynote address speaking to his work on Iraq Veterans Against the War's Winter Soldier campaign. At a time when the nation wrestles with questions about the war and while grassroots activists and advocates experiment with ways to influence the big ticket issues of the day, IVAW, with Nick's help, boldly stepped out off the beaten path to bring together hundreds of veterans to address the occupations abroad and the neglect at home. Nick's talk will show how they made careful and appropriate use of a wide range of communications technologies and tools.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be three workshop sessions, and each session will have 5 or 6 concurrent presentations. Workshops will be identified by technical level; the program is designed to be accessible to beginners while offering options for tech experts.&amp;#8232;&amp;#8232;We are still working on the final schedule, but here are just a few of the workshops you can expect to see this year:&amp;#8232;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On-Line Polls and e-Campaigning in Resource-Poor Communities&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keeping it Simple: technology tools that won't make you want to rip your hair out&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking your website to the next level with free online tools&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Strategies for shaping the media/tech future&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building a News Portal with Drupal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Untapped Power of Social Networks for Grassroots Action&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facebook to Phone Trees: Multi-Generational Outreach Strategies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Managing &amp;amp; Recruiting Tech volunteers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helping Your Computer System Grow Up&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Voter Databases&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?..And More!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need overnight accommodations, UMASS Lowell has dorms available at reasonable rates; $50 per person for a single room and $34 per person for a shared room. Rooms can be reserved when you register for the conference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, the Grassroots Use of Technology conference is one of the only events that brings technology and endusers together, allowing us to learn from each other.&lt;br /&gt;Don't wait, register today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you on June 28!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Highlights of the day:&lt;br /&gt;Keynote Speaker,  Nick Jehlen of Action Mil  draw lessons from his recent work on the Winter Soldier campaign organized by  Iraq Veterans Against the War.  &lt;br /&gt;Non-profit Internet Starter  Kit: Take Your Website to the Next Level with These Free Online Tools  &lt;br /&gt;Online  Mentoring: Innovative Uses of Technology in Creating and Managing  Mentor-Mentee Relationships  &lt;br /&gt;You Can't Get What You Want Until You Know What  You Need: Choosing the Right Software  &lt;br /&gt;Making the Most Out of the Organizers' Database   &lt;br /&gt;The Untapped Power of Social Networks for  Grassroots Action  &lt;br /&gt;Getting the Clicks: e-Campaigning  in Communities with Few  Computers   &lt;br /&gt; Managing Your Website with Today's  Tools   &lt;br /&gt;Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  Roadmap   &lt;br /&gt;HAVA Great Idea? (HAVA stands for Help America  Vote Act)  &lt;br /&gt;Facebook to Phone Trees: Multi-Generational  Outreach Strategies  &lt;br /&gt;Organizing the Organic Internet  &lt;br /&gt;Helping Your Computer System Grow Up   &lt;br /&gt;Keeping it Simple: technology tools that won't  make you want to rip your hair out.  &lt;br /&gt;Collaborative eLearning   &lt;br /&gt;The Point: A Web-Tool for Collective Action  &lt;br /&gt; Managing &amp;amp; Recruiting Tech  volunteers  &lt;br /&gt;Strategies for shaping the media/tech future:  Policy, funding &amp;amp; organizing   &lt;br /&gt;Open Media Boston: Building a News Portal with  Drupal&lt;br /&gt;Lowell is a beautiful, historic city that still remembers its working-class roots The intersection of rivers and canals make it a wonderful place to be on an early summer day.  So join us for some engaging connections and some rock-solid knowledge sharing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214831151000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210773089000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Grassroots Use of Technology conference!</name><id>7936107</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214658000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7936107/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>