<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>HOLIDAY INN SELECT WOBURN</address_2><address_1>15 Middlesex Canal Park </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.497452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-897-4000</phone><name>Scoreboard Sports Bar and Grill </name><city>Woburn</city><id>1173954</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.158722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE!!!: Red Sox Natives founder Jon is hosting. Seems we've lost the original hosts for this event! I don't have a ride so I won't make it. Frank has a family emergency. HOWEVER, please still go. I know there are still people going. Just ask hostess for Red Sox Natives group.  OR, if you like, you can join me at THE POINT in Boston.  I'll be there for the game.  GO PATRIOTS!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;============================&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CROSSLISTED EVENT! This event is crosslisted with Red Sox Natives; It's the Weekend, WTF do I do now?; Single Geeks; Nerds and Professional Group. JOIN THE FUN! Fenway Frank from the Red Sox Natives group will be the host for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;========================================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a 2012 Red Sox Natives Exclusive Event! The 2012 Patriots Season Opener.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at Scoreboard for a Patriots Game Viewing Party to watch the 2012 Season Opener as the New England Patriots take on the Tennessee Titans on Sunday, September 9.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive early after Noon time to get yourself a prime seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing. This will be an informal gathering in the bar area. We strongly suggest that fans arrive early and put in for a table if you want seats or just move around the bar area and enjoy the mayhem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game Time is 1:00pm. SCOREBOARD SERVES FREE WINGS AT HALFTIME!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scoreboard Manager and Assistant Organizer Lauren will have a full house. Expect some specials, give-aways and surprises in the house. Maybe even lines!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no event fee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AND we will also be able to watch the Red Sox Home game vs Toronto at 1:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay for the whole game or leave whenever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will invite some guests. Please check back for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives organized weekly viewing parties last year with guests from several other invited groups attending. We had a blast with up to 80 people attending at various locations in Boston, Woburn and Wakefield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scoreboard has been one of our venues for watching Patriots, Red Sox, Bruins and Celtics games over the past several years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have never been to Scoreboard, it is located at 15 Middlesex Canal Park next to the Holiday Inn and Showcase Cinema off Route 128 in Woburn. Scoreboard has over 30 High Definition and Plasma TVs ranging in size from 50 to 92 inches. Parking is free. More info at &lt;a href="http://www.tpsscoreboard.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tpsscoreboard.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own food and drinks. PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER AND TIP YOUR SERVERS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space is limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask Lauren or the Scoreboard hostess to direct you to other Meetup people (Red Sox Natives group) or request a table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347217585000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346853118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patriots Viewing Party at Scoreboard--Season Opener Patriots at Tennessee Titans</name><id>80938612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347206400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/80938612/</event_url></item>