<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>403 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-3400</phone><name>Cafe Luna</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669119</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thursday night is live music JAZZ night at La Luna Caffe. &lt;br /&gt;We will get together at the La Luna cafe in Central Square in Cambridge between 7:00pm and 8:00pm. You can arrive at any time between 7:00-8:00. Then we will go for a 30 minute walk to Harvard Square and sit down for a short time at Cafe Paradiso. Those who do not want to walk may remain at La Luna and take in the Jazz. For those walking, after resting at Cafe Paradiso we will walk back to Central Square. Cafe La Luna closes at 11pm on Thursdays; and, Cafe Paradiso closes at 10pm on Thursdays.  This should be a special European style promenade.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is free after 6pm in Central Square so you can look for the two municipal outdoor parking lots on Bishop Allen Drive (Norfolk St, Douglass St). The lot behind McDonalds/Quest Diagnostics is practically beside La Luna. The lot behind Blockbusters is very busy. There is an indoor parking garage on the corner of Green St and Pearl St with a max fee of $5 ($1/hour).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can reach me at my cellular number when you arrive if you are not certain where the group is located 1-508-498-1651.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179615697000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178560208000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday 7:00pm Cafe La Luna/Walking/Cafe Paradiso/Walking Event</name><id>5752023</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179442800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/5752023/</event_url></item>