<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Doty Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02576</zip><lat>41.803616</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Flagship Cinemas Inc</name><city>Wareham</city><id>3238052</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.769302</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ladies, this movie comes out on June 29th and I've gotta say that the write-up on it has me counting the days to see it. What better movie for a bunch of fun girls to get together and go out to see??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just in case you haven't heard - Magic Mike is an upcoming comedy film directed by Steven Soderbergh starring Channing Tatum, Alex Pettyfer, Matthew McConaughey, Cody Horn, Joe Manganiello, and Matt Bomer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;McConaughey says that filming the dance scene was addictive. &lt;br /&gt;

 "At first it was scary as hell, but then it became like a drug, and I couldn’t wait to do it again," he said. "Look, I love to dance, but I’ve never been a stripper. Channing’s one of the best hip-hop street dancers I’ve ever seen, and I didn’t want to challenge his style, so I worked on my own strengths. I also knew that my dance had to be the dirtiest. It had to be wonderfully filthy."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;....and it just makes sense to go out dancing afterwards! Probably Piper Beau's at 207 Main Street, Wareham since it's close by and the band Chain Drive is playing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341024955000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337274686000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Girl's Night Out to see Magic Mike Movie</name><id>65207212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341012600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/65207212/</event_url></item>