<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 1/2 Beacon St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358084</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 227-0270</phone><name> The Boston Athenaeum</name><city>Boston</city><id>913311</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060636</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For more information: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonathenaeum.org/node/1159" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bostonathenaeum.org/node/1159&lt;/a&gt; Discussions of religion (and politics, and money) tend to be the hot-button, no-holds-barred destroyers of family dinners&amp;mdash;and even friendships. For the true believers and the true unbelievers, it&amp;rsquo;s impossble to find common ground: either God exists or He doesn&amp;rsquo;t, and never the twain shall meet. But what if religion isn&amp;rsquo;t all true or all nonsense? Alain de Botton argues that the supernatural claims of religion are entirely false, and yet religion still has some very important things to teach the secular world. In Religion for Atheists de Botton suggests that atheists shouldn&amp;rsquo;t trash religion; instead, they should steal from it&amp;mdash;because the world&amp;rsquo;s religions are packed with ideas on how we should live in and arrange our societies, build a sense of community,make our relationships last, dampen feelings of envy and inadequacy, get more out of art, and build sustainable businesses. For non-believers, de Botton&amp;rsquo;s message offers a doctrine-free pass to the range of consoling rituals and ideas that religion represents. For believers, de Botton&amp;rsquo;s appreciation for the message&amp;mdash;if not the medium&amp;mdash;of religion should be welcome. Seeing things through de Botton&amp;rsquo;s eyes, both believers and non-believers can at last come together at the dinner table&amp;mdash;and argue about something else, for a change. Alain de Botton is the author of non-fiction essays on themes ranging from love and travel to architecture and philosophy. His books include The Consolations of Philosophy, How Proust Can Change Your Life, The Art of Travel, and The Architecture of Happiness. To Reserve: This event is open to the public. The fee is $10 for members and $20 for non-members. Reservations are required but cannot be accepted until Thursday, March 1 at 9:00 a.m. To register, please log onto your My Athen&amp;aelig;um profile (&lt;a href="https://bbd.bostonathenaeum.org/" class="linkified"&gt;https://bbd.bostonathenaeum.org/&lt;/a&gt;) to make a secure online payment or call the Athen&amp;aelig;um&amp;rsquo;s reservation line, (617) 720-7600. Reservations are non-refundable. Book Sales: Alain de Botton will sign copies of his book at a reception following the lecture, books will be provided for sale by Zimmara. If you wish to reserve or purchase a book or books in advance, please visit Zimmara or call 617-734-7689.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331852212000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330955127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Talk, Alain de Botton, Religion for Atheists</name><id>55029732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331676000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/55029732/</event_url></item>