<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #000000"&gt;This is a combined trip with the AMC (Appalachian Mountain Club). The AMC requires a signed liability waiver for participation so ALL participants will need to read the waiver (&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/AMC%20Liability%20Release.pdf"&gt;read it by clicking here&lt;/a&gt;) before you arrive and sign it at the trailhead in order to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for hiking (and just a touch of bushwhacking) up the Fire Warden’s Route to Mt. Hale. We’ll bypass the 5 mile road walk that comes with doing the Hale Brook Trail and instead hike up the Little River Valley and follow a moderate ridge to the summit. There are many beautiful forest scenes along the way, and other closer-in views (rather than the big expanses). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~1.5 MPH&lt;/strong&gt;) out and back trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 7.5 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and c&lt;strong&gt;limb about 2,400 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. It should take an average hiker &lt;strong&gt;about 7 hours to complete this trip&lt;/strong&gt; (this does not include time for rest breaks).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

This event is considered to be Intermediate because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

To prevent any delay in confirming your trip registration, please respond to all fields, and indicate “None” in any field where the circumstances are not applicable, rather than leaving a blank space. Once you have submitted your complete trip registration information, a leader will contact you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Bring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need things like warm layers, wind protection, goggles, snow shoes, and traction. I will update everyone if weather conditions dictate that we bring more than what is described here If you are unsure about what this means, check out the AMC's recommended winter day hiking list at &lt;a href="http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Winter_Dayhike_equip.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Winter_Dayhike_equip.pdf&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The following items are very important to bring and get a special call out: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

•Good insulated winter boots. &lt;br /&gt;

•Snowshoes are mandatory -- the snow will be deep at altitude. &lt;br /&gt;

•You should also bring crampons along. We will decide at the parking lot whether to bring them on the hike. &lt;br /&gt;

•If you have them, MicroSpikes or Stabilicers may also come in handy. &lt;br /&gt;

•2L of pre-heated water, in insulated bottles, at least one of which is easily accessible while on the move. &lt;br /&gt;

•Good supply of energy food that won't freeze hard in winter temps. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. If you don't have the required items you put yourself and everyone else at risk. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountain-forecast.com/peaks/Mount-Hale-New-Hampshire/forecasts/1236"&gt;Click here for the weather&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We will meet at 8:00am, all geared and ready to go, at the turnaround at the end of Little River Rd, off Rt. 3 in Twin Mountain, NH. If you prefer to drive up without being fully geared up and packed up, be sure to arrive enough ahead of time to allow for this (30 minutes works well if you need to put on your shell gear, boots and gaiters, and get your backpack and snowshoes adjusted and ready).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

From Boston, allow 2:45 for the drive, plus whatever time you will need for carpool meet ups, rest stops, gasoline, coffee, breakfast, bad road conditions, etc. Take I-93 North up to Exit 35, which is Rt.3 North. In 9.3 miles, turn Right on Little River Rd. The turnaround is about a mile in. GPS coordinates: 44.251163,-71.557903.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.251163,-71.557903&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=43.313188,-71.372681&amp;amp;spn=3.417187,3.103638&amp;amp;sll=42.036922,-71.683501&amp;amp;sspn=3.488049,3.103638&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFRs4owId8Ry8-w&amp;amp;oq=boston&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;Click here for Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $25 from Boston MA, $20 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex Cowen</member_name><member_id>73326852</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1364908182000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363031143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Hale from the Fire Warden’s Route</name><id>108754202</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364731200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/108754202/</event_url></item>