<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 3rd Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Intrepid Labs</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6978782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.080132</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join EFactor for an information packed event that will bring social media and marketing professionals to teach you everything you need to know about startup marketing. Learn from a panel of leading experts how to develop and implement an exciting new social media marketing strategy. Network with fellow entrepreneurs and meet marketing professionals to ensure your company’s success!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us to discuss:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are the newest cutting edge Social Media Marketing trends? &lt;br /&gt;

 How to create the right marketing strategy for your startup &lt;br /&gt;

 How to build the right marketing team for your company &lt;br /&gt;

 How to avoid common marketing and social media mistakes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.efactor.com/smmboston"&gt;http://www.efactor.com/smmboston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regular Price - $15 (When you sign up online)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Price at the door - $20&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Speakers:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.efactor.com/newleaflegal" target="_blank"&gt;Shannon Jamieson&lt;/a&gt;. Shannon is an attorney and co-founder of New Leaf Legal, a progressive flat-fee law firm specializing in corporate and intellectual property matters, offered exclusively for artists, entrepreneurs and emerging businesses.  Shannon's practice within the firm focuses on a variety of entertainment and IP matters, including acquiring, buying, selling and licensing of copyrights and trademarks, as well as entertainment contracts. &lt;a href="http://www.efactor.com/profile/view/id/1840607/" target="_blank"&gt;Molly DeLong&lt;/a&gt;. Molly leads the Real Bullets Branding strategy team with a passion for creating exhilarating branding with a thorough understanding of consumer trends in the digital age. Molly works to create meaningful partnerships for her clients and digital strategies that can translate across multiple channels.  Molly is a Boston native with a degree in Consumer Science and Marketing from University of Wisconsin-Madison. 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First 10 people to arrive will receive iPhone Speck Cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350437704000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Marketing Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Marketing-Learning-Group</urlname><id>1338478</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Marketing Learning Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349889378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EFactor Presents: Social Media Marketing </name><id>86380022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350426600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Marketing-Learning-Group/events/86380022/</event_url></item>