<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Arrow St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.868.2033</phone><name>Pierre Menard Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>347668</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the first night of a multi-city tour a trio of three young poets promoting widely-noticed new books: Elisa Gabbert, Chris Tonelli and Joe Hall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ELISA GABBERT is the poetry editor of Absent and the author of The French Exit (Birds LLC) and Thanks for Sending the Engine (Kitchen Press). With Kathleen Rooney, she has co-authored several collaborative poetry collections, including Don't ever stay the same; keep changing (Spooky Girlfriend Press) and That Tiny Insane Voluptuousness (Otoliths). Recent poems can be found in Denver Quarterly, The Laurel Review, Puerto del Sol, and Salt Hill. She currently lives in Boston, works at a software startup, and blogs at The French Exit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHRIS TONELLI is one of the founding editors at Birds, LLC. He founded and co-curates the So and So Series and co-edits the So and So Magazine. He is the author of four chapbooks, most recently No Theater (Brave Men Press) and For People Who Like Gravity and Other People (Rope-A-Dope Press). His first full-length collection is The Trees Around, and new work can be found in upcoming issues of The Laurel Review and Fou. He teaches at North Carolina State University in Raleigh, where he lives with his wife Allison and their son Miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JOE HALL is the founder of the Washington, DC reading series Cheryl’s Gone. A 2007-2008 George Mason University Thesis Fellow, his work has appeared in Versal, Hayden’s Ferry Review, Handsome, Cimmaron Review, among others, and his reviews appear frequently in Phoebe and The Celadon Review. Joe lives with his partner Cheryl wherever they go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will be held under the wooden beams of the lovely Pierre Menard gallery - around the corner from the Harvard Book Store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wine and refreshment will be enjoyed before, during and after!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273841016000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273620087000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tonelli, Hall, and Gabbert at Pierre Menard</name><id>13454785</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273791600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/13454785/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/5/global_14983573.jpeg</photo_url></item>