<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 John F. Kennedy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371391</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard University Institute of Politics‎</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9498002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Greetings, &lt;br /&gt;

On behalf of the BBC I’d like to invite you to a unique discussion and radio recording. &lt;br /&gt;

The Public Philosopher is a BBC radio show hosted by Professor Michael Sandel. It’s designed to engage a live audience in a debate that takes current controversial topics and highlights the philosophical and moral ideas behind our points of view. &lt;br /&gt;

This particular edition will take place at The Forum at Harvard’s Institute of Politics. In this special recording (which will be broadcast on BBC Radio on 30 October), the focus is on healthcare and welfare – key issues in November’s elections. &lt;br /&gt;

Professor Sandel will look at the current presidential campaign through the lens of the long-running struggle between American individualism and community. These big philosophical themes lurk just beneath the surface of the debate between Romney and Obama, and the evening will explore some of the questions that are rarely asked on the daily news. &lt;br /&gt;

What are the roles of government and the individual in health care provision? Will this election be a turning point in the historical American debate over the welfare state? And what is the appropriate role of government and the market in American society? &lt;br /&gt;

We would request that you arrive at 5:30 p.m. for a 6:00 p.m. start. The recording will last about 1 ½ hours. A map and directions to the Institute can be found by following this link: &lt;a href="http://www.iop.harvard.edu/contact-us" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.iop.harvard.edu/contact-us&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The nature of the event means that not everyone in the audience will get the chance to contribute a comment, but a number of audience members will get the opportunity to air their views. Also, we hope that even those who do not get the chance to participate directly will find the debate engaging and well worth attending. &lt;br /&gt;

If you are interested in attending, please email the producer Mike Wendling at michael.wendling@bbc.co.uk to reserve a seat. &lt;br /&gt;

Many thanks, &lt;br /&gt;

Mike Wendling &lt;br /&gt;

BBC Radio&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Morabito</member_name><member_id>10170370</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349879082000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348759474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BBC Radio Event</name><id>84359982</id><headcount>80</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349820000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/84359982/</event_url></item>