<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Transition Town&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Film, Potluck &amp;amp; Conversation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film, Transition Town, is a moving and inspiring story of the people that looked peak oil and climate change square in the face, and responded with creativity, compassion and genius. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Peak oil and climate change are two of the greatest challenges we face today; the Transition Town movement is firmly rooted in the idea that people taking action now in their communities can not only tackle these environmental threats but also, in the process of doing so, lead more fulfilling lives. It is about hope in an otherwise bleak seeming future. Above all, it’s about the power of an alternative vision for how society could be and not waiting for government or politicians to get it right.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt; &lt;i&gt;--- Caroline Lucas MEP, leader of the Green Party of England and Wales, &lt;br /&gt;and co-author of Green Alternatives to Globalisation: A Manifesto.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Transition Town&lt;br /&gt;$10 donation, $5 students&lt;br /&gt;Film at 7, Community conversation at 8:30, Organic potluck at 6:30 pm - bring a dish to share!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Community Conversation will be called, Fossil Fuels Anonymous, to explore our societal addiction to oil and to discover the alternative, Conscious Consumerism. We will discuss what life could look life after oil and how can we begin preparing now …  Step One is acknowledging the fact that we are all dependent on oil to maintain our current lifestyles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Growing Green Wellness Center&lt;br /&gt;197 New Britain Ave, Hartford&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Future oil price rises will have a massive impact on food security, and unless we address the problem now, we could face the prospect of food shortages – and the possibility of starvation in some developing countries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We must change energy, trade and agriculture policies if we are to avoid a food crisis precipitated by ‘Peak Oil’ – the point at which half of global oil production has been consumed, and beyond which extraction goes into irreversible decline, and prices rise accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many industry experts predict that Peak Oil will happen by 2020: an increasing number argue we are close to, or have already passed, the peak of oil production. Already, world oil and gas production is declining at an average of four to six per cent annually, while demand is growing at two to three per cent. The last time more oil was discovered than used in a single year was a quarter of a century ago.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&amp;lt;object width=&amp;quot;400&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;300&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;embed src=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=8029815&amp;amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;amp;show_title=1&amp;amp;show_byline=1&amp;amp;show_portrait=0&amp;amp;color=&amp;amp;fullscreen=1&amp;quot;" target="_blank"&gt;http://vimeo.com/moog...&lt;/a&gt; type=&amp;quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;400&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;300&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/embed&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/object&amp;gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268611503000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266352627000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Transition Town</name><id>12620800</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268438400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/12620800/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/1/global_13154001.jpeg</photo_url></item>