<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>280 The Fenway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-566-1401</phone><name>Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum</name><city>Boston</city><id>698253</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098228</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>After Hours is live music, art, conversation, cocktails and more in an inviting atmosphere. Linger around the courtyard bar and listen to live music or sample the tasty menu in the Gardner Café. Experience something different each month – from impromptu gallery talks to cutting-edge contemporary performance – and spend time in the galleries exploring what the Gardner is all about. Members and Isabellas get in free! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Art, music and atmosphere: what will you discover After Hours? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May 21st, 2009 – Primavera&lt;br /&gt;Explore inside and out tonight as we head towards summer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Courtyard Sounds: Enjoy ambient sounds from DJ Die Young as he spins live from the courtyard (5:30 to 8:30 PM) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gallery Travels: Visit the galleries with this self-guided tour exploring how Gardner incorporated art and landscape into the museum’s spaces. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Viewfinder: Listen in on a discussion about John S. Sargent’s famous portrait of Isabella Gardner (every half-hour), plus other impromptu gallery discussions (5:30 to 8:30PM)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ask the Gardner’s Gardener: Chat with the museum’s gardener and horticulture staff and learn how they keep the courtyard garden blooming and green all year round! (5:30 to 7:30PM) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hands On: Swing by the outside gardens and pot up a few nasturtium seeds to take home and grow. Yeah, yeah, we know it’s a little hokey, but you’ll love it! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sketching in the Galleries: Create your own masterpieces with drawing in the cloisters and galleries (6 to 9PM) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artful Flavors: Indulge in the culinary arts, signature cocktails including the all-new Madame Gautreau, and more at the courtside bar and Gardner Café. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Hours PLUS&lt;br /&gt;May 21st, 2008, 7:00pm - TBD &lt;br /&gt;More Information Coming Soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets&lt;br /&gt;After Hours Tickets  Adults: $12 After Hours Plus Tickets (Includes admission to After Hours) Adults: $23 &lt;br /&gt;Order by Phone Box Office: 617 278 5156&lt;br /&gt;Tickets also on sale at the door, subject to availability. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artful Flavors @ After Hours&lt;br /&gt;Artful culinary offerings are also being served up After Hours! Indulge in all-new specialty cocktails and snacks at The Courtside Bar adjoining the interior garden, or sit down for dinner and drinks at the award-winning The Gardner Café featuring a full menu of sweet and savory dishes to fulfill your culinary, as much as your cultural, appetites! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Courtside Bar&lt;br /&gt;Indulge in “Courtside Cocktails” and all-new “Courtside Bites” offerings at a Courtside Bar adjacent to the interior garden, open 5:30 to 9:15 pm. “Courtside Cocktails” include “THE MADAME GAUTREAU” (an all-new specialty cocktail inspired by one of Isabella Gardner’s favorite paintings), along with wine, beer, and non-alcoholic alternatives. And a changing array of “Courtside Bites” (available for just $1) will adequately sustain you to explore the galleries and art activities that await.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gardner Café&lt;br /&gt;The Gardner Café is also open during After Hours, serving up sweet and savory dishes, cocktails and other culinary offerings from 5:30 to 9 pm. Tables are available on a first-come, first-served basis. Reservations are available for museum members only by calling 617 566 1088.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside the doors.  I'll have a sign or Meetup pin.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243114365000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238278938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gardner After Hours</name><id>10058550</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242941400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/10058550/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/6/5/global_7869429.jpeg</photo_url></item>