<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi,&lt;br /&gt; Fed up with the ties between big money and  US politcs, in 2000,  90-year old  Doris Haddock staged a cross-country walk in protest. Four years later she ran for the Senate seat in New Hampshire. This is her story- but I'd like to know what's in her chocolate chip cookie recipes! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doris and the director will  both be present at this screening !!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the fan favorite award at this year's SXSW Film Festival in Austin, Texas.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Vastly entertaining...one of the most captivating election documentaries in recent memory...The film unfolds with a powerful and universal story about a citizen?s love for her country.  Run Granny Run should be required viewing for anyone between the ages of 4 and 94, whether you can vote or not.&amp;quot; Matt Dentler, SXSW&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Run Granny Run by Marlo Poras (2007, 77 min.). Doris Granny D Haddock is the nation's oldest political newcomer. At ninety, she laced up her sneakers and walked across America to rally against the influence of big money in elections,making both friends and enemies inside the Washington beltway. Now ninety-four and still fed up with politics, she jumps at an unexpected chance to run for US Senate. With just four months until election day, Doris and her motley crew craft a feisty campaign that personifies her democratic ideals of a government of, by, and for the people. An unlikely portrait of a remarkable activist and an exploration of our fragile democracy in the corporate age.    The MFA's description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And the obligatory complete review:&lt;a href="http://www.eyeforfilm.co.uk/reviews.php?id=6257" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eyeforfilm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also catch Run Granny Run on HBO this Fall, but I don't think Doris Haddock will be in your living room. Oh and by the way, this screening is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191951952000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189360157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Run Granny Run at the MFA- Granny Present</name><id>6325088</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191779100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6325088/</event_url></item>