<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 Brainard Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.733029</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bow Tie Cinema City</name><city>Hartford</city><id>684699</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.661139</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Well, let's start with &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Visitor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In a world of six billion people, it only takes one to change your life. Sixty-two-year-old Walter Vale is sleepwalking through his life. Having lost his passion for teaching and writing, he fills the void by unsuccessfully trying to learn to play classical piano. When his college sends him to Manhattan to attend a conference, Walter is surprised to find a young couple has taken up residence in his apartment. Victims of a real estate scam, Tarek, a Syrian man, and Zainab, his Senegalese girlfriend, have nowhere else to go. In the first of a series of tests of the heart, Walter reluctantly allows the couple to stay with him. ? &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Site and Trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.thevisitorfilm.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thevisitor...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was initially put off by the saccharine schmaltz-fest vibe oozing from the trailer, but reviews have been uniformly positive, and the film appears to live up to director Tom McCarthy's debut effort, the excellent &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Station Agent&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; (if you've never seen this gem, you need to go rent it ASAP!) Richard Jenkins is an excellent actor as well, this should be fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>H</member_name><member_id>7440817</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214518785000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213658781000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Visitor</name><id>8154871</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214345700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/8154871/</event_url></item>