<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>127 Smith Place </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.394054</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Moms And Paws</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>4812112</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.151420</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This one will be on a Saturday for a change! Some of you will remember I spoke about a place in Woburn. It turned out not to available after all, but I think this place will be even more fun for the Cavs (and us too)! If you go to the Mom and Paws Website, you can see photos of this brand new facility. I have not seen it in person yet but I will check it out before the meetup to make sure it's as good as it looks. :) If 10 dogs or fewer attend, their charge is $5.00/dog, which they collect as we leave. If more than 10 arrive, there is a group rate which would be less per dog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the easiest route to take from the North Shore (not the most direct, but the least complicated!): From Rt. 128, take Exit 29, which is Route 2. Go East on Rte 2 (towards Boston and Cambridge). Rt. 2 remains a highway all the way until it reaches Rte 16 aka Alewife Brook Parkway. You bear Right at the Alewife MBTA station, staying on Rt. 2. At the rotary, turn Right onto Concord Ave (towards Belmont) and Right again onto Smith Place. Go past the WOW (Work-Out-World) sign, all the way to the end of Smith Place; then Left onto Mooney, and you'll see the signs for Mom and Paws. Park anywhere in the driveway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;127 Smith Place is very near Fresh Pond. At the Fresh Pond Circle, you take Concord Ave off the rotary (you're going West towards Belmont, not East towards Boston) and Smith Place is the second right turn off Concord.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karla Rab</member_name><member_id>10717717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330655378000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328564078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore a new indoor experience in Cambridge at Moms and Paws</name><id>51292242</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330196400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/51292242/</event_url></item>