<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;For those of you unfamiliar with his films, Canadian Guy Maddin is sortofa more whimsical David Lynch from his earlier days, ala Eraserhead.   Maddin's work can be erratic: his ballet interpretation of the Dracula myth (&amp;quot;Dracula, Pages from a Virgin's Diary&amp;quot;) in 2002 was brilliant, but I was disappointed with both 2003 films :&amp;quot;Cowards Bend the Knee&amp;quot; and to a lesser degree with &amp;quot; The Saddest Music in the World&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inspired by the aesthetics and melodramatic flourishes of silent cinema, Central European literature and the desolation of his native Winnipeg, Guy Maddin has fashioned a career like no other. A Super-8-cranking modern-day Eisenstein, filming plots that would make John Waters blush, Maddin embraces a cinema where expressionism, somnambulism and lurid sexual neuroses unite ? and conquer! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRAND UPON THE BRAIN! In which the shocking truth is finally revealed about young Guy Maddin and his hellish childhood on a remote island, under the hyperwatchful eye of a crazed mother hellbent on restoring her youth and a diabolically distant scientist-father, proprietors of a mom-and-pop orphanage they surreptitiously operate within the dank confines of the family lighthouse. WATCH! as the sex instinct grabs hold of young Maddin and his sister! THRILL! as the Mysteries of the Light House are divined by teen detectives! REEL! at the headstrong invention and heart-stopping rhythms of the elder Maddin?s heroic silent moviemaking!!   Description from The Brattle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?Nuttily wonderful. One of the year's 10 best films. Once again, Mr. Maddin has ransacked film history and his own delirious imagination to create a work like none other: a silently shot film about a man who, on revisiting his childhood home, hurtles unto a past where orphan children, coy lesbian lovers, and a mad scientist converge. Delightful!? ? Manohla Dargis, The New York Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete review:&lt;a href="http://metromix.chicagotribune.com/movies/mmx-070518-movies-review-brand,0,5301723.story?coll=mmx-movies_top_heds" target="_blank"&gt;http://metromix.chica...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the custom, Tom will be holding a Meet-up sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then we're off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183393581000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179877299000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guy Maddin's Brand Upon the Brain</name><id>5807281</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183159800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5807281/</event_url></item>