<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>96 Winthrop street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372280</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tommy Doyles</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1114814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Have a great time putting your esoteric knowledge to good use. Stump trivia is a fun social event. We will break into teams of 4-6, competing with other teams at the bar for prizes and bragging rights. Tommy Doyle's has a good pub dinner menu and an excellent beer selection. After trivia you may stick around for karaoke. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Saying you aren't any good at trivia is no excuse not to come join us. Do you watch TV? Movies? Listen to Music? Eat? Know a little history? Geography? Everyone knows something about the world and can make a great contribution to the game as well as to the conversations while we play. Come on out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trivia starts at 8:00.  Please arrive at 7:30 to eat, drink &amp;amp; socialize.  Tommy Doyles gets crowded on trivia nights and it is usually difficult to save seats past 7:45.  If you arrive later you might not get one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find you will not be able to go, please change your RSVP so we are not holding chairs from other teams and then not using them. Thank you for being considerate of your fellow Social Fun members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trivia is free.  Please bring cash for what you eat and drink.  It makes paying the bill much easier!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us on the second floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marty</member_name><member_id>11553838</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354160239000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353904082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Stump Trivia in Harvard Square</name><id>92814262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354149000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/92814262/</event_url></item>