<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 302 &amp; George Street</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.078011</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>837242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.283012</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of us Bretts are organizing a hiking weekend April 24th and 25th.  We'll be staying at the lodge Friday night and heading out Saturday morning to Zealand Hut, where we'll stay Saturday night.  The hike to the hut isn't too strenuous, so we'll probably eat lunch and head out for some more hiking and hanging at the falls in the afternoon, heading home on Sunday after breakfast.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Yes for more info on reservations and meeting up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some info about the hut and the hike:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in Zealand Notch, the former scene of indiscriminate logging and devastating fires in the nineteenth century, this hut occupies a choice four-season spot near waterfalls and outstanding views at the eastern edge of the Pemigewasset Wilderness. A popular family destination, this is the perfect place to spot a moose and other abundant wildlife — and to go backcountry skiing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basics&lt;br /&gt;Location: Zealand Notch&lt;br /&gt;Elevation: 2,700 feet&lt;br /&gt;Access&lt;br /&gt;Summer: Easy 2.8 mile hike.&lt;br /&gt;Winter: Moderate 6.5 mile snowshoe or ski (Zealand Rd is closed in winter). More challenging approaches also available.&lt;br /&gt;Adjacent huts: Galehead Hut, Mizpah Spring Hut. &lt;br /&gt;Hut borders Whitewall Brook, whose cascading waters fill chutes and pools—dip your feet and enjoy the soothing sounds.&lt;br /&gt;Accommodations&lt;br /&gt;Sleeps 36 in four coed bunkrooms.&lt;br /&gt;Fall, winter and spring self service includes access to kitchen facilities, mattress, pillow and bathrooms. No blankets are provided (bring sleeping bag).&lt;br /&gt;Summer full service includes hearty dinner at 6 p.m. and breakfast at 7 a.m., mattress, pillow and three wool blankets on each bunk (bring linens or sleeping bag).&lt;br /&gt;Main hut building with wood stove lit at 4 p.m. during self service season.&lt;br /&gt;Resident staff available with trail information and weather reports.&lt;br /&gt;Small retail store with safety items, snacks, souvenirs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Krissie</member_name><member_id>6035276</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272292245000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271253221000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A night at Zealand Hut: Hiking weekend</name><id>13179872</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272063600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/13179872/</event_url></item>