<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; on the PHONE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note: This is a long distance call; not toll-free. &lt;br /&gt;** Phone # &amp;amp; worksheets will be sent to you after you RSVP : YES&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******************************************************** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Chime in&amp;quot; from 8 - 9 pm ...mastermind with Ann Ide, join in....&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- with your questions &lt;br /&gt;- to get support and suggestions &lt;br /&gt;- to share your LOA experiences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ann Ide, BostonLOA member and New Possibilities Life Coach,&lt;/b&gt; presenter at our September's meetup, is on the call to answer any questions and help you understand further &lt;b&gt;how to live in a relaxed, vacation frame of mind every day, – feeling that happy, harmonious, relaxed feeling and be productive and successful as ever! &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Comments from some of our members who participated at our &lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/calendar/11040473/"&gt;September's meetup&lt;/a&gt; with Ann:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Sweet and Perfect!” &lt;i&gt;- Lisa&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“A wonderful example of pivoting toward a better feeling thought pattern.” -&lt;i&gt; Lidia S&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I am so accustomed to thinking about the outcome, which is short sighted and drawing negativity to the very thing I am trying to do professionally and personally. This was a great opportunity in learning and self reflecting. I look forward to future groups.”  &lt;i&gt;- Kim F&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Ann Ide:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;www.NewPossibilitiesCoaching.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann is a certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming (NLP) and Hypnotherapy, and a certified NLP Life Coach with over 15 years experience. She has trained and consulted people nationally. Her passion is helping people move beyond suffering and mere survival, and creating “New Possibilities” in their lives for greater harmony, happiness and success. She provides personal and group coaching, guided meditations, and business workshops.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254092172000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252554752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BostonLOA TELE-Meetup: LOA Masterminding with Ann Ide</name><id>11335462</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252972800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/11335462/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/a/global_10628618.jpeg</photo_url></item>