<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Enjoy the amazing art of glass blowing while sipping wine in their very craft! I came across this event from another meetup so thought you guys may enjoy this as well. So come and enjoy some wine and witness this amazing art form at the Diablo Glass School in Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Diablo Glass School&lt;br /&gt;123 Terrace St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02120&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT!!!   PLEASE PURCHASE YOUR TICKETS BEFORE RSVPING YES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.diabloglassschool.com/wineandcheese.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets can be found here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Diablo's Event Description:&lt;br /&gt;A team of four glassblowers will gather molten glass from the furnace to blow Venetian-style wine glasses. Wine and cheese will be served in our lounge. The wines will be a selection of 15+ Bordeaux from Terroir Wines in conjunction with The Wine Emporium. Other fine glassware will be exhibited and sold in our flame-working shop. The entry fee is $35. Reservations are required as space is limited.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More About Diablo Glass School:&lt;br /&gt;Diablo Glass School opened in 2001, creating a public access glass arts studio in Boston, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Diablo is a place where beginners and experienced are welcome to share a nurturing environment, to grow and develop their creative skills in a warm, inviting atmosphere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Diablo offers different level classes and facilities in various disciplines, exposing a broad spectrum of people to exciting glass techniques in glassblowing, flameworking, fused glass and stained glass.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By connecting students to professional national and international glass artists, we provide a learning experience that constantly offers new information and challenges.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check out pic</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce Turnbull</member_name><member_id>4018534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245366774000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240874020000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine Tasting And Goblet Making Demonstration</name><id>10280512</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243722600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/10280512/</event_url></item>