<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>310 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357006</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 482-6439</phone><name>Old South Meeting House</name><city>Boston</city><id>669048</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us at this lunchtime lecture at the Old South Meeting House. Price: $5.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Old South Meeting House Site&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.oldsouthmeetinghouse.org/osmh123456789_1773L/Calendar/DispForm.aspx?ID=259" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.oldsouthme...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Which famous American inventor was born on Milk Street and baptized at the Meeting House? Which congregation member died in poverty, despite her international fame? Who spent her youth being 'finished' in Boston and attended services each Sunday with her extended family? Join the education staff of the Meeting House and learn more about some of its famous and not-sofamous congregants. Discover what it was like to attend Puritan services, and hear about life in colonial Boston for some of the Meeting House members.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I am guessing the first person was Ben Franklin. If you go to the Granary Burial Ground you can find a monument to the Franklin family there. Can anybody guess the other two people they refer to?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Begins&lt;/b&gt;: 2/11/2010 12:15 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Ends&lt;/b&gt;: 2/11/2010 1:00 PM &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price&lt;/b&gt;: $5; Free for members &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will get there a bit before noon to save half a pew or so for the group up near the podium, placing a red MEETUP sign on the aisle. T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, and a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag. The Old South Meeting House is in Downtown Crossing across from the large Borders Bookstore. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Old South Meeting House, Wikipedia&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Old_South_Meeting_House" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Old South Meeting House, in the Downtown Crossing area of Boston, Massachusetts, gained fame as the organizing point for the Boston Tea Party on December 16, 1773. 5,000 colonists gathered at the Meeting House, the largest building in Boston at the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] After the Boston Massacre in 1770, yearly anniversary meetings were held at the church until 1775 featuring speakers such as John Hancock and Dr. Joseph Warren. In 1773 5,000 people met in the Meeting House to debate British taxation, and after the meeting a group raided a nearby tea ship in what became known as the Boston Tea Party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Old South Meeting House was almost destroyed in the Great Boston Fire of 1872, and the congregation then built a new church (the 'New' Old South Church at Copley Square) which remains its home to this day. Once twice a year, on the Sunday before Thanksgiving, the Old South congregation returns to Old South Meeting House for services in its ancestral home&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296074253000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264708180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beyond Sam Adams: Colonial Characters of Meeting House @ Old South Meeting House</name><id>12451457</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265908500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12451457/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/c/global_6131516.jpeg</photo_url></item>