<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>1 Bennett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-5000</phone><name>Charles Hotel </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>744847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2121" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvard.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;... and the &lt;br /&gt;Need for Social Connection&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;a panel discussion with JOHN T. CACIOPPO, Mazharin Banaji, Nancy Kanwisher, and Stephen Kosslyn &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is a &lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Book Store&lt;/a&gt; event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;R.S.V.P. at connection@harvard.com to reserve a place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event begins at 6:00. Please arrive by 5:45 p.m.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to present University of Chicago neuroscientist JOHN T. CACIOPPO and esteemed colleagues for a panel discussion of the powerful influence of social context as documented in Loneliness: Human Nature and the Need for Social Connection. Dr. Cacioppo will be joined by Mazharin Banaji, Nancy Kanwisher, and Stephen Kosslyn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Cacioppo's groundbreaking research topples one of the pillars of modern medicine and psychology: the focus on the individual as the unit of inquiry. By employing brain scans, monitoring blood pressure, and analyzing immune function, he demonstrates the overpowering influence of social context—a factor so strong that it can alter DNA replication.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He defines an unrecognized syndrome—chronic loneliness—brings it out of the shadow of its cousin depression, and shows how this subjective sense of social isolation uniquely disrupts our perceptions, behavior, and physiology, becoming a trap that not only reinforces isolation but can also lead to early death. He gives the lie to the Hobbesian view of human nature as a &amp;quot;war of all against all,&amp;quot; and he shows how social cooperation is, in fact, humanity's defining characteristic. Most important, he shows how we can break the trap of isolation for our benefit both as individuals and as a society.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John T. Cacioppo is the Tiffany and Margaret Blake Distinguished Service Professor and director of the Center for Cognitive and Social Neurosciencen at the University of Chicago, and president of the Association for Psychological Science. He lives in Chicago. Loneliness was co-authored by William Patrick, former editor for science and medicine at Harvard University Press and current editor in chief of the Journal of Life Sciences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Main lobby; before &amp; after. I'll have the Renoir pinned to my jacket pocket.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225345506000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219597516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Human Nature ...</name><id>8610049</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222464600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/8610049/</event_url></item>