<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Chestnut St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.075863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Music Hall</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>671468</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.759360</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Last Station&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Writer-director Michael Hoffman (Restoration) delivers a thrilling comic-dramatic account of Leo Tolstoy’s final months. Played with quiet authority by Christopher Plummer, our Tolstoy has renounced writing fiction, built a school to educate peasants and advocates socialism, pacifism and sexual chastity. His new secretary (James McAvoy) becomes the comic foil between two formidable opponents scheming for control of Tolstoy’s estate. One is Chertkov (Paul Giamatti) a rigid true believer, who wants to spread Tolstoyan doctrines around the world. The other is Sofya (Helen Mirren), Tolstoy’s wife of 48 years and the mother of his 13 children, who proved her dedication by copying, by hand, War and Peace…six times. Their marital squabbles are riveting, with Mirren’s hairpin turns between comedy and tragic humiliation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(U.K., 2009, 107m) Courtesy of The Little Film Company.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We recognize that for some of our patrons, Telluride by the Sea dates – which are determined by the Telluride Film Festival in Colorado  - are in conflict with Rosh Hashanah. In an effort to be sensitive, we have worked hard to ensure that more people are able to participate in our film weekend by scheduling additional screenings late Sunday night and Monday September 21.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252287409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Telluride by the Sea '09 -The Last Station</name><id>11306657</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253399400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11306657/</event_url></item>