<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Dogtown Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.636408</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dogtown Park</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>773083</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.661129</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE #2 11/1/10:  Ok so don't kill us, yes we are changing this again.  One of our great members took a ride and researched where the best place is to meet.  It seems that the best place is right at the Dogtown Road entrance.  Below are the directions to this entrance:&lt;br /&gt;In Gloucester from Washington Street turn right on Reynard Street.  Drive to Cherry STreet and turn Left 1/10 of a mile past the Cape Ann Sportman's Club, take a Right turn up a steep hill with a &amp;quot;historic Dogtown&amp;quot; sign as a marker.  Go 3/4 of a mile to the small parking area near the gate, this is where Dogtown Road and your hike will begin.  If anyone is interested in meeting at the Friendly's Circle rotary and carpooling up to Dogtown, please include this in your RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPdate 11/1/10- We are changing the meeting location of this hike.  The original hike is an advanced trail and to accommodate all levels we will be leaving from the Blackburn Industrial Park entrance.  The directions to this entrance are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to the end of Route 128, go through the Blackburn Circle rotary and enter the Blackburn Industrial park. Head towards the radio tower in the back. Park here then find the Old Rockport road just off the pavement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the beginning of Old Rockport Road, then proceed to Babson Rock Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before the weather turns bad, let’s go out to Dogtown and go on a hike.  We can park at the Rockport T Station free of charge and then walk out to Summit Ave, where the trail begins.  For those of you who don’t know what DogTown is, here is a little history:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogtown (also Dogtown Commons or Dogtown Common or Dogtown Village) is an abandoned inland settlement on Cape Ann in Massachusetts. Once known as the Common Settlement and populated by respectable citizens, the area later known as Dogtown is divided between the city of Gloucester and the town of Rockport. It is in an area not particularly suited to agriculture, due to its poor and very rocky soil. Nevertheless it was settled, beginning in 1693, because its inland location afforded protection from pirates and from enemy natives. Another attraction was the fact that the area lay on what was originally the only direct land route between Sandy Bay (Rockport's original name) and Gloucester. The peak of population, from about 1750 to the turn of the nineteenth century, has been estimated at around one hundred families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the last occupants were suspected of practicing witchcraft, including Thomazine &amp;quot;Tammy&amp;quot; Younger, whom some knew as the &amp;quot;Queen of the Witches.&amp;quot; Tammy lived on Fox Hill, by Alewife Brook, and would reputedly place a curse on teams of oxen carrying fish from the harbor as they crossed the bridge there, unless their driver paid her a &amp;quot;toll&amp;quot;. A reputed witch often associated with Dogtown was Peg Wesson, but in fact she lived in Gloucester, not Dogtown. The last resident of Dogtown, a freedman named Cornelius &amp;quot;Black Neil&amp;quot; Finson, was found half-dead living in a cellar-hole in the winter, and was removed to the poorhouse in Gloucester in 1830; he died shortly afterward.&lt;br /&gt;Most of the land is held in trust by Gloucester and Rockport and is therefore protected in perpetuity. The current state of Dogtown affords rich recreation opportunities to hikers and bikers, dog-walkers, nature lovers, cross-country skiers, geologists and historians. The area is peppered with house-sized boulders, including one named &amp;quot;The Whale's Jaw,&amp;quot; which it formerly resembled before collapsing after a picnic's campfire got out of control in 1989.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please beware that some of the trail has rough terrain and proper foot attire should be worn.&lt;br /&gt;Poor weather will cancel this event, so please check back on the site prior to heading out.&lt;br /&gt;Our 4 legged friends and children are welcome to attend this event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nov/Dec:  November 1-Dec  11 we will be collecting donations for the Lazarus House in Lawrence.  If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you in Dogtown&lt;br /&gt;Donna  &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will gather near the cars in the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289185920000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287279590000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Dogtown</name><id>15133149</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289152800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15133149/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/7/d/global_18785757.jpeg</photo_url></item>