<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,  &lt;br /&gt;John Cassavetes, considered by many as the first independent film maker in the U.S. is a director whose works I would like to know better. Love Streams was his last film and should produce an engaging discussion afterward. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cassavetes's career of risk taking comes to a climax in this rich, original, emotionally magnificent 1984 film about a brother who is unable to love (Cassavetes) and a sister who loves too much (Gena Rowlands). For half its length the film follows their separate experiences--he as a celebrated novelist living a life of desperate dissolution in Los Angeles; she as a wife and mother undergoing a painful divorce in Chicago--and then brings them together for a rocky reunion. At the climax they trade roles, and each is alone again in a new way. Cassavetes follows his vision to the limit, a course that takes him through extravagance, indulgence, and hysteria&amp;quot; Chicago Reader  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a full review: &lt;a href="http://rogerebert.suntimes.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/19980107/REVIEWS/801070304/1023" target="_blank"&gt;http://rogerebert.sun...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is a bit over two hours long and so I for one won't be staying for the second half of the double-feature (Mike Leigh's High Hopes).  We should get to the restaurant before 9 pm which will give us a good hour for discussion on this  weeknight event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the custom, Tom will be holding a Meet-up sign near the front row at the movie's conclusion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it, &lt;br /&gt;Tom &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187706131000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184111234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>John Cassavetes' Love Streams at HFA</name><id>6004010</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187217000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6004010/</event_url></item>