<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Mugford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01945</zip><lat>42.505762</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-631-8987</phone><name>Me &amp; Thee Coffeehouse</name><city>Marblehead</city><id>793682</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.851010</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;What a great evening of folk music THIS is going to be!&amp;nbsp;Lori McKenna &amp;nbsp;is GREAT! Another MA singer songwriter with a voice to break your heart.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Hayley Reardon, very young folk singer prodigy, opens - she's pretty amazing!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please buy your own ticket at Brownpapertickets.com or look for the link on the Me and Thee website. Tickets cost $21 + fee in advance and $24 at the door if you want to risk it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I charge $1 to help cover Meetup organizer fees - you can pay that on the night. Thanks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;About Lori:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;Lori&amp;rsquo;s unusual combination of professional and personal life, at least in the context of the modern music industry, is well-documented. She grew up in Massachusetts in a musical household. Her father was an excellent singer, and her mother played the piano. Two of her older brothers were songwriters, one of whom (Richard) she considers largely responsible for her career. He accompanied a reluctant Lori to open mic nights and gave her confidence that she was good enough. She began performing her songs in public at age 27, after she and her husband Gene already had three children. She and Gene continue to maintain a happy home in Stoughton, Massachusetts, adding two more children to their full lives. In addition to family, place has an important role in Lori&amp;rsquo;s songs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/lorimckenna&amp;amp;nbsp"&gt;http://www.myspace.com/lorimckenna&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #00ffff"&gt;About Hayley:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #00ffff"&gt;When Hayley Reardon first picked up a guitar in July 2008, this young songstress uncovered both a deep passion and an obvious natural talent, unleashing a flood of beautifully constructed, delicately phrased songs.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #00ffff"&gt;At 12 years old, Boston's WUMB was first to publicly recognize her emerging talent as a winner at the 2009 Boston Folk festival Songwriting Contest. In the ensuing year this 13 year old has achieved additional recognition in numerous competitions including the YouTube/What's Your Issue 2010 Music Video Competition, The North Atlantic Arts Alliance 7th Annual Songwriting Contest, and the 2010 Indiegrrl International Songwriting Competition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #00ffff"&gt;&lt;a href="http://hayleyreardon.com"&gt;http://hayleyreardon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #00ffff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at The Landing (Front St, Marblehead)  for dinner at 6.30 pm then walk to the show. Or meet at the venue at 7.45 pm.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323557143000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319510792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lori McKenna and Hayley Reardon at the Me and Thee in Marblehead</name><id>38596472</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320451200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/38596472/</event_url></item>