<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;So here we are: now entering the magical Winter Holidays season! When I've wondered aloud how our time together might be made more &lt;em&gt;fun&lt;/em&gt;, to &lt;em&gt;naturally&lt;/em&gt; attract more members and others (friends, family members, decluttering buddies- and buddy prospects/candidates), some of you have stated &lt;em&gt;most emphatically&lt;/em&gt; that there is **&lt;em&gt;NOTHING**&lt;/em&gt; fun &lt;em&gt;whatsoever&lt;/em&gt; about decluttering!! &amp;nbsp;I respectfully would disagree: I have heard &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;great&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;satisfaction, delight, joy, and passion&amp;nbsp;welling from deep within members who&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;finally&lt;/em&gt; are&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;succeeding&lt;/em&gt; in their decluttering endeavors! This being the perennial season of Miracles and transformation, when all things can become new ... how about if we at least &lt;em&gt;consider&lt;/em&gt; changing our perspective of decluttering to one re-envisioning the &lt;em&gt;Possibilities?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So- how can we make exhilarating, even &lt;em&gt;breathtaking&lt;/em&gt;, breakthroughs possible for &lt;em&gt;many more&lt;/em&gt; of us? First, it might be great if we begin each meeting by re-envisioning and talking more about our &lt;em&gt;dreams&lt;/em&gt; that currently might seem to be blocked by clutter. For example, at one meeting, I noticed a member very intently scanning the Dating classifieds in a newspaper before our formal discussion began. As it turned out, during the meeting she determined that she really had&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;only a few hours&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;of decluttering left&amp;nbsp;to be done ... including her dining table, at which she said she might like to have more holiday dinner parties (apparently she's hosted parties of up to twelve guests- sounded like &lt;em&gt;great&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;fun, too!)- especially&amp;nbsp;to meet more single, mature Jewish men. (&lt;em&gt;So,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;in fact- any mature Single Jewish Men out there: you might want to identify yourselves here in a Comment below, for an invitation to a festive meal! As I recall, your hostess lives in the Metro West area.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, I am hereby opening this event's planning for&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;all of&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to input as you see fit- to mould this gathering into something that hopefully will be more beneficial to many more of our membership.&amp;nbsp;So- have an idea? Perhaps even a change to the date, time, or venue (location), at this early stage? If so, and if I can't come, I'll just RSVP so, and name you as the Event Host to run with the ball for this event (then I might set up another event in which I&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;participate).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DO INVITE A FRIEND(S!) who might benefit&lt;/strong&gt;, as well ...&amp;nbsp;ideally some Prospective Decluttering Buddy&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;that you know and trust already, perhaps to launch your joint project together&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;right there at our meeting, that night&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;- also to multiply our social Fun element! OR perhaps you will come away from our Meetup with an inspiring, reinvigorating &lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt; Decluttering Buddy(ies), or &lt;em&gt;ideas&lt;/em&gt; for buddies who live close to you or with whom you already associate otherwise, to help you steer into the weeks ahead with a clearer, more peaceful, restorative, and energizing living space! ...Whenever one of our events attracts a large group, we still&amp;nbsp;can get a lot done, perhaps by breaking into smaller groups - to derive benefit from&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;large and small groups. Larger numbers of meeting&amp;nbsp;participants can serve to motivate us more, validating with "social proof" the significance of our determination to take better control of our space and time - to achieve better focus on whatever&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;we most want&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to do with our lives in the time remaining to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our current venue,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Andala Coffee House&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;is across Franklin Street just behind the big, red-brick First Baptist Church at the intersection with River Street in the heart of Central Square, Cambridge ... photos, transit directions, and more information&amp;nbsp;are&amp;nbsp;here&amp;nbsp;on Yelp:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/andala-coffee-house-cambridge"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/andala-coffee-house-cambridge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Andala, we meet downstairs , where no background music is piped in, generally&amp;nbsp;(some music can just&amp;nbsp;be heard upstairs) - well suited to discussions and NLP demonstrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please arrive by 6:30 pm&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to order refreshments, ALSO ALLOWING EXTRA TIME TO FIND PARKING, if needed, in or near Central Square. Parking in a lot is available ONLY&amp;nbsp;in City Lots 4, 5 , and 6 ("back of Central Square") off Norfolk Street &amp;amp; Bishop Allen Drive -- but NOT in the private lot to the left of Harvest Co-op, i.e., off Essex Street, which is carefully monitored and ticketed ... meters in the city lots and on streets around Central Square operate until 6 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And while no purchase minimum for refreshments is specified by our host venue, &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;participants are encouraged to order something substantive to&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;support the business in appreciation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;of Management's permission to meet in their space&lt;/strong&gt;. Please also be advised that&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;commercial eating establishments generally cannot permit on-site consumption of refreshments brought in from elsewhere&lt;/em&gt;, due to liability concerns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;AGENDA&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Approximate)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30 pm- Order dinner&amp;nbsp;or other&amp;nbsp;refreshment: ~$2 for coffee, tea, or soda (and upward) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:00 pm- Celebration together of Decluttering&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Successes!!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:15 pm- Discussion: Your Dreams ... and&amp;nbsp;Decluttering as a Step Toward Them &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 8:45-9 pm- Wrap-up (feel free to leave, or to linger and chat after this point) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Notepad &amp;amp; pen or other note-taking device, calendar to schedule Action Items (next steps). Dress comfortably,&amp;nbsp;in layers (e.g., wear a sweater in case the restaurant is cooler than you'd prefer).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RECOMMENDED READING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Make Room for God: Clearing Out the Clutter&lt;/em&gt;, by Susan K. Rowland&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hung by the Tongue: What You Say is What You Get&lt;/em&gt;, by Francis P. Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Biology of Belief: Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter, &amp;amp; Miracles&lt;/em&gt;, by Bruce H. Lipton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get the Life You Want&lt;/em&gt;, by Richard Bandler&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Richard Bandler's Guide to Trance-formation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;EXCERPTS are provided&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;in previous Meetup descriptions, e.g., August 1, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MEETING FEE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The $5-per-person meeting fee (payable via PayPal, preferably, or in **CASH ONLY**&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;(NO CHECKS!)&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to Judy Stitt at the event&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;before presentation begins&lt;/em&gt;, please) helps to compensate (1) any main presenter for his or her time, training, and specialized knowledge generously shared with us, and gasoline for travel into town, and (2) the organizer(s) for time spent planning, administering, and coordinating events, and interfacing with members as needed - also to defray Meetup.com's monthly charge assessed organizers for this Web site and other resources to serve our group.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will set a Meetup tent-sign at our place, at least until the formal meeting begins at 7 pm</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323296175000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320763512000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Decluttering as A Step Toward Our Dreams</name><id>40400592</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323129600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/40400592/</event_url></item>