<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 West 87th Street</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10024</zip><lat>40.788380</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jazz on Amsterdam Avenue</name><city>New York</city><id>1518161</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.974525</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Even though the original RSVP deadine is past, it is still possible for folks to come on this trip.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ROOM IS BOOKED! Because this is the tail end of the school vacation and Easter weekend, the rooms were  filling up fast.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Room is booked for the people who RSVPed in time! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;We are staying at a brand-new hostel called "Jazz on Amsterdam Ave."  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jazzhostels.com/jazzamsterdam.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jazzhostels.com/jazzamsterdam.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jazzhostels.com/jazzamsterdam.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jazzhostels.com/jazzamsterdam.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jazzhostels.com/jazzamsterdam.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jazzhostels.com/jazzamsterdam.php&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;  It is part of the "Jazz" chain of hostels and is on the Upper West Side  in a nice area, accessible to the subway and lots of attractions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO JOIN US, &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;you need to make your own room reservation&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Contact the hostel directly (link is above!) We were able to get one room for the four of us, but there may be other rooms/beds available in the hostel...or you can check with Hosteling International which is in the same part of town: &lt;a href="http://www.hinewyork.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hinewyork.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hinewyork.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hinewyork.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you decide to join us, please RSVP "Yes" once you have booked your room/bed!&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Then you will get any emails about the trip as we get closer to the time.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TENTATIVE schedule&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday, April 22:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;11:30am: Take Megabus to NYC.  Approx cost: $40 RT  &lt;br /&gt;4:00pm: Arrive NYC.  Check into hostel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;NOTE: This is a hostel, NOT a hotel. That means bunk beds and a shared bath!&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;7:00pm: Head down to the East End for dinner. Excellent Mexican at www.hechoendumbo.com&amp;lrm; or Italian at www.cucinadipesce.com&amp;lrm;  &lt;br /&gt;10:30: Go see the NeoFuturists do their ever-changing show "Too Much Light Makes the Baby Go Blind."  This is a constantly changing show in which the actors attempt to perform 30 short plays in 60 minutes.  Live, raw and organic theater at it's best! Tickets are $11 plus the roll of a six sided die. ($12-$17).  Hard to explain, but I have seen it 4 times and it's been great every single time!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nyneofuturists.org/site/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nyneofutur" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nyneofutur" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nyneofutur" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nyneofutur" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nyneofutur&lt;/a&gt;...  &lt;br /&gt;After the show, go back to hostel and collapse.  Or go for a late-night drink or find some jazz in the East End.  NYC is the city that never sleeps, after all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, April 23:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Breakfast at the hostel or at any nearby deli!  &lt;br /&gt;10:00am: Get ourselves to the Metropolitan Opera House, where we can get standing room tix for the evening's performance of "Il Trovatore" Verdi's great tragic opera about kidnapping, enchantment, betrayal, love and murder.  (Typical opera, in other words!)  Price: $24.00 for orchestra standing room tickets.  &lt;br /&gt;After that, free time to explore the city.  Some folks might want go down to Battery Park and take the Staten Island Ferry (FREE) which gives a great view of the Statue of Liberty.  There is also a fantastic place on the lower East Side called the "Tenement Museum" which tells the stories (some very moving) of the immigrants who came to NYC at the turn of the century. &lt;a href="http://www.tenement.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tenement.o&lt;/a&gt;...  &lt;br /&gt;BROADWAY OPTION: If anyone wants to see a Broadway play, they can go down to the TKTS booth at Times Square which sells same-day half-price tickets to many current shows.  Price: Between $45 - $75 depending on the show.  &lt;br /&gt;5:30: Dinner, at a place TBD.  Price: Between $30 - $75 per person, depending on where we go and how much alcohol you drink!  Many places have really good "pre-theatre" deals.  &lt;br /&gt;8:00pm: OPERA!  Wear comfy shoes!  &lt;br /&gt;11:00pm: Back to the hostel or find a bar/jazz club/whatever suits your fancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday, April 22:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Breakfast, check out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11:00am: Easter Sunday...and lots of services to choose from (if you are so inclined!)&amp;nbsp; St Bart's Espiscopal has a wonderful atmosphere and terrific choir. &lt;a href="http://www.stbarts.org/&amp;amp;nbsp" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.stbarts.org/&amp;amp;nbsp" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.stbarts.org/&amp;amp;nbsp" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.stbarts.org/&amp;amp;nbsp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.stbarts.org/&amp;nbsp&lt;/a&gt;;;;;; There is also St Pat's on 5th Ave.&amp;nbsp; For those not interested in church, there are plenty of excellent Sunday brunches or, if it's a nice day, a walk in Central Park might be nice!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1:00pm Museum visit!&amp;nbsp; Guggenheim just opened several new exhibits and is a cool place.&amp;nbsp; Estimated price: $20 per person  &lt;br /&gt;4:00pm: Early supper at a burger joint or similar.  Price: $10 - $20  &lt;br /&gt;6:00pm: Board bus home!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total estimated cost per person: $300 (including both dinners, hostel, bus, opera and subway pass.  Broadway show and drinks, late-night entertainment and breakfasts are extra...)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone will be responsible for booking their own bus to NYC.   Final payment for hostel reservations will be due about 2 weeks before the trip for those who RSVPed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We will all try to meet for coffee a few weeks before the trip so we can get to know each other and chat about the schedule!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please email me with any questions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Start spreadin' the news..."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meeting place TBD</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303773693000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295743974000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New York City weekend "on the cheap!"</name><id>16148356</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303488000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/16148356/</event_url></item>