<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>118 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.367222</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Bodymind Integration Center</name><city>Watertown</city><id>725562</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.187240</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This evening is run jointly with HOLISTIC-HEALTH-SPEAKER-SERIES.  You can sign up here or at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/HOLISTIC-HEALTH-SPEAKER-SERIES-AND-STUDY-GROUP/calendar/14332471/?from=list&amp;amp;offset=0"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Become &amp;quot;Energy Intelligent&amp;quot;!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~ We all use our five senses to perceive the world around us, and to help us make choices. Yuliya Cohen, tonight’s teacher, is a pioneering energy researcher Yuliya Cohen, and will teach us how to perceive the world through the energetic membrane of our biofield.&lt;br /&gt;Gaining mastery of your biofield raises your &amp;quot;Energy Intelligence&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;E.Q.,&amp;quot; which is different from your I.Q.. Learning techniques that Yuliya teaches can:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Help you step into your power and the fullness of your being&lt;br /&gt;• Give you a sense of belonging and connection&lt;br /&gt;• Heal even chronic illness and trauma and restore your natural immunity&lt;br /&gt;• Make you happier by helping you benefit from any situation&lt;br /&gt;• Decrease stress&lt;br /&gt;• Create harmonious relationships and deep intimacy&lt;br /&gt;• Help you understand why some people are easy to connect with, while other are difficult, and what to do about it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yuliya writes, “The time has come to recognize that our experiences are shaped through the complex interactions of interdependent energy fields--not just through the mechanisms of the brain. You simply cannot understand human experiences without understanding the power and intelligence of the human biofield—and if you get to know your own biofield, you will experience life on this planet as much more fun, and you will come from a more knowledgeable and empowered place. It can also make a huge difference in the quality of your relationships!&lt;br /&gt;“During this evening’s experience, you will discover that the energy field is essentially what gives us life. Both personal and universal in nature, this fundamental structure is there to assist you in exploring your individual path for your soul's journey.”&lt;br /&gt;Yuliya adds that her techniques help alleviate many undesirable conditions, and “they eliminate psychological traumas in particular with an efficiency and speed far superior to conventional treatments.”&lt;br /&gt;This class will be eye-opening for some. I think it will be of great use to anyone wishing to heal a specific condition, and also for anyone who just wants to gain &amp;quot;Energy Intelligence&amp;quot; -- i.e., have greater knowledge of universal laws and structures and greater ability to enjoy life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Paul G., your host&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. Yuliya's original title for this class was &amp;quot;Knowing and Using Your Biofield: A New Paradigm in Effortless Healing.&amp;quot; I asked Yuliya why she calls her healing “effortless.” She replied that activating your biofield membrane sets up your energetic boundary. That membrane keeps you safe and protected in the world. When the biofield membrane is activated, then (just as in cellular communications) nature and the universe take over, your mind gets a break, and being and healing becomes virtually effortless.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~Yuliya Cohen is a trained energy healer, medical intuitive, and Energy Psychology therapist and researcher. She was an engineer and computer science researcher in Russia, moved to the U.S., and for the last 25 years, has applied the scientific method to her bioenergetic field research. She is someone who believes many “new age” concepts, but she got to those beliefs through the scientific method!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She has generated a unified system of energy field principles that have been successfully applied by thousands of clients and healing professionals throughout the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yuliya is the founder of the Energy Restructuring Institute; the creator of the Energy Restructuring™ System; and has been on the faculty at the New England School of Acupuncture. She has presented at the Kripalu Yoga Center in Western Massachusetts, the Osher Institute at Harvard Medical School, and other educational and research institutions. Yuliya also presented at the Association for Comprehensive Energy Psychology (ASEP), the Canadian Association for Integrative and Energy Therapies (CAIET), and The International Society for the Study of Subtle Energies and Energy Medicine (ISSSEEM).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She offers a wide range of lectures, workshops, and training based on her experiences as an Energy Psychology researcher and on the innovative principles described in her Energy Psychology textbook, “Energetic Boundaries: The New Paradigm for Healing Without Effort.”&lt;br /&gt;You can read more about Yuliya at www.healingwithouteffort.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282228749000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281064160000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Knowing and Using Your Biofield</name><id>14336475</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282086900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/14336475/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/6/global_11525046.jpeg</photo_url></item>