<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Cummings Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.560047</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cummings Center</name><city>Beverly</city><id>943062</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887695</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This route will lead us through 4 different state parks or forests along wooded and secluded roads, through historic town centers and into West Newbury where a newly identified nesting pair of &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/?pageID=eoeeapressrelease&amp;amp;L=1&amp;amp;L0=Home&amp;amp;sid=Eoeea&amp;amp;b=pressrelease&amp;amp;f=100601_pr_band_eagle&amp;amp;csid=Eoeea" target="_blank"&gt;Bald Eagles&lt;/a&gt; has been seen.  Our route takes us past several bodies of water with open sky line views and perhaps just maybe we may be able to steal a glimpse of the birds.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginning in Beverly at the Cummings center on route 62 (Elliot St) near the Balch street entrances at the back of the campus we'll head north along roads generally parallel to route 1A through the towns of Wenham, Ipswich and Rowley.  We'll pass through the Parker River marshes on our way into Newbury and Newburyport then turn west and southerly toward West Newbury and Byfield.  Past several reservoirs and through shady lanes we'll keep an eye (and ear) out for those birds.  We'll stop for lunch at a little variety store on Main street in Byfield (mile 39 or so) then head south again into the shade of the Georgetown-Rowley state forest.  Passing through Topsfield center on our way back to Beverly along route 97.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a &lt;a href="http://www.mapmyride.com/ride/united-states/ma/beverly/375127690826343025" target="_blank"&gt;route map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be aiming for an average pace of 14-15 mph so I would expect to finish this in about 6-6.5 hours depending on the length and frequency of stops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things to bring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A bike (road, hybrid whatever you can keep the pace on) and helmet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A spare tube and patch kit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Water or sports drink and plenty of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Energy snacks/Cliff bars or similar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Money for lunch, water, etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunblock.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cummings Center is located on route 62 (Elliot street) in Beverly and is about a 5 min pedal north of the Beverly commuter rail station.  Feel free to contact me with questions or comments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing lots of you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Dan&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan</member_name><member_id>11982073</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287357869000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284228364000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>62 Mile Beverly - Newburyport Loop</name><id>14735094</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287322200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/14735094/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/7/global_17076615.jpeg</photo_url></item>