<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>320 Congress Street, 1st floor (corner of Sleeper and Congress)</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.358429</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cantina</name><city>Boston</city><id>11812262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059776</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For our first meetup of the year, several of our members have graciously volunteered to show us their recent Grails related projects:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you let people browse 1000 possible trips quickly and intuitively… while being bookmarkable and SEO-friendly? Jeff Winkler will present on building a great user experience... serving pages in 100 milliseconds using vanilla GSPs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ben Duong and his team have a problem with bloated repos. He has created a Grails app that monitors the size of a git repository on a per commit basis. A small UI sits on top that shows the size of each directory over the time of the commits, which allows his team to rapidly check how their efforts in reducing repository size are coming and also allows us to track down commits that bloat our repo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julian Flaks will demonstrate a social site focused on Action Sports and the Outdoors, whose server side is completely Grails based. The functionality that he will be focus on includes: content posting, endless scrolling UI screens, and social notifications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's always interesting to see what others are working on and the techniques they've used to solve their problems. I hope to see you all there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, this time we'll have a change of scenery: Cantina has moved offices! We're now located by the Children's Museum in the Innovation district. It's located at the corner of Sleeper and Congress Streets and is near South Station.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Pember</member_name><member_id>9587085</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365041438000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Grails-Boston</urlname><id>1458975</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Grails Users' Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361245310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grails Demonstrations: What we've been working on</name><id>105281702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362010500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Grails-Boston/events/105281702/</event_url></item>