<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>299.989990234</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Introduction to Digital Photography&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This class is for beginners through intermediate photographers. Any digital camera is fine for this class, however, DSLR's will have more of the features discussed in some classes. The 8 lessons listed below take nine hours to complete plus time for image review.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an added value you don't have to worry about taking notes in class because you will have access to my online training website called &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.morethanasnapshot.com/"&gt;morethanasnapshot.com,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in which you will have access to videos of all the lessons plus practice activities for you do do at home.  This is a $200 value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 1: Getting to Know Your Digital Camera &lt;br /&gt;

 Understanding your camera controls and functions. The five most valuable features. Features to avoid. Checklist of what your camera can and cannot do. How to get the most out of your digital camera. The biggest advantage of shooting digital: the right way to use your LCD monitor. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Use Dpreview to compare your camera to 2 others in its class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 2: File Formats and Quality Settings &lt;br /&gt;

 JPEG and other in-camera options such as Raw and TIFF: pros and cons of each shooting format. Tips on shooting with RAW capture and image conversion. Storage and memory issues - doing digital photography on the road. Why you should convert your JPEG pics to TIFF format in the computer. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: JPEG A JPEG That Has Been JPEG'ed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 3: Introduction to Image Enhancing Software &lt;br /&gt;

 Adjusting brightness, contrast, color balance, color saturation and sharpness in a few steps. Introduction to image correction with RAW converter software. And a bonus: a brief introduction to software for making long panoramic images from several photos made for exactly this purpose. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Correct a Technically Poor Image in Under 60 seconds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 4: Controlling White Balance and Other Aspects, In-Camera &lt;br /&gt;

 The color of light for the non-physics major. Understanding the white balance options. The easy way to getting the correct white balance. Adjusting the in-camera level for sharpening and color saturation. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: White Balance Before and After; also, Saturation/Sharpness Before and After&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 5: Composition, Tripods and Lens Choice &lt;br /&gt;

 Principles of visual design. Putting the Rule of Thirds to good use. An easy way to understand the Golden Rectangle. Shooting vertical as well as horizontal photos. Understanding lens focal lengths. Wide angle and telephoto options with digital SLR "focal length magnification factors". &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Rule of Thirds/Orientation: Before and After&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 6: Digital Exposure 101 &lt;br /&gt;

 The primary exposure concepts. Why cameras sometimes make images that are too dark. Using Exposure Compensation, a simple method for perfect exposures. Learn where to meter from and use Exposure Lock. The part ISO plays in exposure. Tip: Use a Semi Automatic mode while maintaining full control. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Exposure: Over, Under and Just Right / Create and HDR image&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 7: Creative Control of Apertures (f/stops) and Shutter Speeds &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn "depth of field" and motion control with aperture and shutter speed selection, using the camera's automatic and semi-automatic modes. A primer on depth of field. Prevent blurring from camera shake and subject movement. Great news about exposure when changing f/stops or shutter speeds in certain camera modes. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Aperture/Depth of Field Control; also, Shutter Speed/Motion Control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 8: Exposure Evaluation and Low-Light Photography &lt;br /&gt;

 Using the camera's histogram (and "loss of highlight detail warning") to evaluate exposure and contrast. The challenges and compromises of night photography. ISO Equivalents - changing ISO on the fly. Minimizing digital noise (graininess). Shooting at night - with and without a tripod. Making beautiful images in low light. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Night Shoot - Before and After; also, High Contrast vs. Low Contrast&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please enter the front door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary</member_name><member_id>7489043</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357700502000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1534645</id><group_lat>41.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6600036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294885063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Digital Photography (5 - 2 hour classes)</name><id>hpcgqyrcblb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357689600000</time><rsvp_limit>3</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Photography-Workshops/events/95380532/</event_url></item>