<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MODIFICATION TO MEETUP - &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;meetup starts at 1PM!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; (alternative in case of a large turnout in original meetup below).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BECAUSE OF THE LARGE TURNOUT, AND WE JUST GOT A GIG FOR A VALENTINE'S DANCE HAITI BENEFIT WE NEED TO REHEARSE FOR - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEETUP WILL HAVE TWO PARTS: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1)  Regular meetup for everyone starting at 1PM  &lt;br /&gt;2)  Rehearsal for Haiti Benefit for participants starting around 4PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for any inconvenience, but part of the goal of the group is to get out and play, and this is a great opportunity - and the gig is a week away!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;We will have another Jam/rehearsal session this Sunday Feb 7th &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt; 1PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, I auditioned for and am now the keyboard player of the House Band of an Open Mike at a local Nitespot.  Once things are settled in, in about two weeks, I will make it a weekly meetup, so you can come out &amp;amp; play.  It's low pressure, but start practicing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Agenda of the meetups are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Record a CD of originals &amp;amp; possibly covers. &lt;br /&gt;2) As soon as we have enough material rehearsed, we will have a local show. &lt;br /&gt;3) We will also be going to open Mikes in the meantime. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will sequence the agenda based on interests, so please answer questions on your interests &amp;amp; goals.  If there are lot of people, we will split the group into two, Group 1 from approx. 1PM until 4, and group to from approximately 4 until 7PM.  Approximately is the operative word...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also Important:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Dance Party to Benefit HAITI Relief&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valentine’s Day and the To Haiti with Love fundraiser can be a fantastic memory. Money – lots and lots of money will be on the way to Haiti with your help&lt;br /&gt;Do you know haw many 10 thousands of orphans are in Haiti now because of the quake?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to go to dance or volunteer, email:&lt;br /&gt;Nancy M. McCabe &lt;br /&gt;I will check to see if there is any way we could play some music there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nancy McCabe, Event Coordinator 617.549.3152&lt;br /&gt;To HAITI with LOVE&lt;br /&gt;A Dance Party to Benefit HAITI Relief&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE HELP US SPREAD THE WORD &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, Feb 13 7:30 - 10 PM&lt;br /&gt;$20 Adults, $12 Students&lt;br /&gt;First Church UU &lt;br /&gt;404 Concord Avenue, Belmont &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265738999000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265100761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jam Rehearsal Recording Session #5</name><id>12494150</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265565600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/12494150/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>