<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>115 State Street</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05602</zip><lat>44.262577</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Vermont State House</name><city>Montpelier</city><id>833439</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.580520</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>When:  January 9, 2010 from 10 am to 1 pm (open to the public) and 1 pm to 4 pm (members only)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Where: Vermont State House, State Street, Montpelier, VT&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Who:  Liberty lovers from Vermont, members and friends alike.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;What:  Join us in this celebration of the Campaign's Core beliefs in Liberty, Fiscal Responsibility, Limited Government, and Free Markets.  During the Members meeting we will discuss plans for 2010 and discuss the future focus and direction for the Vermont Campaign.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Who:  speakers at this convention include:&lt;br /&gt;            Campaign members: Jessica Bernier, Matt Cropp, Audrey Pietrucha, and Maurice Kinney.&lt;br /&gt;            Guest Speakers: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Tom Licata from Vermonters for Economic Health (discussing the coming fiscal train wreck this coming legislative session)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pasha Roberts from Linepoint LLC (discussing his production company's latest effort an animated, liberty-oriented film)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Peter Orcetti, blogger, journalist, and Campaign member (discussing the role of alternative media on today's political environment)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Finally, Campaign and Liberty Alliance activists from around New England:&lt;br /&gt;Jim Azzola from Connecticut's Campaign for Liberty and Liberty Forum.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Chris Lawless from New Hampshire's Campaign for Liberty, NHLA and the Free State Project&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;David Kopacz from MA Tea Party and MassLPA.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please note that &amp;quot;membership&amp;quot; is defined as holding an on-line account with the Vermont Campaign for Liberty through the National Campaign's website.  If you are email only and don't have an account, please consider joining.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Steven J. Howard&lt;br /&gt;Interim State Coordinator&lt;br /&gt;Vermont Campaign for Liberty&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>go to the second floor.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263222579000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260394758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2010 Vermont Campaign for Liberty Convention</name><id>12054215</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263049200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/12054215/</event_url></item>