<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Okay, I'm going to give this event organizing thing a shot and see if I can get some Meetup people to join me and some Meetin folks for some indoor paintball action.  It should be a good time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some things you should know: COST: $30 Per Person for Paintball.  Obviously, this is going to be a road trip, so if you need a ride or can give a ride, please post that when you RSVP. I've reserved a party room for us, and we'll have a host. From what I understand, this will serve several purposes: for those that haven't played, he'll give us some guidance; we'll watch a short video; and most importantly, we'll have a party room for 3 hours, so we can bring drinks (no alcohol, unfortunately), food, and have a good old time. If you're worried about ruining your clothes, the paint will wash out, but you can buy a disposable camouflage suit for $5, or I'd suggest bringing a change of clothes. The paint might sting, depending on where you're hit, but you'll have a chest protector, goggles, and you'll be wearing a helmet. According to insurance statistics, more people have been hurt golfing or fishing than playing paintball. You should wear comfortable, loose fitting clothing and athletic shoes. Also, please go to the web site before the event, download the waiver, and sign it. This will speed up the sign in process. I'm probably missing something, but it's a good start anyway. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start the group at 10, and if there's enough interest, we'll go higher. So sign up early and sign up often: you'll be glad you did.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside near the registration area</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205174795000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>You'll have a blast!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203092929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indoor Paintball: Woburn</name><id>7336637</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1205001900000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/7336637/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/2/global_2186386.jpeg</photo_url></item>