<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>210 South Street, Unit 5-1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.349743</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bob French's place</name><city>Boston</city><id>432243</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057630</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Boston Tea Party&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I have secured the Fanueil Hall venue for the December 16th Tea Party Rally.  The hall seat s about 800 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are guaranteed access from 3:00 pm to 6:00 pm, but will most likely be able to start earlier,I will have that confirmation by Monday.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am calling for another meetup to finalize all plans and ideas for this event. Bob French has generously agreed to lend the use of his apt for this on Monday the 26th starting at 6:30 pm. 210 South St Apt 501.&lt;br /&gt;Please attend this meetup if you are willing to take on a task for this event. Feel free to add to or comment on the following ideas.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I want to set the bar high for this event, but also want to keep all ideas realistic, so if you have one, please do the homework first and then present your ideas.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I will be away from my emails from Thursday until Saturday evening, &lt;br /&gt;but please feel free to call me. 508-930-5530&lt;br /&gt;We need to act on this plan ASAP as time is very tight&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Speakers:&lt;br /&gt;Joe has contacted HQ to see if Rand Paul could attend and/or if Ron would do a live video feed. (We need a tech guru to lead the set up for live video feed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; If anyone from the group would speak at this rally, please step forward.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Anyone know of other speakers that would attend please contact them.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Advertisement:&lt;br /&gt;I have contacted the graphics guru that created the Boston Tea Party page to see if he would draft a similar graphic as an invitation for the event.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This could also be used as an ad in the Boston Globe and/or other circulations.&lt;br /&gt;(Need a media coordinator to maximize the press coverageand generous donors to sponsor ads)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Radio: need ad and costs&lt;br /&gt;Flyers: posting the event throughout Boston&lt;br /&gt;Facebook ?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Media coverage:&lt;br /&gt;Live web cast of event &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Contact CNN, FOX, Globe, etc?.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Extras:&lt;br /&gt;Balloon &lt;br /&gt;Tea Bags ? Stephanie is ordering 1000.&lt;br /&gt;M&amp;amp;M?s  - red, white &amp;amp; blue with Ron Paul message on them.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Entertainment;&lt;br /&gt;We are looking for famous artists, (1 is plenty), that could attend and play a few songs and speak in support of Ron. Approximately 15 ? 20 minutes (acoustical preferred)&lt;br /&gt;I contacted John Mayer and hope he responds&lt;br /&gt;All ideas are encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;Reenactment: We could perform a symbolic dumping of tea into the harbor with participants stating what liberty infringement or TAX is being dumped.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cost:&lt;br /&gt;The Hall - $800.00 for 4hrs&lt;br /&gt;Insurance and police - $150.00/ hr or $500.00 total&lt;br /&gt;Big helium balloon ? roughly $500.00 ? $600.00 including helium ? need to make a sign to hang from it.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Advertising? Depends what we want to accomplish and can afford.&lt;br /&gt;We could start a chipin, but realistically we need someone willing to fund this event without the hassle of trying to raise the needed cash in such a short time frame.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Thanks&lt;br /&gt;Bob Dwyer&lt;br /&gt;508-930-5530&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ureneck</member_name><member_id>4211251</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196292650000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195691948000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Tea Party Fanueil Hall Planning Meeting </name><id>6785213</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196119800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/6785213/</event_url></item>