<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Function Room, Second Floor</address_2><address_1>2 Clocktower Place</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.759793</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Clocktower Place</name><city>Nashua</city><id>1018143</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.469199</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The amazing raw duo Angela Stokes-Monarch and Matt Monarch are going to be at the Nashua Raw Vegan meetup in August!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meet-up starts at 6pm and talks will begin between at about 6:45 so please arrive on time to mingle, meet the dynamic duo and to not miss a moment of the talk!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is NOT a raw food pot luck so you do not need to bring any dishes to this event. Food will not be served so you'll probably want to eat something before you come or bring a snack with you. Also, raw food products will be on sale so feel free try something new and to munch out during the talks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not familiar with Matt and Angela, they are 2 of the most prominent raw foodists out there spreading their wealth of knowledge and inspiration. Angela once weighed 300 pounds and lost about half her weight on the raw food diet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are their websites: www.rawreform.com and www.rawsuccess.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are new to the raw vegan lifestyle, this is a great meeting to learn more about it. If you are seasoned, this is a great meetup to meet others into this lifestyle and to just have a fun, inspiring evening with 2 people who have touched and helped so many people. And maybe we'll learn a thing or 2 :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a charge of $15 that fully goes to Matt and Angela. Also, they will be selling some yummy raw products!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to see you soon! Hope you can make it. Please spread the word to others that may be interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what will be discussed that evening:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Monarch, author of ‘Raw Spirit’ &amp;amp; 'Raw Success' and Raw Food Educator has been eating 100% raw for nearly 10 years now. You can learn more about him at www.rawsuccess.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this talk he discusses:&lt;br /&gt;# Is the Raw Food Diet for you?&lt;br /&gt;# Overcoming Health Challenges&lt;br /&gt;# Why some diets work and some don’t&lt;br /&gt;# Difficulties that may arise on your journey&lt;br /&gt;# Benefits of eating Raw Foods, juicing and colonics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angela Stokes lost over 150lbs and overcame morbid obesity with a raw food lifestyle. She runs www.rawreform.com and is visiting from the UK to share her message of natural recovery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She speaks about:&lt;br /&gt;# Healthy, rapid weight loss&lt;br /&gt;# How to break overeating patterns&lt;br /&gt;# Balancing detox with slimming&lt;br /&gt;# Taking care of the body naturally&lt;br /&gt;# Addressing the underlying issues&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249750414000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248271293000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Angela Stokes &amp; Matt Monarch</name><id>10931952</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249509600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/10931952/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/c/global_9807004.jpeg</photo_url></item>