<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I would enjoy company on Election Eve to either Celebrate or Commiserate. After living in Florida during elections in 2000 and stuck working in Nashville (a blue county in a red sea) in 2004, I'm now ecstatic to be north-coastal New England. And now how exciting that the electorate map has the potential to be drastically altered from the recent past. If you've been biting your nails and obsessed with this election as much as I have been, and want to share in watching the results please join in. My bumper sticker says &amp;quot;Got Hope?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My tv watching room is small but friendly/cozy. If you aren't opposed to the potential of a cushion on the floor when the standard seats run out, please stop by. It's a work night but bring what you'd like to drink (please drink responsibly). Will we need champagne?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Malyna for inviting me to be a co-organizer for this group. It's been really great meeting everyone and I look forward to more opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. If you have pet allergies, this is probably not for you. sorry:(&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A NICE SITE FULL OF GREAT POSTERS &lt;a href="http://www.designforobama.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.designforo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226681025000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224637497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Election Eve – Results Watching Party</name><id>9006993</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225845000000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/9006993/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/3/global_3163235.jpeg</photo_url></item>