<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I want to be very clear on this - I'm having a meeting on August 23 at Music Together in Yarmouth and I am going to keep the meeting at Borders at the Maine Mall on August 24 at 7 pm.  I will work for next month to find a more stable place to have the second meeting.  I'm hoping to have two meetings a month in order to accomodate as many people as possible.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again I want to mention to anyone that is coming that I'm going to ask everyone to tell how they learned about the Law of attraction, what book or movies they've partaken of, and any organizations that teach the LOA that they've belonged to.  I also thought that it would be fun to share any experiences that we've had when we were able to purposely use the LOA  for our own benefit.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also asked in the other meetup scheduling that everyone donate a dollar or two to help pay for the cost that the Organizer must pay in order to organize the meeting (seems kind of strange to me, as you have to do all the work to setup the meetings and run them, etc. etc. and then you have to pay to do that too - actually it's kind of comical, as it's the first time I've ever paid money in order for me to do work.)   This maybe why you've had problems with people wanting to take the Organizer position.  - Ha! Ha!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also mentioned in the last meetup scheduling that I teach the Science of the Law of Attraction at Portland Adult Education, as well as privately and also run a support group for my students that have taken my class.  This is one of the reasons why I felt that I should step up and be the organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am really looking forward to meeting like-minded people on Monday and Tuesday evenings. I send my best wishes to all and hope to see you soon,  Cheryl&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282776085000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>MegaMagnets</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PLOAConnection</urlname><id>1426391</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Laws of Attraction Connection</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282402161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland  Law of Attraction Connection</name><id>14493417</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282690800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PLOAConnection/events/14493417/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/5/global_14523685.jpeg</photo_url></item>