<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Independence Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.603863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-256-0800</phone><name>Radisson Chelmsford</name><city>Chelmsford</city><id>1237113</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.346352</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>That's what Jody Marchand must do after her tragic ordeal...this is a fundraiser for healing. &lt;br /&gt;read her story below...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When and Where: &lt;br /&gt;Friday, October 1, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;6:00 - 10:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;Radisson Hotel &lt;br /&gt;10 Independence Drive &lt;br /&gt;Chelmsford, MA 01824 &lt;br /&gt;Tickets: $10 each &lt;br /&gt;Friends P Live Music &lt;br /&gt;Raffles P Food &lt;br /&gt;Tickets are available at the &lt;br /&gt;Northeast Association of REALTORS® &lt;br /&gt;3 Courthouse Lane #9 Chelmsford &lt;br /&gt;and The Owl Diner, 244 Appleton Street, Lowell &lt;br /&gt;For more info, call 978-458-2901&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a tragic moment of domestic violence, &lt;br /&gt;Jody Marchand was shot in her Westford &lt;br /&gt;home by her husband, who also shot and &lt;br /&gt;killed their daughter Olivia (aka Liv). &lt;br /&gt;Jody miraculously survived the ordeal, &lt;br /&gt;though the pain of the loss of her &lt;br /&gt;beautiful, loving daughter has been &lt;br /&gt;immeasurable. Her will to keep going and &lt;br /&gt;her perseverance are an inspiration to &lt;br /&gt;many of us and she is in need of physical &lt;br /&gt;and spiritual healing. &lt;br /&gt;Proceeds from this fundraiser benefit the &lt;br /&gt;Live for Liv Foundation, established to &lt;br /&gt;support Jody Marchand during her long &lt;br /&gt;road to recovery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have tickets for purchase at the meetups I attend, tomorrow at the Princeton Station, being the first night. You may also buy them at the NE Realtors office as noted above, but please let me know if you do, so I can get a count and maybe I can round up tables for us. I might call the office and ask them to keep a count, if they can, if you say your with meetup. The tickets will go fast. &lt;br /&gt;This was a very sad occurrence, and I know I can count on my friends to support such a worthy cause, we go out together all the time anyway...what a great reason for us this time :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also have &amp;quot;Live for Liv&amp;quot; bracelets at $5 each. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also sponsor the event, check out the website at www.liveforliv.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286190954000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280976612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live for 'Liv' Benefit :)</name><id>14325003</id><headcount>400</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285970400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/14325003/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/a/global_16961514.jpeg</photo_url></item>