<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Enjoy a cozy evening at Patti's place for an International Wine Tasting Party! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beth DeGeer, a Wine Connoisseur, from Wallingford Center Street Wine &amp;amp; Spirits, will guide us through the Tasting. There will be 6 white and red flights from various regions of the world. Beth will also be available to answer questions on your favorite wines!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These wines will also pair well with tasty appetizers and finish with a fantastic chocolate fountain and fruit tasting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tasting: 6:00-8:00pm - Tasting starts at 6:15pm &lt;br /&gt;Post Tasting: 8-11pm - Enjoy your favorite wine with fresh pizza delivered while playing silly Board Games &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost is $20.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Appetizers will include: &lt;br /&gt;Various Cheeses &amp;amp; breads &lt;br /&gt;Stuffed olives &lt;br /&gt;Grapes &lt;br /&gt;Chicken Skewers &lt;br /&gt;Steak Skewers &lt;br /&gt;Cheese Ravioli &lt;br /&gt;Italian Salami &lt;br /&gt;Chocolate fountain &amp;amp; fresh fruit/marshmallows &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wines - Pairing with Appetizers &lt;br /&gt;2008 Chateau St Michelle Riesling - Columbia Valley - CA &lt;br /&gt;2008 Gavi Di Gavi - White - Villa Rosa - Italy &lt;br /&gt;2008 Kanu Chenin Blanc - Stellenbosch - South Africa &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wines - Pairing with Chocolates &lt;br /&gt;2006 Monte Antico Toscana - Red Blend - Tuscan - Italy &lt;br /&gt;2008 Maipe Malbec - Mendoza, Argentina &lt;br /&gt;2006 Echelon - Pinot Noir - France &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miss Kitty &amp;amp; Kewpie will be offering 2 wines for the group to enjoy! If anyone has a wine they would like to bring and share feel free to let Patti know... &lt;br /&gt;1987 Porto Kopke Colheita &lt;br /&gt;2008 Stump Jump - Red - Australian &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things to bring: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wine Glass &amp;amp; wine charm or a way to identify your glass throughout the night. &lt;br /&gt;An extra folding chair. Keep in your car in case you need it. &lt;br /&gt;Your favorite Board Game. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual...you can pay online at Have Fun, Will Travel meetup site, if you are a member of that group. Otherwise you can pay by check to Terri Bruno, 319 Todd Road, Wolcott, CT 06716. All checks must be received by January 11th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI...Center Street Wine &amp;amp; Spirits offers Friday Night Wine Tastings between 4:00-8:00pm. They are located at 382 Center Street in Wallingford! Beth hopes to see you there sometime!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Address will be sent via email to attendees prior to event</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263855959000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261450073000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>International Wine Tasting and Party!</name><id>12129468</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263682800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/12129468/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/3/global_12354643.jpeg</photo_url></item>