<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Burlington</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01890</zip><lat>42.449940</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borders Bookstore</name><city>Winchester</city><id>439938</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.149990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>THE TWELVE WEEKS OF WINTER COUNT-DOWN  EVENT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: The Mill Restaurant Tavern, Westminster, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: 2 hours starting at the posted time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE TO MEET: At the posted time, with 1/2 hour leeway for late-comers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Route 2 west to route 140. You'll see a small sign beforehand on your right signalling The Mill. Off the exit ramp, take a left and go 1/2 mile. It's on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE SCENE: The Mill restaurant, though surprisingly little known, is probably the quaintest, yet affordable, restaurants in greater Boston. A restored mill with duck pond, covered bridge, waterfall and stream right there in front of you. All that, but in December the place is decorated for the holidays and is redolent of smokey fireplaces. Game plan is to meet and paint in the tavern and optionally eat upstairs. Prices are to fit all budgets and dress is casual.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OTHER:&lt;br /&gt; IF LOST: If you become lost getting there, call.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; MEDIA: Unless you are accustomed to painting indoors in crowded conditions, it is recommended you stick to dry and/or simple media. Oils are not recommended because of their residue and fumes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Emerald&lt;br /&gt;617/968-0627&lt;br /&gt;westpointusma@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Emerald, CFA</member_name><member_id>3007793</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542725000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>painter-84</urlname><id>576650</id><group_lat>42.4500007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Plein Air Artists Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196888559000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>12 WEEKS OF WINTER COUNTDOWN: The Mill Restaurant, Westminster</name><id>6862792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197140400000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/painter-84/events/6862792/</event_url></item>