<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I chose 12 pm in hopes to beat the traffick of the usual 1 pm time for events, wether it helps, dont know..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVERYONE: PLEASE PARK CONSCIENTIOUSLY SINCE THERE ARE MORE THAN I THOUGH INTERESTED IN THIS TRIP, DOUBBLE PARK WITH FELLOW MEMBERS IF POSSIBLE AND LEAVE A PATH FOR THE WALKERS AND BIKERS WHO USE THE TRAIL. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OH AND PLEASE PRINT THE MAP OF THE ISLANDS FROM THE LINK BELOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is beach traffick we will all most likely hit it and we will waite a while longer before heading out on the water..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Saturday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 75. North wind around 7 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: N wind around 6 kt becoming SSW in the afternoon. Mostly sunny. Seas around 1 ft.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Thimbull I-lands are an interesting place to have a relaxing slow paddle and will be an all day event checking out as many places as we can fit in, a stop on one or two islands are possible for snacking.&lt;br /&gt;But i have to verify which ones are allowed on this day.. I know Outer Island is OK and that is on the destination for the snack if you all can make it out that far....or you may be the sharks snack..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have a special GPS which identifies the islands by name, nav aids, and all tracking info for a smoothe and worry less day on the water with way points and an easier return to our start point.&lt;br /&gt;But if most of you have the map of the islands its going to be easy anyway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Branford, Branford River (close enough) starting with September 5, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa   5     High  12:01 AM     6.2   6:22 AM     Set  7:19 AM      99&lt;br /&gt;     5      Low   6:03 AM     0.2   7:17 PM    Rise  7:26 PM&lt;br /&gt;     5     High  12:19 PM     6.4&lt;br /&gt;     5      Low   6:25 PM     0.3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is good, we will have an easier time getting in the water..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course Rain, high winds or bad weather cancels this event but closer to the time i will update on tides, and other weather factors and a final decision will be made about 10 am the day of the event if there is a possibility of bad conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An overcast day is fine for us and will reduce beach attendance so that part of traffic will be reduced although a bit more boat traffic may occur.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please have spare water, a hat, sunglasses, sunscreen, gloves, life jacket, whistle, and if possible, a paddle float &amp;amp; pump in case you go in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a secluded parking area which is not that near the center of Stony Creek (The Ball Field &amp;amp; old Trolly Track &amp;quot;Future new put in also&amp;quot; path to the water is OK for us, but you have to do a bit of Portage, we will help each other so dont worry, its only 150 paces..)  the Stony Creek area  is not recommended for a group our size and the local residents resent us for taking up any parking in town all day..so if you want to try the town dock/launch and park near by on some side street go ahead..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;further info on the parking area are :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lisrc.uconn.edu/coastalaccess/site.asp?siteid=694" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lisrc.ucon...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a map of the Islands use this link, If you cant make my event check out CT Costal Kayak tours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctcoastalkayaking.com/files/thimbletour.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctcoastalk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traffick avoidance Driving Directions will be added soon as i am done reviewing the possibility of higher than normal beach traffic and developing alternate routes which seem to avoid that traffick so we can avoid the problem spots.&lt;br /&gt;But use your GPS and other mapping software for your particular start locations and roots..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think rte 91 south to maybe rte 22 is an alternate at this time..&lt;br /&gt;but 91s-95n is still shortest ?????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;From the Exit for Leetes Island rd (Exit # 56) follow  the road to Thimball Island road,&lt;br /&gt;follow the road down towards the center of Stony Creek,&lt;br /&gt;as soon as you go under the rail bridge take the next right turn street (West Point Road &amp;amp; Ball Field), go strait to the ball field parking lot..there is enough places for about 30 cars if possible keep em tight since there may be more than 30, dont know..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics on maybe 1 to 2 or so foot waves..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 20 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this ocean all day trip and new carbon paddles &amp;amp; paddle leaches..Now All Kayaks come with &amp;quot;Yakpads&amp;quot; brand Gel High Back Seats also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ya wont get that from your local Rent-A-Yak places..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub, Recreational Kayak with Werner Carbon Kaliste Paddle= Pungo 12' with flotation bags installed=   al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper, Short Sea Kayak = Riot Tourlite 15' with Fiberglass Werner Camano or Greenland wood paddle=     Elaine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna, Long SOT Sea Kayak with Werner Carbon  Kaliste Paddle= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', =  Alex &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner, Long sea Kayak with Werner Carbon  Kaliste Paddle= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'=    Durelle or Susanne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenlander, Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Werner Fiberglass  Camano Paddle or Greenland wood Paddle= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= Durelle or Susanne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because the potential for falling in on this trip is higher than most trips, i can only rent to those that have  actual familiarity with the boat asked for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BARBIE-q SPOT IS 7 FALLS Stat Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use # 1 Saybrook Rd Higganum CT for destination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Easiest route from  parking lot is, left onto Thimball island rd to Leetes Island road to right onto rte 95 north,&lt;br /&gt;Take ret 95 north for apx 12 miles to exit # 63 &lt;br /&gt;then take left onto rte 81 north to the intersection of rte 9,&lt;br /&gt;get onto rte 9 to exit # 10= Aircraft Road,&lt;br /&gt;take a right after exit onto rte 154 = Saybrook Rd for apx 1 half mile, we will be on the left side of the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes if you are familliar with an alternate and/or  have a GPS use any route you want..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok see ya there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear an orange hat and have the kayak trailer.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252960151000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250528842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THIMBULL I-LANDS PADDLE EVENT, Recreational &amp; Sea Kayaks Barbie-Q at 7 Falls SP</name><id>11130862</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252166400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/11130862/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/9/global_10249785.jpeg</photo_url></item>