<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 New Park Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.747210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 236-6677</phone><name>Cinema City at the Palace</name><city>Hartford</city><id>532404</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.713217</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The movie starts at 7:45.  Please arrive no later than 7:30.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the 1960s this group of rougue DJs, on a boat in the middle of the Northern Atlantic, played rock records and broke the law all for the love of music. The songs they played united and defined an entire generation and drove the British government crazy. By playing Rock n Roll they were standing up against the British government who did everything in their power to shut them down. The band of rebels is lead by The Count, played by the Academy Award Winning Philip Seymour Hoffman, Quentin the boss of Radio Rock, Gavin the greatest DJ in Britian, Midnight Mark, Doctor Dave and Young Carl who comes of age amidst the chaos of sex, drugs and rock n roll. The film features an unbelievable selection of music including The Beatles, The Stones, Beach Boys, Dusty Springfield, The Who, Jimi Hendrix, Smokey Robinson, David Bowie, Otis Redding, Cat Stevens just to name a few. The film is laugh out loud funny and speaks to the rock n roll rebel in all of us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Critics:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This is a message movie, and the message of Pirate Radio is pretty simple: All you need is love, and you can get by with a little help from your friends . . . even if you can't use anything from the Beatles catalog.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;br /&gt; - Betsy Sharkey&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This lightweight British comedy is set in 1966 and captures a sense of the era through its costumes, production design, dialogue and, above all, its top-notch soundtrack.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;USA Today&lt;br /&gt;- Claudia Puig&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Pic generally stays afloat on the strength of its characters but sometimes threatens to sink under its overlong running time and vignettish structure.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Variety&lt;br /&gt;- Derek Elley&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby prior to the movie</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260148953000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259643506000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pirate Radio</name><id>11987475</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259973000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/11987475/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/8/global_5165560.jpeg</photo_url></item>