<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 110</address_2><address_1>211 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.843800</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-462-8994</phone><name>The Winners Circle</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>1102079</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.897400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: black"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let’s go watch the &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;NE Patriot’s&lt;/span&gt; play against the &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Miami Dolphins&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Winner’s Circle has it all: plenty of dinning tables and &lt;b&gt;77 televisions&lt;/b&gt; all around the restaurant, some in each room and at the tables/booths.  Other attractions there are pool tables, arcade games, keno, scratch tickets, great pub menu, cheap beer/mixed drinks and dart boards (although you can’t play darts until after the game is over!).  So come on out and enjoy the company and the game!  If you have darts bring them, I will have mine w/me maybe we can grab a game after the game?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not into Football but want to come anyways?  Feel free there is so much to do at the Winners Circle you can find something to do to pass the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME:&lt;/b&gt;  The game starts at 1:00, let’s meetup at 12:15 to avoid the crowd and get tables.  Please note  depending on how many people RSVP for this event we may not be able to all sit at the same table, but if we get there early enough then we can grab as many tables/chairs as we need, the tables are close.  So come on out and meet some new people, check out a great venue, and of course have some fun.  You never know who you will meet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;/b&gt; There is plenty of parking in their parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the Winners Circle website at: &lt;a href="http://www.winnerscirclema.com/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.winnerscir...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a pay as you go event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Winners Circle is conveniently located off of Routes 95 and 495, check out their website for more information and directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will only wait for 15 minutes before heading in to the restaurant if you are running late and not able to make it at the meetup time, then come on in and find us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside in the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257874657000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256410503000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Are you ready for some football??</name><id>11701916</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257700500000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11701916/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/7/4/global_11382884.jpeg</photo_url></item>