<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Feng Shui your Life!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;Mary Stewart of Feng Shui Boston has offered to host a special workshop for our group Women Supporting Women Through Life's Incredible Journey's.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this hands-on, interactive workshop, each participant will work from her actual home or business floor plan and learn how to energize success, wealth, opportunities, health &amp;amp; smooth relationships using optimal:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Placement &amp;amp; directions for sleeping, dining, &amp;amp; working&lt;br /&gt;• Personal Colors&lt;br /&gt;• Artwork &amp;amp; Decorative accessories&lt;br /&gt;• Good fortune symbols &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This exclusive event will be limited to a class size of 15.  A special tuition rate of $38 for Women Supporting Women Through Life's Incredible Journey's members includes a 2.5-hour workshop, refreshments, expert advice and written training materials.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Feng Shui is….&lt;br /&gt;Awakening dreams&lt;br /&gt;Achieving balance&lt;br /&gt;Discovering serenity&lt;br /&gt;Stimulating senses&lt;br /&gt;Celebrating beauty&lt;br /&gt;Honoring the sacred&lt;br /&gt;Creating Sanctuaries&lt;br /&gt;Living with intention&lt;br /&gt;Transforming lives&lt;br /&gt;A way of living&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Literally “wind and water,” Feng Shui is the ancient Chinese art of creating beauty, harmony, and tranquility in any environment while living in harmony with nature.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Artful furniture placement, a balance of elements, color, sound, scent, lighting, artwork and decorative accessories all contribute to creating positive chi.   When your chi is flowing, you attract greater abundance, new opportunities &amp;amp; success.  Relationships become smoother and you have more energy to do the things you are passionate about.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: chocolate"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;PRE-registration and PRE-payment are required to reserve your spot, not just your RSVP here on the site.  Please email Mary directly she will give you the address to send your check to.  For credit card payments please leave the information on Mary’s answering machine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TO REGISTER: e-mail your name, address &amp;amp; phone directly to Mary.  Preparation details will be sent upon registration/payment.  Checks and credit cards accepted.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please update your RSVP with PAID when you have paid for the workshop.  Mary will email you the address of this event, the event will be in Newburyport, MA.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;E-Mail:  FengShuiBoston@aol.com ~ Web: www.FengShuiBoston.com &lt;br /&gt;Office phone number (toll free): 888-963-3888&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to come but this date isn't good for you, please send me an email and let me know.  I may be able to schedule a few of these events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;center&gt;Mary Kathleen Stewart, CPIA&lt;br /&gt;Certified Feng Shui Master &lt;br /&gt;Traditional Compass School Feng Shui&lt;br /&gt;Certified Practitioner of Interior Alignment&lt;br /&gt;President &amp;amp; Founder, Feng Shui Boston&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mary Kathleen Stewart, CPIA, President &amp;amp; Founder of Feng Shui Boston, Inc. is a Feng Shui Master who makes radio and television appearances, lectures widely, delivers workshops and seminars, writes for newspapers, journals and internet magazines.  Mary manages a successful residential &amp;amp; commercial consultation business and feng shui school that has transformed thousands of lives over the past decade.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A 1997 graduate of Babson’s Executive Development Program with 21 years of sales and marketing expertise, Mary left the corporate world to advance her feng shui knowledge, studying with several world experts. She trained in Malaysia with Lillian Too, the world’s best selling author of feng shui books.  Mary earned her Master Practitioner’s Certification at the Institute of Feng Shui in Kuala Lumpur.  A Certified Practitioner of Interior Alignment (CPIA), she was professionally trained in creating Healthy Homes &amp;amp; Offices by Space Clearing pioneer, Denise Linn.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her work has been featured in The Boston Globe, Boston Magazine, The Improper Bostonian, The Patriot Ledger, New England Condominium Magazine, Point South Magazine, World of Feng Shui Magazine, The Ipswich Chronicle, Living Well Magazine, Environments, Beanies &amp;amp; More Magazine; Norwell Mariner, The Ithaca Journal, The Tara Drive Show House, Angie’s List, Channel 4 News, Fox 25 News, NECN, The American Builder &amp;amp; Channel 10 News. She wrote and starred in a 13 episode television series that has been airing continuously throughout the world on Zee Network since 2001.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The location is in Newburyport, I will update as the date gets closer!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242571893000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Women Supporting Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Women-Social-Network-Group</urlname><id>1379831</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Women Supporting Women Through Life's Incredible Journeys</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239156587000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Feng Shui your Life Workshop for the Adventurous!  </name><id>10140751</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241370000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-Social-Network-Group/events/10140751/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/9/global_7285529.jpeg</photo_url></item>