<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research and Development Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1534447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Atahualpa theme by Bytes for All is, far and away, the best free customizable theme available for WordPress, and it can easily hold its own next to premium themes like Thesis. It's incredible interface gives power users everything they need to implement any design they can think of, while providing enough structure that even a total novice can become a Web designer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Atahualpa is the perfect choice for:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beginners: The custom design interface can actually help you learn CSS in a controlled environment&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pros: Direct, easy access to code gives you all the power you could ever ask for&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;People on a budget: It's free! and it's at least as good as any premium theme out there&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Wood, founder of Social Bootstrap, will demonstrate the Atahualpa theme, highlight some of it's cooler functions, show off a few Atahualpa-based site designs, and answer your questions about this amazing WP theme.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation will be geared toward the intermediate WP user, but beginners and pros will not feel left out unless they have an inferiority complex or something.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Front desk security will direct you after you check in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>James Coletti</member_name><member_id>7809368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266885405000</updated><rating><average>2.86999988556</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>68</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254763234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston WordPress Meetup Oct 2009: The Atahualpa Theme (Intermediate)</name><id>11552881</id><headcount>68</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256598000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/11552881/</event_url></item>