<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 3.3 mile loop hike of moderate difficulty near the south-central shore area in this 1,200 acre sanctuary with a complex 39 mile trail system that has a unique blaze system (&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/reading_trailblazes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt; ). North-south trails are marked with a circle shaped blaze. Square ore triangular trails weave back and forth connectin g circle trails. Crossover trails that connect two circle trails of different colors are marked with an X of the color of the circle they lead to. Complicated?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a fair chance of some ice on the trail given the cold weather and wetness of recent days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go need to have: &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots or comfortable winter boots (no sneakers!) - There could be snow or it could be wet/muddy! &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too. &lt;br /&gt;* Gloves - MUST have &amp;amp; warm ones too! &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket - BRIGHT color better. &lt;br /&gt;* Hat - You loose 20% of your heat through your head! Protect those ears too. &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 1 PM at the parking area. We would finish up at about 4 PM and head home or have a supper out if the group feels like socializing more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General directions (from a trail source):&lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 58 off I-95&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 77 south (toward Guilford) about 0.5 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Turn right (west) onto Route 1 and go 0.7 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Bear left onto Peddlers Rd. and drive 1.1 miles&lt;br /&gt;* Parking area on left just past Denison Dr.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aproximate location/directions via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=540+Peddlers+Rd&amp;amp;city=guilford&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Westwoods Reserve website (with trail maps):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Westwoods interactive trail map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/inter_map.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guilford Land Trust (maintains Westwoods):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guilfordlandtrust.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guilfordla...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203358268000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>A winter (meaning cold here) hiking experience without much difficulty!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203129582000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at Westwoods Reserve Trails in Guilford CT</name><id>7339909</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203184800000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7339909/</event_url></item>