<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Between Church, Elm, Temple and Chapel streets</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.330002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lower New Haven Green</name><city>New Haven</city><id>309557</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.940002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>so filming is set to begin in New Haven for select scenes for the upcoming 4th Indiana Jones film, and it seems that Lucasfim/Paramount and the New Haven Office of Cultural Affairs are conspiring to bring us a supersize helping of the franchise this Tuesday evening with the highlight being (as far as i'm concerned) a screening of &amp;quot;Raiders of the Lost Ark&amp;quot; on the lower green at 9:15. apparently free popcorn will be available, but you may wish to bring a blanket, bug spray, and of course booze.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i'll probably be arriving a little before 7 to catch a performance by the &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.angelsintheair.com" target="_blank"&gt;Aerial Angels&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; street performers. why? here's the description from the infonewhaven flyer: &amp;quot;All female acrobatic troupe featuring whip cracking and fire eating.&amp;quot; need more be said?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;since there's a gap between the angels performance and the flick, i may mosey over to Bottega Cafe for as-yet-unknown drink specials, or to the &amp;quot;Temple Grill of Doom&amp;quot; (no, really, that's what they're calling it) for $1 burgers and dogs. there's no telling if the staff will be chanting &amp;quot;kali ma, shakti day&amp;quot;, but if you go you might want to keep your heart covered just in case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;questions? comments? insults? call ben (your contact for this event): 203-554-5144. feel free to drop me a buzz anytime before 9 to find out where i/we am/are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ps for more details on everything else Indy-related going on that evening between 5 and 9, &lt;a href="http://www.infonewhaven.com/d/2007/06/15/72848" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183079052000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182804716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tues. 6/26 - Movie on the Green: Raiders of the Lost Ark</name><id>5934618</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182906000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5934618/</event_url></item>