<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WEATHER: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today: Sunny, with a high near 82. Southwest wind between 3 and 9 mph. YEAH LOOKS GREAT!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight: Patchy fog after 3am. Otherwise, mostly clear, with a low around 63. South wind around 6 mph becoming calm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday:  NNW wind 6 to 8 kt becoming S in the afternoon. A chance of showers and thunderstorms before 9am. Seas 1 ft or less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trip will pass the hordes of sweaty and grubby dust covered people on Rocky Neck Beach with kids peeing and pooping in the water..(DONT FALL IN HERE ya might get a salty turd in your mouth ruining your appitite for a snack later) on our way to Grizwald, Huntly, Watts, and a few smaller un-named islands along with some of the Pattaganset river area..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our snack are can be anywhere but i also like the point for that..or anywhere it looks great.&lt;br /&gt;then its back strait to the Boat Launch area and the Barbie-Q&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;apx distance: 5-6&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update the weather/ event about 10 am the day of the event if its questionable,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO FAR ITS LOOKING GREAT!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN, WIND OVER 10 MPH AND SEAS 1-2 FEET IS MY SET MAX LIMIT  FOR REC &amp;amp; SEA YAKS on this particular trip, however there is always an alternate plan with an event nearby if necessary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please have some safety gear... one of which should be a whistle, this is really something cheap and lets those know you are in trouble.. MOST OF US HAVE PUMPS, PADDLE FLOATS, PADDLE LEASHES AND STUFF, so there is enough of us to help you if you dont..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I dont plan on going out too far/deep, but this is open water and not easy at all to swim to any shore so be prepared as best as you can, we will be there to assist you but have a whistle so you can let us know of any trouble.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please look at the short video on my site to show a demonstration of a paddle float entry,&lt;br /&gt;It makes all our lives easier if you do go in including yours..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For an informative view of the area we plan to paddle use the link below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctcoastalkayaking.com/files/pattagansetttourmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctcoastalkayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa   1      Low   2:12 AM     0.6   5:46 AM     Set  1:28 AM      78&lt;br /&gt;     1     High   8:22 AM     4.5   8:07 PM    Rise  5:29 PM&lt;br /&gt;     1      Low   2:17 PM     0.9&lt;br /&gt;     1     High   8:40 PM     5.0&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a beach snack&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The barbie q can be done later after the trip at our past spot of 7 Falls Park (exit 10 (aircraft rd) off of route 9, take right , go apx .5 mile, park on left...Bring some Pot Luck food and some scrap wood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting to the paddling spot..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;apx GPS address: #  20 Oakridge Drive, Old Lyme CT LOOK for boat launch signs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;take I 91 south to rte 9 south,&lt;br /&gt;go to end and take left onto I 95 North, go 2 exits&lt;br /&gt;take exit # 71 = 4 Mile River Road&lt;br /&gt;At end of exit take left, this is 4 Mile River Road going SOUTH to the shore.. (unless they moved the exit)..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay on 4 Mile River Road for apx 0.7 miles.&lt;br /&gt;You will meet rte 156 = Shore Road,&lt;br /&gt;Take the right onto Shore Road heading South.&lt;br /&gt;in apx 0.6 miles look left for OAKRIDGE DRIVE.&lt;br /&gt;TAKE THE LEFT ONTO OAKRIDGE DRIVE&lt;br /&gt;go about half way around the circle, look for the boat launch sign and a road off to the right going to the river..go to end and unload then go back to parking lot..walk back to water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I get there as fast as i can..BUT THIS IS BEACH TIME AND BEACH TRAFFIC IN MIDDLETOWN AND TO ROCKY NECK. so we will expect some delays from other members also..but by 12:45 or so, we go..cant wait much longer than that..LOL....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 20 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this ocean all day trip and new carbon paddles &amp;amp; paddle leaches..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;un-reserved kayaks by apx 9 am. will not be taken to the site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub Pungo 12' with flotation bags installed, Recreational Kayak with Carbon Kalista 230 strait w/  small shaft dia Paddle= =  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper  Riot Tourlite 15', Short Sea Kayak , no paddle = AL-R&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The  Bananna Yellow Cobra Expidition SOT 18' , Long SOT Sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista 230 bent &amp;amp; small shaft dia Paddle=  = ALEX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyline Wind Dancer 18', Long sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista 220 bent w/ small shaft dia Paddle= Durelle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red NDK Greenlander Pro 18' , Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Camano 220 Fiberglass or Wood Greenland Paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya all there,&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the PIMP GOLD Toyota Avalon with Kayak trailer and Orange cone. i WILL WEAR MY ORANGE HAT ALSO</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249748378000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248187422000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rec/Sea Kayak Event @ 4 Mile River out to Ocean Islands &amp; Potluck BBQ after</name><id>10923507</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249142400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10923507/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/global_5044522.jpeg</photo_url></item>