<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>29 Elm Street (left door)</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.388855</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Trish's House</name><city>Somerville (near Porter Square)</city><id>7085782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hi everyone!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;So excited to be the new co-organizer of this group with Naomi. More about us soon. We would love to hear your thoughts about the group and any ideas you have! Seems the group has had a couple of different incarnations. In the meantime, here's a great event where we can meet each other and also network with two other entrepreneur groups. I've had the pleasure of hosting this event several times and every time magic happens. It doesn't matter if its a small group or large....Its fun and helpful in both expected and unexpected ways. Hope you can make it! Trish&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have an idea or problem that you would love to get feedback or help with?  Love helping others succeed? Here's the chance to have dedicated time for a small group to focus on your project or idea and pay it forward at the same time. Everyone will have approximately 15-20 minutes. (If it’s a large group we will break up into smaller groups)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some ideas about how you might use the time:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Brainstorm new marketing ideas or get feedback on your marketing materials&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Get feedback about a rough idea or concept that you have&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Practice your "pitch"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Ask for help with a problem or issue you are having&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Have the group help define "next steps" for you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• The possibilities are endless!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a free meetup. It will run from 7pm to 9pm. Snacks and beverages will be provided. This event will include three meetup groups: Entrepreneur Allies, Nonprofit Connector and Entrepreneurship for a Sustainable Planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Trish</member_name><member_id>45572632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337437118000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Sustainability Partners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>green-business-allies</urlname><id>1366456</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Green Business Allies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336430770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brainstorming and Barn Raising</name><id>63839242</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337036400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/green-business-allies/events/63839242/</event_url></item>