<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>WE ARE MEETING @ 9:00am to make sure we can all get a seat. The breakfast/brunch closes at 10:30am. And since no reservations can be made guaranteeing us a seat, we need to arrive there earlier between 9:00am-9:15am so they'll be able to work with us.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Omni Parker House (let's meet in the lobby at the School Street entrance near the sofa and chairs)  &lt;br /&gt;60 School Street&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02108&lt;br /&gt;(617) 227-8600&lt;br /&gt;Price: Somewhat Reasonable&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.omnihotels.com/FindAHotel/BostonParkerHouse/Dining.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.omnihotels...&lt;/a&gt; (check them out on the web)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever wanted to walk the Boston Freedom Trail? Well... now is your chance :] But... let's have brunch first at the very historic Omni Parker House, which is situated right along the historic Freedom Trail. And then afterward... let's walk. A good walk (after eating brunch) while taking in some of the city's great history and beautiful architecture. I can't think of a better way to spend a Sunday afternoon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Parker House America's Oldest Hotel:&lt;br /&gt;As you pass through the sculpted bronze doors of this four-diamond luxury Boston hotel, you will be enveloped by the timeless beauty that has made the Omni Parker House a  landmark since 1855.   Experience the perfect blend of modern amenities and historic charm at America’s longest continuously-operating hotel, located right on the Freedom Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is where the Boston cream pie and the Parker House roll was first conceived. It is also where the legendary Saturday club (Emerson, Thoreau, Longfellow, Hawthorne and honorary guest, Charles Dickens ) held their meetings. It is also where John F. Kennedy announced his candidacy for the US Congress, proposed to Jackie and had his bachelor party.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a much more impressive but brief history on the Parker House (PDF) click on the link below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.omnihotels.com/upload/images/hotels/bospar/pdf/bospar_history%20book%20pages.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.omnihotels...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;PS- While I was living NYC... I got so use to having many friends around that enjoyed exploring the city at the ground level - by walking every inch of its neighborhoods, parks, main streets, and even many of the more obscure nooks and quiet side streets. I miss those times and experiences of trekking about a city and seeing and noticing everything, and discovering and learning all kinds of new things that I wouldn't have seen otherwise. And there was always so much to see. I miss knowing a city on that level. In many ways the city became like an old friend just as it did for so many artists, photographers, writers and poets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On weekends, we would often start at Columbia at 116 Street and Broadway and walk clear to Soho (about 6 miles), meandering through all the different neighborhoods and parks along the way. Along the journey my friends and I would stop off for a coffee, tea or even a bite to eat and then continue on our way, never failing to stumble onto all sorts of cool places, things and even some interesting personalities along the way. I was always amazed that each time we did this trek and we did it many times, I always discovered and learned something new and interesting about the city in which I lived. In many ways my relationship with Manhattan grew much stronger because of those long walks. I started to notice, and discover things about that city that most people didn't see. I honestly feel that this is why my friends and I had a much greater and more intimate relationship with the metropolis. It's because we didn't see it that way at all. It wasn't big to us. Instead we saw Manhattan as a series of very small (almost cozy small town like) neighborhoods and collections of parks and shops, diners, cafes and other kinds of eateries, and of bars and pubs and of course the people and personalities that frequented them. We couldn't help it and it was because of those long walks we did on the weekends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you walk and explore a city to such an extent, you discover and learn things about it that will forever change the way you think of it and see it. You will begin to see things that most people simply miss. If you decide to venture out on one of these long walks, bringing along a camera or a notepad to record what you see :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet me just inside the Enterance on 60 School Street --</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239747510000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234005559000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch at America's Oldest Hotel and Historic Walking Tour</name><id>9692221</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239541200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9692221/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/9/global_7612601.jpeg</photo_url></item>