<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mount Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-401-8047</phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>221452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come check out Conspiracy Cafe every Sunday from noon to 8!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Conspiracy Cafe at 45 Mt. Auburn St. in Harvard Sq. is open &lt;b&gt;every&lt;/b&gt; Sunday from noon to 8:00 pm. It offers a unique setting for 9/11 Truth activists and those curious to learn more about current events through books, DVDs, film screenings and informal discussions, in a casual cafe environment. The Conspiracy Cafe offers a wide selection of books, cds, &amp;amp; other media.  So whether your desires are social, intellectual or oriented toward activism, the Conspiracy Cafe has something for everyone. Hope to see you at the next Conspiracy Cafe!  So what are you waiting for?  Bring a friend, bring yourself, bring an open mind!  Come check out what Conspiracy Cafe is all about!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FILM LINEUP FOR THIS WEEK'S EDITION:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00 - 1:30 The Secret Government&lt;br /&gt;Bill Moyer's 1987 scathing critique of the criminal subterfuge carried out by the Executive Branch of the US Government to carry out operations which are clearly contrary to the wishes and values of the American people. The thrust of the exposé is the Iran-Contra arms and drug-running operations which flooded the streets of our nation with crack cocaine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_sstDwKTCpM" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:30 - 3:00   9/11 Mysteries&lt;br /&gt;9/11 Mysteries demolishes the 'official' 9/11 conspiracy theory more graphically than any movie previously released. See for yourself what really happened in the 3 demolished buildings in the weeks before 9/11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=93sIWihJ-sw" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:00 -  4:40   Who Killed John O Neil&lt;br /&gt;Traumatized by the September 11th attacks, one man struggles to dismantle official history, at the expense of his sanity and even his life. Grappling with multiple realities - and multiple personalities - he must retreat into his mind in pursuit of the truth. In a fictional film about non-fictional events, there is a place where belief and faith will blind you, where nothing is sacred, and to get there all you have to do is ask:  &amp;quot;Who Killed John O'Neill?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dmniC9kdcPE" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:45 - 5:35   Money As Debt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Debt - government, corporate and household has reached astronomical proportions. Where does all this money come from? How could there BE that much money to lend? The answer is: there isn't. Today, money IS debt. If there were NO DEBT there would be NO MONEY. This short clear, concise video explains the history of money &amp;amp; explains our debt based monetary system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_VvKoCgv5sM" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:40 - 7:45 Police State 2000&lt;br /&gt;For at least 10 years now, our local state &amp;amp; county police have been merging with the military more and more.  This film demonstrates that scary phenomenon with footage of police working with foreign troops for martial law &amp;amp; processing people into FEMA centers.  Now with legislation such as the John Warner Defense Reauthorization Act &amp;amp; the new Presidential Decision Directive 51 make that scary vision a reality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gt2pQgW3wX8" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We offer these DVDs at a nominal cost to pay for the renting of the democracy center &amp;amp; the cost of the raw materials needed for this to happen!  We charge $2 for the first 5 dvds you get, then $1 for every additional dvd after you get 5.  We also have a good supply of books &amp;amp; stuff too!  Thanks again!&lt;br /&gt;DVDs offered by Conspiracy Cafe:&lt;br /&gt;A1  = Terrorstorm  Final Cut&lt;br /&gt;A2  = 9/11 Press for Truth  &lt;br /&gt;A3  = America: Freedom to Fascism&lt;br /&gt;A4  = Improbable Collapse &lt;br /&gt;A5  = Hacking Democracy &lt;br /&gt;A6  = David Ray Griffin: 9/11 The Myth &amp;amp; The Reality &lt;br /&gt;A7  = 9/11 Mysteries Part 1: Demolitions &lt;br /&gt;A8  = Sir! No Sir! &lt;br /&gt;A9  = Kill the Messenger&lt;br /&gt;A10 = Steven Jones in Austin (molten spheres stuff)&lt;br /&gt;A11 =  American Blackout&lt;br /&gt;A12 = Refuge of Last Resort&lt;br /&gt;A13 = The Future of Food&lt;br /&gt;A14 = Money As Debt&lt;br /&gt;A15 = Who Killed John O Neil?&lt;br /&gt;A16 = The Secret Government&lt;br /&gt;A17 = Loose Change Final Cut&lt;br /&gt;A18 = Police State 2000&lt;br /&gt;A19 = Police State 2 The Takeover&lt;br /&gt;A20 = Police State 3 Total Enslavement&lt;br /&gt;A21 = Pretext for the North American Union&lt;br /&gt;A22 = David Ray Griffin: 9/11 &amp;amp; the American Empire&lt;br /&gt;A23 = In Lies We Trust Dr Len Horowitz&lt;br /&gt;A24 = Mike Ruppert: Denial Stops Here  &lt;br /&gt;A25 = The Power of Community&lt;br /&gt;A26 = Barrie Zwicker: The 9/11 News Special You Never Saw&lt;br /&gt;A27 = Oil, Smoke &amp;amp; Mirrors  &lt;br /&gt;A28 = Everybody's Gotta Learn Sometime  &lt;br /&gt;A29 = Order Of Death/Dark Secrets Inside Bohemian Grove&lt;br /&gt;A30 = July 4th Compilation (Press For Truth, Hacking Democracy, Money As Debt, Improbable Collapse)&lt;br /&gt;A31 =  Century Of Self&lt;br /&gt;A32 = Merchants Of Cool&lt;br /&gt;A33 = The Great Global Warming Swindle&lt;br /&gt;A34 = Fiat Empire&lt;br /&gt;A35 = 9/11:  The Road To Tyranny&lt;br /&gt;A36 = 9/11 Martial Law: Rise Of The Police State&lt;br /&gt;A37 = Ground Zero 9/11/07 Compilation (Press For Truth, Hacking Democracy, Money As Debt, 9/11 Mysteries)&lt;br /&gt;A38 = Beyond Treason&lt;br /&gt;A39 = The Money Masters&lt;br /&gt;A40 = Conspiracy Of Silence&lt;br /&gt;A41 =  Diamond Empire&lt;br /&gt;AND MANY MANY MORE!!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the dvd table!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4883658</member_name><member_id>4883658</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203440999000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Come check out some documentaries in the screening room...  Buy some cheap dvds &amp; books!  Meet other 9/11 truthers in your community!</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203100543000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conspiracy Cafe!</name><id>7337342</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203267600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7337342/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/2/6/global_3233926.jpeg</photo_url></item>