<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Industrial Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03087</zip><lat>42.811161</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>FDI-YGY Corporate Training Center</name><city>Windham</city><id>7557962</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.253571</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Thursday Ralph Plumb talked about generating organic (F.R.E.E.) traffic. Ralph's marketing methods and systems are recognized as the most effective by the experts and gurus around the world. He was personally referred to us by Than Merrill and Paul Esajian of Fortune Builders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ralph told the room on Thursday night that everyone should take advantage of affiliate marketing. He also said Network Marketing is affiliate marketing on STEROIDS. So....Thu night, I'm inviting you to come see how it works and to meet a legend in the industry. &lt;br /&gt;

When you can meet a multi-millionaire to pick his brain...DO IT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*******************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THU 8/23 Meet Industry Legend, Networking and Business Building Expert - Steve Schulz!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thu - 8/23/2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 pm - Networking&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30 - YGY Overview and training&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FDI YGY Training Center&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 Industrial Dr, Windham, NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve Schulz is a master networker and a master of creating passive residual income. He has earned over $15 million dollars during his career and he will tell you he's just getting started! He will also tell you that he started as a struggling 5th grade teacher, if he can do this, anyone can do this. You just have to follow the system he's going to share. Steve has been interviewed in many publications, most recognized being "My first year in Network Marketing" by Mark Yarnell. He plans to share a different option for you, one where you can create true monthly residual income without having to deal with tenants, trash and toilets.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345774532000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>57</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345296012000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet Industry Legend Steve Schulz</name><id>78279842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345762800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/78279842/</event_url></item>