<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OBON - The Buddhist Day Of The Dead &lt;br /&gt;

October 28, 2012 @ BFF of Ct &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

1) Remember your ancestors &lt;br /&gt;

2) Bring a photo of one or two ancestors &lt;br /&gt;

3) Read more below: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

On this day, we will remember with gratitude and love our ancestors and those friends who have passed on. We recognize that we are a direct continuation of our ancestors and they still exist within us, in our DNA, and without them we would not exist. Our first ever Obon event includes the Flower Ceremony in which participants will receive a small white or red flower pin symbolizing the living or deceased parents. This is an emotionally moving experience and underscores the Buddha's teachings of interconnectedness, gratitude and love. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Participants will be given the opportunity to verbally share their love and gratitude to a parent or ancestor. Also, participants can bring a photo of a deceased ancestor to be put on the altar during the ceremony. The discussion topic will be on the Mahayana Contemplation of No-Coming, No-Going. Non-traditional date. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Visit www.bffct.net &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer complimentary meditation lessons for those new to buddhism. Just arrive 15 min. before 10 a.m. and ask the peron at the front desk for the mini lesson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Visit our main website  at &lt;a href="http://www.bffct.net"&gt;www.bffct.net&lt;/a&gt; for Calendar and more information on our beliefs and practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;p.s. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;REMINDER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Hosted by the Buddhist Faith Fellowship. Even though just one or two people from Meetup have RSVPed, &lt;strong&gt;you can expect 35 - 45 people in attendance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Hosted by the Buddhist Faith Fellowship. Even though just one or two people from  Meetup have RSVPed, you can expect 35 - 45 people in attendance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351444524000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347326475000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhist Meetup Group - Topic: Obon - The Buddhist Day Of The Dead</name><id>dsjphcyqnblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351432800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/81821052/</event_url></item>