<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>160 State St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359438</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617) 742-2286</phone><name>Black Rose</name><city>Boston</city><id>798320</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053797</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Kaela will not be present at this event but will share the attendance list with Lydia, our Citizens Schools contact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citizen Schools is a national nonprofit that partners with middle schools to expand the learning day and increase opportunities for low-income children. Citizen Schools is currently recruiting volunteers to teach 12-week hands-on apprenticeship courses that build students' skills and fuel their imaginations. Volunteers receive up-front training, weekly lesson-plan support, and work with a group of 15 students for 90 minutes each week, with a trained staff member to support you in the classroom at one of Citizen Schools’ Boston or New Bedford area schools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interested in learning more? Attend the Citizen Schools Meet and Greet! Learn more about Citizen Schools and how you can get involved while meeting other Bostonians invested in making a difference. There will be a brief informational session around 6:00 and Citizen Schools staff members present the whole time to answer any questions you have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who: You! &lt;br /&gt;

 What: Citizen Schools Meet and Greet! &lt;br /&gt;

 When: Thursday, August 9th, 5:30-7:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Where: The Black Rose, 160 State St. Boston MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ready to sign up today? If this opportunity to deeply impact a group of middle school students for a semester interests you, fill out a brief interest form &lt;a href="http://www.citizenschools.org/volunteer/sign-up/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.citizenschools.org/volunteer/sign-up/&lt;/a&gt; and a staff member will contact you to share more information, discuss possible topics, and you can see if it’s right for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This special volunteer opportunity is provided for you by a partnership with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Volunteers &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn more: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bigenoughtodeliver/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/bigenoughtodeliver/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And The Boston Spanish Language Meetup. &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn more: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonspanish/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/bostonspanish/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lydia</member_name><member_id>54427002</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344627648000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonspanish</urlname><id>145862</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344394929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Are you interested in Teaching Spanish?</name><id>76813152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344547800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonspanish/events/76813152/</event_url></item>