<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Dow Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03057</zip><lat>42.871604</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Purgatory Brook Trail</name><city>Mont Vernon</city><id>6907162</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.691042</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/4/6/event_57309542.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In Bedford heading 101 W at the intersection where the highway for 101 ends and you take a left to stay on 101 West (where 114 starts and Boynton St ends):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  &lt;span&gt;Continue onto&lt;/span&gt; NH-101 W/New Hampshire Route 101 W/Route    101 W for 17.6 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.  As you approach the 17.6 miles mark you will cross a railroad track and come to a traffic light. Do not turn left, but continue straight across the intersection.  Continue onto N River Rd for 0.8 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. At a 4 way intersection continue straight across.&lt;/span&gt; Continue onto  N Purgatory Rd for 1.4 miles.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. You will come to a T intersection.&lt;/span&gt; Turn left onto&lt;/span&gt; Dow Rd and go 0.5 miles passing 17 Dow Road.  Here the road dead ends in a circular cul-de-sac with a hiking kiosk to the right.  Park here.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : left"&gt;Depending on your hiking ability you can choose to do a easy approximately 3 mile - one waterfall hike or a moderate 6 mile - 3 waterfall hike. The first half of the overall hike the 3 mile hike will be a line hike taking in the lower falls the largest of the 3 waterfalls on Purgatory Brook. This hike will proceed down stream to the lower falls and then back upstream to where the trail first intersects with the stream.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whether you choose to do the 3 mile hike or the 6 mile hike the whole group will be doing the first half of the overall hike which would be rated easy unless just hiking 3 miles is an issue for you.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Once the first half of the hike is over you can chose to continue on upstream to take in the middle and upper falls or return back to the cars if you have had enough hiking for one day. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The second half of the hike is also a line hike and is approximately a 3 mile hike. At the upper falls we will turn around and head back downstream following the same trail. The second part of the hike is more difficult as there is more uphill and downhill going on and the ground is rougher compared to the first part of the hike. Thus if you complete the whole hike it might be considered a moderate hike although the elevation gain isn't that much per say. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Whether you end up doing the 3 mile hike or the 6 mile hike we will all be starting at the same place and time. Please answer the question when you RSVP.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Especially if you are doing the 6 mile hike you should bring some snacks or food for yourself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Once on Dow Road continue 0.5 miles to the end (having passed 17 Dow Road) where it dead ends in a circular cul-de-sac and park.  There is a trail hiking kiosk there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338343124000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335486923000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Purgatory Brook - Choose a 3 mile 1 Waterfall or 6 mile 3 Waterfalls Hike</name><id>62318202</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338127200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/62318202/</event_url></item>