<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Team, please choose one of the following two books and join us in a great conversation about what you have read. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;While finishing the book of your choice is always recommended it is not required.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What Makes a Terrorist: Economics and the Roots of Terrorism ~ Alan B. Krueger&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many popular ideas about terrorists and why they seek to harm us are fueled by falsehoods and misinformation. Leading politicians and scholars have argued that poverty and lack of education breed terrorism, despite the wealth of evidence showing that most terrorists come from middle-class, and often college-educated, backgrounds. In What Makes a Terrorist, Alan Krueger argues that if we are to correctly assess the root causes of terrorism and successfully address the threat, we must think more like economists do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Krueger is an influential economist who has applied rigorous statistical analysis to a range of tough issues, from the minimum wage and education to the occurrence of hate crimes. In this book, he explains why our tactics in the fight against terrorism must be based on more than anecdote and speculation. Krueger closely examines the factors that motivate individuals to participate in terrorism, drawing inferences from terrorists' own backgrounds and the economic, social, and political conditions in the societies from which they come. He describes which countries are the most likely breeding grounds for terrorists, and which ones are most likely to be their targets. Krueger addresses the economic and psychological consequences of terrorism. He puts the terrorist threat squarely into perspective, revealing how our nation's sizeable economy is diverse and resilient enough to withstand the comparatively limited effects of most terrorist strikes. And he calls on the media to be more responsible in reporting on terrorism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What Makes a Terrorist brings needed clarity to one of the greatest challenges of our time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Boy Who Harnessed the Wind: Creating Currents of Electricity and Hope ~ William Kamkwamba&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starred Review. American readers will have their imaginations challenged by 14-year-old Kamkwamba's description of life in Malawi, a famine-stricken, land-locked nation in southern Africa: math is taught in school with the aid of bottle tops (&amp;quot;three Coca-Cola plus ten Carlsberg equal thirteen&amp;quot;), people are slaughtered by enemy warriors &amp;quot;disguised... as green grass&amp;quot; and a ferocious black rhino; and everyday trading is &amp;quot;replaced by the business of survival&amp;quot; after famine hits the country. After starving for five months on his family's small farm, the corn harvest slowly brings Kamkwamba back to life. Witnessing his family's struggle, Kamkwamba's supercharged curiosity leads him to pursue the improbable dream of using &amp;quot;electric wind&amp;quot;(they have no word for windmills) to harness energy for the farm. Kamkwamba's efforts were of course derided; salvaging a motley collection of materials, from his father's broken bike to his mother's clothes line, he was often greeted to the tune of &amp;quot;Ah, look, the madman has come with his garbage.&amp;quot; This exquisite tale strips life down to its barest essentials, and once there finds reason for hopes and dreams, and is especially resonant for Americans given the economy and increasingly heated debates over health care and energy policy.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269275876000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258992289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February's Discussion: What Makes a Terrorist &amp; The Boy Who Harnessed the Wind</name><id>11938778</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267052400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/11938778/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/global_12822284.jpeg</photo_url></item>