<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Friend Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364281</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The North Star</name><city>Boston</city><id>6465492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060905</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;CROSSLISTED WITH RED SOX NATIVES AND OTHER MEETUP GROUPS. We expect a good crowd to come out for this! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;================================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a 2012 RED SOX NATIVES EXCLUSIVE EVENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at The North Star for a Patriots Game Viewing Party to watch the New England Patriots take on the Buffalo Bills in Buffalo on Sunday, September 30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early at 12:30pm to get yourself a prime seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game Time is 1:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no event fee for our reserved section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay for the whole game or leave when ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be inviting some guests. Check back for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives organized weekly Patriots viewing parties last year with guests from several other invited groups attending. We had a blast with up to 80 people attending at various locations in Boston, Woburn and Wakefield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Star will be our Primary Home for watching 2012 New England Patriots games (as well as hosting Trivingo).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff will welcome you to The North Star with Cornhole to add to the Tailgate feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Star is super conveniently located next to the TD Garden and on the Green and Orange Lines and Commuter Rail at North Station. The Red and Blue Lines are within a 10 minute walk and street parking is also available if you arrive early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own food and drinks. PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU GO AND TIP YOUR SERVER.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space is limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Sox Natives Team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jeff has reserved a large section for us. Ask the hostess to direct you to our sign-in table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349035280000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347887670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patriots Viewing Party at The North Star - Pats @ Buffalo Bills</name><id>82753862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349022600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/82753862/</event_url></item>