<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Due to the unsettled weather for Thursday, Nov. 5, I am rescheduling this meetup for Monday, Nov. 9 at 2:45 p.m.  I would ordinarily go anyway, but with the H1N1 virus so prevalent I do not wish to make anybody sick from getting too cold or wet.   Hope you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have volunteered to organize some hikes during the week.   This is purely an exploration hike.  I have not been on the trail though I have located the preserve in South Glastonbury on Great Pond Rd.  Most likely we will follow the Dana Rim Trail, which is about two miles round trip through woods, past ponds and skirting some farms.  Park along Great Pond Road near the Great Pond Preserve sign, which is visible from the road.  We will gather along the curb (I drive a silver Rav 4) and starting our hike from there between 2:45 and 3 p.m.  Trail we follow depends upon start time.  It may be a shorter loop or the longer Dana's Rim Trail.&lt;br /&gt;This 70-acre preserve is owned by the town and managed in cooperation with The Nature Conservancy.&lt;br /&gt;The terrain is gently rolling with good footing.&lt;br /&gt;Great Pond itself is a 12-acre glacial drawdown pond. It experiences great fluctuations in water level&lt;br /&gt;throughout the year.  Along the wooded uplands the preserve provides a home for a diverse&lt;br /&gt;community of plant and animal species. On the Pond Trail, just beyond the bridge, you will see the largest&lt;br /&gt;red cedar tree in New England. This tree has a circumference of about 10 feet and is 150 years old. The&lt;br /&gt;overlook at the edge of the pond is a great place for birding. Migrating waterfowl and wading birds favor&lt;br /&gt;this area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be parking on the street about 1/3 mile down the second entrance to Great Pond Rd.  The first entrance has a large sign that says Great Pond and goes through a bunch of neighborhoods.    The second entrance is about 1/4 mile beyond the first entrance and is still named Great Pond Rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the Great Pond Preserve follow the link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.glasct.org/index.aspx?page=195" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.glasct.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions &lt;br /&gt;Route 2 East to Exit 7. Route 2 splits here and Exit 5 is a left hand exit. You will then be on Route 17. Stay on Route 17/Main Street for approximately 5 miles. Great Pond is on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 2 West to Exit 10. Take a left onto Manchester Road. Go to stop sign and take a right onto New London Turnpike. At the next light take a left onto Chestnut Hill Road. Follow Chestnut Hill Road until the intersection with Main Street. At that light take a left onto Main Street/Route 17. Stay on Route 17/Main Street for approximately 5 miles. Great Pond is on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location of Great Pond Preserve: 400 Great Pond Rd.&lt;br /&gt;follow mapquest link&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=South+Glastonbury&amp;amp;state=ct&amp;amp;address=400+Great+Pond+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_______________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>June M</member_name><member_id>9270463</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258296533000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256675432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Great Pond Preserve, South Glastonbury, CT. Rescheduled to Mon Nov 9</name><id>11725992</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257795900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11725992/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/f/global_705503.jpeg</photo_url></item>