<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;The Random Group was founded as a way for strangers to meet and become friends, all while enjoying the great outdoors. In the beginning there would be a couple of events each month – now there are two or three each week. Even with all of these events on the calendar you may have noticed that most of them fill up quickly – often there is a waiting list of people who are interested in participating.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;One solution to the full event/waiting list thing is to expand the size of each event so that more members can participate in each one. Since we like to keep the size of our groups small this isn’t a realistic option. A better one is to encourage more of our members to organize their own events so there are more opportunities for people to get together and get out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;What makes organizing this group so easy is the quality of people that have already stepped forward to organize and run events – they are some of the “best people” that you will find anywhere. Some have been with us since the start, some only get out in summer while others just get out in winter, and some are just starting out. In the end though, without volunteer organizers like them we are just a big group with an empty calendar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;The primary focus of the group is hiking – it doesn't matter if it's a one-day hike or a multi-day backpack. Other events include biking (rail trail, road, and off-road), kayaking (rivers, lakes, and ocean), skiing (downhill and cross country), and various adventure races. It would be great if we could also get some easy (5 miles / 3 hours) and moderate (5-10 miles / 3 – 6 hours) hikes on the calendar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Do you think that you have what it takes to organize and run your own events? If so please &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/pages/Expectations_of_Organizers_with_the_Random_Group"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to read a summary of what we expect of our leadership team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;While not required, most of our organizers have taken an outdoor leadership class through the Appalachian Mountain Club. In fact, some of our organizers actually go back to teach and mentor future leaders. Here is a listing of the upcoming classes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;AMC Boston Chapter Spring Leadership Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/101415732"&gt;AMC Mountain Leadership School - Backpacking Trips&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a&gt;AMC Mountain Leadership School - Day Trips&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;If this sounds like fun and you want to get more involved let us know so we can talk more about what you can do to work towards running your own events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364846504000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362363758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Do you have what it takes to lead your own events with Random?</name><id>107455502</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364835600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/107455502/</event_url></item>