<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>450 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363593</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-9278</phone><name>Central Square Theater</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1044961</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100953</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.centralsquaretheater.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.centralsquaretheater.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Boston ASL Meetup buddies at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ASL Interpreted Performance of The Mountaintop at Central Square Theater, 450 Massachusetts Ave., Cambridge, Saturday, January 26 2013, 3pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description of the Play:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The date is April 3, 1968. Having just delivered his magnificent oration "I've Been to the Mountaintop," at Mason Temple in support of a sanitation workers' strike, Reverend Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. returns to Room 306 at the Lorraine Motel in Memphis. A maid comes to his door with coffee. An unlikely relationship is forged that ventures into the political and personal, compelling him to confront his destiny and the fate of the nation on the eve of one of the most critical moments in American History. Winner of the Olivier Award for Best New Play, The Mountaintop is presented in celebration of the 150th Anniversary of the Emancipation Proclamation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contains adult themes, profanity, and smoking. Suggested ages: 13 &amp;amp; up. &lt;br /&gt;

 How to purchase tickets?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accessible seats are available by calling 617-576-9278 x210. These seats will appear as sold when looking at the online seating chart. Mention the code ACCESSIBILITY to save.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets for patrons who wish to be seated in the section for the ASL Interpretation should also call 617-576-9278 x210. $25 tickets are available for that section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: BEFORE the SHOW at 2PM there will be a Symposium on Disability Rights discussion led by Michael Muehe of the Cambridge Commission for Persons with Disabilities and activists Joanne Daniels-Finegold and John Kelly. Boston ASL members can attend this as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359241454000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>ASL Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonasl</urlname><id>1298565</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston ASL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358944105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>See an ASL-interpreted performance of The Mountaintop</name><id>100977582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359230400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonasl/events/100977582/</event_url></item>