<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Build It and They Will Come- A Celebration of Science and Technology Entrepreneurism&lt;br /&gt;When:              Tuesday, October 26, from 6:00 p.m. to 10:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Whre:              Work Bar Boston&lt;br /&gt;                        711 Atlantic Avenue&lt;br /&gt;                        Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;Register:           &lt;a href="http://biotechbrew2010.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://biotechbrew201...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be it life science or high technology, Massachusetts, as a whole, and Boston, in particular, has served as a hub for the entrepreneurial community that has built it all.  Breakthrough therapeutics, killer apps, mind bending tech and many other novel enterprises have been driven by the innovative spirit ever present in our community.  Now more than ever, that very entrepreneurial spirit and drive is needed to build the next generation of opportunities that will spur economic growth and put us back on the road to prosperity. Boston Region Entrepreneurship Week or is shining a spotlight on the entrepreneurial spirit in and around Boston. The goal is to bring together entrepreneurs, researchers, clinicians, investors, technology and business professionals, students, among others to promote active inter and cross-disciplinary networking toward fostering the creation of the next generation of novel opportunities and enterprises.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288234131000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286204596000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Celebration of Science and Technology Entrepreneurism</name><id>14994223</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288130400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/14994223/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>