<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>On December 5th the (cool, independent, non-profit) Brattle Theater in Harvard Square &lt;br /&gt;runs another in its series of older Dr Who stories paired with episodes from the new series. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Essential details: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Calendar listing is &lt;a href="http://brattlefilm.org/2010/12/05/hooked-on-who-triumph-of-the-master/" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket price is $7 for either show or $10 for both. You can reserve online &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/38zyj8a" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. It is likely to be sold out by 12/5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are two Dr Who stories being shown -- an older episode, Logopolis, at 7PM, and a 2010 episode, The End of Time at 930. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; If you are planning on coming to only the second showing, please note that in your RSVP &lt;/b&gt;so we can try to &lt;br /&gt;grab an empty seat for you when (or if) people leave after the first. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will send my cel number to people who RSVP yes before the event, probably a week or so before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Some further information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;what is Dr Who?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(from wikipedia)&lt;br /&gt;Doctor Who is a British science fiction television programme produced by the BBC. The programme depicts the adventures of a mysterious and eccentric humanoid alien known as the Doctor who travels through time and space in his spacecraft, the TARDIS (an acronym for Time And Relative Dimensions In Space), which normally appears from the exterior to be a blue 1950s British police box. With his companions, he explores time and space, faces a variety of foes  and saves civilizations, helping others and righting wrongs, as well as improving the way people, aliens and robots choose to live their lives.&lt;br /&gt;(end quote)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to allow the series to live past the actor playing the main role, every so often some catastrophe will nearly kill the Doctor and cause him to &amp;quot;regenerate&amp;quot; -- he essentially changes bodies, to some extent his personality will change but he retains his knowledge of his past lives. Very convenient, as this allows a new actor to step into the role.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;what are the episodes showing 12/5 about?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Logopolis (1981) and The End of Time (2010) we see two incarnations of the Doctor doing battle with a foe called The Master. The Master is an amoral mirror reflection of the Doctor's character -- another alien of the same race who plays as a sort of Moriarty to the Doctor's Sherlock Holmes. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside the theater with a meetup sign by 6PM, earlier if I can make it. There will likely be a line, so if you are definitely going and able to get there sooner and possibly grab seats for us, please let me know. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Drew G.</member_name><member_id>11870528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291653335000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288896930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Doctor Who at the Brattle: Triumph of the Master</name><id>15340359</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291590900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15340359/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/d/global_12522509.jpeg</photo_url></item>