<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 190, next to Middlesex Bank</address_2><address_1>162 Cordaville Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01772</zip><lat>42.287444</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-259-2847</phone><name>Acara Yoga Studio</name><city>Southboro</city><id>1390683</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.525164</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please Join Us for&lt;br /&gt;Our FREE Evening of Guided Meditations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Note: This is not a meetup event.  Acara Yoga Studio and Ann are co-sponsoring this event for all who wish to participate. We're sharing this opportunity and experience with you, as it is always an easy way to align and to feel gooooood!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We invite you to come and immerse yourself in the space of spirit with peace, love and feeling good. Come to relax and align with who you really are and to open yourself to the joy in all that you are. This is always a most wonderful evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The evening will consist of 2-3 &lt;i&gt;guided&lt;/i&gt; meditations.  All you'll have to do is listen to Ann’s voice as she guides you through the meditations, each one usually about 15 - 20 minutes long, with discussions in between.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’ll have the chance to experience deep, full-body relaxation to release all physical and mental tension and stress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The meditations will also lead you into magnificent feelings of peace, love, happiness and hope- essentially feeling really, really good!&lt;br /&gt;If you like, you can bring a mat, blanket, and pillow to fully relax lying down. Or you can use the chairs provided, too, of course. Please arrive a little early to get settled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;All are welcome. The class is appropriate whether you are a beginner to meditating, or experienced.  &lt;u&gt;Please invite others to sign up and join you.&lt;/u&gt;  Forward this to your friends, family and groups.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Space is limited, so either RSVP'ing  thru this site, or registration is required.  Non- meetup people should register by sending name, e-mail, and phone number to: annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com.  They’ll receive confirmation of their registration and a reminder&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “Ann’s guided meditation was heavenly.  With a soothing voice and joyful manner, Ann skillfully guided me, and a room full of others, to a place of happiness.  For me it was sheer joy.  After having been gently guided to experience absolute physical and mental relaxation, I experienced one of the most profoundly powerful moments I have felt because I was able to access pure love and joy.  I am grateful to Ann for her gentle and loving manner and her skill and dedication. “ Renee J. Montana LMT, NCMT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Rt. 9 to 85 south exit (Hopkinton/Milford); turn rt. onto MA-85 (Cordaville Rd.); studio is in Town Centre Plaza on left, next to Middlesex Savings Bank. Acara Yoga sign is on door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285427294000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283192204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Evening of Guided Meditations for the Community </name><id>14592947</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285370100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/14592947/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>