<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>173 Hartford Rd.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06001</zip><lat>41.838306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 242-1158</phone><name>Penwood State Park</name><city>Simsbury</city><id>930144</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.786479</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is one in a series of section hikes traversing the Connecticut portion of the Metacomet Trail from North to South.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each hike will be 5 to 7 miles of moderate hiking over a 3 to 4 hour duration. The group will meet at the end of the trail head and car pool to the beginning. We will then walk back to the cars and make arrangements to pick up the cars that were left at the start. It would be nice to have a group of people who are interested in completing all of the sections. Connecticut Forest and Part awards a patch to those who do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Section 3 – Penwood State Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 5.3 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terrain:&lt;/strong&gt; Ascend the Ridge line and follow the rolling trial along the ridge line&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pace:&lt;/strong&gt; A moderate pace with breaks for water and views but the intent is to cover the distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When:&lt;/strong&gt; Sunday 10AM EDT 17 June 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting location:&lt;/strong&gt; 173 Hartford Road, Simsbury CT. Enter Penwood State Park and drive 200 yards to parking area. We will split up into car pools and drive to the trail head at 2 Tunxis Road, Simsbury, CT The parking lot of "The Mills" just off route 189 in the Tariffville section of Simsbury&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who to look for:&lt;/strong&gt; Red Dodge Wagon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Drink:&lt;/strong&gt; A snack and a quart of water. Plans can be discussed for an after hike lunch meeting location during the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail Map:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.ctxguide.com/ctxguide_232.htm"&gt;http://www.ctxguide.com/ctxguide_232.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background:&lt;/strong&gt; The Metacomet Trail traverses the traprock Metacomet Ridge which extends from Long Island Sound to the Massachusetts/ Vermont border. This ridge, rising hundreds of feet above the Connecticut River, Farmington River, and Quinnipiac River valleys, is a prominent landscape feature of central Connecticut. From south to north, the trail uses the ridges of the Hanging Hills, Short Mountain, Ragged Mountain, Bradley Mountain, Pinnacle Rock, Rattlesnake Mountain, Farmington Mountain, Talcott Mountain, Hatchet Hill, Peak Mountain, and West Suffield Mountain. Abrupt vertical cliffs with visible talus slopes and frequent viewpoints are common throughout. Views are generally to the west from West Suffield Mountain south through Ragged Mountain; west and south in the Hanging Hills. The Farmington River cuts through the ridgeline between Hatchet Hill and Talcott Mountain in the Tariffville Gorge (east of Simsbury). Historic features along the trail include Old Newgate Prison museum and copper mine in East Granby; Heublein Tower on Talcott Mountain with expansive view of four states; the Hill-Stead museum in Farmington, Connecticut, notable for its French impressionist painting collection and gardens; and Hubbard Park of the Hanging Hills of Meriden, designed with the help of famous landscape architect Frederick Law Olmstead.[1][6][7] The traprock ridges and talus slopes of the Metacomet Ridge are also home to several unique microclimate ecosystems that support species of plants that are unusual or endangered in this part of New England, and are a seasonal migration path for raptors.[8] Viewshed from the ledges include agrarian land, suburbs, small towns, river corridors, the eastern Berkshires ridgeline, and metropolitan Meriden and Hartford.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;

 By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Please make any general comments regarding how to improve or alter the overall processes of all the sections in the "Hike the Metacomet" thread under the DISCUSSIONS tab.  Questions and comments to this section should be posted below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Penwood State Park</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1340156862000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338825431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Section Hike The Complete Metacomet Trail - Section 3</name><id>67674982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339941600000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/67674982/</event_url></item>