<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturbridge Village</address_2><address_1>1 Stallion Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01566</zip><lat>42.110557</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Oliver Wight Tavern</name><city>Sturbridge</city><id>1165478</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.096290</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;Last year we (22 of us) enjoyed a fantastic 'huge' Brunch at The Oliver Wight Tavern in Sturbridge.  It is amazing how much food they serve for this 'Sunday Brunch'.  The Oliver Wight Tavern is located just outside the Visitor center entrance to Old Sturbridge Village on the left side just before you enter the winding road to Sturbridge Village. The dining room is gigantic, can sit 300 people, the decor and atmosphere is so New England!  Those that went last year raved about the food, the quantity, and the price!  Yep, it's only $19.95 plus tax and tip.  Great Price for all you get!  Just a sampling of the menu: Omelets made to order, scrambled eggs, applewood smoked bacon, sausage, assorted muffins &amp;amp; danish, buttermilk pancakes, waffles (with M&amp;amp;M's, chocolate chips, strawberries, blueberries &amp;amp; fresh whipped cream), seasonal sliced fruit, carving station with Ham, Roast Turkey and Prime Rib.......on top of huge selection of desserts!  You won't believe all you get for just $19.95.  Please rsvp yes only if you are certain you can make it, as I need to make reservations for this event.  Of course if something comes up and you can't make it, kindly change your rsvp.  You Will Love This Place!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Linda/Meetup tables</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286837966000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283550079000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FANTASTIC SUNDAY BRUNCH!</name><id>14649784</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286724600000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/14649784/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/7/global_17677175.jpeg</photo_url></item>