<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>319 Main St</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05055</zip><lat>43.714775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dan &amp; Whits General Store</name><city>Norwich</city><id>8170872</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.308914</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hike up the AT from the Elm St. Trail head, starting with 5 min easy terrain, then ~30 min. up hill, then ~30 min. moderate terrain. At Cossingham, we'll pause to take in stunning northeast views to Smarts Mt &amp;amp; Mt Cube and greet the sheep and cows, and then we have the option to add additional loops near Cossingham as time permits. We can stop at the pub at the Norwich Inn for their famous home brew/pub food afterwards. MEETING PLAN: There's limited parking at the Elm St. Trail head, so we'll meet in the left side back area of the Dan &amp;amp; Whits parking lot. Look for a white vehicle with an orange bandana. I will drive up to spot the car at 5:30 and ride my bike back down Bragg Hill so we'll depart for the trail head upon my return ~5:50. Its 1 mi. from D&amp;amp;W, so we should be on the trail by 6pm. There will be plenty of time to do this short hike before dark, especially with a car spotted. Even so, its always a good idea to carry a headlamp/flashlight (I'll have an extra) and a few snacks, plenty of water, bug repellant etc. Friendly dogs are welcome along. Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342270606000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341948062000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking A.T. in Norwich VT</name><id>72771092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342215000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/72771092/</event_url></item>