<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>140 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.177994</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 429 1500</phone><name>The Meadows</name><city>Holliston</city><id>959576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.442941</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have our HOLLISTON MEADOWS PET RESORT meetup on Oct. 18th, from 3-5 pm, Halloween party, costumes welcome.  I will try to find a photographer, professional or amateur, to take pictures!  Please let me know if you know of anyone that could do this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOLLISTON MEADOWS is at 140 Summer St, Holliston, MA.  (508) 429 1500.  Anne Byers, the director is our contact person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let other pet owners know, including owners on the South Shore and Cape Cod, which is closer to HOLLISTON than to SUDBURY where our other meets take place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is FREE because the Meadows has generously offered us meet space each month for FREE.  However, we will want to bring food and beverages, pot luck, and so let me know as soon as possible what you can bring, so we can coordinate it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALSO, HOLLISTON MEADOWS PET RESORT has an ADOPTION program.  Currently they have a MALTESE, named Silvia, who is 10 years old, in EXCELLENT physical condition (seen by Dr. Poling, who owns the MEADOWS and HOLLISTON ANIMAL HOSPITAL) and needs a new home.  Anne Byers who is the director of the Meadows, is going to send me a picture of Silvia along with information about her personality and medical condition.  I will forward it out to all members of our meet.  Anne can be reached at (508) 429 1500 if you want more info right away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maltese and Small Dog Best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;(508) 380 6829&lt;br /&gt;(508) 561 6881&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256247026000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254159907000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BOSTON MALTESE &amp; TINY DOGS,  HOLLISTON MEADOWS, Oct. 18, 3-5pm Halloween Party</name><id>11488520</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255892400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/11488520/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/c/global_83228.jpeg</photo_url></item>