<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday, July 11th from 7-9pm we will have an "Intermediate and up" level meetup at the Cambridge Rec Center in Cambridge. There will be 
&lt;strong&gt;two courts&lt;/strong&gt; available for play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What is intermediate?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- Intermediate players should possess a firm understanding of game strategy, and have a good grasp of skills (passing, setting, hitting). &amp;nbsp;You must be able to consistently bump-set-spike. &amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;This is not a recreational game at a beginner level.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also note that we do not play advanced formations (5-1, 6-2, etc.). &amp;nbsp;If that's important to you, I invite you to seek out the advanced groups that play in this meetup. &amp;nbsp;We're here to have fun and practice, but we also expect a decent, clean level of play so we can enjoy the game more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This game is intended to be approximately Yankee C- level or equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;How to get involved:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The entrance to the gym is on Cambridge Street opposite Harvard Market. The nearest intersection to the entrance is Cambridge Street and Roberts Road.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Please RSVP if you plan on attending. If you show up at the game but do not have a "Yes" RSVP, you will not be guaranteed to get playing time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Please be serious about RSVP's. If you RSVP "Yes" and don't show up, it means you have prevented someone else from attending. Also, please change your RSVP if you find out you can't play, as soon as possible. Changing the RSVP a few hours before the game time means that there will be less people who can play, as most people prefer some advance notice that there are spots available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost of the meetup will be $5. Jason will collect the money from the group all at once just before we begin playing. &amp;nbsp;The money goes to cover the cost of the court rental.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The nearest T stop is Harvard Square. The gym is about a ten minute walk from the T stop.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The front desk will buzz you in.  Then just walk toward the gym at the end of the hall and look for Jason.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310497948000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309815169000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Intermediate Indoor Volleyball</name><id>24536901</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310425200000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/24536901/</event_url></item>