<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Conscious Movie:  &lt;b&gt;The Power of Forgiveness&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, November 7th • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It’s also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movie Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To forgive someone can be simple. But this simple act can have powerful consequences - and may lead to a personal and spiritual transformation. Recently, the study of forgiveness has come into its own. Researchers are examining the psychological and physical effects of forgiveness under an amazingly wide variety of conditions, ranging from petty insults to sexual assault to 9/11. Clinicians now help guide people to forgive transgressions and get on with their lives. From Ground Zero to Northern Ireland to the Amish countryside, THE POWER OF FORGIVENESS explores this important concept, and reveals how forgiveness can transform your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snacks will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is free.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're just around the corner from the Stony Brook T-stop on the Orange line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226453759000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223570879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie:  The Power of Forgiveness</name><id>8930645</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226104200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/8930645/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/2/b/global_5805115.jpeg</photo_url></item>