<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Causeway St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364704</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Harp</name><city>Boston</city><id>429530</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's Saturday night! Drink, dance and enjoy the music. This meetup is full of options:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. The live band is upstairs. They start a little after 10pm. Their music selection is every song you ever loved while growing up in the 90's&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hyjinxband.com/songlist.cfm"&gt;http://www.hyjinxband.com/songlist.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Downstairs is a DJ with dancing (I was told there's also dancing upstairs when the band is on plus they have a DJ going upstairs when the band is not playing).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cover charge: Subject to change if they see a line (remember that, guys?) but for now it's $10 at 9pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WARNING: I will be at the bar upstairs at 730PM. I will chill there probably till around 9pm, after which time, I will be moving about the bar with my peeps. On the dance floor, look for the guy with only two dance moves (the dice and the single Ronnie). That guy is probably me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RECOMMENDATION: Do not arrive after 9pm! You will get stuck with a cover, or waiting in line, and if you don't know the meetup crowd, you may never find us.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: THIS IS NOT A SINGLES MEETUP!!! Translated into Jersey Shore language: Don't be creeping! Now...It's a T-shirt time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's most fun if we meetup at the bar a few hours before the band, throw a few back, enjoy a few laughs, make friends and then roam about the facilities. I encourage you not to get there late as that happened last week and people couldn't find us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send me your suggestions and input into the meetup soon.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Upstairs Bar</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave </member_name><member_id>10064486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335148126000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333406191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Night Social: Live Music and Dancing</name><id>58973952</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335051000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/58973952/</event_url></item>