<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Upstairs (between Knapp and Washington Streets)</address_2><address_1>3 Beach Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351558</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-451-2395</phone><name>My Thai in Chinatown</name><city>Boston</city><id>813594</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062557</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A wonderful friend, Val, who has been challenged by clutter for years (and who came to some of our meetings a few years ago; she isn't in Meetup, though, so isn't part of our group) will be featured on a hoarding reality TV show on Wednesday, March 13, at 9 pm, and is inviting friends to watch that (I've just now learned that Val &lt;span&gt;was also on Anderson Cooper’s Show, &lt;em&gt;Anderson Live&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;). The show is &lt;em&gt;Hoarding: Buried Alive&lt;/em&gt;, on TLC cable TV:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://tlc.howstuffworks.com/tv/hoarding-buried-alive"&gt;http://tlc.howstuffworks.com/tv/hoarding-buried-alive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Val mentioned that her case was selected for filming because her sisters also have clutter/hoarding challenges. I asked if she might consider talking with our Meetup group about the experience and her learnings from it, and she consented because so many of you showed interest. Recently some friends and I shared dinner with Val in her home (which now is lovely, warm- and very hospitable!) ... Val is a wonderful cook and gracious hostess, so we are hoping for more such times together there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Might &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; be interested in coming to this Meetup, too, to learn about such an experience as Val has had? If so, what questions might you want to ask? Feel free to post as Comments below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meeting's fee is $5 per person, in part to encourage commitment because no-shows have been a challenge when meetings have been offered for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We then could also consider together, &lt;em&gt;in person and as a group&lt;/em&gt; at the end of meetings like this, &lt;em&gt;future&lt;/em&gt; programs for which B.U.'s Hoarding Project (Dr Gail Steketee's research team) or other specialists in clutter, organization, or other aspects of personal growth, could offer us insights and other helps ... I'd like to invite representatives from a variety of approaches to speak with us (the B.U. office has said that &lt;em&gt;we&lt;/em&gt; just need to come up with program topics: they cannot do this for us).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for &lt;em&gt;all input&lt;/em&gt; - including days of the week and times of day/evening that are most do-able for you to meet within the next few months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hoping to see you at this upcoming meeting! Participants are welcomed to leave early or stay later to talk further, as schedules require or as inspiration motivates.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will post Meetup signs at the restaurant entrance &amp; up the stairway to the restaurant</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364166472000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352689747000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Talk with a friend who'll be on a hoarding reality-TV show in March</name><id>91002302</id><headcount>4</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364151600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/91002302/</event_url></item>