<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1057 Kingstown Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02879</zip><lat>41.451012</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South Kingstown Public Library</name><city>United States</city><id>1529044</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.495087</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This will be our last meeting of 2009. As discussed at our November meeting, we will be starting a &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Group Portfolio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; tonight, so I am asking all attendees to &lt;b&gt;pre-select&lt;/b&gt; several stocks they feel might make good candidates. Each attendee will submit 1 candidate and explain why they feel that stock is worthy of consideration. We will go around the table until everyone has suggested 2 stocks for the portfolio, so please pre-select a sufficient number of &amp;quot;hopefuls&amp;quot; that if someone else beats you to it, you'll have alternates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The object will be to follow this &amp;quot;proposed&amp;quot; portfolio and critique each of the stocks, propose entry points, exits (both profit and protective), money management, scaling in/out, etc at our meetings. Members are welcome to paper-trade or actually trade the stocks if they so choose, but are entirely on their own with respect to the results. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/confused.gif' border='0' alt='confused' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to make arrangements to attend the January meeting - Our own Jeff Gardener will present an overview of a software scanning system that he developed... should be very interesting! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this meeting is after-hours, we are free to use the Library's parking lot. Our meeting room is downstairs and just to the right of the staircase (the Peace Dale Room).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newcomers are certainly welcome, so if you know of others who might be interested in joining us, please refer them to this site or just bring them along to the meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you all there, and look forward to a lively meeting! Meanwhile...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trade Green, &lt;br /&gt;Ray&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raymond Dreczko</member_name><member_id>4521820</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261177653000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>IBD Enthusiasts and Traders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ibd-739</urlname><id>559772</id><group_lat>41.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258485673000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charlestown IBD Forum</name><id>11896619</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261004400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ibd-739/events/11896619/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/a/global_8444314.jpeg</photo_url></item>