<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person over 16</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>this is an event in conjuction with Queeche VT as it's only about 40 to 45 min Drive away and can hit both locations...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link: &lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/saga" target="_blank"&gt;Saint-Gaudens National Historic Site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From western Massachusetts and points south, take Route I 91 North to Exit 8 (Ascutney). Bear right, proceed through the traffic light and across the Connecticut River. At next light, turn left onto NH Route 12A and go north about 8 miles (10 minutes). Saint-Gaudens Road will be on the right 1.5 miles past the Cornish-Windsor covered bridge. Proceed up Saint-Gaudens Road .5 miles. The parking lot will be on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hours of Operation and Season:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The park will reopen for the season on Saturday, May 26, 2007. The exhibit buildings will be open daily, 9:00 a.m. to 4:30 p.m., from May 26 through October 31, 2007. From November 1, 2006, through May 25, 2007, only the grounds are open and an entrance fee is not charged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The grounds may be accessed from 8:00 a.m. until dusk, year-round. During the winter months, most areas of the park are not maintained for public use. Visitors should take care as pathways may be snow covered and slippery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fees:&lt;br /&gt;An entrance fee of $5.00 per person is charged for visitors age 16 and over. The receipt is valid for seven days and may be used for re-entry to the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;this is a nice way to fill in time between the Morning and Evening Launches at the Queeche VT Balloon Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;any questions plz feel free to contact me&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;thnx,&lt;br /&gt;~Will&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182182497000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180999541000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saint-Gaudens National Historic Site</name><id>5853124</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182009600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/5853124/</event_url></item>