<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>372 Elm St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.311790</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>203-865-1242</phone><name>Rudy's</name><city>New Haven</city><id>518104</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.933010</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Happy Hours series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rudy's - a New Haven original since 1936&lt;br /&gt;A must-see if you haven't been yet!  With the most eclectic mix of people anywhere in the city, this comfy pub is a New Haven institution.  As they self-describe: Doing it's best to prevent Prohibition from returning, Rudy's has a number of foreign and domestic beers on tap, a full bar and quite the selection of bottled beers. CT's best frites w/ a choice of 25 sauces! (They make these fresh on the prem, In And Out Burger style..)  The renowned juke box can dish out Merle Haggard, Black Flag, The Kinks, Modest Mouse, Judas Priest and Abba all in the span of 15 minutes.  Also there for your enjoyment are a pool table and pinball machine.  Place an order for Large Frites and you'll be very popular!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;UPDATE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Specials for our group from 6-9pm are: &lt;br /&gt;$5 large frites &lt;br /&gt;$3 pints and $10 pitchers of Newcastle Brown Ale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Note: Rudy's is a Cash-Only establishment. There is an on-site ATM in the back by the pool table, and Bank of America is on Elm, across the street from Rudy's. There is also an ATM at the Howe Laundromat, located at Howe and Edgewood, one block south of Rudy's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your contact for this event is:&lt;br /&gt;Ed: 203-583-9668&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204153682000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203472387000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour at Rudy's, a New Haven Original!</name><id>7366698</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203980400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7366698/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/c/global_351724.jpeg</photo_url></item>