<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, is proud to present a retrospective of films by one of cinema’s most acclaimed directors, Milos Forman. The eight-film series includes major critical as well as rarely seen earlier work. The retrospective begins with Forman’s Czech social and political satires that together catapulted him to international attention. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Firemen’s Ball&lt;/b&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;/u&gt;(Horí, má panenko) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last film Milos Forman made in his homeland is perhaps the finest example of the Czech New Wave’s trademark combination of warm humanism and stinging social commentary. A party organized by a small-town fire department builds into comic mayhem—and thinly veiled political allegory—in this satire which was banned by the Czech government. This deceptively simple masterpiece is a sharp, lucid representation of human weakness and moral decay. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, please join us for discussion at a nearby eatery, &lt;i&gt;Tiger Lilly&lt;/i&gt;, a Malaysian restaurant near Symphony Hall.  Or, stay for another of Forman's films, &lt;u&gt;Amadeus&lt;/u&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for the group during final credits as I will be holding a Meetup Sign down in front of Remis Auditorium.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be standing at the front holding a Meetup Sign during final credits</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224482312000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219012632000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Firemen’s Ball</name><id>8564719</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220045400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8564719/</event_url></item>