<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;Please indicate when you RSVP if you are joining us for the hike, the dinner or both. Also please do call 978.544.7853 to RSVP for the dinner with Johnson's Farm Restaurant at the Elks. Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Come join me for the after the big meal hike to wear away some calories, have fun and be guilt free after enjoying it all;-).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;We can do the approximately 6+ mile loop around Long Pond at a good pace of 2 MPH since it is relatively easy with a few small ups and downs......these trails are great on the joints with mostly nice soft pine- needled terrain so that last piece of pumpkin pie you had to force down because you were already full like a little piggy will wear off nicely;-). This is part of the 22 mile Tully Trail System.The description below calls this trail strenuous because it is actually also a bike trail and strenuous to bikers. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Parking is at the Tully Lake Campground parking lot which is across the street from Long Pond. This is a gorgeous area to enjoy. According to our local weather forecast, we will be enjoying sunshine and 50 will be the afternoon high. Sounds nice to me;-)!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Well behaved dogs are absolutely welcomed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;Also anyone interested in joining the fun at a community dinner put on by our own local Johnson's Farm Restaurant is welcome. It is from noon until 3 pm. I will be there for noon. Please let me know if you are joining me but also call for your own reservation @ 978.544.7835. this meal is at no cost but donations are excepted and the food is fabulous and this is for anyone regardless of income. Please do not spend Thanksgiving alone as many of us single folks tend to do. This dinner is hosted at the Athol-Orange Elks Club on rt 2A(also known as New Athol Road) west of Hannaford Plaza and east of WalMart. &lt;strong&gt;We can meet in the lobby. I have long brown hair and will have a meetup sign(for those who don't already know me).&lt;/strong&gt; Please click here for a map.....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ad364c"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.elks.org/lodges/ContactUs.cfm?LodgeNumber=1837"&gt;http://www.elks.org/lodges/ContactUs.cfm?LodgeNumber=1837&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long Pond Trail....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/130"&gt;http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/130&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tully Trail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Royalston, Orange, Athol, and Warwick, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A challenging 22-mile loop trail(yellow blazes)incorporating the most scenic features of the beautiful Tully area. Camping at a shelter near Royalston Falls and at Tully Lake Campground. A 6-mile mountain bike loop also accessible from the campground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 22-mile loop of the Tully Trail is the result of impressive cooperation among government agencies, private organizations (in particular, &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/6"&gt;Mount Grace Land Conservation Trust&lt;/a&gt;), individual landowners, and volunteers. It showcases various types of land conservation - state and commercial forests, wildlife management areas, and land conserved by organizations such as &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/92"&gt;The Trustees of Reservations&lt;/a&gt;. In addition to forests, hikers also discover wonderful wetlands - lakes, ponds, rivers, streams, waterfalls, swamps, marshes, and bogs. Ridgelines and hilltops afford spectacular views of North Quabbin valleys and further hills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;makes a broad loop around &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/45"&gt;Tully Mountain&lt;/a&gt;, and the&lt;/span&gt; major trailhead is at &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/82"&gt;Tully Lake Campground&lt;/a&gt;, where parking, restrooms, and tent sites are available. Parts of the trail allow easy or moderate hiking, but others require strenuous effort; spring and storm overflows can close parts of the trail. The trail is marked by rectangular yellow blazes and the blue-and-white Tully Trail logo. For those seeking additional challenge, the Tully Trail connects in the north to the white-blazed &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/126"&gt;Metacomet-Monadnock Trail&lt;/a&gt;. A trail shelter at the eastern junction of the two trails is available on a first-come basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of the Tully Trail doubles as one arc of a strenuous six-mile mountain bike loop around Long Pond; access is also from the Tully Lake Campground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;To campground trailhead: From Athol Center take Rte 32 north. Go about 4 miles, past Tully Dam. Turn right onto Doane Hill Rd. and go about 1 mile to parking lot on right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a maroon Chevy Monte Carlo.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353666482000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353373695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's wear off that Turkey Dinner Hike...Gobble, Gobble;-)/Dinner optional.</name><id>92110982</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353610800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/92110982/</event_url></item>