<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Coolidge Corner Theatre is proud to be the only Boston venue exhibiting NT Live, a series of four plays broadcast live from London's prestigious National Theatre onto cinema screens around the world. Each play is presented in stunning high-definition. This is the final presentation of the series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 regular / $17 for Coolidge Members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/img/13169674507577949/toolbar/italic.gif" target="_blank"&gt;http://img2.meetupsta...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE HABIT OF ART: World Premiere&lt;br /&gt;Live Simulcast: Thursday, April 22, 2010 @ 7:00pm (doors and pre-show @ 6:30pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Auden often said that metre and rhyme led him down unexpected paths to thoughts he wouldn’t otherwise have had, and in this respect versification and fornication are not so different.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Britten (Alex Jennings), sailing uncomfortably close to the wind with his new opera, Death in Venice, seeks advice from his former collaborator and friend, W H Auden (Tony Award-winning actor Richard Griffiths). During this imagined meeting, their first in 25 years, they are observed and interrupted by, amongst others, their future biographer and a young man from the local bus station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;You are a rent boy. I am a poet. Over the wall lives the Dean of Christ Church. We all have our parts to play.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alan Bennett’s new play is as much about the theatre as it is about poetry or music. It looks at the unsettling desires of two difficult men, and at the ethics of biography. It reflects on growing old, on creativity and inspiration, and on persisting when all passion’s spent: ultimately, on the habit of art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In the end,&amp;quot; said Auden, &amp;quot;art is small beer. The really serious things in life are earning one’s living and loving one’s neighbour.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dirrected by Nicholas Hytner&lt;br /&gt;Starring Richard Griffiths, Alex Jennings&lt;br /&gt;2h35m including one 20-minute intermission&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each production in this series has been exceptional.  This play is written by Alan Bennet, author of &lt;u&gt;The History Boys&lt;/u&gt; , 2004; Winner of the Best New Play 2005, the Society of London Theatre Special Award 2005, and the Tony Award for Best Play, 2006.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet outdoors at Panera Bread across the street from the Coolidge as early as 6:00 pm in order to enjoy the Habit of the Art of Meeting Up before the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268871154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Theatre Live: THE HABIT OF ART</name><id>12917957</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271977200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12917957/</event_url></item>