<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Since only a few of you RSVP'd, it might rain, and the Bruins are going to Game 7 Thursday night - I'm moving this to Saturday at 11:30.  We can grab lunch afterwards, and if you want I can show you around the Fenway Community Gardens as I'll be heading there to check out my plot anyway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doug&lt;br /&gt;--------&lt;br /&gt;Let's take a walk through the South End.  I've only been there once, during the day, about 3 years ago.  I will be bringing a printout of the Google Map.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This walk is completely open to suggestions as to where to walk if people have been in the area before.  I just drew some lines on the map of what looked to be interesting.  I mapped out about 4 miles, so it should fill about 90 minutes or so fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Along the final road I picked there are some places to eat, if anyone is up for that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;ll=42.345192,-71.074247&amp;amp;spn=0.021505,0.038624&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;msid=117398343489237033278.00046997da3b4c5cadbb4" target="_blank"&gt;Here's the map.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll wait up to 10 minutes for the Yes's, but won't for the Maybe's.  If you are on your way, please call or text me (NOT while driving!), so we know to wait up for you.  If not, call when you're nearby and join us - we can walk in circles for a bit :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doug&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See my pic, and I'll email my cell # to the RSVPs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug</member_name><member_id>4908818</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242660946000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242001801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South End exploration - Boston Commons to Hynes (RESCHEDULED)</name><id>10381823</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242487800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10381823/</event_url></item>