<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>46 Bridge Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.763428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Behind chiropractic office</name><city>Nashua</city><id>7528542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449173</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Monthly Nashua video screening&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://geneticroulettemovie.com/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://geneticroulettemovie.com/"&gt;Genetic Roulette&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genetically Engineerred Foods...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experts expose the &lt;strong&gt;SERIOUS THREATS&lt;/strong&gt; and how corporations like Monsanto hide the evidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN EVIDENCE&lt;/strong&gt; points to genetically engineered foods as a major contributor to rising disease rates in the US population, especially among children. Gastrointestinal disorders, allergies, inflammatory diseases, and infertility are just some of the problems implicated in humans, pets, livestock, and lab animals that eat genetically modified soybeans and corn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monsanto’s strong arm tactics, the FDA’s fraudulent policies, and how the USDA ignores a growing health emergency are also laid bare. This sometimes shocking film may change your diet, protect you and your family, and accelerate the consumer tipping point against genetically modified organisms (GMOs) already underway. Don’t miss this film!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a new venue in Nashua at 46 Bridge Street in the rear of a chiropractic office. If you've been in Nashua for a while, you'll know the building as the old Maine Manufacturing Company office. Here's what it looks like: &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/maps/2dAI" class="linkified"&gt;http://goo.gl/maps/2dAI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the parking in the rear and if that is full, there is some available on the right side of the building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any folding chairs, please bring one for yourself. We're not sure we'll have enough. Also, plan to bring snacks. We can get this location set up better and better to suit our needs, so come on over so you can check it out and make suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll get together at the new place at 7 like we did before, so please come early or be there at 7 so we can get off to a great start at our new location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the basement room that you access from the rear of the building</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354676589000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354024093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - Genetic Roulette</name><id>qqflqcyqqbgb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354665600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/92996952/</event_url></item>