<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Adobe Connect url address for this meeting is at...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://adobechats.adobe.acrobat.com/r66656819/" target="_blank"&gt;http://adobechats.ado...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simply enter in as a Guest and typ ein your name to enter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be first real meeting of the worldwide Flex User Group. Sorry for taking a while to get things started. We needed there to be enough people in the group to make this work. Speakers typically like having an audience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I'll kick things off by taking about Degrafa which is a graphical framework for Flex. If you haven't heard of Degrafa yet, it is an open source graphical framework built for Flex and uses MXML instead of Actionscript. With Degrafa, you can do advance graphical techniques such as skinning, masks, shapes, repeaters and advance styling straight from your MXML code. It can programmatically create and manipulate your graphics at runtime and make your Flex applications look even better. I will show how to install Degrafa and it can speed up your Flex development.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting will be held online over an Adobe Connect session. I'll post the url soon. As with the ColdFusion meetup group. This is design to be a worldwide Flex User group held over Connect giving people that do not have a local user group the same material and resources. The meetings are free and once we become an official Adobe User group, there will be software prizes and giveaways. So please pass the word along and help build up this user group.&lt;a href="http://adobechats.adobe.acrobat.com/r66656819/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://adobechats.adobe.acrobat.com/r66656819/" target="_blank"&gt;http://adobechats.ado...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Mason</member_name><member_id>4527001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216420449000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215055052000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Degrafa : Declarative Graphics Framework</name><id>8268396</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216247400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/8268396/</event_url></item>