<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 John F. Kennedy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371391</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Kennedy School - Belfer, Weil Town Hall, Lobby Level</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10300462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role of Religiously-Based Nonprofits in US Social Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Harvard University&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontline with Faculty Seminar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All FwF seminars are open to the public&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

BRYAN HEHIR | Parker Gilbert Montgomery Professor of the Practice of Religion and Public Life, HKS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday, Apr 18 | 4:15 – 5:15 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Belfer, Weil Town Hall, Lobby Level, Harvard Kennedy School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The objective of the session will be to explore where such agencies “fit” in the social system, how they differ among themselves and how they conflict and produce specific policy challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;J. Bryan Hehir is the Parker Gilbert Montgomery Professor of the Practice of Religion and Public Life. He is also the Secretary for Health Care and Social Services in the Archdiocese of Boston. His research and writing focus on ethics and foreign policy and the role of religion in world politics and in American society. He served on the faculty of Georgetown University (1984 to 1992) and the Harvard Divinity School (1993 to 2001). His writings include: “The Moral Measurement of War: A Tradition of Continuity and Change; Military Intervention and National Sovereignty; Catholicism and Democracy;” and “Social Values and Public Policy: A Contribution from a Religious Tradition.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Frontline with Faculty Series is a venue for Harvard faculty affiliated with the Hauser Center to share their work and research with faculty colleagues, as well as students in an informal setting that will allow for spirited discussion, debate and exchange. The seminars link faculty experts from Harvard Schools and beyond on a wide range of topics.  The Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations at Harvard University seeks to expand understanding and accelerate critical thinking about civil society among scholars, practitioners, policy makers and the general public, by encouraging scholarship, developing curriculum, fostering mutual learning between academics and practitioners, and shaping policies that enhance the sector and its role in society.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366328071000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357590728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Religiously-Based Nonprofits</name><id>98420402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366316100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/98420402/</event_url></item>