<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a special evening with celebrated Canadian musician Melissa Auf der Maur (Hole, Smashing Pumpkins), who will present her HD fantasy film &lt;u&gt;Out Of Our Minds (OOOM&lt;/u&gt;), part of a multidisciplinary conceptual project that includes her 2010 solo album Out Of Our Minds  and a new comic book. Described by Auf der Maur as a “blood-and-witches fantasy” about “the hunt for the heart,” the film is a Norse-inspired, music-filled experimental saga without dialogue in which a crashing car opens a gateway to parallel worlds and other time periods. OOOM was conceived and produced by Auf der Maur (who also plays the central character), directed by Tony Stone, and features a score by Auf der Maur and Los Angeles psychedelic rockers The Entrance Band. &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;It premiered at Sundance in 2009. “A flamboyant and fantastical new film . . . A 28-minute rush of stunning images, expressive music and narrative experimentation . . . A journey through parallel worlds that brings together a Viking heart, a car crash and a bleeding forest for an unforgettable climax, this imaginative mini-epic is proudly self-produced, shot in HD and fuelled by solar power”&lt;/span&gt; ICA (Institute of Contemporary Arts/London). Colour, HDCAM. 28 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Post-screening Q&amp;amp;A and music performance with Melissa Auf der Maur.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DDVEC5wJsQQ&amp;amp;feature=player_embedded" target="_blank"&gt;Out of Our Minds OOOM Trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at Panera Bread starting at 6:00 pm for light dinner and conversation.  Look for a Red Meetup Sign on a table, hopefully out on the patio, or inside in front of the fireplace.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shown in Theater 1, this special event will probably sell out.  Why take a chance?  Get advanced tickets at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=615521cb-c61a-41c9-abd2-f75643670013&amp;amp;evtinfo=7563~3c2614bd-0781-48b8-a8a2-e21eaa37e962&amp;amp;" target="_blank"&gt;OOOM Tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be gathering members at the Panera Bread starting at 6 pm, inside or outside,depending on weather.  Look for the Meetup Sign, and an emial will be sent to all who RSvP the night before the event. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286668497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MELISSA AUF DER MAUR (Screening and LIVE Performance)</name><id>15058328</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287702000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15058328/</event_url></item>