<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We've invited Carlton SooHoo to share his knowledge and experience with inexpensive lighting solutions for head shots, environmental portraits and group shots. We'll explore lighting these scenarios using equipment many of us already have -- pop-up flash, mounted flash and external flash.  Please bring your camera and flash to this workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the first hour, Carlton will lead a discussion on the Nikon's CLS** (creative lighting system) vs. working with pocket wizards (a radio transmitter for firing remote flash units). He'll also offer advice and suggestions for getting your own lighting kit together for relatively little money. &amp;#8232;After the discussion, we'll set up situations where each of us can get some hands-on experience using our own existing equipment supplemented by other lighting accessories such as pocket wizards, umbrellas, and reflectors and other light modifiers. The inexpensive lighting kit will be demonstrated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Advanced photographers who have flash triggers such as pocket wizards, Microsync Digital, Elinchrom skyport system, etc. are encouraged to come and share their knowledge as well. Also followers of David Hobby’s Strobist blog (www.strobist.com) are encouraged to come and share their knowledge in this communal learning setting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Homework: New to digital SLR folks - please know: 1) how to set your camera into manual mode where you can adjust shutter speed independently from aperture, 2) how to set flash compensation plus or minus one to three ev (exposure values), 3) how to set ISO, and 4) what your camera’s flash synchronization speed is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8232;Meetup Notes:&lt;br /&gt;-- The organizers will work on getting some models in so the photographers can concentrate on learning about the lighting. Drop me an email if you know anyone who would like to participate as a model.&lt;br /&gt;-- Canon users: we'll try to make information available regarding equivalents on your camera if you send me an email with your Canon model.&lt;br /&gt;-- Point-and-shoot photographers are encouraged to sign up to take advantage of the opportunity to shoot the lighting scenarios.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of the limitations of the venue, this workshop will be limited to 15 photographers. We encourage you to sign up early. If the meetup fills up, we will implement a waiting list so drop me an email to let me know you're interested. If a spot opens up, the waitlist will be cleared on a first come, first serve basis. Or, if there's enough interest, we'll consider scheduling a second session. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is also being run on March 22, &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/calendar/9616843/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and on March 28, &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Newenglandphoto/calendar/9680578/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the 1st parking lot on the right as soon as you enter the property.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1238519503000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233832618000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Small flash portrait lighting workshop</name><id>9678587</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237050000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/9678587/</event_url></item>