<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 William T Morrissey Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.309647</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Savin Hill Yacht Club</name><city>Dorchester</city><id>1527219</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043594</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Becky Linhart enjoyed her experience so much in the Sisters Under Sail women’s program that she joined their board. Now she’ll be coming to our Pelagic meeting to talk this non-profit organization and about her experience on their Tall Ship. Sister’s Under Sail has boarded over 450 girls from all over the country and Canada. They not only walk the talk, but they are the only tall ship in the world that sails with an all-female crew. Their focus is to help young teens and women learn what can happen when focusing on a common goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Becky has grown up summers sailing on Lake Erie and spent the last 30 years sailing and racing boats in and around Marblehead. She is also a new crew applicant for Pelagic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pelagic Sailing Club meets at Savin Hill Yacht Club, Dorchester, MA, on the second floor at 6:30pm for social hour and pizza, 7:30pm for meeting, 8:00pm guest speaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information check out our website at: pelagicsailingclub.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dedicated to bringing together competent skippers and competent crew for their mutual sailing benefit!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robin G. Coles</member_name><member_id>10488766</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348796453000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347334088000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Becky Linhart Introduces Pelagic to Sisters Under Sail</name><id>81839992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348785000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/81839992/</event_url></item>