<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's hike the Sarah Doublet Forest.  It is recommended that you wear hiking boots and bring bug spray, suntan lotion and plenty of liquids.  Also bring a flashlight.  With any luck, you may need it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Sarah Doublet Forest:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Doublet Forest is the largest property of the Littleton Conservation Trust. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trails:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well-developed and maintained. The kiosk at the parking area has copies of trail maps and other information about the property. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Knapp-Jenkins Trail (yellow markers outgoing) takes you from the parking area past the old foundation with standing chimney and across the AT&amp;amp;T cable line to the Wunnahu Loop. This trail goes up and down through overgrown pasture and into pine forest passing an old stone quarry. When you return to the cable line, go down hill a few steps to find the Tatatiquinea Loop which goes down past some vernal ponds and into a wonderful yellow (in late autumn) area of witch hazel shrubs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can return on the AT&amp;amp;T line or reverse direction (red markers) on the trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another trail proceeds from the parking lot area downhill to the shore of Fort Pond. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the intersection of Charter Way and Nashoba Road, a new trail has been established that proceeds northerly through the Nagog Hill Orchard woodlands and private property to Nagog Hill Road. The trail continues on the northerly side of Nagog Hill Road, as shown on page 16. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;History:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Littleton, Massachusetts was originally a Praying Indian Village.  Back in 1646, Rev. John Eliot, known as the Apostle to the Indians, began an effort to organize the Massachusetts Indians into Christian Villages.  With the backing of Cromwell’s England and 12,000 pounds sterling, he began a long-term mission to the Massachusetts and translated the Bible into Algonquin in 1663.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although he was a Puritan, Eliot was also a humanitarian and he felt that the best way to assure their survival in the midst of heavy English land-pressure was to organize the Indians into English towns and lifestyles.  They were to convert to Christianity, have deeded towns, live in English houses, wear English clothes, and worship Puritan style in Meeting houses.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between 1651 and 1658, Eliot and his assistant Daniel Gookin organized seven Praying Indian Villages in Massachusetts Bay Colony, and Nashoba was the sixth.  All told there were at least 14 such villages in Massachusetts with between 45 to 60 inhabitants each.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In an interesting twist, Eliot allowed the Indians to choose the sites of their new Villages.  The local Concord Indians led by an early convert, their Sachem Tahattawan, requested the &amp;quot;nashope&amp;quot; lands close by.  With such latitude to location, it would not be unexpected for the Indians to choose places that were special or important to them.  It is also known from Eliot that &amp;quot;nashope&amp;quot; was Tahattawan’s main residence, again marking these lands as desirable. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Indian Plantation of Nashoba [also spelled Nashobah] was formally granted by General Court in 1651 and was laid out in a lozenge-shape carved from a gore of unsettled lands situated between Groton, Chelmsford, Concord, and Lancaster.  Its sides were approximately 3 x 4 x 4 x 4 miles in length and the area encompassed most of current day Littleton and a portion of Boxborough (which was formerly Littleton).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Village thrived until King Phillip’s Indian War in 1675-76, when the Nashobas were rounded up and dumped on Deer Island in Boston Harbor to freeze and starve.  Only a handful survived to return.  The Plantation was rapidly sold to English settlers seeking land and by 1714, it was completely in English hands as the Town of Nashoba, and re-incorporated as the Town of Littleton in 1715.  The surviving Indians were given the Indian New Town, a 500 acre tract of rocky hill between and including portions of Nagog Pond and Fort Pond (which was named after the Indian fort there).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is an oral tradition in Littleton that Sarah Doublet (the last Indian to hold title to the 500 Acre Indian Reservation of 1714) lived in a cave somewhere in what is now the Sarah Doublet Forest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 495 &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 31, Route 119 East toward Littleton. &lt;br /&gt;Stay straight to go onto GREAT RD/MA-119/2A.  &lt;br /&gt;Go about 3 miles and watch for a large horse farm on your right, then the &amp;quot;Entering Acton&amp;quot; sign on your right.  &lt;br /&gt;The turn onto Nashoba Road is just after the Acton sign. &lt;br /&gt;Take a RIGHT onto Nashoba Road (the right is before the traffic light at the pond). &lt;br /&gt;Follow Nashoba Road for a mile or so to a Stop sign. &lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the Stop Sign. &lt;br /&gt;Go less than 1/4 mile and take a left onto Charter Road (a small dirt driveway) &lt;br /&gt;Follow the dirt road to the parking area at the top of the hill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 2 West from 95 &lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 2 West to the rotary at the Concord Prison.  &lt;br /&gt;At the rotary, take your second right onto route 2A. &lt;br /&gt; Follow 2A past the intersection with Route 27.  &lt;br /&gt;About a mile or so after crossing 27, you'll see a pond on your left. &lt;br /&gt;Go through the lights at the pond (they are for  the shopping plaza on the right) &lt;br /&gt;Take an almost  immediate left onto Nashoba Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Follow for a mile or so to a Stop sign. &lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the Stop Sign. &lt;br /&gt;Go less than 1/4 mile and take a left onto Charter Road (a small dirt driveway) &lt;br /&gt;Follow the dirt road to the parking area at the top of the hill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.littletonconservationtrust.org/guide/sarah-doublet/sarahdoublet.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.littletonc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Access is by way of Charter Road (a dirt road) leading off Nashoba Road. A Trust sign is on the corner of this dirt road and Nashoba Road. The dirt road leads to a parking area on the left where another Trust sign is located. Another access way is through the Ed Bell trail starting at the town-owned parking lot on Nagog Hill Road. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear a Meetup name tag.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276639374000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274758908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Hike: Sarah Doublet Forest</name><id>13586084</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275750000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/13586084/</event_url></item>