<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Broad St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.559936</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-347-2528</phone><name>Russell Library</name><city>Middletown</city><id>720835</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.652034</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>COME HEAR THE PLAN! OPERATION PEOPLE POWER!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for the details of the Pathway to Critical Mass and the Profound Plan to restore Constitutional Governance throughout the land!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bob Schulz, Chairman of the We The People Foundation for Constitutional Education will be speaking at the Russell Library, 123 Broad Street, Middletown, CT on Saturday, June 12 at 10 am, giving us all the information about the national movement to restore the Constitution and rid ourselves of government tyranny.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you tired of a government that doesn't listen to you? Are you tired of sending &amp;quot;good&amp;quot;people to Hartford or Washington and then having them vote for laws that are unconstitutional?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you tired of your only choices being Republican or Democrat career politicians?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you tired of your pockets being picked to fund unconstitutional laws or given to corporations &amp;quot;too big to fail&amp;quot; or to people more interested in being on the dole than being productive citizens?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then join with your fellow patriots across the nation to stop the madness and the slide to socialism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come hear what it's all about on Saturday, June 12 at 10 am at the Russell Library,&lt;br /&gt;123 Broad Street in Middletown. The conference is free but seating is limited, so call now for your reservation. Estelle Stevenson (203)518-0948.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276370833000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276312351000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bob Schulz of We the People Speaks</name><id>13776477</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276351200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/13776477/</event_url></item>