<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1904 Canton Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.223400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 333-0690</phone><name>Blue Hills Trailside Museum</name><city>Milton</city><id>669267</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116940</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hiking for Justice has been requested over the years by several SoJusters - we're excited to finally be hosting it! We'll be hiking up a trail in the Blue Hills reservation and then having lunch together nearby at Suffolk Grille.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Need a ride? Have space in your car?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please post a note when you RSVP (or on the wall of the event) so we can help coordinate carpools.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Thinking about biking there?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post that and we'll try to coordinate riders heading there together - and can provide a suggested route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hiking Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're starting out by meeting in the parking lot of the Blue Hills Trailside Museum. We'll take the red (rugged) trail up to Eliot Tower and catch our breath while taking in the great views. Then we'll take the blue Skyline trail (more great views) over to green (less rugged) trail - Puddle's Path turns into Wolcott Path - down to the Trailside Museum. Total hiking time is estimated to be 2-2 1/2 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, we'll head over to Suffolk Grille, which is about a half mile from the Trailside Museum, for lunch. Check out their &lt;a href="http://suffolkgrille.com/pdf_files/Luncheon_menu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;menu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/BlwU8BxSwL2rPGjenlTloswB_O-mJZ3G66QQIIIRj8V0m7tnkRHEc-5VB0nLNdz1djiM0Tear4Hr1BYrEkCHnTcw1Q=s512" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So look no further if you want to cross-promote your events and campaigns, you're seeking like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over 1300 members and 3 1/2+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277762992000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275227941000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking for Justice</name><id>13638200</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277650800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/13638200/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/b/global_4697339.jpeg</photo_url></item>