<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Inca Trail!&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.3viajesaldia.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/04/machu_picchu.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.3viajesaldia.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/04/machu_picchu.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;December 11th – December 19th, 26th, or ?&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Approximate Cost:&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;$1,600&lt;/span&gt; for 8 days&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;$1900&lt;/span&gt; for n14+ days -- No joke, really! &lt;br /&gt;*The primary costs are the airfare and the trek – the rest is downright dirt-cheap-inexpensive.  Welcome to peru!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total Deposit&lt;b&gt; $750&lt;/b&gt; - you are responsible for the rest. Read on. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;____________________________&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GREETINGS EVERYONE!  Seriously, if this isn't a trip of a lifetime then you're money back. ok, false advertising about the return your money part, but I've come up with a way for everyone to win in a big way. I'm currently in Bolivia and am spending a year traveling just two countries, maybe three - bolivia, peru and ecuador. My goal is to learn everything there is to possibly learn about Inca history and the history and culture of as many pre-Inca civilizations i can handle in the year. And yes, to trek my butt off while doing it.  I swear this is the most beautiful place on earth for me - it's literally so stunning that I feel if you were thinking of doing something like this but never had the knowhow, just think about it. I purposefully chose and became closely affiliated with a great trekking company which agreed to slash it's prices if i could bring a group down, and i get the benefit of being on the &amp;quot;inside&amp;quot; and have at cost access to all their treks. So it's a great deal for all of us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, I understand this is holiday season so you can choose how long you want to stay after the trek. So for the minimum stay of 8 days, we’re going to hike the classic 4d/3n Inca Trail that ends in Machu Picchu.  This requires 2 days of travel, one from home to Cuzco and then another for your return at the end, and a mandatory 2 days of acclimation in Cuzco, 11,000 feet. On the trek itself, all you do is trek. They will set up the campsites, cook our meals (3x/day), break down each site, and yes, CARRY ALL OF OUR GEAR other than your daypack. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here's what's Included in the trek&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Transportation from hotel to Km 82&lt;br /&gt;• Cook, cooking equipment, dining tent, tables and chairs&lt;br /&gt;• Porter to carry all of your gear up to a maximum of 15kg&lt;br /&gt;• Meals during the excursion (3 breakfasts, 3 lunches, 3 dinners and 3 Snacks / optional vegetarian). &lt;br /&gt;• Tea time everyday (tea, coffee, wantan, popcorn, cracker.)&lt;br /&gt;• Professional bilingual guide&lt;br /&gt;• Cook, assistant and carriers for the camping and food equipment&amp;#61472;&lt;br /&gt;• Cooking tent and camping equipment for the contributors (Porters)&lt;br /&gt;• Entrance fees for the Inca Trail and the sanctuary of Machu Picchu.&lt;br /&gt;• Tourist train from Aguas Calientes to Cusco or Aguas Calientes to Ollantaytambo and Cusco by bus.&lt;br /&gt;• First-aid kit, oxygen bottle and safety rope.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;____________________________&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About me. I’m a Peru and Inca freak - it's totally true and I'm proud of it.   I’ve personally done all the legwork for before and after the actual trek and think this itinerary is amazing.  I’ve cut out all the middlemen (other than our trek organizer, Karina from Munayki-Peru, who’s the BEST!) and came up with a price for everyone that’s about half (or less) than if you booked all this through an American tour company.  Seriously, I’ve hand-picked everything.  But I could only do this with the carrot of getting at least 10 people. And know this – because it’s really important. Prices down here in Peru for food and incidentals are DIRT DIRT CHEAP.  Your dollars will go forever here so expenditures won’t add up fast even if you try.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the trek ends and we descend from Machu Picchu on the 7th day, this is where the 2nd leg begins for those who choose to stay. And believe me, I’m 1000% sure you’ll curse yourself if you miss it.  I’ve personally mapped out a route where we’ll see the entire Sacred Valley of the Incas, starting with Ollaytantanbo and ending in Pisac where I think the ruins there come in 2nd place to Machu Picchu.  For those five days we’ll pack in so much hiking and climbing and great sightseeing - and shopping for those who want to.  The Andes are simply insane -- the Rockies will seem like ant hills.  Expect to climb and descend some serious elevations. You WILL exert yourself. This I promise - but almost anyone can do it so don't be intimidated. I did it with a knee I damaged just 2 months before, and because of a shoulder injury, i could do no exercising either. i could have gone another week. strenuous yes, impossible no. I know of 60+ year olds who finished in style. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to a trip i ran late august into early september. There you'll see what people thought of the journey and you can probably get a good impression of what to expect.  :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hvhikers/calendar/13591560/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what you'll need to pay for in your deposit, and then what you need to pay on your own:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deposit: $750 and pays for the trek, internal r/t flight from lima to cuzco, your 1st nite stay at hotel in Cuzco, and private porter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Own costs:&lt;/b&gt; (these are more or less accurate)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;International flight to Lima - $735 thru american airlines as of time of posting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hotel 2nd night and night before you return to Lima - $70 total maximum depending on occupancy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ticket for all the ruins in Cuzco and Sacred Valley  - $40 total&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 nights in Ollaytantambo - $25 total for both nites&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 nights in Pisac - $30 total for three nights&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;transportation from Ollaytantambo to ruins to Pisac for the day - $20&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;optional day trips from Pisac to ancient caves and to medicinal hot springs - $20-30 total&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Total = $800&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: The trek i just organnized filled up well, but only after everyone was hit with the deadline as if they wanted to see if anyone else signed up before they made their own deposit. This serves to only hurt everyone, including yourself. CONSIDER THIS THE DEADLINE ALREADY.   If there isn't enough interest, you will absolutely get a complete and full refund but at the time i'm listing this, we already have four people paid and more are coming shortly so we're going!  I have no interest in keeping anyone's money if the trip doesn't fill. And airfare only goes up not down. We don't have much time before December 11th so please sign up fast and when we hit 10 people, you can all buy your flights.  Also, there is a limited number of spaces the government provides for the Inca Trail. Let's not lose out by delaying. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;____________________________&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEND DEPOSITS TO: keng223@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;kindly note there is a fee for not linking your bank account to paypal. If you pay via credit card, please include an extra $18 so I am not responsible for it. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Links to Photos:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/104071400636929104697/Hotel?authkey=Gv1sRgCM63uLXKssO5cQ&amp;amp;feat=directlinkhttp://picasaweb.google.com/104071400636929104697/Hotel?authkey=Gv1sRgCM63uLXKssO5cQ&amp;amp;feat=directlink"&gt;Hotel in Cusco (photos) &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/104071400636929104697/VilcabambaTrekAugust24th2010?authkey=Gv1sRgCOSbqOjg6LWyswE&amp;amp;feat=directlink"&gt;Vilcabamba Meetup Trek (Aug 24, 2010)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;____________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peru Packing List&lt;br /&gt;Clothes (essential)&lt;br /&gt;2 non cotton tshirts&lt;br /&gt;2 non cotton long sleeve shirts&lt;br /&gt;2 pair non cotton hiking/trekking pants&lt;br /&gt;3-4 pair wool socks&lt;br /&gt;Hiking boots gortex preferred&lt;br /&gt;1 fleece or warm sweater/sweatshirt&lt;br /&gt;Sneakers (to give your boots a rest, optional)&lt;br /&gt;Sleepwear&lt;br /&gt;More underwear than you think you may need&lt;br /&gt;*the rest is up to you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you should buy in Cuzco: total cost $12&lt;br /&gt;Alpaca sweater&lt;br /&gt;Alpaca gloves&lt;br /&gt;Alpaca hat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you can buy in Cuzco: &lt;br /&gt;Fun peru t-shirts ($3-10 each)&lt;br /&gt;Tons of inexpensive clothes and gifts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Accessories&lt;br /&gt;Backpack&lt;br /&gt;Daypack&lt;br /&gt;Headlamp&lt;br /&gt;rain hat&lt;br /&gt;pancho (breathable) * if you have a tarp for your daypack you can bring a weatherproof jacket, but panchos are best because they cover your pack too. &lt;br /&gt;Trekking poles if you have them, otherwise you can buy walking sticks here for cheap&lt;br /&gt;Deet&lt;br /&gt;Sunglasses&lt;br /&gt;Sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;All purpose tool &lt;br /&gt;Earplugs (just in case you have a snorer in your tent)&lt;br /&gt;Camera with an extra battery or two&lt;br /&gt;First aid: bandaids, disinfectant, advil, blister pads just in case&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken</member_name><member_id>68115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292073338000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286326568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MACHU PICCHU AND THE CLASSIC INCA TRAIL + THE SACRED VALLEY OF THE INCAS</name><id>15015816</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292068800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15015816/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/6/5/global_18525429.jpeg</photo_url></item>