<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>705 N Shore Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02151</zip><lat>42.428020</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 284 7800</phone><name>Ocean View Kennel</name><city>Revere</city><id>302549</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.982704</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NEXT MONTH'S MEET:  JULY 15&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As many of you who attended our last meetup heard already, we are going to have a special Boston Maltese Meet on July 15th at Ocean View Kennel, 705 North Shore Drive, Revere, MA (right on the ocean; tel # (781) 284 7800 with Lisa Cutter, who visited our last meetup and spoke with us about dogs and how they play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ONLY MALTESE FROM OUR GROUP WILL PARTICIPATE IN LISA'S PROGRAM OF ACTIVITIES.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME:   1-4pm as usual.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa's family (including her mother who owns three Maltese, one of whom is mine) owns Ocean View Kennel and Lisa runs doggie daycare activities there every week.  She told us about the space (roomy play yards fenced with 8 foot high fencing and surfaced with gravel)  in which  she will run games and activities for our dogs  which is separate from where we can talk, eat, etc. We will be able to  watch our dogs playing games, etc. through a window.  It turned out at our last meet, as Lisa pointed out, that our dogs are too interested in sitting with us and also &amp;quot;protecting&amp;quot; us at our usual location to join in with Lisa and her activities. And that to enable them to do so, they would have to be in a separate, but visible space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will send out directions later on, but in the meanwhile, you can turn to Ocean View Kennel's website at   www.oceanviewkennel.com .    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                      *  *  *  *  *  *  *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPECIAL NOTE:  It is with great sadness that I report that yet another one of our little Maltese, Bella, owned by  the Spagnolos of Wakefield, has met with an untimely death at the hands of a bigger dog.  While out on a walk with her twelve year old owner, Bella was attacked by a pit bull WHO WAS NOT ON A LEASH  and who snuffed out her little life.  We will post a picture of Bella in Memoriam on my website, www.laptopmaltese.com in the Gallery Page.  Our hearts go out to the Spagnolos.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And after seeing this happen to other Maltese owners,  I am going out on a limb to make a strong recommendation:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DON'T TAKE YOUR MALTESE FOR A WALK , but if you MUST DO SO, CARRY BEAR MACE.  I know of a couple Maltese owners that always carry bear mace with them when on a walk due to past bad experiences.   It seems extreme, but the risk is not worth it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone wishing to extend sympathies to the family can email me (laptopmaltese@aol.com)and I'll give you their email address.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184692335000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181761271000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Maltese Meet Special Event - at Ocean View Kennel with Lisa Cutter</name><id>5887708</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184518800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/5887708/</event_url></item>