<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Dudley Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.280804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-877-4036</phone><name>Cushing Memorial Park</name><city>Framingham</city><id>935388</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.431477</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/a/c/event_211570412.jpeg" width="213" height="167" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Come celebrate St. Patrick's Day by showing off your green and your Bully Breed Ambassador. As always all breeds welcome! Since There is more snow on it's way I chose Cushing Memorial Park on Dudley Road in Framingham, Ma.  It is a 1 mile paved loop that gets plowed all winter.  If the weather permits we can extend our walk out of the park and make it 2.5 mile loop.  We will meet near the Cushing Chapel.  There is parking infront of the Chapel, and (after the snow melts) on the side of the Chapel (Dr. Harvey L Cushing Way).  Feel free to show some St. Patricks's Day colors (that would be green).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BEFORE ATTENDING, PLEASE READ BELOW:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just a friendly reminder regarding etiquette at NEBBC-hosted/sponsored events, but nevertheless needs to be taken very seriously and is expected to be followed, especially considering the size of the club and all the newbies! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Dog/Handler Etiquette:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ The person holding your dog's leash should be YOU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ NO flexi-leashes. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Avoid head-on greetings between dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ &lt;em&gt;Until&lt;/em&gt; you are familiar with individual dogs AND handlers, contact between dogs must be kept to a minimum. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Prevent your dog from lunging on leash, whether it is in play or not. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Dog(s) must be kept under owner control &lt;em&gt;at all times.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Do not allow your dog to surprise, or "sneak up on" other dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ A VERY important note: Just because two dogs are friendly, does &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; necessarily mean they are going to be friendly with &lt;em&gt;each other&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Make no assumptions and DO NOT LET YOUR DOG GREET ANOTHER DOG until you have asked and BEEN GIVEN PERMISSION by the owner.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ If your dog is reactive, use your good judgement.  (Be up front, and give everyone their space.  Do not "test" if your dog will be ok by letting him go up to unsuspecting dogs/handlers if you've known him to be aggressive toward either.)  Muzzling is an option and an opportunity to still expose your dog while keeping everyone safe.  Take all necessary precautions.  You are still representing our club and our dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~ Dog must be wearing a securely fitting collar/harness or combo thereof with NO chance of slipping it. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This is not intended to sound harsh, but with the size of the club and with our emphasis on raising awareness &amp;amp; promoting responsible ownership, it is very important that this etiquette be taken seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not hesitate to contact Cassie-Leigh Stock at justcassie101@gmail.com with any questions or concerns.  Remember, we want you to be there!  We just need to all be responsible for the safety of our dogs &amp;amp; of others around us.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maria Soma</member_name><member_id>12357610</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363563856000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359119446000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>St. Pitties Day Walk!</name><id>101319992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363532400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/101319992/</event_url></item>