<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 288-1807</phone><name>Unitarian Society of New Haven</name><city>Hamden</city><id>105528</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"How to Get Media Attention and Promote Your Group"  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In this intensive training workshop, activists will be taught the ins and outs of the following:  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Writing effective letters to the editor &lt;br /&gt;

Writing effective press releases  &lt;br /&gt;

Holding press conferences and carrying out publicity stunts &lt;br /&gt;

Preparing talking points for media appearances &lt;br /&gt;

Handling yourself on radio, TV, and with print reporters &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Also covered will be powerful ways to use online social media. For many volunteer groups this has the advantage of no cost and less formality. And many activists are already involved in social media and simply need to focus their efforts more organizationally. Included in this topic area are ideas on the following:  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Developing an improved Web presence &lt;br /&gt;

Spreading your message through Facebook &lt;br /&gt;

Making effective use of blogs and online forums &lt;br /&gt;

Producing viral videos    &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The secret behind all of this is "message clarification" in advance of media campaigns. It's the core of this no-nonsense, succeed-every-time seminar that has been given to groups all over the country as UnitedCoR builds and promotes local coalitions from coast to coast. Practical handouts will be provided, but come prepared to take notes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your seminar presenter is Fred Edwords, national director of the United Coalition of Reason. He has over 35 years experience in freethought leadership, having served as executive director of the American Humanist Association, editor of the &lt;em&gt;Humanist&lt;/em&gt; magazine, and president of Camp Quest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daisy</member_name><member_id>3632340</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361052668000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Atheist-Humanist-Society-of-CT-and-RI</urlname><id>1443202</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0299987793</group_lon><name>Atheist Humanist Society of CT and RI</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357757379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Publicity / Billboard Workshop with Fred Edwords</name><id>98761672</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361041200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Atheist-Humanist-Society-of-CT-and-RI/events/98761672/</event_url></item>