<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Noonhill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02052</zip><lat>42.158528</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Noon Hill Reservation</name><city>Medfield </city><id>1223503</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.302945</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Trustees of Reservations will hold its March Hike of the Month on March 28th from 1pm to 3 pm at Noon Hill located on Noon Hill Road, in Medfield.  Explore a new trail, uncover historic facts, and meet other hikers.  Join a ranger from the Trustees, a member from Friends of Medfield Forest and Trails, and our growing group of hikers as we venture to the top of Noon Hill for a view of the rolling hills of Walpole and Norfolk.  This event is free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From intersection of Rts. 27 and 109 in Medfield, take Rt. 109 West for 0.1 mi. and immediately turn left onto Causeway St. Follow for 1.3 mi. and turn left onto Noon Hill Rd. Entrance and parking (15 cars) on right.  There is limited parking so carpooling is recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Noon Hill&lt;br /&gt;204 acres  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ascend the hill to enjoy treetop vistas, amble around Holt Pond, or follow trails that leads through an adjacent Trustees reservation to the Charles River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes Noon Hill a special place?&lt;br /&gt;In the heart of historic Medfield, you can discover woodlands, waters-edge views of the Charles River, and abundant wildlife. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wooded trails wind through the varied terrain of Noon Hill, making it perfect for hiking, cross-country skiing, mountain biking, and horseback riding. At 370 feet, Noon Hill rises gently above the surrounding landscape. Follow the short trail that leads to its peak and you'll be rewarded with sweeping views south across the rolling hills of Walpole and Norfolk. A loop trail around Holt Pond gives you a wonderful opportunity to explore freshwater habitat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A short trail extension across Causeway Street connects Noon Hill to Shattuck Reservation. Both reservations are managed with adjacent conservation land owned by the Town of Medfield.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spring brings a variety of migratory songbirds and wildflowers such as pink lady’s slippers and Canada mayflower. The properties and surrounding lands provide habitat for white-tailed deer, red fox, raccoon, and ruffed grouse. During the fall, Noon Hill makes a great place to watch the annual hawk migration, when raptors wing their way south for the winter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thousands of years ago, glacial action carved depressions through the hill. Exposed bedrock along the tops of the ridges is further evidence of the glacial activity that shaped the land. The reservation's slopes and ridges are forested with pine, beech, birch, and hemlock; in spring, the forest floor is scattered with wildflowers. From the height of Noon Hill, the land slopes gently toward the Charles River and its tributary, the Stop River. Many lowland areas have become red maple swamps, and much of the land to the north and east of the Reservation is floodplain of the Stop River, a tributary of the Charles River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails&lt;br /&gt;4.5 miles of trails. Moderate hiking, strenuous in places. Noon Hill is a link in the Bay Circuit Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When to Visit&lt;br /&gt;Year-round, daily, sunrise to sunset. Allow a minimum of 1 hour, 2 hours if also visiting Shattuck Reservation. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in front of CVS pharmacy.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269967020000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269017659000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Noon Hill walk, Medfield</name><id>12933221</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269793800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/12933221/</event_url></item>