<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Start-Me-Up: Legal Advice Lunch Series for College Entrepreneurs, Sep 28&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; September 28: Legal Overview for Start-Ups&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT – This program will provide an initial understanding of the various company structures - including corporations, limited liability companies, sole proprietorship and partnerships - as well as other fundamental legal issues related to launching a new company, such as granting equity to founders and adopting critical employee and consulting agreements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN – Tuesday, September 28th, 12-2pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE – Flybridge Capital, 500 Boylston Street, 18th floor, Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; November 16: Intellectual Property for Start-Ups&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT – This program will provide you with insight into intellectual property law and practical advice on what you can do now to protect your IP and what you should be planning to do as your start-up develops and grows.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN – Tuesday, November 16th, 12-2pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE – Pepper Hamilton, 125 High Street, 15th Floor, Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speakers: Robin Lockwood, Senior Associate at Flybridge Capital; Kate Castle, Vice President of Marketing at Flybridge Capital; and Robert Chow, Partner at Pepper Hamilton&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register now at &lt;a href="http://thecapitalnetwork.cloverpad.org/Events" target="_blank"&gt;http://thecapitalnetw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This FREE lunch series is presented by: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Capital Network is a Boston based non-profit organization providing programming and networking opportunities to entrepreneurs looking to build the skills necessary for creating your own start-up company.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay-in-MA, a program of Flybridge Capital, provides programming at an affordable cost for students currently enrolled in Massachusetts colleges.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pepper Hamilton LLP, a multi-practice law firm with more than 500 lawyers nationally.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289936003000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284997784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intellectual Property for Start-Ups</name><id>14832061</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289926800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/14832061/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>