<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>(address email to confirmed registrants.)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.350384</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Beautiful Private Home</name><city>Newton</city><id>1270046</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.186440</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>95.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Saturday, Aug 28, 11am-5pm, $75/person PREPAID BY MON, AUG 16, $95 thereafter &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are discounted spots for two or three single females to gender balance at $50. Email me if interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you crave deeper intimacy and sensual connection in your relationship(s)?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are you curious about integrating spirituality and sexuality?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would you like to explore a quality of touch that nourishes not only the body, but also the soul?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this experiential workshop you will learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To cultivate Exquisite Presence for Soulful Connection&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The elements to create your own individualized Sensual Rituals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to effectively Provide and Receive Nourishment and Healing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keys to Accessing Greater Pleasure ~ while Giving or Receiving&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tantric Breathing to Ignite and Circulate Sexual Energy ~ Within in you and Between you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this clothes-on workshop you will learn tantric principles and practices to create a sacred container, enhance connection, energy cultivation and exchange, and give and receive deeply nourishing touch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benefits you will walk away with:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Concrete tools to take your connection to new depths&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Skills to access new horizons of pleasure&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced trust and ability to surrender&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to all, regardless of relationship status, gender identity or sexual orientation. You may attend alone or with a partner or a friend. No previous experience necessary. Beginners welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Limited Space. Register early to assure your spot!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The location will be at a beautiful private home in Newton Center, with a watsu pool. Directions will be emailed to confirmed registrants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Bodyworker, Tantra Educator and Intimacy Coach with over twenty years experience in the field of body-mind integration. Her training in Massage therapy, CranioSacral Therapy, Taoist and Hindu Tantric Practices, Meditation and Body-Oriented Psychotherapy provides a uniquely integrative approach to Conscious Relating and Sacred Sexuality. She is passionate about assisting others in increasing their capacity for Intimacy and Pleasure, and in accessing their full Aliveness and Passion! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more info or to inquire about Private Coaching, contact Brynn via email (organizer) or call 415-244-1652. &lt;i&gt;Free initial phone consultation!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;What past students of this workshop have said:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;“My soul was deeply nourished. It was a good blend of experiential and didactic. Wonderful group of like-minded souls! ”  - Laurie A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “This was a wonderful, comfortable way to learn about some of the Tantric principles. I enjoyed this very much and feel open to learning more. ” – Karen W&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “This was a very good course... The group leader Brynn was fantastic... I would recommend this seminar to anyone with a curiosity about touch and what role it plays in one's own life, as well as what role it may play in your relationship with others. I am very glad I took the seminar and am looking forward to some more exploration. ” – Michelle O&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Address will be emailed to confirmed registrants</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283097812000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279686599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Principles of Sacred Sensual Touch</name><id>14166046</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283007600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/14166046/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/a/0/global_9965280.jpeg</photo_url></item>