<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/5/6/2/event_83177762.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Come join us this new year with silly hats, funny shirts, and just have some plain old fun for our modern day 2012 winter celebration without the woo! This will be pot luck style as usual. For those attending, it will be helpful if you can list your food, drinks, and/or snacks that you can contribute under this Meetup event page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The science swap was really fun last year, so we&amp;rsquo;re doing it again! Be creative, have fun, and no need to go shopping for this. Bring some kind of wrapped up science, reason, or skeptic themed item from your home. Some ideas: book, video, uniquely themed item, etc. If you feel inclined to purchase something, keep it around $15. This was a blast last year. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see all the interesting items. We will probably swap around 8pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll also honor the late great Christopher Hitchens with a fun poster board. Bring your favorite quotes or pictures to stick on the board. You can prepare something at home if you&amp;rsquo;d like, but you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to make it during the party. Darrick&amp;rsquo;s got his favorite quote and he can&amp;rsquo;t wait to put it up. A fight may break out for the best quotes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll play some rounds of quick party games. Hmm... and maybe some prizes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The past years' parties have been fun and we're looking forward to bringing our friends back together for another great time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darrick Fauvel</member_name><member_id>2719698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326114532000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lowellatheists</urlname><id>13032</id><group_lat>42.6300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3300018311</group_lon><name>Atheists of Greater Lowell</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325477151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Season of Reason Party!</name><id>46218722</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325970000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lowellatheists/events/46218722/</event_url></item>