<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Fenway Park</address_2><address_1>82A Lansdowne Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.347164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 262-2424</phone><name>The Bleacher Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>735764</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097854</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Red Sox Natives Organizers and the Bleacher Bar thank you for all of your support! RSVPs and on-line ticket sales are now closed. Limited $20.00 tickets will be available at the door for early arrivals! Remember to bring your cameras!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A special thank you goes out to our sponsor Games Away Tours Inc. for their generous raffle and event ticket donations that helped make this event possible.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday is the last day to purchase your $15.00 event and raffle tickets for this event on line as RSVPs will be closed at 6 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAFFLE PRIZE - Day Trip for 2 from Games Away Tours Inc. to New York Citi Field with Mets vs Cardinals Game Tickets on July 29 (motorcoach transportation included). Purchase a ticket to this event and you are entered into the raffle. Natives purchasing tickets for friends receive additional entries. You do not have to be present to win the raffle. ***Stay and watch the Celtics vs Lakers Game 4 at 9 pm too!***      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets to this event have now been made available to other groups and the general public. Please purchase your tickets in advance before it sells out.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Wally the Green Monster for Happy Hour at Bleacher Bar.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a private event coordinated by the Red Sox Natives, so come out and support one of our more unique and biggest events! One of your Organizers, Beth runs the Bleacher Bar and is looking forward to meeting more of the Natives.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sox will be out of town, playing Cleveland at 7:05pm and the game will be shown throughout the bar.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes on this event:     &lt;br /&gt;- Arrive at 6:30pm before Wally arrives at 7pm.    &lt;br /&gt;(He will be off leash, so there is no telling what he might do to a late comer)    &lt;br /&gt;- Light food/apps will be provided    &lt;br /&gt;- Includes hot dog buffet     &lt;br /&gt;- You receive a Wally photo card    &lt;br /&gt;- Take your own photo with Wally    &lt;br /&gt;- Wally is a pretty popular monster and commands an appearance fee. The charge for this event goes to secure his Wallyness and the appetizers. &lt;br /&gt;-cash bar &lt;br /&gt;-bleacher bar menu available for order  &lt;br /&gt;-stay and watch Celtics vs Lakers Game 4 which begins at 9 pm   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAFFLE &amp;amp; GIVEAWAYS -    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Games Away Tours Inc. Day Trip for 2 to New York Citi Field for Mets vs Cardinals with Game Tickets on Thursday, July 29. Transportation by Motorcoach is included.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-$50.00 Gift Card from our Host, The Bleacher Bar    &lt;br /&gt;-Natives Author Steve Masse will be giving away his just released book &amp;quot;Short Circus&amp;quot; Summer time   Reading at its best!    &lt;br /&gt;-50 Fenway Stickers from sponsor Suphafans Streetware who will be at the Bleacher Bar     &lt;br /&gt;-Christopher Klein will be giving away his book &amp;quot;A Die-Hard Sports Fan's Guide to Boston&amp;quot;    &lt;br /&gt;-Autographed Keith Lockhart CD of Red Sox Music  &lt;br /&gt;-Sam Adams Swag Bag   &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;-Any money left over will be pooled into our Natives charity fund. (To grow and be distributed to a worthwhile cause YOU will have a chance to vote on at our yearly Natives Cavalcade to Quorum in the fall.)    &lt;br /&gt;- The starting cost for this event is $15, and is subject to increase as the RSVP's increase. (More Wally time and apps) So get in early and cheap! Tickets will be $20.00 at the door if available.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited spots - Payment required in advance on line - This will be fun....    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beth    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jon     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frank    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>6918204</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1276794887000</updated><rating><average>4.94999980927</average><count>20</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>129</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269361041000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Natives Happy Hour with WALLY! (A Natives Exclusive event!)</name><id>12968080</id><headcount>110</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276209000000</time><rsvp_limit>130</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/12968080/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/1/global_14028673.jpeg</photo_url></item>