<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Northampton, MA</address_2><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.320000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159330</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.660004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.anoblelie.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/f/6/event_97482742.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Valley 9/11 Truth had planned to host a forum on March 31st to discuss 9/11 truth actions ten years after.. However, organizers at our &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/48862262/"&gt;last meeting&lt;/a&gt; from Connecticut and the Berkshires decided to have an informal forum instead at &lt;a href="https://nationalpeaceconference.org/Home_Page.html"&gt;this Conference in Stamford, CT&lt;/a&gt; a week earlier. This is the reason for changing an all-day to just an evening event. Please note the new date and time for this event. We will likely begin the &lt;strong&gt;film at 7:00PM&lt;/strong&gt;, beginning at 6:00 please come for checking out resources that will be available and for an informal meeting with Valley 9/11 Truth to plan on our next program. You are welcome to bring food and drink to this meeting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is a review on the film:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentary A Noble Lie exposes Oklahoma City bombing as government&amp;nbsp;black-op&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;small&gt;Posted: February 27, 2012&amp;nbsp;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://truthandshadows.files.wordpress.com/2012/02/oklahoma_city_bombing.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://truthandshadows.files.wordpress.com/2012/02/oklahoma_city_bombing.jpg?w=614" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Craig McKee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The official narrative is simple: A right-wing extremist and his accomplice struck a blow against the American government by setting off a truck bomb in front of the Alfred P. Murrah Federal Building in Oklahoma City, April 19, 1995.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The result was 168 dead, including 19 children, and more than 800 injured. The bombing left the American people fearing a new &amp;ldquo;terrorist&amp;rdquo; enemy: the home-grown, militia-loving, anti-government extremist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good story. Not true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth about Oklahoma City involved not only a terrible human tragedy but also a story of government conspiracy, media complicity, destruction of evidence, intimidation, and torture. It happened two years after the 1993 bombing of the World Trade Center and six years before the false flag operation of 9/11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Film producer Christopher Emery began researching the Oklahoma City bombing back in 2000, even moving to Oklahoma City from New Mexico in 2003 so he could be close to witnesses and other sources of information. The result of all these years of work is a remarkable piece of investigative journalism and documentary filmmaking called &lt;em&gt;A Noble Lie.&lt;/em&gt; The film does the work that the mainstream media refused, and still refuses, to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re trying to rewrite history,&amp;rdquo; Emery says. &amp;ldquo;We want to make sure this never happens again.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The title, as we&amp;rsquo;re told at the beginning of the film, is taken from Plato&amp;rsquo;s Republic and refers to the propping up of a myth in order to maintain social harmony and keep the elite in their present position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film features powerful never-before-seen TV footage and interviews with survivors, victims&amp;rsquo; family members, police officers, rescue workers, and citizen investigators who have been fighting to expose the truth for the past 17 years. It also uses government documents to reveal new information to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also interviewed is talk show host and activist Alex Jones, who is a major supporter of the film. Jones says that in the months leading up to the bombing, the media were actively conditioning the population to fear militant extremists. He says that people are starting to see through false flag ops like Oklahoma City and 9/11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The government is going to have trouble in the future engineering atrocities like Oklahoma City because the public is really getting wise to their tricks,&amp;rdquo; Jones said in the film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;A Noble&lt;/em&gt; Lie, we learn that ATF employees (Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives) who worked in the Murrah Building received messages on their pagers prior to the bombing telling them not to go to work. And when the bomb went off at 9:02 a.m. none of the children of ATF workers were present in the building&amp;rsquo;s daycare center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film also reveals that the public persona of convicted bomber Timothy McVeigh was a complete fabrication. Rather than being a radical who hated the government, Emery says, he was actually a CIA sharpshooter and assassin who had been involved in covert government drug trafficking operations. He had been decorated several times, even receiving one commendation while he was in prison for the bombing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;McVeigh was a very cunning, very talented sharpshooter,&amp;rdquo; Emery says, &amp;ldquo;He was a puppet, a showpiece for the official narrative.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emery says that McVeigh&amp;rsquo;s job was to infiltrate militia groups and pose as an anti-government extremist to build up this false persona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parallel that jumps out when you consider this aspect of the plot is to Lee Harvey Oswald, the man who the media still refers to as the assassin of President John F. Kennedy even though he was never charged with the crime. Oswald had a persona created for him as well so it would appear that anti-U.S. entities were really behind the assassination. The government created a cover story that Oswald was a Communist (he defected to the Soviet Union only to come right back) when in fact he had been an operative for U.S. military intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Noble Lie&lt;/em&gt; also conclusively proves that the blast damage at the Murrah Building could not have come from the truck bomb that McVeigh is alleged to have placed there. Debris was blown &lt;em&gt;out&lt;/em&gt; from the building, travelling hundreds of feet against the force of the blast. If the truck bomb had done all the damage, the force would have blown debris &lt;em&gt;into&lt;/em&gt; the building. Emery says one of the rubber seals that held the windows in place on the north side of the building was found a block and a half away after the blasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film also provides proof that there was more than one blast, with timed charges, planted in the building, set to go off over a period of several seconds. Some survivors avoided death when they ducked under their desks after the initial blast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We learn the heartbreaking story of patrolman Terrance Yeakey, who was one of the first to respond after the bombing took place (he was there is less than 10 minutes) and who was credited with saving several lives that day. Yeakey was collecting evidence about the bombing, and he was subjected to daily harassment and intimidation from his fellow officers because he refused to go along with the official version of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His early arrival at the site showed the government&amp;rsquo;s official description of the bombing to be false. They had claimed McVeigh&amp;rsquo;s truck contained an ammonium nitrate bomb, but if that were true, the air would have been unbreathable for some time after the bombing. This was not the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A year after the bombing, and shortly before he was to start work at the FBI, Yeakey was brutally murdered, although his death was ruled a suicide. For this to be true, however, Yeakey would have had to cut his wrists and neck before leaving and locking his car. He would then have had to climb a barbed-wire fence, walk more than a mile through a field, and then shoot himself through the head at an unusual angle. No gun was found. No investigation was conducted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Was the bombing a &amp;lsquo;sting gone wrong&amp;rsquo;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of those interviewed in the film was Hoppy Heidelberg, who was a member of the Federal Grand Jury that investigated the bombing in 1995. Heidelberg was dismissed from the Grand Jury because he insisted on the right of jurors to call witnesses and to view the Alfred P. Murrah videotapes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After seeing the film, Heidelberg reacted angrily to the suggestion by Charles Key, a state representative and founder of the Oklahoma City Bombing Investigation Committee, that the bombing was a &amp;ldquo;sting gone wrong,&amp;rdquo; a suggestion also made by another committee member, Dale Phillips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One comment that upset Heidelberg was when Key says in the film: &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;Some in the media would accuse us [OKBIC] of saying the government blew the building up, which we never said, and I don&amp;rsquo;t believe.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emery praises the work Key has done pushing for the truth on the bombing over the years, although he reaches a very different conclusion as to how it happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my view, Key&amp;rsquo;s belief is similar to someone believing that the 9/11 &amp;ldquo;attacks&amp;rdquo; happened because of government bungling. Fortunately, &lt;em&gt;A Noble Lie&lt;/em&gt; just does too good a job of exposing the government lies and deceptions for the &amp;ldquo;sting&amp;rdquo; theory to hold any water at all. The idea that things just got &amp;ldquo;out of control&amp;rdquo; flies in the face of so much of the evidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I had a criticism, however, it would be that the sting contention kind of comes out of nowhere, and it isn&amp;rsquo;t directly refuted by anyone in the film. Had Heidelberg or former Tulsa police officer Craig Roberts (who was interviewed) been asked directly about this theory, both would certainly have forcefully discounted it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an article in American Free Press, Roberts commented on the sting theory: &amp;ldquo;People saying this have never been in law enforcement. That bell just doesn&amp;rsquo;t ring true to me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article I&amp;rsquo;ve just scratched the surface of the evidence unearthed by Emery, director James Lane and writers Wendy Painting and Holland Vandennieuwenhof.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The makers of &lt;em&gt;A Noble Lie&lt;/em&gt; have made an important contribution to the quest for truth about the bombing. And according to Emery, there&amp;rsquo;s more to come. A second film is in the works that will include more explosive evidence to reveal the true circumstances of the bombing. That film will be out sometime next year, he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story told in &lt;em&gt;A Noble Lie&lt;/em&gt; shows conclusively that the government&amp;rsquo;s version of what happened is not only untrue, but a deliberate lie. With the WTC bombing and Oklahoma City, the public was prepped for the mother of all false flag operations, the fake &amp;ldquo;terrorist attacks&amp;rdquo; of 9/11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;They were turning up the ratchet in terms of body count,&amp;rdquo; Emery says. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s all part of a sequence of events, part of a bigger picture.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in purchasing a copy of&lt;/em&gt; A Noble Lie&lt;em&gt;, you can find it at anoblelie.com or infowars.com.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;"Either you are with us or &lt;br /&gt;

 you are with the terrorists."&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - &lt;strong&gt;George W. Bush&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;(1946- ) 43rd US President, &lt;br /&gt;

 Yale Skull &amp;amp; Bones Society&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Resources links ~ &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/"&gt;FlybyNews.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;27 February 2012 - Truth &amp;amp; Shadows - Craig McKee&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://truthandshadows.wordpress.com/2012/02/27/documentary-a-noble-lie-exposes-oklahoma-city-bombing-as-government-black-op/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Documentary &lt;strong&gt;"A Noble Lie"&lt;/strong&gt; exposes&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Oklahoma City bombing as government black-op&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;26 February 2012 - GCTV - Jonathan Mark&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://gctv.org/videos"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;The Reflecting Pool Filmmaker &lt;br /&gt;

 and 4 other Interviews Online&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Look under Category for Flyby News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 2012 - Truthquake Radio - Robert Barron &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.archive.org/details/TruthquakeRadioFlybyNews-JonathanMarkInterview1-29-12Show58"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Interview with Jonathan Mark&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;em&gt;a flyby perspective&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;11 September 2011 - VIDEO - Corbett Report&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.corbettreport.com/911-a-conspiracy-theory/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9/11: A Conspiracy Theory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Everything you ever wanted to know about &lt;br /&gt;

 9/11 conspiracy theory in under 5 minutes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;January, 2012 - &lt;a href="http://actorsandartistsfor911truth.com/index.htm"&gt;Actors and Artists for 9/11 Truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://actorsandartistsfor911truth.com/confess.htm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Violation of Trust&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Help AA911truth Create A Feature Film!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;31 January 2012 - &lt;strong&gt;Corbett Report Radio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.corbettreport.com/corbett-report-radio-060-a-violation-of-truth-with-howard-cohen/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Violation of Trust with Howard Cohen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;In first 3 minutes, watch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://youtu.be/EJAVMUMjr3Q"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9/11 - WTC-7 - Exposed!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Video clip produced by&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="http://thepatriots.us/"&gt;Robert Bowman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;16 August 2011 - Youtube - AE911truth&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hZEvA8BCoBw&amp;amp;feature=player_embedded#%21"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Architects &amp;amp; Engineers&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Solving the Mystery of WTC 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://911expertsspeakout.org/911-explosive-evidence-experts-speak-version-12/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9/11: Explosive Evidence&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Experts Speak Out -&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1014738186,11057,"&gt;New 9/11 Investigation&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1014738186,11057,"&gt;vs&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1014738186,11057,"&gt;New World Order&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;One of the common failings among honorable people is &lt;br /&gt;

 a failure to appreciate how thoroughly dishonorable some &lt;br /&gt;

 other people can be, and how dangerous it is to trust them.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - Thomas Sowell &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;(1930- ) Writer and economist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Frances Crowe community space, (in back part of Woodstar Cafe building)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333757935000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327096081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Noble Lie: Oklahoma City 1995</name><id>48945942</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333663200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/48945942/</event_url></item>