<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Actually, this event will be held on July 2, but I thought I could use the Fourth in the title in celebration. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who are still in there area on the Fourth of July weekend, I thought we could go scout out a cool little area I found right in Danvers, on the edge of Hathorne, MA. &amp;nbsp;It is actually practically in my backyard and is home to what I am calling the world's largest burdock among other cool little surprises. &amp;nbsp;It is also about the time for elderberry blooming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the most enjoyable walk, I am going to purpose that we meet at my place and then walk the half mile to the foraging site as this will allow us to check for things along the side of the street as well. &amp;nbsp;If, however, this is too much walking for you, let me know and I will give directions to park and meet us closer to the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire walk would take approximately an hour from my place to back again just walking it. &amp;nbsp;The event will obviously last longer depending on how often we stop, study, observe and interact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So please bring a water bottle, good shoes and an eye for spotting interesting plants! :-) &amp;nbsp;We will head out promptly at 2:15.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the location:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My location is right at the intersection of Route 1 and Route 95,&amp;nbsp;conveniently&amp;nbsp;located between all points North Shore. &amp;nbsp;This area is a housing complex however so please park in a non-numbered space. &amp;nbsp;Come to Unit 901&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Unit 901</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310572348000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308852679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fourth of July Foraging</name><id>23271311</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309629600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/23271311/</event_url></item>