<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>140 Glastonbury Boulevard</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06033</zip><lat>41.721386</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>The Shops at Somerset Square</name><city>Glastonbury</city><id>461500</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.620450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come one and all. We are meeting for a GLASTONBURY, CT canvass. Tee meetup location is the shops at Somerset Square. Find directions here: &lt;a href="http://theshopsatsomersetsquare.com/map.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://theshopsatsome...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 10:00 a.m., wave signs for an hour or so and then head out to the designated canvassing areas. We meet back in the afternoon to report results and do a 2nd sign wave, possibly with new meetup members who couldn't make the first one. Depending on when canvassing ends, we'll be back as early as 3 p.m. Second sign wave will be from time of arrival till at least 5 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The turnout for canvassing has been low. It's the Holidays, it's cold, we're all very busy. That's why I'd like to do the second wave where maybe people who worked or had errands can stop for an hour and help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have the handouts. We have the yard signs. We will have DVD's. We need Ron Paul supporters in the streets getting this material to the uninformed masses.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet on the side walk in front of the shopping plaza across from the highway on/offramp to wave signs while waiting for all participants to arrive.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Earl L.</member_name><member_id>4314674</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Searles</member_name><member_id>4735307</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199113703000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Your effort may be what pushes the good Dr. to a victory in CT. Don't be that guy/gal who sat at home while freedom lost another election.</why><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198427889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday sign wave and canvassing</name><id>6959195</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198940400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/6959195/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/8/global_1872280.jpeg</photo_url></item>