<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Eliot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372595</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Charlie's Beer Garden</name><city>Cambridge </city><id>966779</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/Home/Articles/The-32nd-Annual-Oktoberfest-and-Honk!-Festival-Par.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: yellow"&gt;32nd Oktoberfest and Honk! Festival Parade&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00 - 2:00 Let's Meet up at Charlie's  Beer Garden along with members of &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/calendar/14389014/"&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Fun with Alcohol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, outdoors next to Charlie's Kitchen, 10 Eliot Street  and head over the the parade reviewing stand to watch the HONK! Fest parade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 2:00 - 4:00 PM,  we will split up into smaller groups to make the loop around Harvard Square to explore the 6 music stages, street vendor booths, visit John Harvard's Brew House. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:00 - 6:00 PM Re join back at Charlie's again  to have some German grilled food and a pint or two your favorite Oktoberfest beer. Mine is &amp;quot;Spaden&amp;quot;...so many to choose from on draught!. &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB @ ALL TIMES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: For those wishing to avoid the crowded bar scene, limited patio seating is available on the sidewalk in front (you must order food to be seated at a cafe table).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noon - 6PM Six stages of live entertainment including a main stage in the Super Crosswalk, A Dance Stage at Holyoke Center on Forbes Plaza, a Club Passim Stage, a Busker Stage, and two Honk Band Stages!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;50 plus International Food Vendors! Enjoy authentic Oktoberfest dishes at the Sandrine’s booth featuring Chef Raymond Ost’s world renowned Choucroute, hot soups and Vanilla Crème Brule. Enjoy the ceremonial Keg Tapping and Toast and authentic Bavarian food, beer and costumes at Grendel’s Den.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People watch (and be watched) from a cozy corner of the Grafton Street/Sam Adams Beer Garden (across from the Main Stage)! Grab a seat on a hay-bale inside the Upper Crust Beer Garden along Mount Auburn Street and enjoy a great view of the Honk encampment in Winthrop Park!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your every food desire with Chef Jasper White’s Shrimp on Skewers, corn and clam chowder at the Summer Shack booth, and Chef Paul O’Connell’s Cuban Sandwich, delicious healthy burgers at the b. good grill, Korean Bar-b-que, Ben and Jerry’s ice cream, fudge and kettle korn, and international flavors from Café of India and the Midwest Grill, and a host of Thai, Nepalese, Jamaican, Chinese, and Mediterranean booths from which to choose!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See Oktoberfest Schedule &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/Home/Articles/The-32nd-Annual-Oktoberfest-and-Honk!-Festival-Par.aspx"&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info, please call 617-491-3434 or &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com"&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;www.harvardsquare.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will disclose my cell number after you rsvp "yes"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286831965000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281533293000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oktoberfest in Harvard Square</name><id>14389014</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286730000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/14389014/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/9/global_11214841.jpeg</photo_url></item>