<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>(note that this meetup is being held on a Wednesday, not a Thursday.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to everyone intrigued by neuro-linguistic programming (NLP). Here are the details of the October meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight’s topic: Using NLP to get a date, a job, or a lobster dinner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NLP has a number of great tools for setting, refining, and achieving goals.  We will learn one particularly powerful tool (which I picked up this summer) for refining and achieving your goals.  There will also likely be at least one bonus exercise, some more ideas about “what is NLP”, humor, drama, suspense, and profound insights into the human condition.  Bring a goal you’d like to achieve (if its something besides a date, a job, or a lobster dinner).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular. I will stay for a while after the meetup, if you want to discuss specific issues that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be: &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;www.NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258676363000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254439996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The NLP October Meetup - Using NLP to get a date, a job, or a lobster dinner</name><id>xppwcymnblc</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256771700000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/11523944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/0/3/global_11325075.jpeg</photo_url></item>