<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1060268</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369168</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>March 1, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HI! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just a reminder of our upcoming interfaith bookclub gathering... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope this note of mine finds you well, with peace and joy in your heart. Winter is almost over and we are looking forward to an explosion of spring life.  Sorry if this reminder is a bit overdue, but I was blessed with an unexpected gift: a two weeks visit to Taiwan... A refreshing and uplifting time. God is good!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am really looking forward to seeing you on March 7th, at 4:00PM... &lt;br /&gt;So, mark your calendar: &lt;br /&gt;TIME: March 7th, 2010 at 4:00PM &lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY - Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We begin our reflection and sharing on THOMAS MERTON'S book: &amp;quot;THE INNER EXPERIENCE - Notes on contemplation&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the book, I read the following: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Thomas Merton's last work before his untimely death in Thailand. Even though it was started in 1959, he had been working on this examination of the contemplative life still in 1968(the year of his death). It's somewhat like a bridge between his earlier works on mysticism and monasticism and his later works on eastern thought, namely his fascination with Buddhism. Some of the subjects touched on here you will see familiarity with insights he touched on also in &amp;quot;New Seeds of Contemplation&amp;quot;. He talks a lot in this book about the inner self and our relationship to society, as well as taking aim at some of the actual problems of a contemplative life, as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether talking about Taoism or Zen, or the Desert Fathers, Merton interlaces the wisdom of various religious traditions here, thus proving himself to be an advocate of interfaith dialogue. The contemplative life is a life lived in a kind of mystery, in a sense of awe. Not a life of spiritual gaining or possession. Merton talks here about something he often did, &amp;quot;the sublime life.&amp;quot; This he says, is planted in every soul... And perhaps the most wonderful aspect of this book is the fact that Merton is able to appeal to people of all walks of life. Be that a Christian, Buddhist, or even a Jewish person. There is always something to be learned and contemplated when reading Thomas… Enjoy this magnificent book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you can all make it. I personally continue to be enriched by your presence and by our common sharing and reflection. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you all on Sunday - March 7th, at 4:00PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blessings on you and your family... let us continue to be bridge and not obstable makers... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PEACE &lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx &lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries &lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144 &lt;br /&gt;pino.ma@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268168875000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267541632000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UPCOMING MEETING!</name><id>12755905</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267995600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/12755905/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/a/global_4353546.jpeg</photo_url></item>