<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>108 Blackstone</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.361954</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Durty Nelly's</name><city>Boston</city><id>2527081</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056320</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;****UPDATE** Forgot about B's game! Bruins take on the Canadiens at 7:30pm. Come on down and root for your Boston teams.****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey hey! So, I decided I will suck it up and go out to watch the late Monday Night Football extravaganza Patriots vs. Chiefs.&amp;nbsp; I'll be hanging out down at Durty Nelly's in the Haymarket.&amp;nbsp; Come on by!&amp;nbsp; I know it's a work night but it's okay to be a little bleary eyed the next day for this short holiday workweek. Right? RIGHT!&amp;nbsp; Game time is 8:30pm and I should be there by 7-7:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Durty Nelly's is a small "neighborhoody" bar located on Blackstone Street across from the greenway.&amp;nbsp; Greg, our trusty bartender, will be slinging drinks and working the grill/fryer for your drinking and eating pleasure. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are responsible for your own food and drink. PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU GO! Durty Nelly's is conveniently located very near the Haymarket stop on the Orange and Green Lines and a short walk from the Blue Line at Government Center. This event is being cross-listed with Red Sox Natives and Social Fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be the girl in the red Welker jersey.&amp;nbsp; HOPE TO SEE YOU THERE!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask bartender for me!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321926165000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321625295000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MNF with the Patriots v. Chiefs AND Bruins @ Canadiens!</name><id>41617552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321921800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/41617552/</event_url></item>