<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Fellswater's small and border piper Matthew Phelps performed in a notloB concert at the Loring-Greenough House April 17, 2010 as a part of Doug Lamey's band, Tri. Welcome back, Matthew!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fellswater is a four piece Celtic ensemble that plays a wide range of music from Traditional to modern compositions, and draws from the heritage of all the Celtic nations, especially Scotland, Ireland, Brittany and Canada. Our instrumentation changes depending on the musical selection and includes whistle, flute, guitar, mandolin, bouzouki,violin, smallpipes and border pipes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betsy Ketudat, Fiddle &lt;br /&gt;

Betsy Ketudat graduated from Fredonia State University with a degree in Violin Performance. Betsy has since played in many chamber groups throughout the Boston area and has been a member of the Middlesex County Volunteers Fifes and Drums since 2000, playing both violin and fife. In 2005 she was featured violin soloist at the Yshalle Tattoo in Basel, Switzerland. As a fifer with MCV, Betsy has performed throughout England, France and Switzerland, at the 2007 Edinburgh Military Tattoo, the 2010 Edinburgh Military Tattoo's Salute to Australia, and in concert with the Boston Pops. Betsy has also played in numerous local performances with MCV and MCV’s chamber consort, and appears on four MCV albums, playing both violin and fife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jim MacConduibh, Guitar/Bouzouki &lt;br /&gt;

Jim MacConduibh has been active in the Boston music scene since 1982---as a drummer. As an antidote to the constant din of rock'n'roll, circus and military drums, he and wife Sarah MacConduibh became interested in the new-Celtic movement of the mid-1990's, playing with the likes of Skip Healy, Matt Glover, and the New Hampshire Strathspey &amp;amp; Reel Society. He is the survivor of myriad international tours, including Baghdad in 2007 and at the 2010 Edinburgh Military Tattoo Salute to Australia in Sydney. Longtime Director of Middlesex County Volunteers Fifes &amp;amp; Drums, Jim resides in West Medford with Sarah and five cats and a dog. Jim plays guitar, bouzouki and mandolin with Fellswater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sarah MacConduibh, Flute/Whistle &lt;br /&gt;

Sarah MacConduibh has been a member of the Middlesex County Volunteers Fifes &amp;amp; Drums (MCV) since 1984 and is presently MCV’s Business Manager and fifer. Sarah’s extensive performance resume with MCV has included recording eight full-length albums, tours to England, France, Ireland and Switzerland and local performances too numerous to list here. 2007 featured performances with the Boston Pops as well as a month-long run at the Edinburgh Military Tattoo. 2010 featured performances at the Edinburgh Military Tattoo's Salute to Australia in Sydney and four performances with the Boston Pops and 2012 found her in Switzerland for the Basel Tattoo. Sarah has played with several folk groups over the years on a variety of instruments, ranging from fiddle, flute, whistle and fife. Sarah plays whistle and flute with Fellswater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matthew Phelps, Smallpipes &lt;br /&gt;

Matthew Phelps began piping at the age of eight under the instruction of Pipe Major Thomas Shearer of Connecticut and had additional instruction at the Gaelic College of Celtic Arts and Crafts in Nova Scotia. Matthew competes at the Professional level and has also competed over the years in the U.S., Canada and Scotland with the following bands: Trumbull and District Pipe Band of Connecticut, Gaelic College Pipe Band of Nova Scotia, Saint Andrews College Pipe Band of North Carolina, Tulach Ard Pipe Band of Massachusetts, and Halifax Regional Police Pipes &amp;amp; Drums of Nova Scotia. Matthew currently works as a full time piping instructor and performer; he has opened concerts for Niamh Parsons, John Whelan, and J. P. Cormier. In addition to playing with Fellswater, Matt is the Pipe Major of the Stuart Highlanders Pipe Band (grade 4). Matt plays smallpipes and border pipes with Fellswater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fellswater's website: &lt;a href="http://fellswater.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://fellswater.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested donation $10-20 sliding scale + $1 preservation fee &lt;br /&gt;

20% discount for JP Tuesday Club members. &lt;br /&gt;

Reservations suggested and strongly recommended, email notlobreservations at gmail dot com &lt;br /&gt;

More info at the notloB website - &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Please sign up for our concert announcements - &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee from JP Licks &lt;br /&gt;

Pastries from Fiores&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;notloB Folk Concerts has produced not-for-profit concerts in the greater Boston area since 2007. The series is volunteer-run; 100% of the donations go to the musicians and production expenses. Admission is by suggested minimum donation. A suggested minimum donation (varies by concert) is requested. If you cannot support the artists with dollars, please consider volunteering your time and energy. Your donations cover venue rental, sound system rental, sound engineer, publicity and other production expenses. 100% of the balance goes to the artists (many of whom travel many miles). Sometimes there are shortfalls, so extra donations are gladly accepted. If you cannot afford the suggested donation amount, consider volunteering! And please, no credit cards or checks, cash is appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photography, video recording, &amp;amp; sound recording. No still, video or sound recording is permitted without permission of the artist and the house. If you would like to share photos of past concerts, email the pictures and/or web link to notlobreservations at gmail dot com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In this era of pop-driven acoustic music, notloB is keeping the folk tradition alive." &lt;br /&gt;

~ Jack Hardy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upcoming: &lt;br /&gt;

3/9 Bronwyn Keith-Hynes and Catherine Bowness &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/302018473243058/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/302018473243058/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361679303000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360807139000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>notloB Parlour Concerts presents Fellswater</name><id>104526422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361667600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/104526422/</event_url></item>