<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:45, so let's meet at 7:15 in front of the theater. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP up to date and call me with any last-minute changes, so I know who to wait for!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lesley's organizing a &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/calendar/10784190/"&gt;dinner before the movie (at 5:45) at Chipotle Grill&lt;/a&gt;, if anyone wants to go:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow for Transformers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;I was surprised (in a good way) by the first Transformers movie. And now the 2nd one is out, so let's hit the theater for an action-packed, twisted-metal-full 2 and a half hours of &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809943432/info"&gt;Transformers&lt;/a&gt; mayhem. Shia LeBeouf tends not to disappoint.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;With the help of the Autobots, the soldiers of NEST, and an old adversary-turned-ally, Sam and Mikaela must uncover the secret history of the Transformers presence on earth, and the sacrifices that have to be made to save it from an ancient threat sworn on returning here for revenge... an ancient Decepticon named THE FALLEN.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the theater doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers &lt;i&gt;each&lt;/i&gt; for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this meetup with a specific time a few days before, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Transformers 2!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247347152000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246466194000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Transformers: Revenge of the Fallen</name><id>10779477</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247007600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10779477/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>