<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Doane Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01368</zip><lat>42.651386</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Tully Lake Campground</name><city>Royalston</city><id>1380437</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.207810</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Does getting stuck in traffic on the way to the Cape or NH
beaches annoy you?&amp;nbsp; Avoid the holiday traffic and head out
Route 2 to beautiful Tully Lake in Royalston, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at the boat launch on Doane Hill Road, near the
entrance to Tully Lake Campground.&amp;nbsp; There is a short dirt road
and dirt parking lot on the opposite side of the road heading up
hill from the campground entrance. &amp;nbsp; Please arrive in time to
start paddling at 9:30 AM.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We'll head up the river to
Long Pond and find a smaller river that heads up toward Roylaston
falls.&amp;nbsp; We may be portaging over some beaver dams in that
area.&amp;nbsp; Once we explore that area we can head back to the
launch area and people can either leave or stay to paddle into the
main lake where we can explore coves and islands and go for a
swim.&amp;nbsp; Bring a lunch and we'll stop on shore somewhere or eat
in our kayaks.&amp;nbsp; Plan on about 2 hours to go up to Long Pond
and back and another 2+ hours out on the big lake.&amp;nbsp; The last
time a bunch of us paddled here we spent almost 7 hours on the
water!&amp;nbsp; Bring plenty of water, snacks and sunscreen and an
appetite for adventure.&amp;nbsp; I can't remember if there are
porta-potties at the launch, but there is a restroom building with
flush toilets at the campground within a modest walk or short drive
from the launch site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who are not in a hurry to head home after paddling,
there are hiking opportunities in the area (Doane's Falls,
Royalston Falls and The Ledges) and there are picnic tables, grills
and a rest room at the opposite end of the lake, near the dam on
Route 32.&amp;nbsp; It is where the paved launch is for trailered
boats. You could head home that way and have a picnic dinner.&amp;nbsp;
There is also a disc golf course at the dam. I do not know what
parking and table availability will be like, so you may need to be
flexible.&amp;nbsp; There is so much to do in this area besides
paddling!&amp;nbsp; It is a great destination for a full day of
activities for those with time and stamina.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained
leaders or instructors.&amp;nbsp; The organizers only set the time and
place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible
for their own safety.&amp;nbsp; Each participant is responsible for
evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if
their skills and equipment are appropriate for those
conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Canoe Launch Parking Lot on Doane Hill Road in Royalston, MA</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310342910000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307985379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle at Tully Lake in Royalston, MA</name><id>22029101</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309786200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/22029101/</event_url></item>