<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Salem Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.260864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-799-1655</phone><name>Worcester Public Library</name><city>Worcester</city><id>999847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.800133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello All! We have a quick change of plans for the August meetup. We have been invited to join forces with the 7 Hill's Camera Club for an intersting night at the Worcester Library, Banx Room. We have meet with this group before and had a wonderful time. SO I think it would be a nice op for us to visit with them again. Here is the note I got from Casey, It's what made me want to change the plans for the evening! Note the time change to 7PM!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We have an opportunity for August's Meetup. As it turns out, our Meetup and the 7HCC Digital Group meetings are on the same night. Also, I'll have the Viewfinder Sessions video finished and was planning on showing it that night to one or the other. It might be worthwhile combining the meetings. The library venue is a good one for a video and the two groups memberships won't be torn as to which meeting to attend. Just food for thought.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Casey&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd still like for us to discuss the fundraiser for Eric and Steve. I'll ask for a few mins from the 7 Hills folks to discuss this as well...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are looking for donations of small items - small prints matted or framed, cards, magnets or what ever you have that we can sell at stART on the Street as a fundraiser for Eric Milot who lost his studio to the Bernet Mill fire. All proceedes from the sale will be donated to Eric and Steve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't know about stART on the Street please check out the web site at &lt;a href="http://www.startonthestreet.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.startonthe...&lt;/a&gt;  I'll need some volenteers to watch the booth during the day. So if you think you can spend a few hours doing this please sign up at the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****I think we will just move this part of the agenda to the Meetup for Sept.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your camera bag! We'd like to take a peek inside and see what you carry with you! Some newbies are interested in the bags themselves and would like to see what we have and why we like it. So bring them out to play!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I mentioned Cafe Dolce and our need to fill the place with framed prints! Please be ready to sign up for this...I've seen your work and this is a great place to display it! So come on folks sign up for a month long show!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update folks with more details later! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Till next time- Keep shooting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna and Scott&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188963508000</updated><rating><average>4.09000015259</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185496400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Worcester Photography August Meetup</name><id>6082712</id><headcount>41</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188514800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/6082712/</event_url></item>