<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.355270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fisher College - Trustee Reading Room</name><city>Boston</city><id>1032437</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.074030</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A panel of amazing speakers will be coming by to talk about their diverse career paths and industries. Feel free to invite others. There will be opportunity for networking with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Sean McDevitt&lt;/strong&gt;, VP, CSMG &lt;br /&gt;

 2. &lt;strong&gt;Ryn Miake-Lye&lt;/strong&gt;, Founder and Principal, Science Driven &lt;br /&gt;

 3. &lt;strong&gt;Chad Griller&lt;/strong&gt;, Project Manager, Ameresco &lt;br /&gt;

 4. &lt;strong&gt;Uchenna Onyeachom&lt;/strong&gt;, Director of Global Health, Healthsystem Plus Inc &lt;br /&gt;

 5. &lt;strong&gt;Linda Sharpe&lt;/strong&gt;, V-TRAC Program Manager, &lt;span&gt;MacroSys LLC (at the USDOT Volpe National Transportation Systems Center)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Sean McDevitt:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;As a seasoned executive in the technology-enabled business services market, Sean leads business development and client engagement efforts at CSMG, a TMT-focused strategy consultancy. Sean’s track record of delivering profitable growth and superior financial results spans five countries in three continents. Prior to his current time at CSMG, Sean held senior executive positions at tech-startups, at other professional (finance and strategy) consulting firms and at the UK’s leading directory assistance and information services provider, for which he helped launch three multinational subsidiaries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Ryn Miake-Lyn, PhD:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;For over 20 years, Ryn has grown expert innovation. Ryn is an entrepreneur, successfully leveraging prior experience as the Director of Research at Harvard Medical School’s Dept of Cell Biology and as the Director of R&amp;amp;D Operations at Millennium Pharmaceuticals. As founder and principal of the independent practice ScienceDriven, she partners with clinical and scientific innovators in biomedical R&amp;amp;D and cultivates shared value for organizations offering the best therapeutic options to patients most likely to respond. As a Principal of Build from Scratch to Last, Ryn mentors fellow founders and assembles self-directed teams who are eponymous. Ryn currently sits on the Boards of Community Water Solutions and the Downtown Boston Rotary Club.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Chad Griller:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Chad is a member of the management team of Ameresco, the largest independent provider of comprehensive energy efficiency and renewable energy solutions. With 10 years’ experience in engineering, construction and senior management under his belt, Chad provides construction project management services, throughout the project life cycle, starting with development activities through costing, execution, completion and implementation. At Ameresco, he further assists the engineering group in project development, scope, subcontractor selection, capital cost, installation estimating, and scheduling. He also manages vendors and subcontractors, cultivating positive and effective business relationships. Chad is also an active member of the Rotary Club International&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Chad is a past president of the Carbondale Aspen Glen Rotary Club in Carbondale, Colorado.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Uchenna Onyeachom:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;One of Uchenna’s many hats is as the Director of Global Health and Principal Investigator of Abuja Heart Study which is the largest cardiovascular disease project in black population at Healthsystem Plus, a private, non-profit focused on International Health and Public Health Programs. In this post, he is responsible for Cardiovascular, Venous and Lymphatic Disease Outcome Research, but his prior experience also makes him a Global health expert with experiences in HIV/AIDS, Tropical Medicine and Maternal, Child and Newborn health. He has consulted and advised Government and Multilateral agencies like WHO,UNICEF, NIH and FDA. Additionally, Uchenna serves as the current Assistant District Governor for Rotary clubs in Boston, Cambridge and Chelsea and the District Rotaract Chairman.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Linda Sharpe:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;Linda has 30 years of experience in applying her skills in research and systems analysis to strategic planning, policy development, and business process re-engineering. She currently applies those skills in the Volpe Center of the US Department of Transportation. Linda has been a principal contributor for organizations such as Unisys, Cambridge Systematics. Prior to her current post, she was a Senior Associate at Booz Allen Hamilton leading transport-focused system development and research analysis projects. N&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;ot only was she the first African American woman to serve as president of the MIT Alumni/ae Association, Linda&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;currently serves on the boards of WalkBoston and MAB Community Services (parent organization of the Massachusetts Association for the Blind and Visually Impaired) and is a former Advisory Board member for the Women's Transportation Seminar - Boston.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raquel F</member_name><member_id>72837312</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368670358000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrotaract</urlname><id>1501340</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Rotaract - A Service/Social Club for 18-30 Yr Olds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366379782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crooked Paths to Success: Boston Rotaract Professional Development Panel</name><id>115140992</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>8100000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367534700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrotaract/events/115140992/</event_url></item>