<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet for dinner and drinks then see a wonderful play with other culture vultures at the Lyric Stage Company in Boston. &lt;b&gt;Please note that you need to book your own tickets for this play - seating is in the Orchestra, side section via ArtsBoston discount website.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you can't make it for dinner but want to see the play, you can just come straight to the theater. (Please let me know your plans so I can look out for you).&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Year of Magical Thinking (starts at 7.30 pm) at the Lyric Stage Company, 140 Clarendon St, Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Insistently hypnotic&amp;quot;  The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joan Didions best selling memoir (which is a fabulous book) recounts an almost unfathomable period in her life as she grappled with her husband’s sudden death and daughter’s illness. This stage adaptation captures the compassion, humor, and bewilderment of a fiercely intelligent woman as her world lurches suddenly from the ordinary to the unimaginable. Filled with raw candor this “unmissable theater”(Variety) is a love letter to a child and a tribute  to an extraordinary, unconventional marriage, all told by a brilliant storyteller with a gift for the absurd. Featuring 2008 Elliot Norton Award-winner Nancy E. Carroll.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weekdays: $37 OR DISCOUNT PRICE ($25)  VIA WWW.ARTSBOSTON.ORG IF YOU BOOK RIGHT NOW!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call my cell if you don't recognize me from my photo!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233967530000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230765604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Year of Magical Thinking (theater) + pre-theater dinner at Firefly Bistro</name><id>9416185</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231455600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/9416185/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/6/global_5526982.jpeg</photo_url></item>