<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Labor Day Retreat (Open to both Singles &amp;amp; Couples) Canaan, New York-September 2-5, 2011 4 Days and 3 Nights of lodging, meals, and tuition. SAVE $100 &amp;#150; $495 pp (Single man or woman)/$895 per couple $595 pp(Single man or woman)/$995 per couple (after August 27th, 2011) Revitalize and Revolutionize your capacity for &amp;amp; Intimacy and Sensual Pleasure with others.(for men and women, couples and singles. We make every attempt to keep this event gender-balanced-gender-balanced) Our current culture provides very few opportunities to develop our intelligence in intimacy and emotional connection with others. Many of us pay a high price for what we do not know, by attempting to learn this crucial wisdom through trial and error in relationships. Often this creates tension and projection with our partners, and we find we have nowhere to turn. While some choose to withdraw and retreat from the misunderstandings of human emotions to safety and solitude, others attempt through yet another relationship only to find no answers. Most of us long for a safe, unconditionally loving environment within which to ask our questions and discover new answers that provide us with both a clear understanding and workable practice toward the genuine happiness that we so long for in our relationships. The Sensual Love &amp;amp; Intimacy Retreat is the perfect solution. Within a safe, serene , and honoring environment, you will immerse yourself in getting the best training and education ever in creating and keeping love and intimacy strong and expanding in your life. This training teaches how to create a safe and nurturing container where you can weave and navigate your innermost desire for love, intimacy, love, and sexual expression with another person Through this training, you will gain the ability to be totally present and focused on another person&amp;#146;s pleasure as well as fully surrendering to your own. This will be an unforgettable week where you can become more of the man you&amp;#146;ve always wanted to be. In Sensual Love &amp;amp; Intimacy Labor Day Weekend Retreat, you will experience: * Powerful communication skills that will keep you intimately connected your partner * Mastering the Man/Woman game of Love &amp;amp; Sex * Step-by-step instruction on Sensual Touch and Expanded Orgasm * Creating your Intimate Community * Developing life-long practices with your own sexual energy leading to greater health, happiness, and longevity. We have totally taken over a beautiful 10 acre, 25 room Inn surrounded by beautiful forests and waterfalls just 2.5 hours north of New York City, with easy access by bus or train service, you will enjoy 4 days and 3 nights of learning as you learn the art of Sensual Love and Intimacy. Immerse yourself in getting the best training and education ever in creating and keeping love and intimacy strong and expanding in your life.Immerse yourself in this new paradigm in love, intimacy and sexual expression within a safe, respectful environment. This training teaches how to create a safe and nurturing container where you can weave and navigate your innermost desire for love, intimacy, love, and sexual expression with another person Through this training, you will gain the ability to be totally present and focused on another persons pleasure as well as fully surrendering to your own. TEACHERS- Richard Anton Diaz, is the founder of Sexy Spirits in New York City, Co-Producer of the Sacred Sex Round-Up, and former Ballroom dance champion. His training in the both the physical and psychological aspects of partnership dancing led him to appreciate the powerful dance between the sexes and the necessary integration of cultivated sexual energy and sensual love through conscious practice in order to achieve greater health, happiness, and longevity. He is a certified Taoist Instructor under Master Mantak Chia, creator of Taontric Massage, and offers courses in Sexual energy Cultivation, Orgasmic Providers, and Sensual Loving Touch. Lisa Carrillo is a coach and creator of the Loving Your Love Life approach a method which facilitates our movement into the state of natural connection and pleasure through open-hearted awareness. &amp;#147;We move beyond our limits of how we think life and relating should work into the creative unknown and expand our capacity for pleasure. Whether we are practicing greater presence in our lives or are expanding our sensual relating, we often run into the limitations of our capacity for feeling good. Ran Baron is an educator and a public speaker in the field of theology, eastern philosophy, and mysticism. He has instructed numerous meditation workshops, Yoga retreats and has given hundreds of talks and lectures about the nature of spirituality and self-inquiry. He has lived through many different paths and was ordained as a Hindu priest (Brahmana), was certified as a Yoga Instructor, a Tai Chi instructor and has been studying and practicing Buddhism, Tantra, Zen, Hinduism and Yoga in many of its different flavors, sharing and teaching of his own views and vast experience in his talks. Monique Marco will be leading the Naked Yoga class every morning at the SLI Retreat. Her expertise is a combination of yoga and fashionably healthy living. Additionally, she is also a certified &amp;#147;StripXpertise&amp;#148; teacher and offers professional lessons and guidance in positive body image for women through striptease, erotic dance and lapdance.Monique believes that being grounded in your body and understanding its intelligence is integral to spirituality. Imani will be our amazing chef offering a vegan menu with some delicious raw food delights! She is author of The Absence of Soil &amp;amp; Mama-Licious: Recipes for a High Vibe Life. She has raised her &amp;#147;free-range children&amp;#148; to be &amp;#147;real-foodists&amp;#148; with diets consisted of whole, organic, non-packaged, non-GMO foods. Her dream is to acquire nutrient dense land where a thriving community can be born and serve as a model to others what is possible. Imani is a super-nutritarian with an intense desire to secure access to mineral &amp;amp; nutrient dense super foods for all. You will be energized all weekend long with Imani&amp;#146;s meals! Our Retreat at the Shaker Mill Farm InnVoted The Mid-Atlantic&amp;#146;s Best Bed &amp;amp; Breakfasts, and nestled within 10 acres of nature, the Shaker Mill Farm Inn, is a converted 1824 Shaker mill farm with 25 charming rooms, which can accommodate up to 50, all comfortably furnished with private bathrooms. The Inn is located just 3 hours north of New York City by car or easily accessible by Peter Pan Bus Service to either Stockbridge or Pittsfield, MA, or by train from Grand Central to Wassaic, MA. We will be arranging a pick-up from the drop-off points for a slight additional van fee.(NOTE: All reservations must be made through Sexy Spirits. For information or Registration GO HERE, or call (212) 581-2640&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315008384000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314397781000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sensual Love &amp; Intimacy Retreat - Labor Day Weekend</name><id>31088431</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315004400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/31088431/</event_url></item>