<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;I've added the start location to the listing. The first building is less than 1/2 mile from the Newton Highlands T stop. I am told that there is plenty of parking there. There is also plenty of parking at the 2nd stop. It's in JP that parking becomes difficult. I will drive and I can take 3 people in my car. I'm happy to return people to the start point or drop them off at a T stop on the way. I suggest that folks use the comments section to organize carpooling during the tour itself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Northeast Sustainable Energy Association (NESEA) hosts it's annual Green Building Open House on October 2. Homeowners and other building owners will open their doors to the public to show off their green technologies, in particular energy efficiency and renewable energy improvements. We will be able to talk with home and business owners, ask questions, and see how their renewable energy technologies actually work from people in the trenches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;The Details:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll tour 3-4 buildings in the morning, followed by lunch at 12/12:30 for those who want more discussion. We'll start in Newton, near the Newton Highlands T stop and end in Jamaica Plain with lunch and/or coffee at Ula Cafe, near the Stony Brook T stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cars will be required between the start and finish. I'm hoping that folks will offer to car share, so that we can keep those emissions down. There is some parking at the building and on the street. &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'm not sure how much parking will actually be available at most of the buildings that we are visiting, so I encourage people to car share. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Me:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm an architect with a background in sustainable design, with a passion for deep energy retrofitting and Passive House design. I love this stuff! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General Information:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many more buildings that we will not be able to visit (a total of 108 buildings will be open in MA alone), but group members can visit on their own until the Open House ends at 4pm.&lt;br /&gt;For more information on NESEA and the Open House, here's the NESEA website: &lt;a href="http://www.nesea.org/greenbuildings/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nesea.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in front of the building. Parking is available at the building, on the street, behind the building at a public park.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristen</member_name><member_id>4775682</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1286197310000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284771074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Green Buildings Open House Tour and Lunch</name><id>14809077</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286028000000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/14809077/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/f/7/global_18022343.jpeg</photo_url></item>