<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are no longer available!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;This screening of The Lifeguard has sold out.  This means that this event is now open only to people who already have their tickets for Sundance USA at The Coolidge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sundance USA preview occurs annually at The Coolidge so watch for it next year and get your tickets in plenty of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;is an exciting event.  We'll view the film with Sundance USA in Park City and 9 other theaters around the country, and the director will be with us in Brookline for Q&amp;amp;A after the film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Lifeguard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coolidge is thrilled to be one of 10 movie theaters nationwide selected to be part of Sundance Film Festival USA. We look forward to welcoming director Liz W. Garcia for a Q&amp;amp;A following the screening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leigh (Kristen Bell), a whip-smart former valedictorian on the verge of 30, is living a seemingly perfect life in New York. When her work aspirations and love life suddenly come crashing down, she hightails it back to the cocoon of the Connecticut suburb where she grew up. Picking up right where her teen halcyon days left off, she moves into her old room with her parents, reunites with her bosom buddies who never left town, and steps back into her high school job as a condo-complex lifeguard. As she takes a transgressive journey back to adolescence, including entering into a forbidden affair, Leigh’s bold flirtation with disaster triggers a ripple effect all around her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wry, sexy, bittersweet story that revels in the fantasy of reverting to a responsibility-free time, &lt;span&gt;The Lifeguard&lt;/span&gt; cleverly and entertainingly coaxes its characters into the realization that safety can sometimes be a trap. With her witty, emotionally persuasive script, first-time director Liz Garcia has invented a delectable coming-of-age story for our times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Lifeguard&lt;/span&gt; has been accepted to the U.S. Dramatic Competition category in the 2013 Sundance Film Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Synopsis courtesy of the Sundance Film Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tickets are onsale now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>5:45 at Paneras for supper; Coolidge lobby after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359687114000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358187494000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Lifeguard * Sundance USA at Coolidge</name><id>99554872</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359675900000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/99554872/</event_url></item>