<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>490 Cambridge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.360894</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Charles/MGH T stop</name><city>Boston</city><id>808638</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070596</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>($5 for BBF card holders)</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>If you think you have seen Beacon Hill, now it's time to see the rest of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come along and enjoy the newly-decorated-for-the-holidays backdrop of Beacon Hill as we explore the Flat. On this walk you will discover one of Boston's least known and most delightful neighborhoods. The &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Flat_of_Beacon_Hill" target="_blank"&gt;Flat of Beacon Hill&lt;/a&gt; is built on 19th century made-land along the Charles River. The Flat is geologically part of Back Bay and culturally part of Beacon Hill, with the architecture of both.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This intimate patch of real estate soon acquired carriage houses and horse stables owned by the wealthy families living on Beacon Hill. Today, many of these edifices have been converted into charming residences and seamlessly blend among the notable landmarks such as the Charles Street Meeting House, the Church of the Advent, and the Sunflower Castle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What do Sam Mayday Malone, a private-eye named Spenser, a Fox Terrier named Igloo, and seven strangers living in an old firehouse have in common? They all know the Flat is where it's at!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tour costs $15 and $5 for &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot card-carrying members&lt;/a&gt; and docents. Boston By Foot membership is a fantastic holiday gift for friends and family members. Visit www.bostonbyfoot.org for more details on membership and our tours.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for folks with Boston By Foot badges, bags, hats, etc.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Bulfinch</member_name><member_id>7618185</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291643362000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290961730000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Flat of Beacon Hill For The Holiday Season</name><id>15573736</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291575600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/15573736/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/b/global_6233947.jpeg</photo_url></item>