<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Washington &amp; Hyde Park Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.299938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Forest Hills subway stn.</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>183700</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113548</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet at 10 am in the lobby of the Forest Hills subway station.  We will walk for 2 hours along the cemetery?s sculpture path and through Franklin Park, and on to the El Embajador&lt;br /&gt;for lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Forest Hills Cemetery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foresthillstrust.org/about.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foresthill...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Forest Hills is one of America's most lovely rural garden cemeteries. It is also a unique Boston cultural resource and historic site. Its 250 acres offer the public a magnificent arboretum, open air museum, and tranquil sanctuary just minutes away from downtown Boston. The cemetery grounds are open every day from 7:30 am until dusk, and the public is welcome to visit. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Historic masterpieces and adventurous contemporary art &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Long before Boston had public parks, Forest Hills Cemetery was created to offer visitors a special place where they could enjoy a magnificent landscape while remembering friends and family. Sculpture became an essential feature of this environment, as people commissioned local artisans or prominent artists of the time to create individual and family memorials. No visit to Victorian Boston was complete without a trip to Forest Hills to see the latest in fashionable art and architecture. &lt;br /&gt;All of what we now perceive as historic sculpture was contemporary in its day. The Trust began exhibitions of contemporary sculpture and site-specific installation work to revive the 19th century practice of engaging artists to design work for this unique landscape. The Contemporary Sculpture Path is an ongoing exhibition of sculpture laid out along a one-mile route which meanders through the Cemetery grounds. The Trust's 2006 exhibition is Dwelling: Memory, Architecture and Place, has been extended until November 30th, 2006.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FRANKLIN PARK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This &amp;quot;country park&amp;quot; is the largest park (527 acres) and crowning jewel of Olmsted's work here. Named for Benjamin Franklin, the park brings together rural scenery, a woodland preserve and areas for active recreation and sports. Franklin Park also has six miles of roads and fifteen miles of pedestrian and bridle paths to explore.&lt;br /&gt;Scarboro Pond, Ellicot Arch and the Wilderness (part of the Necklace's historic forests) are special places to visit. The eighteen-hole William J. Devine golf-course (the second oldest public course in the nation) and the Franklin Park Zoo (added in 1911) are also favorite destinations. Schoolmaster Hill offers a spectacular view of the Blue Hills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;El Embajador&lt;br /&gt;3371 Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;617-524-6812&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the mood for some delicious,authentic and affordable caribbean food? This is your best bet! This is a very upbeat, casual and friendly family run establishment - the minute you walk in, the atmostphere transports you directly to the islands! And the value? Where else could you have Paella - full with fresh seafood, Chorizo, chicken and veggies for under $19!! The Dominican style steak &amp;amp; onions is to die for! Same for the Roasted chicken, the Pork chops... Every dish comes complete with rice and beans, side salad and of course, plantains! Staff speaks limited English but are very friendly and helpful. I've notice this place has a very loyal clientle and it includes all locals - both Spanish and non Spanish speaking. Great even for breakfast and lunch some stop on their way to work for fresh expresso and buttered toast and many get the most generous (lots of meat)Cuban Sandwiches for lunch. Do NOT forget to ask for dessert - tradional Flan is a must! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1164121728000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163557323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Forest Hills Cemetery &amp; Franklin Park walk</name><id>5268106</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1163948400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5268106/</event_url></item>