<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Anyone for an opera...how about this offering at the Coolidge Corner Theater on a Sunday morning....this performance is presented with an English translation. Hi def. screen - you'll really feel as if you are there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I Puritani &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Comunale di Bologna&lt;br /&gt;Music by Vincenzo Bellini&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following five years of extraordinary success with La Sonnambula, Norma and Beatrice di Tenda, I Puritani, the last opera written by a young Bellini, who died at age 34, is the richest example of transition from the lyrical classicism to the passion of romanticism. The first performances, in Paris, 1835, interpreted by the most beautiful voices of the time, became a legend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this production of I Puritani, the Teatro Comunale di Bologna has reunited two young stars who could well become the dream couple in the opera world: Juan Diego Florez and Nino Machaidze. Conducted by the extremely talented Michele Mariotti, I Puritani has been directed by the internationally renowned Pier’Alli, who, for more than 25 years, has set milestones in the story of opera direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2h35m with one intermission&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music by: Vincenzo Bellini&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conductor: Michele Marioti&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Juan Diego Florez, Nino Machaidze&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...we'll need lunch afterwards!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone buys their own ticket which costs $20 (book in advance on line). Get there in time to pick up your ticket - but book on-line at www.coolidge.org  - you'll still have to line up to pick up your ticket though. Show begins at 10.15 am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I charge $1 pp for each event to cover Meetup organizer costs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in foyer at 10 am - order ticket in advance and pick up at the window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271199006000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266638966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Europe's Grand Operas - I  Puritani on a Sunday morning</name><id>12653473</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270994400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/12653473/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/6/global_5526982.jpeg</photo_url></item>