<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Is one of the reasons you belong to this meetup group because you're looking for support in practicing Law of Attraction principles and how to manifest your desires?  We acknowledge that sometimes it's hard to make it to our in-person meetups. So we have a new option for you this month!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A FREE Tele-call to answer your “yearning” questions! &lt;br /&gt;Thursday, February 11th, 7:30 -8:30 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What are you yearning for but are having trouble achieving?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Want to know more about the Law of Attraction or how to use it more effectively?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you have a personal issue you're struggling with that you'd like some help with? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you had two master coaches at your disposal for support, what questions would you ask to help bring you closer to experiencing greater harmony, happiness and success? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's your opportunity to have free access and support with those two master coaches! Send in your question with your RSVP and perhaps you’ll get to have your question addressed. We’ll be incorporating Law of Attraction and other success principles and practices into our answers, so even if your question isn't the one picked this time, you're sure to still learn something valuable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let us know if you're open to being coached on the call, and will be available; or if you just want your question talked about. The call will be recorded and made available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll receive the call in # after you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to talk and co-create with you soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joy to you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You'll receive the call-in # after you RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266453979000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264185548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's a tele-meetup!</name><id>12393791</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265934600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/12393791/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/0/a/global_12735850.jpeg</photo_url></item>