<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Awesome class! Sundays from 10-11:30am, and it's free - give $5 donation or buy something from the store. A mix of short meditations and Q&amp;amp;A. Come early (9:45am) &amp;amp; we'll go for coffee afterwards! Lots of street parking; T-Stops are Harvard &amp;amp; Porter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bodhitree-cambridge.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bodhitree-cambridge.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bodhitree-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bodhi Tree is named after the tree under which the Buddha reached enlightenment. &lt;b&gt;Our intention is for Bodhi Tree to be a place of inspiration and learning.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday mornings, Tsering Ngodup Lama offers free public talks on Buddhist philosophy and meditation in the upstairs, sun-filled room.  Tsering Ngodup is a lama, or spiritual teacher, authorized to teach by HH ShaMar Rinpoche.  People of all ages, backgrounds, and beliefs come together to listen to Buddhist teachings (Dharma), practice meditation, and experience the relevance and benefits of Buddhist philosophy and meditation in daily life.  Accomplished Tibetan musician Pempa Tsering often performs during the talks.  We have plenty of cushions (zafus) as well as chairs for those who prefer them. All are welcome, and no prior sign-up is necessary.  Please check updates on this web site or call in advance since Tsering Ngodup occasionally travels on weekends.  Donations are appreciated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the coming year, we also plan to offer classes on Buddhist texts one or two evenings a week. Please call or stop by for more information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bodhi Tree?s classes on Buddhist philosophy and meditation are offered in affiliation with the Bodhi Path Buddhist centers, under the spiritual direction of HH ShaMar Rinpoche. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bodhitree-cambridge.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bodhitree-cambridge.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bodhitree-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside the store.  Meditation Class takes place on the 2nd floor of the shop; please leave your shoes, coat, bag on the first floor.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218671041000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211853061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Tibetan Meditation Class</name><id>8016124</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214748000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/8016124/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/3/global_4254595.jpeg</photo_url></item>