<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This is a joint Meetup with the New England Over 40 Hiking Group. A few more breaks and a great day to meet other hikers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There has been a lot of snow in the Whites this winter. You can expect variable conditions. Likely to have snow and ice, and most definitely, lots of melting and mud conditions. So, please  be prepared for both winter and spring conditions. You will not enjoy the hike if your cold or wet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will do the Jackson-Webster loop. Starting on the Webster-Jackson trail we will hike to the intersection of the trail (about 1.4 miles) where we will take the Jackson branch left. At 2.6 miles we will reach the summit of Jackson and start going south on the Webster Cliff Trail to the summit of Webster. We will return by the Webster branch of the Webster-Jackson Trail. There are some steep pitches and rock on top of both mountains that we will need to traverse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are hiking some 4000 footers at the end of the Presidential range. You should be in good hiking shape and ready for a 6.5 mile loop hike and 2500 feet of elevation gain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We recommend that you make sure to have properly fitted waterproof boots with gaiters and rain gear and a shell to fend off the likely windy conditions. Bring your stabilizers, mini-crampons or mini-spikes on this hike -- you will likely need them. Make sure to bring layers of NON-cotton clothing to keep warm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the hike, we will probably walk over to the AMC Highland Center and have lunch OR we might get adventurous and drive down to North Conway and test some of the cuisine there (maybe Moat Mountain Brewery for one).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Don who is organizing this event at the Depot station at the height of land in Crawford Notch. A tan Nissan Frontier. His cell phone is (978) 609-5025"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210597891000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>If you are readying yourself for the higher mountains for the summer, this is a good way to start! Good hiking, reasonable distance, a flavor of late Spring hiking conditions.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206538052000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Jackson and Webster  5/10/2008</name><id>7605558</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210424400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7605558/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/5/global_3608437.jpeg</photo_url></item>