<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>After driving past the sign many times I finally checked it out and was really surprised what a great place this is! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet in the parking lot at 10:45, there will be a 1 hour guided tour at 11:15. Free admission. This will be less exercise than our usual 2 hour walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saugus Iron Works National Historic Site is a National Historic Site is the site of the first integrated ironworks in North America, 1646 ? 1668. It includes the reconstructed blast furnace, forge, rolling mill, and a restored 17th century house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the archaeological site of the 17th-century iron-making plant, the museum collection, the 17th-century Iron Works House, and the reconstructed iron works complex, Saugus Iron Works National Historic Site illustrates the critical role of iron making to 17th-century settlement and its legacy in shaping the early history of the nation. The site's enclave setting on the Saugus River, featuring an open-air museum with working water wheels, evokes a unique experience for park visitors. These resources demonstrate 17th-century engineering and design methods, iron-making technology and operations, local and overseas trade, and life and work in the Massachusetts Bay Colony.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original manufacturing site served as a training ground for skilled iron workers for what would become America's iron and steel industry. Iron making provided the infrastructure for the rise of other colonial industries. Called, &amp;quot;the forerunner of America's industrial giants,&amp;quot; the site served as a center for technology, innovation and invention. The site interprets early industrial manufacturing, with its enduring social, political and environmental ramifications.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The blast furnace, forge, rolling and slitting mill, warehouse, and dock area are all reconstructed on original sites and are based upon extensive archaeological excavations done between 1948 and 1953 by Roland W. Robbins. Hundreds of court records, inventories, and accounts of the original iron works were also consulted to produce a full-size (albeit, conjectural) model of the seventeenth century iron works. The &amp;quot;Iron Works House&amp;quot; is a timber framed, 1680s mansion house, still standing on its original location. It was constructed about a decade after the iron works ceased production.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at the Hilltop Steakhouse&lt;br /&gt;www.hilltopsteakhouse.com&lt;br /&gt;855 Broadway, &lt;br /&gt;Route US 1 South&lt;br /&gt;Saugus, MA&lt;br /&gt;Voice: (781) 233-7700&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221706519000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215564179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saugus Iron Works </name><id>8303295</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221317100000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/8303295/</event_url></item>