<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Green St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.316721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-586-5650</phone><name>Green St. Cafe</name><city>Northampton</city><id>1047118</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.637360</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What is the [WesternMass] EatUp! all about, you might ask? Well, Chris and I both have a passion for supporting local, innovative, delicious restaurants in the Pioneer Valley and so far, we have done well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, we will be having our September EatUp! at none other than the “Embattled” &lt;a href="http://greenstreetcafenorthampton.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;Green St Café&lt;/a&gt; in Northampton on Tuesday night, September 29th at 6:30pm. In support of this longtime Northampton favorite, we will happily enjoy some house specialties, among which is what Mary Nelan of Valley Locavore calls “the best risotto in town.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I used the word 'embattled' because about 5 years ago, “&lt;i&gt;business representatives from Smith College told the owners of the Green Street Café that they planned to use the adjacent property to build a new engineering complex which may eventually engulf the neighborhood. Since Smith College owns many of the properties in the Green Street Neighborhood including the Café, the owners of the restaurant say they are being forced to leave. They said that the college offered to compensate them financially, but they found that the cost of starting over in another section of Northampton is more than Smith was willing to provide. As a result, it seems likely that the Green Street Café will have to close&lt;/i&gt;.” [from the Green St. Café website]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This situation has become quite a political issue in Northampton, but I have been assured that the quality of the food and our dining experience will not be affected. (if you’d like to read an update on what’s going on right now and see how the owner’s are creatively coping: &lt;a href="http://www.gazettenet.com/story/243468" target="_blank"&gt;Embattled City Cafe Opens a New Outlet&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are a few snippets from some of the online reviews:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Local, seasonal produce lovingly prepared and served in a dining room with modern hobbit decor. &lt;br /&gt;Don't be surprised if something you order is hung by the warm wood fire in the dining room to roast or if your waiter can tell you the exact farm your salad leaves came from. The food is simple, sophisticated, and delicious. Definitely worth the price. From TripAdvisor.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Street is one of my favorite restaurants in Western Mass. The ingredients are always fresh, in season and often organic; the flavors are always delectable; and the ambiance is comfortable.&lt;/i&gt; From a Squidoo Lens&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The vibe is laid back and bohemian, but they are serious about the food here. Everything is very fresh and tastes like someone really put effort it cooking it.&lt;/i&gt; From Yelp.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sounds great to me! I can't wait!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been offered a prix fixe menu for $25 for appetizer, entree and dessert, though you are welcome to order off the regular menu if you’d like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let us know as soon as possible by RSVP-ing here: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt; so we can give the restaurant and accurate count.&lt;br /&gt;We hope you can make it!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will be in the private room</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256248334000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252104173000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September EatUp! at the Green Street Cafe in Northampton</name><id>11292838</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254263400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/11292838/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/1/e/global_10391662.jpeg</photo_url></item>