<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Highland Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02492</zip><lat>42.305237</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 453-4005</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Needham</city><id>336450</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.218510</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey, everyone, I hope you had a wonderful vacation and are ready to speak French again. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at Panera Bread's in Needham on Tuesday, August 25th, from 7 to 9.  It should be a lot of fun with lots to tell about what you did over summer vacation (sorry if that sounds like grade school).  Really, though, in my French class at Alliance, that's exactly what my French teacher did every Monday.  He made us tell what we did over the weekend.  In my old age, I could barely remember &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/confused.gif' border='0' alt='confused' /&gt;, but it was a good icebreaker.  Everyone spoke and no one cared about mistakes, accents, nor pronunciation.  It was just to get people to talk.  And that's what this Meetup is all about.  Though it isn't school, it is an opportunity to get over our shyness to speak French.  So I do hope you will come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are fluent and not shy about speaking, I know you may not have the patience with those of us who aren't.  Don't be discouraged about coming.  Our June meeting had quite a few fluent speakers present, including native French speakers, so if August is anything like that then you will be able to enjoy lively conversations with those who are more advanced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So no matter what your level, please put aside that evening and join us.  We are a friendly group of people.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>6571667</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Farzi</member_name><member_id>7518569</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253749616000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>french-789</urlname><id>1150221</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Boston Metrowest French Language Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249849756000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>POST VACATION BLUES?  CHEER UP AT THE AUGUST FRENCH MEETUP.</name><id>11071873</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251241200000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/french-789/events/11071873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/0/global_4128560.jpeg</photo_url></item>