<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Atlantic Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02205</zip><lat>42.353001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Federal Reserve Bank of Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>789278</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054928</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

(PLEASE ONLY SAY THAT YOU WILL "ATTEND" ON THIS PAGE IF YOU HAVE THE INTENTION TO COME. Thank you!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, June 23, we will be out in front of the Federal Reserve Bank of Boston to educate the public about the Fed. Most people do not know that the Federal Reserve is NOT part of the government and that it is privately owned. This will be the first in a series of actions against the Fed through the Summer and Fall of 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your signs. Share your knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The intention is to restore Article 1, Section 8 of the US Constitution that gives Congress the responsibility of regulating our currency. Congress is accountable to the People, the Fed Reserve is not. We should not have to "borrow" our own money from a private banking cartel at interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scam has carried on for far too long, and while America slips further and further into debt with these parasitic Banksters, the Fed Reserve has taken it upon itself to bail out foreign organizations while We the People are being dispossessed of our homes and resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NO MORE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please come out to help us fight this Creature from Jekyll Island and please share this event with others. THIS IS NOT A RALLY FOR, OR AGAINST, ANY POLITICIANS. We ask that anyone participating stays on message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MORE INFO: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/164701023660792/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/164701023660792/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340486223000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338856858000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>END THE FED - Boston Rally for Sound Money</name><id>67767282</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340474400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/67767282/</event_url></item>