<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Garden Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381539</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics (CfA)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1343951</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.128653</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Per an e-mail from David Aguilar at the CfA on Wednesday, February 20 (sign up for the CfA e-mail list!):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As we all know, last week ended with a BANG thanks to a dramatic, and damaging, surprise from outer space. For our Thursday Observatory Night presentation we have invited Gareth Williams from the Minor Planet Center to fill in a few astounding details of this event before our main 7:30 presentation, which features Rebekah Dawson on "Gas Giant Mysteries." Doors will open promptly at 6:59 pm and we will begin with Gareth at 7:15. Also, PLEASE dress warmly tomorrow night. The weather forecasters are calling for clear and cold 20 F degrees. Our main target will be Jupiter! See you tomorrow.&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only Nerd Fun members will be counted in the RSVP list. Visit the CfA website (see below), then decide if you would like to bring guests.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Doors open at 7:00 p.m., but &lt;strong&gt;get there early . . . even before &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;6:45 p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Seating is first-come, first-served for the main lecture room. The overflow crowd sits in a separate screening room. Admission is free.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heather and I arrive at different times. I plan to be there by 6:45 p.m. Look for both of us and our meetup signs in the line, at the back left of the auditorium, and/or on the observatory roof. Don't be shy. Say hi and introduce yourselves.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If weather permits, rooftop stargazing through telescopes will follow the presentation. Dress for stargazing. No experience is necessary. &lt;strong&gt;The Center for Astrophysics&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;Amateur Telescope Makers of Boston&lt;/strong&gt; set up all the telescopes. All you have to do is peek through the lens!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Free parking is available to everyone after 5 p.m. (Ignore the "staff only" signs.) Drive up to the back, up the hill. The presentation is up the stairs that are opposite the observatory-in-a-box.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;From the Harvard stop on the MBTA Red Line, take any bus or trackless trolley going west on Concord Avenue in Cambridge (Arlmont Village and Belmont Center buses; Huron Avenue trolley) and get off at the Observatory Hill stop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;For more information about and directions to this event, visit the CfA website:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.cfa.harvard.edu/events"&gt;http://www.cfa.harvard.edu/events&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;or call them at 617.495.7461.&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;A line forms early for this event. Please do not cut in line because we will meet inside the auditorium: go to the back left of the auditorium as you are facing the front. The overflow crowd goes into a separate screening room, so everyone gets in to see the presentation. Even if we don't sit together, we will meet after the lecture and up on the roof. If you are in the separate screening room, turn right after you exit and walk toward the courtyard, then look for signs pointing the way to the telescopes. You can also look for the meetup sign (both Heather and I have one) while we are waiting in line to look through the telescopes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Sitting at the left rear of the lecture hall is a way to let people find me and an empty seat that much more easily. Please sit where you are most comfortable. We will be able to chat after the lecture, while we wait in line for a chance to stargaze through the several rooftop telescopes. Each telescope is usually trained on a different sight in the nighttime sky, so waiting in several lines gives us plenty of time to introduce ourselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;The CfA would prefer that attendees not take pictures, but if you decide to, please do not use a flash.&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;******************************&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the CfA:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observatory Night: "Gas Giant Mysteries," Rebekah Dawson, CfA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tonight Jupiter will rise in our sky as it has for millenia. We would never guess that its current orderly motion underwent an upheaval in the young solar system. New studies tell the tumultuous story of the giant planets, both here and in other planetary systems throughout the galaxy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;******************************&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a Meetup sign. I usually find a seat at the left rear of the lecture hall; look for me there. After the lecture (and weather permitting), we will meet in the courtyard or in the telescope lines up on the observatory roof.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>74173</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361636779000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357081797000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CfA/Harvard-Smithsonian Observatory: Lecture and Observatory Night</name><id>97359862</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361490300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/97359862/</event_url></item>