<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 College St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01610</zip><lat>42.236149</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fitton Field - Holy Cross</name><city>Worcester</city><id>791073</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.811050</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Photo Walk: Worcester Tornadoes &lt;br /&gt;You must register with the Worcester Art Museum to go on this Photo Walk. &lt;a href="https://educationreg.worcesterart.org/CourseStatus.awp?~~10SAPHT317C" target="_blank"&gt;https://educationreg....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Erb will guide the walks and answer photography questions along the way. The routes will be short enough to provide plenty of time for shooting and exploring. Conclude each session with informal photo sharing and receive the link to a dedicated Flickr group to post and share your favorite photos! Bring your camera, photo equipment, sunscreen, water, and a snack, and dress comfortably. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;June 7 - Worcester Tornadoes Love baseball and photography? Here is a unique opportunity to get access to photograph in places on the field, in the dugouts and from the top of the press box! Baseball games are ripe with photo ops. Join Scott Erb for the opportunity to photograph beyond what the fans in the stands see at the game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must register with the Worcester Art Museum to go on this Photo Walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://educationreg.worcesterart.org/CourseStatus.awp?~~10SAPHT317C" target="_blank"&gt;https://educationreg....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are still openings remaining at this time.&lt;br /&gt; Instructor: Scott Erb     Location: 206     View Member Discount  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Code Begins Ends Meets Fee&lt;br /&gt;10SAPHT317C 06/07/2010 06/07/2010 Monday from 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM, 1 Session 50.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Tell a Friend about this Photo Walk!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join one, two, or all three of these educational and social photography classes. Walk around, shoot photos, and have fun with other photographers. Scott Erb will guide the walks and answer photography questions along the way. The routes will be short enough to provide plenty of time for shooting and exploring. Conclude each session with informal photo sharing and receive the link to a dedicated Flickr group to post and share your favorite photos! Bring your camera, photo equipment, sunscreen, water, and a snack, and dress comfortably. May 17 - Hanover Theatre Take advantage of this special opportunity to photograph one of Worcester's Historic Landmarks, The Hanover Theatre, restored to its original glory. Join Scott Erb and to wander around and photograph the grandeur as well as the details of this magnificent building. May 31 - Tower Hill Botanic Gardens Join Scott Erb for a photo walk around the distinctive gardens of Tower Hill. The array of outstanding plants, beautiful landscaping, and wildlife create a wide range of choices for taking stunning photographs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276793866000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271171709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photo Walk: Worcester Tornadoes </name><id>13169669</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275948000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13169669/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/8/d/global_9341773.jpeg</photo_url></item>