<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 south main street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.758622</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-649-0482</phone><name>west hartford town hall</name><city>west hartford</city><id>841100</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.741458</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>ANOTHER UPDATE! The Organizing for CT pro-healthcare people again changed their plans.   They will not be marching from Larson’s office to Dodd’s.   They will be rallying outside Larson’s Town Hall meeting at the West Hartford Town Hall Auditorium at 4:30 before the Larson Town Hall at 5:30.  As disrupting as this is we need to adjust our anti-healthcare demonstration to be outside the W est H artford Town Hall .   The info from Larson’s team is below – scroll all the way through.  S parately I am sending an e-mail with a map clearly showing where the auditorium is located.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This change has the approval and support of Joe Markley, Tanya, Brian Jones, Jim Bancroft via a quick huddle this morning.   Please e-mail all your groups….and call as many as possible.  We hate to cause this disruption but we’re doing our best to have the citizenry and media impact we all desire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In liberty,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bob Mac Guffie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Wednesday September 2, at 5:30pm, grassroots groups from all over Connecticut will be participating in a &amp;quot;Hands off our Healthcare&amp;quot; rally at Senator Dodd's office in Hartford, and the Tea Party folks will be there in force!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Obama for America has organized a march from Larson's office to Dodd's office in support of government run healthcare on September 2nd, and they are scheduled arrive at Dodd's office around 5:30-6pm, and we want to be there to meet them!!!  They are expecting 100 people, and we want at least double that number.  The press is going to be there to cover the marchers and we CANNOT let them report this as being representative of the majority of the people.  There are more of us opposing government run healthcare than supporting it, but we must SHOW UP and LET OUR VOICED BE HEARD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please, if you go to one rally this year, this is the one to go to.  We are in a critical time and we must keep the pressure on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OofA is bringing letters in support of government run healthcare to Dodd's office, and we are going to bring letters in opposition.  Please write a letter to Dodd and bring it for delivery on September 2nd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dodd's office is 30 Lewis Street, Hartford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tanya&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit Connecticut Tea Party Patriots at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://teapartypatriots.ning.com/groups/group/show?id=2978134%3AGroup%3A25814" target="_blank"&gt;http://teapartypatrio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A CALL TO ACTION TO COUNTER A PRO HEALTH CARE MARCH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE WILL MEET THEM AT DODDS OFFICE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Wednesday Sept 2, 2009 Organizing for America in conjunction with&lt;br /&gt;a bunch of other groups is planning a march from Larson's office to&lt;br /&gt;Dodd's office:&lt;br /&gt;Their message is..........&lt;br /&gt;Let's Get It Done: Health Insurance Reform Now - CT Sends Off the Congressional&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE NEED TO BE THERE IN FULL FORCE TO COUNTER THEM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details TBA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info so far from Tanya (State Tea Party Coordinator)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TANYA WRITES&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey Gang, I am going to up this up on facebook as an event.  I think&lt;br /&gt;Jen is exactly right, we should meet them at Dodd's office with as big&lt;br /&gt;a crowd as we can muster.  We have a week and half (pleeeeeeeenty of&lt;br /&gt;time! hee hee) to get this out to our groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's say Dodd's office, 5:30pm?&lt;br /&gt;Since they are doing a march, I am going to guess they have a permit.&lt;br /&gt;Questions:&lt;br /&gt;1) Do we bother to try to get a permit, or just show up?&lt;br /&gt;2) Do we haul out the sound system, or just use voices and bull horns?&lt;br /&gt;3) Should we have our own letters to give to Dodd from people re: just&lt;br /&gt;say no to nationalized healthcare?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tanya&lt;br /&gt;Jen sent me this email earleir today.  Silent No More wants to be at&lt;br /&gt;Dodd's office when they get there, just like Jen suggests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Jen Ezell, 2nd Congresional District Patriot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sept 2, 2009 Organizing for America in conjunction with a bunch of&lt;br /&gt;other groups is planning a march from Larson's office to Dodd's&lt;br /&gt;office:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's Get It Done: Health Insurance Reform Now - CT Sends Off the&lt;br /&gt;Congressional Delegation (Let's Get It Done: Health Insurance Reform&lt;br /&gt;Now Public Events)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join HCAN and OFA in sending our Congressional Delegation back to&lt;br /&gt;Washington with thousands of declarations of support for meaningful&lt;br /&gt;health insurance reform. We will march from Congressman John Larson's&lt;br /&gt;office (221 Main Street) to Senator Chris Dodd's office (30 Lewis St.)&lt;br /&gt;in Hartford. Let's give them the voices they need to hear to go back&lt;br /&gt;to Washington knowing that they have a mandate to vote for real health&lt;br /&gt;insurance reform.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exact parking and staging locations TBA because of large numbers expected.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time:&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, September 2 from 4:30 PM - 6:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Host:&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer Just&lt;br /&gt;Location: 221 Main St. (Hartford, CT)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;211 Main St.&lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT 06106&lt;br /&gt;· ·&lt;br /&gt;Associated Groups:&lt;br /&gt;Amity for Obama, Barack Obama for President '08 - Connecticut Chapter,&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut Drive for Change,&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut for Obama, Connecticut Latinos For Obama,&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut Women for Obama, Danbury,&lt;br /&gt;CT For Barack Obama, Glastonbury for Obama,&lt;br /&gt;Hartford County for Obama, Litchfield County for Obama,&lt;br /&gt;New Haven CT for Obama,&lt;br /&gt;Stamford CT for Obama,&lt;br /&gt;Yale for Obama (aka Yo-Yo)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.so far they have a little over 100 people signed up to attend.we&lt;br /&gt;should plan a larger group to be waiting for them in front of Dodd's&lt;br /&gt;office.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time to act as a larger group.everyone needs to have as many members&lt;br /&gt;there as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Care, Jen&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252096399000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251329165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Counter-ObamaCare Rally in Hartford !</name><id>11210306</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251923400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/11210306/</event_url></item>