<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is an &lt;strong&gt;approx. 10mi fast-paced hike&lt;/strong&gt; of a section of the Midstate Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been hiking the trail for a few weeks. The challenge in the winter is to find accessible parking areas, which is why I did not post any sections before. For this particular section I know that a small parking lot is available. Thus, I can post this hike here for a very small group to complete it together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be hiking approx. 5mi on the trail until we reach the point where I had hiked to previously when hiking southbound. Then we turn around and hike the same approx. 5mi back to the car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, the reason we cannot traverse is the lack of available parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a fast-paced hike. For this reason I am waitlisting everybody--please reply honestly to the questions asked in your rsvp. Esp. in this weather, no breaks are scheduled; just quick stops to grab a bite to eat, adjust layers, snap a pictures,...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I view this as a nice morning work-out for those of us who don't have time to head to the Whites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Due to the scarce availability of parking, I am NOT posting the meet up spot now&lt;/strong&gt;. You will be traveling to Spencer, MA--this should give you some idea of how long your commute will be. I will e-mail the exact location to confirmed hikers the day before the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required gear: microspikes; layers for winter hiking, drink.&lt;/strong&gt;(Should we receive a significant amount of snow between today and the day of the hike, snowshoes will be required as well.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here the link to the list for winter hiking:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While we are not in the Mountains, the recent cold weather had me wearing quite a few layers of clothing that I usually only wear at higher elevation.  The midstate trail is also at times very exposed to wind. In other words, &lt;strong&gt;please approach this walk/workout/hike like you would a hike in the Whites.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A few words on the midstate trail:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for more information: &lt;a href="http://www.midstatetrail.org/index.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.midstatetrail.org/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I do not know what condition the trail we will be hiking is in and what type the trail is; here and there are road sections; other times you walk passed lovely ponds, through woods,... Part of my enjoyment of crossing MA via the Midstate Trail is to discover the state and be surprised by the trail. And the plus side of doing it in the winter: no bugs!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In case of poor weather&lt;/strong&gt;, I will make a decision as to the status of the hike the day before.  It is not the trail that will determine the decision, but the road conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica</member_name><member_id>10925522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359849503000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359314645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAST-PACED Section Hike; Midstate Trail; Spencer MA</name><id>101643322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359808200000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/101643322/</event_url></item>