<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Bootiful Pets&lt;br /&gt;10:30am - 2pm (Cat's begin at 10:30-Dogs at noon)&lt;br /&gt;Salem Common.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I thought this sounded fun for our guys!  Let's get some Frenchie presence!!!!  Perhaps we can walk through town after to check out the happenings!  Please bring your cameras so we can add to our photo page!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bootiful Pets is an outdoor Halloween costume contest for dogs and cats. The Official Cat of Salem will be chosen (must be Salem cat resident). Owners will be asked to share why their cat should win. Prizes for winners. Registration $5. Cat registration 10:00am. Contest 10:30am. Dog registration at noon. Contest 1:00pm&amp;#8232;&lt;br /&gt;Call for Details or potential cancellation:  978.744.2615&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the details-you'll have to scroll down for the event details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hauntedhappenings.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hauntedhap...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In regards to parking-I don't know the area well enough but I'm sure the url above can give insight.  We may just commuter rail it pending distance from the station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Salem is just 16 miles north of Boston on the Atlantic coast. Salem is easily accessible by car, train, and bus. View maps of Salem. From Route 128-North: Take exit 25A and follow Route 114-East into Salem. Once in Salem, follow signs to the Salem Visitor Center, Museum &amp;amp; Historic Sites and Downtown Parking. Please note: I-95 North and Route 128-North share the same road for the loop around Boston. When the roads divide, stay on Route 128-North. At this point, the exit numbers jump from #45 to #28.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although 114-East is the most accessible route into Salem, you may want to seek alternative routes that receive less traffic during Haunted Happenings. Several suggestions of alternative routes from route 128 include: taking exit 26 to Lowell St. in Peabody, or taking exit 24 to Endicott St. in Danvers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are traveling from the south take Route 93 North to the Mass Pike (I-90 East) via the Ted Williams tunnel (Exit 23) East to Route 1A North. Take Route 1A North to Salem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Train service is available from Boston's North Station. Salem is the fifth stop on the Newburyport/Rockport Commuter Rail Line. At Salem's train depot, exit up stairs, only a five minute walk to downtown area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston (30 minute drive): Take I-93 North to Exit 37-A for I-95 North. Follow I-95 North to Route 128 North. Take exit 25A and follow Route 114-East into Salem. Once in Salem, follow signs to the Salem Visitor Center, Museum &amp;amp; Historic Sites and Downtown Parking. Please note: I-95 North and Route 128-North share the same road for the loop around Boston. When the roads divide, stay on Route 128-North. At this point, the exit numbers jump from #45 to #28. Do not follow the signs to Salem, New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Logan Airport (25 minute drive): Take Route 1-A North and at Salem Border, follow the signs for the Salem Visitor Center, Museum &amp;amp; Historic Sites and Downtown Parking. Logan International Airport is the closest airport to Salem. The Manchester, New Hampshire, regional airport is one-hour northwest of Salem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: Take I-95 South (Maine) or I-93 South (New Hampshire) to Route 128-North. Take exit 25A and follow Route 114-East into Salem. Once in Salem, follow signs to the Salem Visitor Center, Museum &amp;amp; Historic Sites and Downtown Parking. Please note: I-95 North and Route 128-North share the same road for the loop around Boston. When the roads divide, stay on Route 128-North. At this point, the exit numbers jump from #45 to #28.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West: Take I-90-East to I95/Route 128 North. Take exit 25A and follow Route 114-East into Salem. Once in Salem, follow signs to the Salem Visitor Center, Museum &amp;amp; Historic Sites and Downtown Parking. Please note: I-95 North and Route 128-North share the same road for the loop around Boston. When the roads divide, stay on Route 128-North. At this point, the exit numbers jump from #45 to #28.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Train &amp;amp; Bus: Train service is available on the Newburyport/Rockport Commuter Rail Line from Boston's North Station. At the Salem Depot, exit up the stairs. It is a five-minute walk to the Visitor Center. Bus service is availabe on bus #450 or #455 from Boston's Haymarket Square. For train and bus information, contact the MBTA for more information at (800) 392-6100 or www.mbta.com. It takes approximately 30 minutes to travel between Salem and Boston by train, and one hour by bus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ferry: Ferry service from Boston is available with a fast, comfortable ride in only 45 minutes from Boston's Central Wharf, home of the New England Aquarium. Scheduled service runs early in the morning and late into the evening. In 2008, ferry service is available from May 23 until November 2. Schedule, fares and reservations are available from www.salemferry.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be by the registration table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274716110000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221760146000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bootiful Pets Costume Contest-part of the Haunted Happenings in Salem</name><id>8784139</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223827200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/8784139/</event_url></item>