<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are invited to the Glider Club party from Richard and Wendy Gammon.&lt;br /&gt;Cost is $32.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.soargbsc.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.soargbsc.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This years party will be, once again, be at the Manor Restaurant in West Boylston. &lt;br /&gt;It is a couple of miles from 3B3.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Manor Restaurant,&lt;br /&gt;42 West Boylston Street&lt;br /&gt;West Boylston, MA 01583&lt;br /&gt;Phone 508.835.4722 / Fax: 508.835.3893 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.ourmanor.com &lt;br /&gt;There are directions and a map on this website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you must now have recovered from the over indulgence of the celebrations and returned from various travels, you must be ready for glider club party. Again we have the splendid Athenian room at the Manor and we will have music and a chance to dance with you significant other. Please bring along your wife, girlfriend, boyfriend etc. for this most swinging affair in our gliding calendar. Make sure you book the baby sitter now so you can enjoy the evening, as we have the room for four hours or so.&lt;br /&gt;The dinner will be a buffet with a choice of three entrees, and there will be a cash bar for booze, bubbly and plonc.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The dress is &amp;quot;smart casual&amp;quot; with our ladies encouraged to come in party or cocktail dresses. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will also have aviation video and photos, but many will be enjoying the chance to meet our new members and also catch up with old friends and the wives of our male pilots that we see so rarely. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We have in the past had some seventy guests and the Athenian room is good for up to one hundred and fifty, so do bring your friends along. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I need you to reply to this e-mail ASAP with your reservation and the number of you party. I have a few names already, but as the 16th is approaching I need to get final numbers into the Manor a week ahead. &lt;br /&gt;Members will have their GBSC account billed for their reservations. &lt;br /&gt;Other guests can pay by check.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please send your request for seat reservations directly to my e-mail, or call me with any questions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Richard Gammon   gamzoom@charter.net&lt;br /&gt;508 835 2049 Cell 508 380 9970&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. in case you were thinking that this is just a bunch of soaring pilots, the members also fly: kit experimentals, Citabrias, Piper Cubs, Various Pipers, C150, C170, C172, C177, C182, C210, Beachcraft, Lancair 4P, and include Jet Ranger pilots and a few airline pilots.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Richard Gammon</member_name><member_id>6719480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263858117000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262900151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THE GBSC PARTY Dinner-Dance</name><id>12254410</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263684600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/12254410/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/8/global_12535032.jpeg</photo_url></item>