<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>690 Asylum Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.768452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Hartford Financial Services Group Plaza</name><city>Hartford</city><id>243433</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.685677</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's the 27th annual Walk Against Hunger and my 26th time taking part!  I hope my tall friends will join me in raising money for a good cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 27th annual Walk Against Hunger takes place on Sunday, May 2, in Hartford. The event is a fundraiser for Foodshare and several other local anti-hunger charities. I hope you'll consider signing up, asking some friends, family, and co-workers to sponsor you, and coming out to join me. These days, Foodshare is needed more than ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To sign up, follow these easy steps:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) go to &lt;a href="http://www.foodshare.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.foodshare.org&lt;/a&gt; and click on the Walk Against Hunger logo&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) click on &amp;quot;Join a team&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) put &amp;quot;Gloria&amp;quot; in the search box and press search&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) select &amp;quot;Gloria's Glorious Gang&amp;quot; and follow the steps to join my team&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternatively to these steps, just go &lt;a href="http://site.foodshare.org/goto/gloriasgang" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you have signed up, you can raise money using the website tools to e-mail friends and family, or you can print out a brochure and go raise some sponsors the old fashioned way, with paper and pencil! Or, alternatively, if you want a paper brochure, send me an e-mail with your snail mail address and how many brochures you would like and I'll mail them. I can also mail a Walk poster or two if you have a place to hang it up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Walk day, come to The Hartford, on Asylum Avenue in Hartford between 1:00 and 1:30 to turn in your pledges and get signed up. Look for me about 1:45 near the stage and the Walk leaves promptly at 2:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there. If you cannot come, but would like to support those of us who are walking, you can go &lt;a href="http://site.foodshare.org/goto/gloriasgang" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to make a donation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet me near the stage at 1:45, I'll be in a red staff shirt</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272993057000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-28</urlname><id>364032</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Heights Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267237015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk Against Hunger</name><id>12721206</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272819600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-28/events/12721206/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/e/b/global_13336331.jpeg</photo_url></item>