<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Forest Hills Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.300010</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-849-9599</phone><name>Forest Hills Cemetery </name><city>Boston</city><id>680064</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104810</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In this breathtaking ceremony of remembrance, visitors to this lush, Victorian landscape make paper lanterns and set them afloat on the peaceful waters of a small lake. This ritual is based on the traditional Japanese Bon Festival, a time when a door opens to the world of the ancestors, allowing us to send messages to the other side. People enjoy picnics on the grass and a multi-cultural program of music and dance. They decorate their lanterns with calligraphy and notes to those who have died. At sunset, a candle is lit in each lantern, and the glimmering lanterns are set afloat. Drifting and flickering with the wind, the lanterns symbolize the soul’s journey when life ends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is free, with a $10 donation per lantern. Parking is $10; we're encouraging people to take the T. No lighting after dark; bring a flashlight to assist your departure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foresthillstrust.org/calendar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foresthill...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a beautiful event with lots of photo opportunities - exotic dance performers, musicians, lantern painting, lanterns floating on the water during sunset, maybe even a spirit or two floating over the lake .....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plan is to meet at the main gate between 5:30pm and 5:45pm, then walk over to the stage and pond area.  We'll try to pitch a spot by the pond to the left front of the stage.  Since it will be crowded, for those arriving later, look for the yellow balloon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Update on transportation:  Street parking is limited and tends to fill up quickly.  However, there is quite a bit of parking available in the cemetery for $10.   The closest T Station is Forest Hills.   Directions are available on the above link.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the main gate between 5:30pm and 5:45pm.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen</member_name><member_id>2854002</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279909328000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278686605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Forest Hills Lantern Festival</name><id>14050970</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279229400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/14050970/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/global_16302065.jpeg</photo_url></item>