<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This event has been moved to a larger location due to the amount of folks coming! Please note the new location!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the Layoff the Worcester Library is having they are cutting back their hours. They are no longer going to be open on Monday Nights, so we have been asked to move our event to Wed night the 20th instead. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Present your Photos Night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wed May 20th&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM until 9:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;United Congregational Church 6 Institute Road Worcester MA 01609&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is your chance to show us your photos! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are opening the Floor to fellow photographers who want to showcase their photos in a presentation to others. We will provide the digital projector and the room. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need to put your work together on a &amp;quot;thumb&amp;quot; drive that can then be transfered to the computer. (Formats can include PowerPoint, PDF, and Pro Show Gold) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are asking the presentations be limited to &lt;b&gt;10 Minutes&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you don't have a presentation- come and watch the shows- maybe you'll be inspired enough to come back the next time and show your own work!!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to see what you got!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna and Scott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS any tech questions about presentations should be addressed to Don Roberts an member on tis site- go to his profile and email him through the meetup site...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's first come first served.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243555346000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238537066000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Present your Photos Night!</name><id>10082136</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242860400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10082136/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/6/7/global_7929431.jpeg</photo_url></item>