<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us to x-country ski or snow-shoe free of charge and with free loaner equipment(limited quantity on a first come first serve basis).  Maybe try out both. We will meet at 10:00 and you can stay as long as you want. Saima Park has their own write-up about the event, which is below.  When you arrive outside the gate, drive thru the gate to the end of road where you will find a rear parking lot and building. There should be at least 4 cars in the lot. Park here, go inside and pick out your equipment. Those that already have equipment are equally welcome.  Hot chocolate and food available for purchase throughout the day.  National Weather Forecast for Saturday as of 2/21/13 is: Mostly cloudy, with a high near 34.  Hike leader: Richard Fallon, Home is 978-400-5564. &lt;br /&gt;

Pets may be allowed but call Veikko's number below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saima Park is a private park in Fitchburg that is owned and operated by the Finnish community in the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions from intersection of Rt. 2 and Rt. 12 in Leominster. &lt;br /&gt;

1.Head North toward Fitchburg on N Main St (Rt. 12), 1.5 mi. &lt;br /&gt;

2.Turn right onto Bemis Rd. 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;

3.Bear right to continue onto John Fitch Hwy 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;

4. At the traffic circle, take the 2nd exit onto Rindge Rd 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;

5. Turn right onto Scott Rd &lt;br /&gt;

Destination will be on the left 404 ft &lt;br /&gt;

Finnish Center of Saima Park &lt;br /&gt;

61 Scott Rd &lt;br /&gt;

Fitchburg, MA 01420&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Siama Park's write-up is below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday Feb 23. 10:00 a.m.-2:00 p.m. Open house for x-country skiing and snow-shoeing. Some equipment is available to borrow. Finnish Center at Saima Park, 61 Scott Rd., Fitchburg. For more information, call Veikko 978 827-4813 or email ldsulin@verizon.net.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Richard Fallon</member_name><member_id>10897888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361643061000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361450617000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come join us to cross country ski or snow-shoe.</name><id>105669432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361631600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/105669432/</event_url></item>