<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/c/c/event_56338572.jpeg" width="147" height="157" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cool Confidence Created: A Diva's Guide to Promoting a Positive Online Image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: $20 (Current WBOA Members receive $5 cash back at the door)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social media has immersed itself into our lives, having become one of the fastest, most widely used methods of communication and interaction in history. We use it to connect with friends old and new, share updates, think out loud, play games, and interact. What about the professional side of social media? How do we as business owners maintain a balance with our online profiles that we share with friends and colleagues?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social media sites such as LinkedIn, Facebook pages, and Twitter are quickly becoming the most popular way to promote yourself and your business professionally online. This discussion will take us on a tour of these sites - how they works, who uses it, best practices, and how you as a professional businesswoman can use it to benefit your personal and professional goals. We will examine the good, the bad, and yes...the ugly, as we explore these multi-faceted professional networking sites that have taken over the Interweb. We will also discuss how to best develop a confident social online image for you and your company by using some key tips and tricks to put you most confident, positive foot forward for all to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is an interactive, hands-on discussion. Participation is expected and encouraged!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kelly A. Galanis is The Red-Headed Diva - a consultant and presenter who help individuals, groups, and organizations to develop a positive, confident social image by educating them on the proper use of Social Media. She is a higher education professional with over ten years of experience working for both public and private institutions. Her tenure includes a 2-year presidential fellowship in the divisions of Academic Affairs and Advancement and University Relations at Westfield State University. This experience allowed Kelly to work on a variety of projects for the betterment of the University, including developing programs for the alumni population and serving as a leadership figure in the community promoting the college and its values. She is currently Associate Director of Alumni Services at Westfield State and just completed her tenure as President of the Massachusetts Women in Public Higher Education. She is a three-time alumna of Bay Path College, where she earned her Associates and Bachelors degrees in Legal Studies and a Master of Science degree in Communication and Information Management. Kelly's dedication and commitment to her profession and volunteer organizations was honored when selected as one of Business West magazine&amp;rsquo;s Forty Under 40 &amp;ndash; the class of 2008. She has been featured in social media articles for Business West and CASE Currents magazines, and is highly sought after to present on the topic for a variety of groups and organizations.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319328393000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316284029000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Breakfast Meeting: A Diva's Guide to Promoting a Positive Online Image</name><id>33926972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319111100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/33926972/</event_url></item>