<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Unit 3</address_2><address_1>21 Pickman Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.527053</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Shana's home</name><city>Salem</city><id>1405824</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.888083</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a &lt;b&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/b&gt;.  Please be respectful of others who may want to RSVP and &lt;i&gt;only sign up for one or two mini-meetups a month&lt;/i&gt;.  See this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt; for more details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;A lot of us probably grew up around and play card games like poker, hearts, spades, gin rummy, go fish, etc.  These card games have things in common with each other, having us think along the lines of having high cards in a suit or trying to make melds of some kind.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Card games found in other cultures and using different decks can have different mechanics which exercise different parts of your brain.  Beating your opponent and working with your partner can require untraditional ways of thinking as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this afternoon, I will be teaching the italian card game Briscola and the chinese card game Tichu.  Both of which are immensely popular in their countries of origin (some estimates say hundreds of millions of chinese play Tichu every day)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep in mind this does have an end time of 5:30 pm to make room for another meetup on this same day.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;Food theme:&lt;br /&gt;The theme for this event will be something &amp;quot;exotic&amp;quot;.  You can interpret that as bringing imported lulos to bringing egg rolls from your local chinese take-out; totally up to you.  We will have generic drinks and snacks on hand.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;About the location:&lt;br /&gt;Pickman Street is located between the Commons and the water. Parking on Pickman can be tight, but there should be ample parking along either Pleasant Street (by the Commons) or Collins Street (by the water) &lt;br /&gt;It will take place on the third floor unit. &lt;br /&gt;Note: there will be two cats present that will be very very sad if they have to get locked up. They are very polite however. If anyone would like to attend but has allegeries please send me a private message.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295279048000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291578651000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: International Card Games</name><id>15649110</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295114400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15649110/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/1/global_11205793.jpeg</photo_url></item>