<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Intermediate (9 miles)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When:&lt;/strong&gt; Wednesday, 3/7, 10:30am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: Wednesday's forecast is good, but please check back a couple days before!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/3/2/e/event_71694062.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Pumpelly Trail is 4.5 miles. Round-trip, it's 9 miles, but in my opinion, it's nicer than the White Dot...less huffing and puffing and more views! (Only one steep section.) We'll start at 10:30am. It doesn't get dark until 6:15 now, and we should be done around 4-4:30 (depending on amount of snow/ice). That gives us almost 2 hours padding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail information:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/trav-rec/mt_monad/mmpumpelly.html"&gt;http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/trav-rec/mt_monad/mmpumpelly.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT Requirements for Winter in Mountains:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The equipment below is very important, you don't need to be some expert mountaineer, just to be prepared. I will not take risks in iffy conditions. Winter hiking isn't much different from summer, but you must be prepared, for safety's sake.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full day's water and food required, in case of emergency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dress in layers, no cotton (danger of hypothermia if you get wet in wind).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hiking boots, snow boots, or hightops required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microspikes required. (Stabilizers like "Yaktraks" are &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; adequate for ice on rocks.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flashlight or headlamp required, in case of emergency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Gaiters" required (they cover boots + keep snow out). We won't know how deep the snow is or what's melted until we get there. &lt;em&gt;(If you don't have time to buy any, just rig something up to keep snow out of your boots, garbage bag + duct-tape, whatever.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cellphone or GPS strongly recommended in case of emergency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always a good idea to bring extra gloves, socks, hat, batteries, first-aid items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals allowed at Monadnock.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Actually found out my snowshoes DO have spikes, but since I originally said they were not needed, we'll just stick to crampons/microspikes. I have it on good authority the snow above the treeline blows away quickly, anyway. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Google Maps, enter, "&lt;em&gt;E Lake Rd, Dublin, NH&lt;/em&gt;" (&lt;strong&gt;without&lt;/strong&gt; "&lt;em&gt;Pumpelly Trail&lt;/em&gt;"). Alternatively, enter, "&lt;em&gt;Barney Rd, Dublin, NH&lt;/em&gt;" (because the trailhead is &lt;strong&gt;just east&lt;/strong&gt; of this private road).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I imagine most members would take Route 2 to 202. (If so, it is Exit 19.) Take Route 202 North into New Hampshire. At the center of Jaffrey, go straight onto Route 137 North. This will take you past the park entrance for the White Dot/White Cross trails. At Route 101 (10-15 minutes), turn left to head west.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The center of Dublin is not far, and has a &lt;strong&gt;rotary&lt;/strong&gt; instead of a light. Next, look for a brown sign on your right with "Monadnock State Park." Both Snow Hill Rd and E Lake Rd are on your left. &lt;strong&gt;Don't take a sharp left...go diagonally left onto E Lake Rd&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E Lake Rd becomes &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lake Rd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. (I don't think there's a sign, this is just FYI.) Look for a brown cottage on the right; the trailhead is on the left. (&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Barney Rd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is on the left after that, so if you pass it, you've gone too far.) Parking is on the left side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Be aware I may not see morning emails/RSVPs. If people want to carpool, please post a comment right here ahead of time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small white Dodge Stratus. Parking is on the road.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331266471000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330753291000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pumpelly Trail, Mount Monadnock (Reschedled from last Monday)</name><id>54774862</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331134200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/54774862/</event_url></item>