<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Updated Update:&lt;/b&gt; I'll be organizing instead of TJ.  -Matt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This is part of the &lt;b&gt;James Whale&lt;/b&gt; film festival going on from September 11 to September 21st at the Harvard Film Archive. Here I thought that Frankenstein was just a good horror film... you can see what is playing at &lt;a href="http://hcl.harvard.edu/hfa/films/2009julsep/whale.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://hcl.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt; the double-feature of &lt;b&gt;The Man in the Iron Mark / The Invisible Man&lt;/b&gt; is Sunday Sept 13 at 7:00 pm. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet outside the Harvard Film Archive and grab seats by 6:40 pm. &lt;b&gt;Matt&lt;/b&gt; will be there by 6:30 pm or so.  He is 6 foot 2, and will be carrying a &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;blue&lt;/span&gt; messenger bag.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you'd like to meet for dinner beforehand, &lt;b&gt;Matt&lt;/b&gt; will also be at &lt;b&gt;Felipe's Taqueria&lt;/b&gt;, 83 Mt. Auburn St. Cambridge, MA. 02138 (&lt;a href="http://www.felipestaqueria.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.felipestaq...&lt;/a&gt;) at 5:30 and will head over to the Film Archive with those who join him when they finish dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Saturday September 12 at 7pm&lt;/i&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frankenstein&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directed by James Whale. &lt;br /&gt;With Boris Karloff, Mae Clarke, John Boles &lt;br /&gt;US 1931, 35mm, b/w, 71 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Universal hoped to repeat the success of the Tod Browning/Bela Lugosi Dracula (1931) with a version of &lt;b&gt;Frankenstein&lt;/b&gt;. When the Laemmles offered the project to Whale, his imagination was fired by the material, and he took total control over both the screenplay and the production design. Taking advantage of the subject’s visual possibilities for the grotesque and the macabre, Whale emulated the look of German expressionist cinema – in striking contrast to the low-key naturalism of Waterloo Bridge, his previous film. The juxtaposition of Frankenstein’s impending marriage and the creation of the monster, who will disrupt that union, remains notably charged and open to the many contemporary queer readings of the film&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bride of Frankenstein&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directed by James Whale. &lt;br /&gt;With Boris Karloff, Colin Clive, Ernest Thesiger &lt;br /&gt;US 1935, 35mm, b/w, 75 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Frankenstein’s success guaranteed that Universal would produce a sequel. Wary of being seen exclusively as a director of horror films, Whale balked at the idea. To secure his cooperation, the studio granted him almost complete freedom, and Whale took advantage of the situation to create his most outlandishly perverse film. The resulting horror-comedy is widely considered his masterpiece and can be read as a darkly satiric assault on the institution of marriage. The film opens with a prologue featuring a ménage à trois between the Shelleys and Lord Byron before settling into the story of Henry Frankenstein returning to the laboratory to create a mate for his monster. The climactic meeting of the would-be spouses is simultaneously hilariously and heartbreakingly grotesque&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;James Whale: Of Monsters, Melodrama and the Production Code:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The story of James Whale’s rise and fall in Thirties Hollywood illustrates the high stakes risks and rewards of filmmaking in the studio era. Whale’s early successes earned him only a brief freedom, and the subsequent decades have been unkind, with some of his best films remaining little-seen and the story of his life and career increasingly encrusted with myth, rumor and speculation. Associated most vividly with Universal’s horror films, Whale in fact distinguished himself in almost every genre prominent in 1930s Hollywood: the musical, the melodrama, the war film, costume drama and screwball comedy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;British-born James Whale began his career in a WWI prison camp. Captured by the Germans, he became active in the camp’s theater, which led him to the London stage after the war, achieving fame with his production of Journey’s End, the celebrated drama about life in the trenches. He came to Hollywood on the coattails of this achievement, ending up at Universal Pictures, where he stayed for most of the 1930s. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Whale was a man of striking contrasts. Although the war left him an abiding antipathy towards Germany, his filmmaking was profoundly influenced by Weimar cinema: the sly wit of Lubitsch, Murnau’s mobile camera, and the visual stylization of German expressionism. Born into poverty, he projected the air of a proper British gentleman that barely concealed the wicked sense of humor so important to his films. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Streaks of perverse wit and a fascination with the dark side of human behavior make Whale’s work from the early and mid-1930s so memorable, yet these qualities are in short supply in his later films, undoubtedly due, in part, to the restrictions of the Production Code, designed to rein in the wilder strains of Hollywood filmmaking after its enforcement began in 1934. Yet there is no one obvious reason for the decline of Whale’s career at the end of the 1930s but rather several. His reign as one of Universal’s most valued directors came to a sudden end when the studio changed management in 1936, due in part to the extravagant cost of Whale’s Show Boat. Removed from the studio’s protection, Whale acquired a reputation for being difficult; he may also have become too disillusioned, or burnt out, to pursue work as hungrily as he would have needed to. And some have also pointed to Whale’s homosexuality as another source of his alienation from the studio establishment. Robert Aldrich later said, 'Jimmy Whale was the first guy who was blackballed because he refused to stay in the closet.' &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;While this retrospective gives central place to Whale’s horror films, which fully retain their visual distinctiveness and the thrill of their subversive natures, it also gives a chance to revisit Waterloo Bridge and Show Boat, two of Whale’s best films, that have in recent years emerged from the shadows cast by subsequent, inferior remakes, while also bringing new prints and rediscoveries from Universal with the rarely-screened gems Impatient Maiden and especially The Kiss Before the Mirror&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission:&lt;/b&gt; &amp;quot;Tickets for all regular screenings are available 45 minutes before show time at the Cinematheque on the lower level of the Carpenter Center. HFA does not sell tickets in advance, and a separate admission fee is charged for each screening. Members may reserve tickets in advance for special event screenings.  $8 - Regular Admission&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hcl.harvard.edu/hfa/general_info.html#directions" target="_blank"&gt;http://hcl.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Harvard Film Archive is located in the lower level of the Carpenter Center for the Visual Arts at 24 Quincy Street, in Cambridge, Massachusetts. We are east of the Harvard Square Red Line T Stop, in between the Harvard Faculty Club and the Fogg Art Museum, one block north of Massachusetts Avenue between Broadway and Harvard Streets in the Harvard University campus&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Although parking in Cambridge is difficult (most of the surrounding streets have restricted parking for Cambridge residents only), metered parking on Broadway and Harvard Streets, as well as the rest of Harvard Square, is free after 6 pm. Film-goers are encouraged to use public transportation, particularly the MBTA Red Line&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt</member_name><member_id>6567601</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252989881000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251136590000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Frankenstein, Bride of Frankenstein @ Harvard Film Archive</name><id>11187541</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252796400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11187541/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>