<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>103 Dike Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02909</zip><lat>41.816017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fete</name><city>Providence</city><id>4996222</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.443375</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Its a Collective Saturday Night!!!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chanteuse, a music series curated by The Jes Powers Project, will celebrating its first a year of great performances and collaborations. This past year Chanteuse has brought together more than 30 performers over the course of six shows; from locally known favorites, to regional bands such as SIRSY, and international indie performer Ember Swift. Chanteuse offers an opportunity for vocalists who are as diverse in sound as they are in styles to showcase their original music and perform together in unique and entertaining collaborations. In partnership with F&amp;ecirc;te, Jess Powers kicks off a new year for Chanteuse with a full lineup of local starlets. Fete has a sound system that continues to amaze audiences, and an elegant atmosphere. I met some of the artists last summer who were creating the interior - it looked amazing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I went to the first Chanteuse show last year at Firehouse 13 and not knowing what to expect, it was a great show and I was really happy I went! The variety of singers is good and its definitely worth a listen. Fete is Providence's newest music venue and and I haven't been yet! So, let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The show starts at 8pm. Doors open at 7:00PM. Tickets are $10 before the show and $12 at the door. Tickets can be purchased from the Fete website at: &lt;a href="http://www.fetemusic.com/event/chanteuse-anniversary-showcase/"&gt;http://www.fetemusic.com/event/chanteuse-anniversary-showcase/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP so I know who you are!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the silver scarf and black cap!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329062928000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328470981000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Collective Saturday Night - Chanteuse!</name><id>51142922</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329004800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/51142922/</event_url></item>