<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>152 Commonwealth Ave Unit M-1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.458334</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(877) 578-4777</phone><name>Lens Pro To Go</name><city>Concord</city><id>1066094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.396617</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Please everyone make sure to add the group &amp;quot;The Great Model Shoot&amp;quot; on facebook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=159978960696860#!/group.php?gid=100281333361530" target="_blank"&gt;The Great Model Shoot group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is also on facebook &amp;quot;The Great Model Shoot v3&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=159978960696860" target="_blank"&gt;The Great Model Shoot v3 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Last time we had around 60-70 people attend! This time we want to make things bigger. Read on....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're planning on having a 65inch tv for tethered shooting and also a 30 inch tv to display pictures from the past shoots that we've hosted (make sure to bring a cd of your best jpegs to be put on display).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This time around for registration we are having everyone go on The Great Model Shoot facebook page and add it as a friend and post a quick comment and e-mail address as well as the traditional paper work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to be using one of the back rooms as a changing and make-up area this time around to make things easier. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So last time this event took place, I asked a few of you as you were leaving if you had a good time and if you would do it all over again, everyone said yes. So my next question to you was if December sounded good, everyone said yes. So here it is again, the Great Model Shoot v3.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event was started with the simple idea of networking photographers with models. Now it has grown to include hair stylists,&lt;br /&gt;designers &amp;amp; make-up artists. This is a jumping point for any photographer. In the past we’ve had people with $500 dollar cameras to $30 thousand dollar cameras come in and shoot side by side. The Great Model shoot is a great place to ask questions and learn about new techniques and network or build up your portfolio. If you’re on the other end of things such as designers, make-up artists &amp;amp; hair stylists;&lt;br /&gt;you get to build your portfolio as well by networking and getting photos of your work. Models will also get to build their portfolio&lt;br /&gt;and network with other models and photographers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ve adjusted the price to compensate for studio rental and all the little extra’s included. This is a great chance to build everyone’s portfolio&lt;br /&gt;in a professional environment. LensProToGo is located in Concord MA and contains all modern equipment from Nikon &amp;amp; Canon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$40 for photographers               $20 for models&lt;br /&gt;                 payable cash the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is what is included with the price.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building everyone’s portfolio&lt;br /&gt;Networking opportunities&lt;br /&gt;Education on styles &amp;amp; equipment&lt;br /&gt;On site technical support&lt;br /&gt;Discount rentals on equipment&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments / lunch&lt;br /&gt;Legal forms for photographers &amp;amp; models&lt;br /&gt;Make-up artists &amp;amp; hair stylist&lt;br /&gt;7 hours of studio time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details at: unitymike.com  (will be updated sometime this week)&lt;br /&gt;Just click on the link for &amp;quot;The Great Model Shoot v3&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're still looking for a few more backdrops and light setups to be used on the day of this event. If you bring a backdrop and light setup then your admission will be discounted for a total of $20 off. &lt;br /&gt;    (Thanks Ed Read for helping out last time around)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Disclaimer:   If you are photographed here, please understand that the photographers will be using them on their portfolio (this is a networking event).  These pictures will be seen on the internet.  The basic concept of this event is photographers take your picture, you get the pictures from them and they also get to use them on their portfolio (internet and hard copy). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy running around making sure everythings going good. Most likely will not have a camera strapped to me for awhile on this day. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hendrickson</member_name><member_id>12134347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293671568000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286378030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Great Model Shoot v3</name><id>hctppynqbqb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292162400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/15021366/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/2/global_18505970.jpeg</photo_url></item>