<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>2ND FLOOR</address_2><address_1>5 Pleasant Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.263517</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 736-0742</phone><name>EPOCA OFFICE</name><city>Worcester</city><id>669439</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802325</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Battle Unauthorized Use of Your Photos Online &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 2 hour free seminar will focus on how to protect your photographic images, whether you post photographs online occasionally to having your own web site filled with your work. We will be covering how photographers can protect their work online from theft by both clients and companies, who are more and more frequently looking to images online as a way to create ad campaigns without having to hire a photographer. The seminar will cover the basics of copyright law, fair use, ways images can be 'stolen' and ways to protect images through watermarking, adding metadata and registering photographs with the US Copyright Office. This seminar is sponsored by the Worcester Photography Center and the key speaker will be Teya Hahn Rutherford. Ms. Rutherford holds a J.D. from Boston University School of Law and is a professional portrait photographer who is a member of WPPI and PPAM, both of which have recognized her talents with awards for her portrait and bridal work.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the front of the room!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222388371000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219159280000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Battle Unauthorized Use of Your Photos Online </name><id>8576477</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222210800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/8576477/</event_url></item>