<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Just for starters, no movie about the Dutch Resistance during World War II has any right to be this wildly entertaining, not to mention this provocative and potently erotic.&amp;quot; - Peter Travers, Rolling Stone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;BLACK BOOK, which takes its title from a secret list of Dutch collaborators, is an impressively old-fashioned yet fashionably embittered movie.&amp;quot; - J. Hoberman, Village Voice &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rachel Steinn is a Jewish woman living in Holland during the early days of World War II. When Axis forces take control of Holland, Rachel's family are killed in a bombing raid while most of the city's Jews are rounded up and sent to Nazi death camps. Rachel manages to narrowly avoid capture, and joins the local resistance movement. With her hair dyed blonde, Rachel can easily pass for a gentile, and when the leader of the Dutch resistance movement learns his son has been captured by Axis forces, Rachel is asked to use her feminine charms to persuade a German commander to arrange for the boy's release. Rachel soon finds herself caught up in a dangerous double life as she becomes a sexual plaything for the Nazis while attempting to bring down their evil empire as a spy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Verhoeven's first film made outside of Hollywood in 22 years, is also his most rapturously reviewed work in ages. Since winning &amp;quot;Best International Film&amp;quot; at the Venice Film Festival last year it has amassed a buzz that one of his films hadn't generated since THE 4TH MAN. Ripe with his trademark stylized flourishes, BLACK BOOK looks as though it may just be good enough to make people stop referring to Verhoeven as &amp;quot;the director of Showgirls&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Paul Verhoeven, w/ Carice van Houten, Sebastian Koch, Thom Hoffman, Halina Reijn. In Dutch, English, German, and Hebrew (with English subtitles), 2h15m &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that start time is approximate until Coolidge Corner comes out with their schedule for next week. Additionally this film has gotten some mixed reviews, some the highest number of stars that can be given, some fair to midling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be hosted by Nicole, who will be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater. Afterwards, we'll head off to a local restaurant (probably the Thai place or Pho Lemongrass) for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177281238000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176471891000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Black Book at Coolidge Corner</name><id>5666408</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177108200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5666408/</event_url></item>