<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>717784</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703319</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Most Dangerous Man in America: Daniel Ellsberg and the Pentagon Papers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With exceedingly well-crafted and intelligent interviews, expertly-paced editing and a tightly written script,  The Most Dangerous Man in America should be required viewing for every citizen in this nation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a history lesson, Judith Ehrlich and Rick Goldsmith’s enthralling new documentary, The Most Dangerous Man in America: Daniel Ellsberg and the Pentagon Papers, is as solid as a textbook, stitching together old broadcast footage, first-person testimony, tart excerpts from the Nixon White House tapes, and noirish recreations into riveting, revelatory political drama.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This fascinating subject matter allows the filmmakers to create a documentary that is at times reminiscent of Man on Wire and The Fog of War both in tone and filmmaking prowess, and it’s equally as entertaining and informative in telling the story of a man whose legacy helped in ending the Vietnam War.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday at 4/17 - Film starts at 7 PM &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271717372000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271250163000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Most Dangerous Man in America: Daniel Ellsberg and the Pentagon Papers</name><id>13179503</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271544300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/13179503/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>