<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Harrison Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Encuentro5 (fifth floor)</name><city>Boston</city><id>610414</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Friends,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March, 2008 ushered in the sixth year of war and occupation “without end” on Iraq. In an act of arrogance and impunity, Congress in a bipartisan vote approved another $162 billion in funding for the wars on Iraq and Afghanistan. Stepped up threats against Iran and the increased likelihood of a U.S. troop “surge” into Afghanistan point to an imperative for action and an independent voice from the peace and justice movement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In light of these developments, grass roots forces from around the country gathered together at the end of June for the National Assembly to End the Iraq War and Occupation in Cleveland, Ohio. At the conference an action plan for the months ahead was discussed and approved in a democratic vote. As part of this plan, over 95% voted in favor of supporting pre-election protests being organized in cities and localities around the country on October 11, 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was on October 11, 2002 that Congress approved the “Iraq War Resolution” granting the Bush administration authorization to invade Iraq. The weeks ahead promise to be filled with debate as the election campaigns gear up. Instead of being spectators who watch the media pundits put their spin on the political pronouncements of the candidates, the October 11 protests present us with an opportunity to be engaged in injecting our agenda, the antiwar agenda, into the intensifying debate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us in an initial planning meeting as we prepare a Boston protest demanding the immediate and unconditional withdrawal of all occupation forces from Iraq and the closing of all military bases. All are invited. Looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, August 9, 3:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;Encuentro 5&lt;br /&gt;33 Harrison Avenue, 5th Floor&lt;br /&gt;Boston (in Chinatown)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Peace and Solidarity,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marilyn Levin&lt;br /&gt;*Arlington/Lexington United for Justice with Peace, New England United&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Liam Madden&lt;br /&gt;*IVAW – Boston Chapter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suren Moodliar&lt;br /&gt;Mass Global Action&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann Glick&lt;br /&gt;*Newton Dialogues for Peace&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nate Goldshlag&lt;br /&gt;Smedley D. Butler Brigade, Chapter 9 Veterans for Peace&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angela Kelly&lt;br /&gt;*Mass Peace Action&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Shannon&lt;br /&gt;American Friends Service Committee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Harris&lt;br /&gt;Greater Boston Stop the Wars Coalition&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Organization for identification purposes only&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3392784</member_name><member_id>3392784</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Schaich</member_name><member_id>4406518</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Harris</member_name><member_id>5188497</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Suren Moodliar</member_name><member_id>5714882</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218481905000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People for Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>stopthewars</urlname><id>708558</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Antiwar</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217807256000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>All out October 11, Initial Planning Meeting</name><id>8469824</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218308400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/stopthewars/events/8469824/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/global_2184137.jpeg</photo_url></item>