<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Providence Pl</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.828985</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.270.4646</phone><name>Providence Place Cinemas</name><city>Providence</city><id>728794</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.425797</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Act now and get FREE PASSES for the screening of THE BEST EXOTIC MARIGOLD HOTEL!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Fox Searchlight Pictures cordially invites you and a guest to a special advance screening of THE BEST EXOTIC MARIGOLD HOTEL starring Judi Dench and Maggie Smith, among other big names. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Wednesday, April 25 &lt;br /&gt;

7:00pm &lt;br /&gt;

Providence Place Cinema &lt;br /&gt;

Providence, RI &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

TO DOWNLOAD A PAIR OF PASSES, click this quick link: &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/IMxdb4"&gt;http://bit.ly/IMxdb4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Tickets are complimentary, but expected to go quickly as there are only a limited number. Please arrive early as seating will be available on a first come, first served basis and is not guaranteed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Description:&lt;/span&gt; THE BEST EXOTIC MARIGOLD HOTEL follows a group of British retirees who decide to “outsource” their retirement to less expensive and seemingly exotic India. Enticed by advertisements for the newly restored Marigold Hotel and bolstered with visions of a life of leisure, they arrive to find the palace a shell of its former self. Though the new environment is less luxurious than imagined, they are forever transformed by their shared experiences, discovering that life and love can begin again when you let go of the past. Rated PG-13. &lt;a href="http://www.foxsearchlight.com/thebestexoticmarigoldhotel/"&gt;http://www.foxsearchlight.com/thebestexoticmarigoldhotel/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is posted as an FYI - if you want to go, please RSVP once you have your tckets so other members know who to look for! Get your passes now and GO EARLY!!!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335423508000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334852797000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Providence Collective - FYI: Free Movie Passes for new Fox Searchlight Film!</name><id>61263612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335394800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/61263612/</event_url></item>