<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Storrow Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.352674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-787-7200</phone><name>Hatch Shell/ Esplanade</name><city>Boston</city><id>696434</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085946</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>i'm completely, thoroughly sick of the rain and i'm dying to skate again.  i'm really looking forward to a nice day of skating around the charles river with like minded folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;why should &lt;b&gt;you&lt;/b&gt; come out and skate?  it might not rain, that's why.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;another reason to come out and skate?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;after the skate, please join me as i head to the border cafe in harvard square to celebrate the lack of rain with a couple of delicious margaritas.  (if it rains, i may go there just to be spiteful.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;but, oh yeah -- the skating.  i'll be at the hatch shell at 2:15.  we'll hang for 15 minutes or so and then we'll take off, skating for an hour or so&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;please note:  this is a skate for &lt;b&gt;all&lt;/b&gt; skill levels.  if you're an intermediate or advanced skater, please feel free to take off ... but please rejoin us to chat as we skate along.  if you're really advanced and you're the first one to border cafe, save me a seat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(you may have detected a pattern here.  the memorial day skate ended at the border cafe, too.  with margaritas.  well, ok -- you got me.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i'll be watching the weather closely on saturday and i'll cancel the skate as early as possible if it rains, so please check this page before you head out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see you around the river.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>i'll email a cell # to all 'Yes' or 'Maybe' RSVPs on saturday morning</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>paul</member_name><member_id>4738108</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247262936000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245905695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Good Lord -- it might not rain on Saturday!  Let's Skate!</name><id>10731873</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246127400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/10731873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/8/global_1713624.jpeg</photo_url></item>