<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>411 Waverley Oaks Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.387138</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Wave Sports Pub</name><city>Waltham </city><id>4385252</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.203247</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;First Annual Piggy's 5K Run/Walk will be held Saturday November 17, 2012 starting at 12:00 in Waltham at The Waverley Oaks Athletic Club. This race is in loving memory of a wonderful man that we suddenly lost last summer. Paul (Piggy) Logue was born, raised and a lifelong resident of Waltham. Paul loved the Waltham community and therefore we thought this was fitting to raise money and give back to the community through the Paul Logue Charitable Fund. This event is generously sponsored by The Waverley Oaks Athletic Club. This course is a fast fairly flat 3.1 miles (5K). The course is paved, therefore strollers or baby joggers are allowed on the course. This year the race is proud to be part of the Race Around Waltham Series (RAW) which encourages support of all Waltham races and promotes friendly competition by tracking runners, walkers and volunteers who participate in six Waltham races for additional prizes. Runners and walkers welcome -- tell your friends and bring the kids! Post-race party at The Sons Of Italy in Waltham that evening at 7:00. Please come and help us celebrate our first annual run in Paul (Piggy) Logue's memory! Food, DJ, raffles and fun!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Course Description&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The event will begin at 12:00pm starting and finishing at Waverley Oaks Athletic Club in Waltham. The course is a fast, fairly flat 3.1 miles (5K). The course is paved, therefore strollers or baby joggers are allowed on the course. In addition for safety purposes no skateboards, roller blades/skates, bicycles, or animals can be taken on the course. Chip timing provided by RaceWire. Top male (s) and female (s) finishers in each age group TBD at time of race&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;T-Shirts&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

First 300 to registered get free t-shirt &lt;br /&gt;

﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim Irving</member_name><member_id>24803612</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353332192000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Waltham-Trail-Runners</urlname><id>1479223</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Waltham Trail Runners</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352660400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Piggy's 5K Run/Walk</name><id>90942402</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353171600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Waltham-Trail-Runners/events/90942402/</event_url></item>