<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jane McGonigal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;tells us how&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reality Is Broken&lt;br /&gt;Why Games Make Us Better&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;How They Can Change the World&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, February 1, 2011&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM  Harvard Book Store&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: : :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is free; no tickets are required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: : :&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is glad to welcome renowned game designer JANE McGONIGAL as she discusses the applications that game-play can have on the everyday world. Her new book is Reality Is Broken: Why Games Make Us Better and How They Can Change the World.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More than 174 million Americans are gamers, and the average young person in the United States will spend ten thousand hours gaming by the age of twenty-one. According to Jane McGonigal, the reason for this mass exodus to virtual worlds is that videogames are increasingly fulfilling genuine human needs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drawing on positive psychology, cognitive science, and sociology, Reality Is Broken uncovers how game designers have hit on core truths about what makes us happy and utilized these discoveries in virtual environments. Videogames consistently provide the exhilarating rewards, stimulating challenges, and epic victories that are so often lacking in the real world. But why, McGonigal asks, should we use the power of games for escapist entertainment alone? Her research suggests that gamers are expert problem solvers and collaborators because they regularly cooperate with other players to overcome daunting virtual challenges, and she helped pioneer a fast-growing genre of games that aims to turn game-play to socially positive ends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Reality Is Broken, she reveals how these new alternate reality games are already improving the quality of our daily lives, fighting social problems such as depression and obesity, and addressing vital twenty-first-century challenges—and she forecasts the thrilling possibilities that lie ahead. She introduces us to games like World Without Oil, a simulation designed to brainstorm—and therefore avert—the challenges of a worldwide oil shortage, and Evoke, a game commissioned by the World Bank Institute that sends players on missions to address issues from poverty to climate change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“McGonigal's penetrating, entertaining look into gaming culture is a vibrant mix of technology, psychology, and sociology, told with the vision of a futurist and the deft touch of a storyteller.... The book moves effortlessly from Herodotus to Halo, stitching together an intellectually stimulating view of human culture past, present, and future. And while not downplaying the potential for negative consequences, such as 'gamer addiction,' McGonigal makes an inspiring case for the way games can both enhance our personal happiness and help society.” —Publishers Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296609092000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294877504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reality Is Broken</name><id>16028611</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296604800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/16028611/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/6/global_5340422.jpeg</photo_url></item>