<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come out and see Jamie Foxx and Robert Downey Jr, two egotistical but often entertaining actors in this film designed to show off their acting chops. Hey, Downey was great as Ironman! There should also be some great music in this film. 

Check out the trailer for the grit this film has to offer - important subject matter but not the usual hollywood fare!

[b]Update[/b]

The movie is is at 7. We (Susan and Fred), should be at the theater lobby at 6:15. If the movie is upstairs, We'll be waiting by the tables at the front of the lobby in front of the giant window. If the movie is downstairs, we will be just behind the rope near the back ticket tearer across from the concession stand. We will both be wearing red meetup hats, so we should be easy to spot.

We strongly encourage you to buy your ticket ahead of time at Fandango.com!

After the movie, the group gathers outside the doors of the room showing the movie, so if you miss us at the beginning you can find us then. And after the second gathering we head out for some munchies and a beer. Or two.

[b]Synopsis[/b]

In "The Soloist," an emotionally soaring drama about the redemptive power of music, journalist Steve Lopez (Oscar® nominee Robert Downey Jr.) discovers Nathaniel Anthony Ayers (Oscar® winner Jamie Foxx), a former classical music prodigy, playing his violin on the streets of L.A. As Lopez endeavors to help the homeless man find his way back, a unique friendship is formed, one that transforms both their lives. "The Soloist" is directed by Joe Wright (Golden Globe winner for Best Drama and Oscar® nominee for Best Picture "Atonement").

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="470" height="264"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/vrrLJT4YS9I&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="470" height="264" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See meetup description for how to find me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan B</member_name><member_id>461418</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246617035000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238938802000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Soloist</name><id>10118965</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240611300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/10118965/</event_url></item>