<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Washington St., Suite 6B</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.518270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-639-1236</phone><name>A Higher Balance Healing Center</name><city>Salem</city><id>1342529</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is a special healing circle for this night, in place of the regular Kriya Meditation practice that happens every Sunday. This class will be facilitated by Mark Kolenski, who has received training in this beautiful process. We will gather, form two circles, say some prayers, write some healing intentions, and then chant OM for 45 minutes. Every 15 minutes, we'll switch new people into the center. A very simple but powerful technique! Come try it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    OM Healing  has been brought back by Mahavatar Babaji of the Kriya tradition to help restore balance and unity in people and the world. More than 500 OM Healing groups world wide come regularly together to chant the cosmic sound of OM as a healing support for Mother Earth, for themselves and the whole of humanity.  Emotions are released and inner peace and love arise. &lt;br /&gt;

    Sound and vibration are the essence of creation.  Universally OM Healing can help uplift the environment and create harmony and unity for all beings and nature. The world needs people who are willing to contribute to the change. It is time to realize the potential within and to share it with the whole world. &lt;br /&gt;

   Donations are appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mark has been meditating (on and off) for thirty years, but it caught him seriously several years ago when Paranahansa Yogananda became his guru. Last year, Mark learned the OM Healing Circle technique and was later initiated into Kriya Yoga through the Atma Kriya organization (&lt;a href="http://www.atmakriya.org/"&gt;http://www.atmakriya.org/&lt;/a&gt;). All this occurred due to a chance meeting between a friend of Mark's and an Atma Kriya monk on a plane back from Europe. After participating in many circles, Mark has been given a blessing by Sri Swami Vishvananda of Atma Kriya to lead OM Healing Circles.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy Copp</member_name><member_id>8642061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344811443000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Evolving Beings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Evolving-Beings</urlname><id>1429576</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>Evolving Beings</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342547739000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OM Healing Circle</name><id>73733042</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344805200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Evolving-Beings/events/73733042/</event_url></item>