<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi!  My name is Andrew and I have volunteered to organize the first Meetup for the Hartford Russian Language Group.  I have very basic skills in Russian, but look forward to learning more about the language and culture together.  I think the most important thing right now is for us to get together and start meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I live in Bristol, CT, but since this is the Hartford Group, I arranged for a meeting room at the Wood-n-Tap, 99 Sisson Ave, Hartford, CT.  The Wood-n-Tap is a nice, casual place with good food.  I have not arranged for any formal meal for the first meeting, we can simply order off the menu as we please.  If we have enough early RSVPs and there is interest, we can order some group-sized appetizers.  Let me know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I see the first meeting as a fairly simple event.  For the first hour or so we can get to know each other over drinks or snacks if you like.  About 8:00pm, I will formalize the activities for a few minutes.  At this time I will look for ideas for future meetups and ask for a couple of volunteers to assist in planning.  I travel some for work and may not always be around, so I'll need some help.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting as many of you as possible next week!  Please RSVP as soon as possible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS.  My email is anderson06143@yahoo.com and the website for the Wood-n-Tap is www.woodntap.com  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Anderson</member_name><member_id>1738935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542609000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Russian Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordrussianmeetup</urlname><id>723352</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Russian Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195088556000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Russian Language December Meetup</name><id>6743301</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197504000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordrussianmeetup/events/6743301/</event_url></item>