<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Friday, January 25th, 6PM - 7 PM  FREE ADMISSION/ GOODWILL OFFERING&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Historic Appleton-Fisk Organ, St. Stephen?s Church, Hanover St., Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organist Gianluigi Spaziani, Grottammare, le Marche, Italy* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*(located Midway up the Adriatic Coast, le Marche is Bordered by Abruzzo on the South, Umbria on the West, and Emilia Romagna on the North)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gianluigi Spaziani è nato nel 1965 ad Ascoli Piceno e vivendo a Grottammare. Ha conseguito il diploma di Pianoforte nel 1987 presso il Conservatorio di Frosinone, il diploma di Organo e Composizione organistica nel 1990 presso il Conservatorio dell?Apulia e il diploma di Concertista d'Organo presso il Conservatorio di Rotterdam(Olanda) nel 2000.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Si è specializzato nell?esecuzione del repertorio musicale rinascimentale e barocco. È direttore artistico della Rassegna Internazionale di Musica per Organo &amp;quot;Riviera delle Palme.&amp;quot; Si interessa al restauro di organi storici della sua regione, le Marche. È organista titolare degli organi di Grottammare. Ha suonato in concerto, in prima esecuzione moderna, numerosi composizioni di autori marchigiani inediti dei secoli XVIII e XIX. È autor di musica per organo e pianoforte. E? attivo come concertista anche in formazione poli-strumentali. È autore di numerosi libri di storia organaria, tra i quali: &amp;quot;L'Organo ad Ascoli Piceno dal XV al XIX secolo&amp;quot; È stato invitato a tenere conferenze sul tema della storia degli organi del Centro Italia. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gianluigi Spaziani was born in 1965 in Ascoli Piceno and lives in Grottammare. He earned the diploma of Pianoforte in 1987 at the Conservatory of Frosinone, the diploma of Organ and organ Composition in 1990 in the Conservatory of the Apulia and the diploma of Concert Organist near the Conservatory of Rotterdam (Holland) in 2000. He has specialized in the execution of the renaissance and baroque musical repertoire.  He currently is artistic director of the International Review of Music for Organ &amp;quot;Coast of the Palms.&amp;quot; He  is interested in the restoration of historical organs of his native region, the Marches. He is tittular organist of the organs of Grottammare. He has played in concert, in the first modern premieres, numerous compositions of unknown Marchigian composers of the18th and 19th centuries. He is author of music for organ and pianoforte. He is active as a concert keyboard artist also in multiple instrument ensembles. He is author of numerous books of historic organs, among which are : &amp;quot;the organ to Ascoli Piceno from the XV to XIX the century&amp;quot; .  He is a frequent lecturer on the topic of the history of the organs in central Italy. (translated, Kevin Galiè)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONCERT PROGRAM:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J. P. Sweelinck: Toccata; Balletto del Granduca; Pavana Lachrimae&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J. Bull: Fantasia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anonimo (Italia, XVIIth Cent.) : Romanesca; Ballo di Fiorenza&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;G. Frescobaldi: Toccata on the 4th Tone (2nd Book of Toccatas)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;S. Haim: Pastorale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;W. Karges: Praeludium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;G. Böhm: Vater Unser im Himmerlreich&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;D. Buxtehude: Passacaglia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A. Kneller: Praeludium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;G. Gabrieli: Cantate Domino&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;St. Stephen's Church, formerly New North Church, is located at 401 Hanover Street in the North End of Boston, Massachusetts. It is the last remaining church in Boston designed by Charles Bulfinch.&lt;br /&gt;The church, made of red brick with white pilasters on the façade and topped by a clock tower and a belfry, was originally designed as the second edifice of the New North Religious Society, a Congregationalist group. Its cornerstone was laid on September 23, 1802, and the building dedicated on May 2, 1804. Three days later the Columbian Centinel wrote:&lt;br /&gt;               &amp;quot;The exterior is in a bold and commanding style; the front is decorated with stone pilasters of a composed order; a series of attic pilasters over them, a tower and a cupola, terminated with a handsome vane, about 100 feet from the foundation. The inside is a perfect square of 72 feet; two ranges of dorick columns under the galleries, and Corinthian over them, support the ceiling, which rises in an arch of moderate elevation in the centre.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Like most Boston congregations of the time, New North went over to Unitarianism, and from 1813 to 1849, Rev. Dr. Francis Parkman, an eloquent preacher and father of the historian, was its minister. By 1822 the church was complaining that ?the young gentlemen who have married wives in other parts of the town have found it difficult to persuade them to become so ungenteel as to attend worship in the North End?;[4] Parkman himself preferred to live in the vicinity of Bowdoin Square.[5] In 1862, with the North End's composition greatly changed by an influx of Irish Catholics, the church was sold to Bishop Fitzpatrick of the Roman Catholic Diocese of Boston and renamed St. Stephen?s.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the Marchigian-looking organist, standing next to the Marchigian-looking organist</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Galie'</member_name><member_id>3336702</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356157719000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>This is a famous organ, and we will have a social hour afterwards. Concert lasts only 1 hour, 6-7PM</why><group><who>Members of this group</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>italian-374</urlname><id>288923</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Italian Language Meetup Group &amp; Lunedì Italiano</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199926558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ITALIAN (Marchigian) ORGAN RECITAL, LECTURE, AND SOCIAL</name><id>7075700</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201302000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-374/events/7075700/</event_url></item>