<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_2><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 141</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1346807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091419</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Please Note - to confirm your attendance at this event, you must register at the MIT Enterprise Forum of Cambridge website at &lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-in-automotive-supply-chain/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-in-automotive-supply-chain/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is the next breakthrough innovation in the automotive value chain?  RFID applies to traceability and synchronization of supplier networks, to manufacturing processes, to logistics, to increasing the driving experience, an in customized advertisements.  Experiences across the world show outstanding technology performance yet adoption is not universal.  What are the main exogenous and endogenous drivers  &lt;br /&gt;to achieve positive ROI?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speakers: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toby Rush, founder and President of Rush Tracking&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Toby  Rush co-founded Rush Tracking Systems and serves as President and  CEO.  Rush Tracking Systems has a proven track record working with  Fortune 100  client organizations to deliver best-in-class RFID  solutions that help  optimize operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rush  has achieved national recognition as an expert in mobile and  wireless  technologies, with extensive experience delivering mobile  enterprise  solutions in challenging and dynamic environments. He has  presented  extensively on RFID and mobility in the enterprise at key  industry  conferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/?attachment_id=3997"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Ricky-Heath_Executive-Picture.jpg" width="85" height="58" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Ricky Heath, AT&amp;amp;T Industry Solutions Practice Leader for Transportation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ricky Heath has been a travel and transportation industry executive   since 1980 having direct experience with all P&amp;amp;L related activities   managing sales, marketing, operations and IT solutions organizations on  a  global basis.  Ricky has helped airlines and other travel related   companies around the world develop and execute major strategic   initiatives and large scale IT projects.  These initiatives include   implementing reservations systems, creating distribution strategies,   leading thought leadership with the development of hosting platforms,   deploying e-commerce programs and marketing technology subscription   models.  Ricky has maintained his focus on the travel and transportation  industry  with 20+ years of executive leadership at Delta Air Lines and  Worldspan  (a global travel distribution and technology company  formerly owned by  Delta Air Lines, Northwest Airlines and American  Airlines).  He now  leads AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s strategic initiatives within the  technology leader&amp;rsquo;s  travel and transportation vertical practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderator: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Juan Pons, MIT Sloan&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Juan Pons&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;was CEO  of Aida  Group that implemented next  generation RFID systems for the  Universal  Postal Union in 24+  countries.&amp;nbsp; UPU moves the most uniquely  identified  products in the  world &amp;ndash; 600billion &amp;ndash; and must exchange data  between 124  national  postal entities (unlike FedEx or UPS which have  centralized   proprietary systems).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Miles</member_name><member_id>10116261</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ning An</member_name><member_id>10728354</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301406222000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294682722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RFID in Automotive Supply Chain</name><id>15994655</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301349600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/15994655/</event_url></item>