<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1360 Worcester Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.298000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Verve Crowne Plaza - Natick</name><city>Natick</city><id>11336722</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.388496</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"I HATE the Republican Party!!" - a common quote by many a random Liberty Activist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I also specifically and solely hate the shortsighted, misguided LEADERSHIP of the MassGOP who actively strangled the grassroots throughout the RNC delegate process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, Jan 31st at 630PM, in Natick, the 80 state committee members of the MassGOP will elect a new chair to lead the MassGOP. There are two candidates that are in a tight race to lead the MassGOP, and YOU can make an immediate impact!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One candidate, is beholden to no one, a self made, successful businessman, that intends a long term plan to engage and listen to and grow the Liberty grassroots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other candidate, a lawyer, that well, works tightly with the current MassGOP leadership. While talking a good game about including the Liberty movement during her campaign for chair, her campaign slogan should be "Meet the new boss, same as the old boss". Another expression useful here is, "Love is an action". You can say you love someone, but unless you show it with actions, it's just a another empty campaign promise. Kirsten Hughes can talk a good game about including the Liberty movement, but the reality is, that the people and lobbyists supporting her will not allow Liberty movement to thrive in Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, the choice is VERY clear, Rick 'Grassroots' Green is the candidate that I can trust to give the Liberty and grassroots, a voice in MassGOP operations. With Rick, I know, that the Liberty Movement has a good chance to influence the direction of the MassGOP. Last Summer, Rick stood up and voted to have the provisional ballots discussed, and counted. Kirsten Hughes website endorsement are generally the state committee people that voted against having the ballots counted. You can compare on MassLibertyCaucus the list of gutless allocation committee members that de-certified the duly elected delegates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My final quote for tonight, "I will forgive, but not forget". The state committee members that cheated the Liberty delegates will eventually be replaced in the 2016 elections, but until then, the Liberty Movement needs exert our influence NOW, to get Rick Grassroots Green elected, and make sure that next time, the 2014 State Convention Caucus, that someone fair and objective counts the votes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would encourage any Liberty supporters to come at 6:30PM on Thursday, an 31st, to the Crowne Plaza in Natick, and hold signs for Rick Green, and let the State Committee members know as they walk in to their election, that the Liberty movement will no longer be quiet. &lt;br /&gt;

 In Liberty, &lt;br /&gt;

Bradford Wyatt &lt;br /&gt;

LibertyClubhouse.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359685937000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359002910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rally for Liberty in MassGOP</name><id>101128812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359675000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/101128812/</event_url></item>