<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Berkshires</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06757</zip><lat>41.679958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Club Getaway</name><city>Kent</city><id>684911</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.490791</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us this July 4th weekend on July 2nd, &lt;a href="http://BostonMeetupGetaway.Org" target="_blank"&gt;http://BostonMeetupGe...&lt;/a&gt; ,  Click Book Now on the right, Mention Boston Meetup when booking by phone to save $25 or type Boston Meetup in the comment box to get the discount !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;July 4th weekend is one of our favorite weekends of the summer. You’ve got an extra day to enjoy all of the getaway sports and adventures… plus you get to experience some of our best special events. Celebrate your independence! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Get Out and Play every sport under the sun. Head out on new adventures. Take lessons from a Pro. Dine on an abundance of delicious food. Socialize. Dance all night. Laugh. Relax. And just have fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The beautiful and rustic Weekend Resort is located on 300 acres overlooking a sparkling lake. In the nearby Berkshire Mountains of Kent, CT, Club Getaway is just 2½ hours from Boston. Just grab a buddy, or come by yourself and make friends everywhere you go. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ice Party&lt;br /&gt;Imagine the coolest party you’ve ever been to! Ice blue walls, Ice blue drinks… You may not make it to the ice hotel in Sweden, but you can make it to the Ice party July 4th weekend. Sip chilled drinks from the ice luge and dance the night away in our ice blue nightclub.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Degenerates &lt;br /&gt;Dance along to one of the tri-state area’s top cover bands, The Degenerates. They’ll be playing your favorite top 40, classic rock, and kitschy 80’s tunes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sushi Making Workshop&lt;br /&gt;Learn the fine art of sushi making. Slice, dice, and roll up your tasting creations. At home, you’ll dazzle your friends and impress your dates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Color War &lt;br /&gt;Team up and compete in every camp’s favorite challenge… Color war! Join in the crazy games along with the Kickball and dogeball competition. May the best team win!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pub Hike&lt;br /&gt;Our newest adventure is a hike through the woods, stopping at rustic bars with unusual drinks along the way. In between pubs, there are fun teambuilding challenges. This is a Getaway original you won’t find at the Hilton. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Improv Games&lt;br /&gt;Techniques long taught in acting classes are available for you to enjoy in this unique, funny and fast-moving workshop. Get past yourself, gain confidence, and have fun.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bruce Jacques&lt;br /&gt;Club Getaway’s and Mount Snow’s legendary Bruce Jacques returns to rock your universe! We dare you to stay in your seat.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pole Dancing&lt;br /&gt;Definitely our hottest, sexiest class. Join Cammi from NY’s Sassy pole girls as she takes to the pole and teaches you all the moves. Girls only!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Scavenger Hunt&lt;br /&gt;Join a team. Hunt for Clues. Sleuth your way throughout campus to be the first to discover the booty!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Asian Feast&lt;br /&gt;Sample dishes from throughout Asia and tantalize your palette. Experience the flavors of Japan, China, Thailand, and Vietnam paired with sake and fine wine.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Paintball&lt;br /&gt;Join an adventure-packed excursion to Liberty paintball. Suit up, load your ammo and get ready for battle pre-sign up and fee. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a great time and Invite friends, &lt;a href="http://BostonMeetupGetaway.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://BostonMeetupGe...&lt;/a&gt; or call 917-868-4268 (if you can't make July 4th weekend , Mention Boston Meetup to save $25 anytime this year at Getaway/ if you have been there already this year, you are elig. for the summer share and can save even more $ , call 917-868-4268 for details, Book Multiple weekends in 2009 for a greater discount) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Invite friends to join our new group, &lt;a href="http://BostonMeetup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://BostonMeetup.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call Greg at 917-868-4268  when you arrive Thursday Night at the Welcome Party !</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>9810390</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248472327000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonMeetup</urlname><id>1477254</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>#1 Meetup - BOSTON MEETUP,  Travel&amp; Events, BOSTONMEETUP.org</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>101</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245769247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Meetup Presents Boston Meetup Getaway July 2nd / July 4th Holiday Weekend</name><id>10715928</id><headcount>101</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246572000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonMeetup/events/10715928/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/4/global_9313588.jpeg</photo_url></item>