<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>591 Donald Lynch Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.353519</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-229-8871</phone><name>Regal Cinemas Solomon Pond Mall 15</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>720524</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.615440</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I see that several members are interested in this movie. I know it's short notice for this Meetup, but thought I would give it a try.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a synopsis of the movie from Fandango:&lt;br /&gt;A high-powered sales executive struggles with his own dwindling sense of self-worth after becoming a victim to corporate downsizing. Bobby Walker (Ben Affleck) has a big house, a new Porsche, a beautiful wife, and two adoring kids. When he's not in the office, he can usually be found on the golf course, perfecting his game or clinching an important business deal. But when the axe falls, Bobby and his colleagues Phil (Chris Cooper) and Gene (Tommy Lee Jones) find their necks on the chopping block, and their futures looking bleak. In order to stay afloat, Bobby reluctantly goes to work as a carpenter for his brother-in-law (Kevin Costner). But building houses is a far cry from the boardroom, and just as Bobby starts to wonder if he'll ever taste success again, he realizes that true prosperity doesn't come in the form of a paycheck, but through the satisfaction of knowing that his family will always be there to support him. Maria Bello, Craig T. Nelson, and Rosemarie DeWitt co-star in a drama from writer/director John Wells (ER). ~ Jason Buchanan, Rovi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will post a more accurate time on Thursday for this film, but let's shoot for around 7PM. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a gray pea coat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Megan Belliveau</member_name><member_id>8940299</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311553873000</updated><rating><average>2.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-579</urlname><id>797632</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8099975586</group_lon><name>The Worcester Movie Fans Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295968580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Company Men</name><id>16178706</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296346500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-579/events/16178706/</event_url></item>