<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Harvard Yard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Memorial Church</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>899800</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.125000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Annual Outstanding Lifetime Achievement Award in Cultural Humanism is presented at Harvard University each year by the Harvard Secular Society on behalf of the Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard and the American Humanist Association. Selected by a committee of 20-30 Harvard students each year, this award is given to a figure greatly admired by our students and community for both artistic and humanitarian reasons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now in its fourth year, the HSS Cultural Humanism committee has chosen the recipients for the award, the MythBusters, based on what they feel is an outstanding contribution to Humanism in culture. The MythBusters – special-effects experts Adam Savage and Jamie Hyneman – take on the task of separating truth from urban legend on their television show with the same name. In true Humanist style, the pair takes on three myths per episode and uses modern-day science to demonstrate, through scientific trials, whether or not some things we take for granted really hold any ground. The award ceremony (April 16 8:00pm Memorial Church) will feature a talk and demonstrations by the pair.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note:&lt;/b&gt; tickets are required for this event, and tickets to previous Cultural Humanism Awards have sold out.  Be sure to purchase your tickets early&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket prices are as follows: Regular: $20.00; Harvard ID Holders: $15.00; Students: $10.00; Harvard Students: $8.00.  &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://ofa.fas.harvard.edu/cal/details.php?ID=40871" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets can be purchased at the Harvard Box Office.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth</member_name><member_id>8893636</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271635728000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265254513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MythBusters at Harvard</name><id>12514526</id><headcount>46</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271462400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/12514526/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>