<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;[Description] &lt;br /&gt;

 The newly enacted business tax-credit education scholarship program is under attack. This bill would repeal the program!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Families need options and the education tax credit scholarships level the playing field for needy families in our communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it's true that the tax-credit scholarships will not likely cover the full tuition at some schools, it is enough to bridge the gap for many families. It also may make it possible for families to transfer to a public school outside their assigned district. Also, many private schools are not as expensive as you think and offer financial assistance. The scholarship program can put educational alternatives within reach for families who otherwise are limited to the school assigned to them by their zip code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hearing will be held in Representative Hall in the State House. Please sign in *against* this bill and indicate if you wish to give testimony. If so, please bring at least 25 copies of your remarks for the committee. Here is the list of all the members of the Ways and Means Committee: &lt;a href="http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/house/committees/committeedetails.aspx?code=H28" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/house/committees/committeedetails.aspx?code=H28&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can't attend, please send the committee a brief email that explains why they should keep the scholarship program in place. If you can tell a personal story of what educational options mean to your family, that's a plus. The committee's email is HouseWaysAndMeansCommittee@leg.state.nh.us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If one of your Reps is serving on this committee, be sure to tell him/her that you are a constituent!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to HB 370: &lt;a href="http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/legislation/2013/HB0370.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/legislation/2013/HB0370.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359664761000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359161354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oppose the Repeal of Tax Credit Scholarships</name><id>101415252</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359653400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/101415252/</event_url></item>