<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Salisbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.273173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 799-4406 </phone><name>Worcester Art Museum</name><city>Worcester</city><id>719621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802015</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here is the big day! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be showing off all the photos you submitted to the Art in the Park Contest Photo Contest in an open Judging forum- The winner will be discovered at this time! This is an open event and anyone can attend. It's going to be a lively event! We highly encourage you to come out and join in the fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To determine the grand Prize and Category Winners and Honorable Mentions, we are employing a panel of 5 judges, all from the Worcester Cultural Arena. The Judging will take place at the Worcester Art Museum on October 18th 2009- 4pm and is open to the Public. All Folks who enter the contest are invited to come see the images judged, hear feed back and comments about their entries, and view all the submissions! Awards will be given at the end of the evening. &lt;br /&gt;The Judges so far are: &lt;br /&gt;Deb McNamara, Chair Worcester Cultural Commission &lt;br /&gt;Helen Beaumont, Marketing and Business Advisor &lt;br /&gt;Dante Comparetto, Worcester Cultural Commission &lt;br /&gt;Cyrus Lipsitt, Art in the Park Committee Member &lt;br /&gt;Claire Forgues, Local Business Owner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to participate? Join us on Flickr and then come to the show! Here is the link....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/groups/artparkphotocontest09/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.flickr.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The awards will be given at the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256249951000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254355968000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Judging for the Art in the Park Photo Contest</name><id>11513656</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255896000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11513656/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/b/global_10161499.jpeg</photo_url></item>