<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>300.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This 10 week class is geared to assist you in becoming aware of where you are on your path, why you’re there and how to get to where you want to be.  Combining science and spirituality, pragmatic and alternative knowledge, this class will provide you with tools that you can utilize to create an amazing and purposeful life.  A three tiered approach to stepping up onto your path, this class provides you with valuable tools that allow you to open up intuitively, hone your psychic abilities and begin living in abundance and spiritual flow.  In addition to the weekly class, you will be required to begin mental and spiritual practices outside of class that will consist of 15-30 minutes dedicated time daily.  If you find yourself presented with difficulties, are wishing to open up intuitively and psychically or if you are simply ready to make a change in your life, this class will provide you with tools to do just that. &lt;br /&gt;Dates: 10 Wednesdays from 7 PM to 8:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;Jan 14th, Jan 21st, Jan 28th, Feb 4th, Feb 11th&lt;br /&gt;Feb 18th, Feb 25th, March 4th, March 11th, March 18th&lt;br /&gt;Cost - $300.00 &lt;br /&gt;Financial Assistance (Sliding scale rate) - $150.00 or higher depending on your ability to pay&lt;br /&gt;Location - Portsmouth, New Hampshire&lt;br /&gt;Contact Isabeau Esby directly for location and payment&lt;br /&gt;603-973-1898 or isabeauesby@me.com&lt;br /&gt;www.IsabeauEsby.com&lt;br /&gt;**Space is very limited, pre-registration required **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Testimonial from a previous student:&lt;br /&gt;A person can find many workshops or multi-week programs offering life renewal or change. But rarely does a person have the opportunity to study with someone who can bring so much 'to the table'.  How to explain the talents of Isabeau Esby. To the point, she is both out of this world and very much of this world.  A person of enormous spiritual gifts, experience and education,  she has be ability to connect a person to metaphysical energies that allude most human beings. She is a successful medium,after all; it is her job to bridge both worlds. Yet she is a grounded mother of two who fully lives in everyday America and understands the challenges in melding spiritual exploration and practices with the pressures and practical demands of our lives. As with all good teachers, she is both an excellent listener and communicator. And her classes are fun - those who expect discussions on spirituality to be ponderous and dreary will be disappointed with Isabeau's classes. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Her 10 week class has given me much to ponder and has allowed me to creatively explore the important life questions facing me now.  Quite frankly, I can hardly wait to get to class. Every time I go, I have one of those 'aha' moments that we hear Oprah  talk about. It is quite addicting.  I believe anyone willing to make the time and the commitment will benefit greatly from Isabeau's class.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A. Webber&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234523248000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230865743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spiritual Awakening Class</name><id>9422915</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231977600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/9422915/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/3/global_6795651.jpeg</photo_url></item>