<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>910 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02026</zip><lat>42.231743</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 329-0097</phone><name>FINZ SEAFOOD &amp; GRILL</name><city>Dedham</city><id>801812</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184052</lon></venue><fee><label>Pre-Registration</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>members or $15.00 non</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Some investors are making serious bank AND helping the environment at the same time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By 'Going Green' with their properties and making strategic changes, taking advantage of little-known subsidies and increasing their property values.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for our &lt;b&gt;June 4th&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/ttk/" target="_blank"&gt;Turning the Key&lt;/a&gt; networking event where we'll have our &lt;b&gt;ForeclosuresMass Green Team&lt;/b&gt; of local environmentally conscious investors and developers presenting what they're doing to make green by going green.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Steve Tise&lt;/b&gt; is a practical type architect who excels at user friendly designs while incorporating energy efficiency. He has designed a ton of affordable and market rate housing products throughout the U.S. and the Caribbean. He is also a well sought-after design consultant assisting a number of Housing Authorities nationwide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;John Winslow&lt;/b&gt;, a top tier architect focused on the renewable energy and green resources as a trade, is also a sought after design specialist in both affordable housing and market rate properties.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to live Q&amp;amp;A, our panel will be covering:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Which improvements can MAKE money vs. COST money&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Government subsidies to help with the costs of conversions (including Weatherization Funds, Energy Rebates, Retrofit Grants and Green Building funds)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Hot topics such as LEED AP Certification, LEED Building, Solar PV products, and Geotherm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; How to determine which changes to make first&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; What environmentally friendly changes have the biggest impact&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Short term vs. long term gains by going green. &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panel's are always our most popular events, so make sure to reserve your spot early by  &lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/ttk/" target="_blank"&gt;pre-registering online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy</member_name><member_id>3494542</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245103459000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243460137000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TTK: How Investors are Making Green by Going Green</name><id>10507411</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244154600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/10507411/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/7/global_8840007.jpeg</photo_url></item>