<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you are interested in participating be sure to read the entire event listing before you RSVP - then answer the questions that are part of the RSVP process. While the objective of this event is to enjoy ourselves, your safety, and the safety of the others, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands, overestimate your skills and abilities, or come unprepared you may put yourself and/or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this&amp;nbsp;before&amp;nbsp;you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the ultimate destination of the this hike is the&amp;nbsp;wooded summit of Wolf (3,480') the real purpose of this hike is to assess the condition of our adopted trail - the 3.3 mile section of the Kinsman Ridge Trail&amp;nbsp;between Route 112 in North Woodstock, NH and Gordon Pond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By adopting a section of the&amp;nbsp;historic 2,175-mile long&amp;nbsp;Appalachian Trail&amp;nbsp;we assumed the responsibility for performing basic maintenance (cleaning drainage and clearing brush to promote the longevity and health of the trail)&amp;nbsp;at regular intervals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Expect frequent breaks along the way so that we can document what we need to do during our upcoming trail maintenance trips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=12568"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs are welcome on this hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this trip we will use the Kinsman Ridge Trail that leaves the parking area on Route 112 to climb towards Gordon Pond and ultimately to the summit of Wolf. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;slow to moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt; round trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 9.2 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 2,200 feet&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;em&gt;for perspective the top floor of the Empire State Building is about 1,250 feet&lt;/em&gt;). &amp;nbsp;This trip is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;Intermediate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I have hiked this trail I have never climbed to this peak - I did all of my research for this trip using the AMC's&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;White Mountain Guide&lt;/em&gt;, a trail map, and the Internet. &amp;nbsp;You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=12568"&gt;Click here for information about&amp;nbsp;Wolf from peakbagger.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/"&gt;Click here for information about trail conditions near Wolf from TrailsNH.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you. Fatigue and other unexpected conditions can alter our plans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not certified or trained in wilderness first aid. You will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you have ANY questions about your ability to participate in and complete this entire trip please contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;It may still be winter in the mountains - expect cold and windy conditions. Temperatures drop 3-5 degrees for every 1,000 feet of elevation gained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;prior&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Footwear&lt;/span&gt;: Sturdy hiking boots. Snowshoes and some form of light traction (microspikes or hillsound crampons) may be mandatory - I will update later. Be sure to have a way to attach these to your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Clothing&lt;/span&gt;: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater. Winter hat. Face shield/balaclava. Winter mittens/gloves. ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Outerwear&lt;/span&gt;: Insulated jacket with hood. Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip. Hydration bladders may freeze during winter - bottles with insulating sleeves work best.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in cold temperatures). Chemical hand/foot warmers. Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack. Extra hat, mittens/gloves, and socks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Optional Items&lt;/span&gt;: Waterproof/windproof pants. Waterproof gaiters. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will begin this hike by meeting in the parking area on the south side of Route 112 at 9:00 AM. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 140 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 40 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.040808,-71.791763(Kinsman+Ridge+Trailhead+%5Bsouth%5D)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFWgCoAIdbYu4-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=44.040808,-71.791763&amp;amp;sspn=0.009008,0.013797&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;Click here the link below for driving directions to the meeting spot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in either a green or a white Toyota Highlander.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305079950000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Participating in trail maintanance-related trips gets your name entered into the member appreciation raffle twice.</why><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303963892000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's grab a peak (Wolf) and visit our adopted trail (AT/Kinsman Ridge Trail)</name><id>17463560</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304859600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/17463560/</event_url></item>