<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>92 Worcester Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.296471</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-875-3115</phone><name>The Melting Pot</name><city>Framingham</city><id>669195</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.399246</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>or so for dinner &amp; drinks</description><amount>37.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Final Summer Melting Pot Excusion - this is in conjuction with the New England 30 and 40 Something's Social Networking Group as well.  7 from each group are invited.  &lt;a href="http://socialnetwork.meetup.com/422/calendar/6067653/"&gt;http://socialnetwork....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Men are welcome again - the deal is good for everyone!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We loved this place so much we had to do it again! How about we take advantage of this deal because it's thrice as nice. For those of you who missed out the first and second time don't miss out this final time! Bring your Summer to a close with a great meal! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join The Melting Pot Framingham for &lt;br /&gt;$30 per person includes: cheese fondue, salad, chocolate fondue &lt;br /&gt;and a choice of a glass of wine or specialty drink!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can upgrade the meal. The $37 (includes tax and gratuity approx) deal does not include meat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meltingpot.."&gt;http://www.meltingpot...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be making a reservation again so I need a solid count by the 20th at the latest. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEMBER GUIDELINES: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive promptly and bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a no-show. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members who miss/no-show three meals for which they have RSVPd &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot;, you will no longer be welcome to my Meet Ups. &lt;br /&gt;No shows and last minute cancellations impact everyone; from the organizer to the person on the wait list (which could or has been you), to the restaurant's who staff based on reservations. Please be considerate by RSVPing YES only if you plan on attending. If you're not sure and think you want to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beantown and Beyond</member_name><member_id>4494456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189263500000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185243359000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Melting Pot Mon Framingham Cross Post NE 30-40 and Beantown&amp;Beyond 20-40 Single</name><id>6067685</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188255600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/6067685/</event_url></item>