<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Valley Falls Rd.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.827274</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 872-6118</phone><name>Valley Falls Park</name><city>Vernon</city><id>128048</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.451019</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hiking about 1.5 miles of very pleasent forest and ledge and a pot-luck picnic on the cliffs! We'll be starting at the pond and going up a hillside to the Hop River Linear Trail (i.e. Rails-To-Trails in Vernon area). Then we'll head up to the cliffs over the park to enjoy the fall colors, good weather, and a picnic!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the parking lot at 4:30 PM and head out to hike the trail. The hike should take about 1.5 hrs. and we should be done by 6 PM at the latest (just about sunset - no sunset views though). Please bring your own main picnic meal portion and something to share with others. Please include in your RSVP what you're bringing to share (no beer &amp;amp; such allowed in park though).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 8.5 miles of blazed trails in the park, as well as a playground, picnic pavilion, toilet facilities and a swimming beach. Portions of the park contain riuns of textile mills and an early trout hatchery and have been declared a national historic site. The park is heavily used for swimming, picnicking, hiking, x-country skiing, fishing, wild flower &amp;amp; wildlife observation and a scenic vista.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;)  is leading on this one so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A park map can be found in the document link. Look at page 13.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.munic.state.ct.us/vernon/VRTT.pdf"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.munic.state.ct.us/vernon/VRTT.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.munic.stat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1161117029000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1160761822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kevin's Hike/pot-luck picnic at Valley Falls Park in Vernon CT</name><id>5196043</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1160944200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5196043/</event_url></item>