<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Willand Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03878</zip><lat>43.223971</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great Bay Facility</name><city>Somersworth</city><id>1173756</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.889627</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Greetings All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I need help (bodies, promotion, minimal monetary support – if able, bodies, donations, and any other help).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As some of you may know, next week is Ronald Reagn’s birthday.  Imagine my surprise when I did not see any major event held in honor of the Gipper.  As fate would have it, I was approached to help with Haiti relief.  I thought it would be neat if he held a gather in honor of America’s greatest president, while helping with a cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of you have the ability to get things done, with a sort turn around.  I need your help now. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feb 5, 6-8 PM, The Gipper’s birth anniversary /Haiti fundraiser.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I have secured the location (Great Bay Facility, Somersworth).  The owner of this facility is a liberty minded, small business owner, and I would like to try an cover some of his cost (he has donated a bunch already). All the proceeds with go to fund two elements of Haiti relief:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Help pay for a group of NH EMTs to travel down to Haiti and help&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Remainder to go to Catholic Relief Charities (they have feet on the ground, and lower cost overhead - always thinking like a conservative).  Hi Jerry,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Starting from the bottom of my emails and working up.  I see a few emails from the opera company.  That is a wonderful idea.  Thanks&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The official invite will go out today.  We will drive the RSVP to the event listing on my facebook, or people will be able to email me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am looking for a few other things: donations for door prizes (simply) and decorations (red white and blue balloons).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Is there anyone on your team that can join me to actively work through the details?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Thanks for being there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Jeff Chidester the host on The Wave will is organizing this event. Please come enjoy and donate.&lt;br /&gt;Semper Fi,&lt;br /&gt;Jerry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerry DeLemus</member_name><member_id>9270878</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265584470000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rochester-912-project</urlname><id>1452537</id><group_lat>43.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>Rochester 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264557701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Haiti Relief and President Reagan's Birthday</name><id>12434131</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265410800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rochester-912-project/events/12434131/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/b/global_8616923.jpeg</photo_url></item>