<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Free for all&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MIT and Boston chapters of Association for India's Development cordially invite you to two talks on&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Gandhian Engineering - Empowering Rural India through Environmental Conservation and Sustainable Technology&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;by&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Mazgaonkar&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the speaker:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though Michael Mazgaonkar was born in the sprawling city of Mumbai, he was raised by parents who were committed to living out Gandhian principles. As a young man, Michael participated in Gandhian youth camps where he learned about issues facing India: specifically the disparities between rural and urban India, and the challenges faced by rural areas when all the educated youth of the area leave their homes for the allure of success in the big cities. Upon completing their university degrees (in Engineering &amp;amp; Physics respectively), Michael and his wife chose to reverse the &amp;quot;brain drain&amp;quot; and made their home in Mozda, an adivasi (tribal) village inside the Shoolpaneshwar Wildlife Sanctuary. For the past 20 years, they have been actively involved in soil and water conservation projects, founding a women's co-op, designing and constructing parabolic solar cookers, solar photovoltaic lamps, and wind electric generators, training young adivasis, and supporting local movements fighting large scale, corporate takeovers of tribal lands and resources. Michael's very life is a demonstration of how Gandhian principles can be utilized to handle the challenges associated with contemporary globalism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;info@aidboston.org&lt;br /&gt;www.aidboston.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Param</member_name><member_id>10902819</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288052149000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287002971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gandhian Engineering by Michael Mazgaonkar</name><id>15100105</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287864000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/15100105/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/8/global_18722040.jpeg</photo_url></item>