<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>43 Pleasant St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04086</zip><lat>43.929836</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Topsham Grange Hall</name><city>Topsham</city><id>422082</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.962750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We have been invited to attend the Sagadahoc County Beekeeper's Monthly meeting for a joint talk about 'backyard beekeeping' and 'what is permaculture?' Master beekeeper Rick Cooper from Bowdoinham and Lisa Fernandes from the Portland Permaculture Meetup Group will each speak on their respective topics. Bring your questions about how to get started with backyard beekeeping! Since we will be guests at their monthly meeting, it would be lovely if a few people could bring yummy (easy-to-eat-with-fingers) desserts. See you then!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From the south- take 295 N to the Topsham exit. Exit right onto hwy 196 E. Turn right onto hwy 201 S ( towards Topsham/Maine St. Brunswick). Go past the Volvo dealership on the left, turn left onto Pleasant St. The Topsham Grange is the first bldg. on the left. ( yellow bldg. with parking lot on the front and side.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Exit 20 park and ride: Take 295 N, exit right at exit 20. Turn right at the first light onto Rt. 1( gas station on right) and head S for &amp;lt; 1/4 mile (past LL Bean Factory store) Park and Ride is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CARPOOL:  If you would like to carpool, plan to meet at the Marginal Way Park-and-Ride in Portland at 6:00 for a 6:15 departure.  Please post on the MESSAGE board if you intend to give or get a lift, including your phone or mobile phone number!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195257737000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192123192000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Permaculture &amp; Pollinators: A joint meetup with the beekeepers!</name><id>6530862</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195084800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/6530862/</event_url></item>