<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>152 Commonwealth Ave Unit M-1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.458334</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(877) 578-4777</phone><name>Lens Pro To Go</name><city>Concord</city><id>1066094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.396617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Saturday February 4th, 2012, 12:00&amp;#150;4:00pm Do you have &amp;#147;extra&amp;#148; photo gear laying about taking up space? Maybe you are looking for a bit of &amp;#145;new&amp;#146; gear at a great price? We have the event for you! Yes, it&amp;#146;s time once again to sell or swap your extra photography gear or buy new toys at the annual CIPNE Gear Swap and sale... to swap/sell. Swapping is a great win-win situation, so bring a list of what you want to get and what you have to give/swap. Items available may range from inexpensive filters (a few dollars) all the way up to expensive studio lights and camera bodies + lenses ($1000+). Sellers: **Please bring your own table.** Research beforehand fair market prices for your gear so they will be more likely to be sold. Consider bringing a friend to help you sell if you want to walk around and buy. In the spirit of cooperation, fairness, and goodwill, be forthcoming in indicating the true condition of gear, and any defects, when asked. Buyers: Research beforehand fair market prices for gear that you want to buy (it&amp;#146;s also useful to bring along a B&amp;amp;H catalog for reference!). Bringing cash and checks are a good idea. Show a list of gear that you want to buy; maybe someone will know where it is available. From a happy and successful previous seller: &amp;#147;The first year I pulled some gear together at the last moment to sell, and with little thought. When I arrived, I barely had things out of the bags and people were already questioning me as to what I wanted for the items. I sold everything, and wished I had been more organized, started earlier -AND brought more items! Start preparing early!! The next year, I was more on top of things, and brought far more. I sold everything - once again; two old cameras, and old backdrop, filters, a broken photo umbrella, some gadgets that I barely understood, and on and on. If it had to do with photography, and I wasn&amp;#146;t using it - I sold it!&amp;#147; Disclaimer: The CIPNE Photo Bazaar and Swapfest is organized and run under the spirit of cooperation and fairness. CIPNE and anyone associated with CIPNE is not liable for any swapping or selling transactions that result in any problems or issues. Participation in this event is under the doctrine of &amp;#147;buyer beware&amp;#148;. LOCATION Lens Pro to Go 152 Commonwealth Ave., Unit M-1, C, Concord, MA 01742 We recommend that you check out the directions for the alternate (much larger) parking lot. Set up: 10:00am&amp;#150;12:00pm Trading time: 12:00&amp;#150;4:00pm Break down: 4:00&amp;#150;4:30pm FREE event! Open to all, tell your friends. Please register here so that we know how many people to expect.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329165647000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326927604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gear swap and sale!</name><id>48676172</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328374800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/48676172/</event_url></item>