<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Tuttle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurie's 909 Steakhouse and Raw Bar</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>10565862</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is now a weekly event hosted by Red Sox Native Bob at Laurie's 909.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join Boston Happy Hour, the Red Sox Natives, Wakefield Weeknights and others to welcome another Morgan White Jr. (from WBZ Radio) Trivia Night at Laurie's 909 Steakhouse and Raw Bar with $1.00 Oyster Night. This is a one-of-a-kind trivia event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morgan is the undisputed Master of the Trivia Universe. After 30 years he continues to amaze folks with his one-of-a kind trivia show at which you provide categories and he uses his mind-boggling breadth of knowledge to create questions on the spot for your chance at prizes. Along with being smart, Morgan is personable and exudes a geeky coolness. The game format is very simple, the first table to answer three questions correctly in a round wins a prize. There isn't any need to figure out a team name, submit answer sheets nor calculate team scores....it's easy breezy as well as highly entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on Mr. White &lt;a href="http://www.morganwhitejr.com"&gt;http://www.morganwhitejr.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trivia begins at 6:45 PM and ends by 9:09 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get there when you can and stay as long as you're able.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're more than welcome to show up for the trivia or just the camaraderie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a cocktail or two, or three and order the $1.00 Oysters from 5 -7pm, an appetizer or dinner from Laurie's full menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All categories are welcome by Morgan for questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will there be Beatles categories at this event and why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your Red Sox, Baseball and Sports category suggestions with you too. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this will be your first time meeting the Happy Hour Crew, check out the photos of those who RSVP Yes so you can find the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay as you order and tip your servers. However, if you sit at a group table a group bill may be provided so please communicate with your server when ordering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie's 909 Steakhouse and Raw Bar is Wakefield's newest Restaurant and Bar with live entertainment several nights per week. Laurie's is located at the Wakefield Commuter Rail Train Station in Wakefield. The Reading and Haverhill Commuter Rail trains stop at Laurie's 909. Laurie's is easily accessible within 10 minutes from Routes 128, 93, 28 and 1. Free parking is available in two lots on Tuttle Street. Check out the MBTA or Hop Stop for additional public transit options including the less frequent and reliable 136 and 137 buses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Say hello to Laurie and Bob when you visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the "Penny Lane" Bar and find out about the 9:09.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information at &lt;a href="http://www.lauries909.com"&gt;http://www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be seated at the bar or tables near the Trivia guys table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361934064000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360349075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trivia with Morgan White Jr. &amp; $1.00 Oysters at Laurie's 909 Steakhouse/Raw Bar</name><id>103690782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361922300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/103690782/</event_url></item>