<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Boylston St. &amp; Dartmouth St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350079</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>575216</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077385</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>March 8 is International Women's Day, our opportunity to come together to speak out for a world where democratic socialist feminist values and programs enable us to live our lives in ways we will never be able to under capitalism and patriarchy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;International Women's Day 2009 will mark the 100th anniversary of the first national day of protest called by the Woman's National Committee of the Socialist Party in 1909. In the century since, the holiday has grown into a worldwide celebration and affirmation of women's struggle, resistance and empowerment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Socialist Party of Boston is promoting two events on International Women's Day, both in Copley Square. At 2:30 pm in the YWCA's Kuumba Library on the second floor of 140 Clarendon St., the &lt;a href="http://boston.wilpf.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Women’s International League for Peace and Freedom&lt;/a&gt; (WILPF), Friends of the Congo, and The Center for New Words will hold a screening of &amp;quot;The Greatest Silence: Rape in the Congo&amp;quot; (Winner of the Special Jury Prize for a Documentary at the 2008 Sundance Film Festival), with discussion of the role of multinational corporations in the Congo, ideas for local community action, and testimony from Jane Ngondo, an activist from the Congo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we'll move across Copley Square to join an International Women's Day event honoring revolutionary women leaders and raising funds for the upcoming March on the Pentagon. This fundraiser will begin at 4 pm, in the &lt;a href="http://www.communitychurchofboston.org/home/" target="_blank"&gt;Community Church of Boston&lt;/a&gt; (565 Boylston St.).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>billie mulcahy</member_name><member_id>4120888</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Schaich</member_name><member_id>4406518</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237598587000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235442536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>International Women's Day</name><id>9808515</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236537000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/9808515/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/8/global_7071368.jpeg</photo_url></item>