<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I (AJ) have been waiting for the new Screening Room here at 360 State Street to open up since I moved in.  Well it finally has, and I thought it would be fun to try out a Movie Night Event at it!       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join me as we try out this new theater location.  A few comfy couches and a few bean bag chairs available with an HD projector and surround sound.  You will have to bring your own food and beverage, but feel free to share!  (Please be careful with food and Beverages kept to a responsible level.)       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note about RSVP's:&lt;/b&gt; I unfortunately have to limit the number of attendees due to seating space.  Please only say YES if you're sure you can come.  If you think you'll be uncomfortable on the couch next to people, then I recommend bringing alternative seating. (We might be able to sneak in some camping chairs, but no promises.)       &lt;br /&gt;IF you're in for this event you will need to provide your First and Last name so I can give the Concierge desk a list of people to be let in. Photo ID may be required.  (You could e-mail me through the options on the site, or leave it in your RSVP if I don't know it already.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This times movie is:  Sleepy Hollow (1999)&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Description from IMDB:   Ichabod Crane is sent to Sleepy Hollow to investigate the decapitations of 3 people with the culprit being the legendary apparition, the Headless Horseman.   &lt;br /&gt;Directed by: Tim Burton, Staring: Johnny Depp, Christina Ricci, Christopher Walken  &lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Ben and Jeanie for offering to let us borrow their copy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;IF&lt;/b&gt;, and being a work night this is a Big IF, we make it through that and still all have the time and energy to do so, then we can do a second feature TBD by those who attend.  (possibly Silent Hill.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can start arriving at 7:00 PM, but I'll be planning to play the main feature at 7:30 sharp.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease) via any damages or causing a ruckus.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF this idea runs smoothly and is met with positive response and feedback, we can see about making it a repeat event with future features.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call me ( 315-345-9348 ) or the Concierge will direct you.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288373056000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287725340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie at 360 State Street Screening Room (Sleepy Hollow)</name><id>15191586</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288306800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15191586/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/e/global_18941310.jpeg</photo_url></item>