<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abduction Experiences and The Importance of Ufology&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a special evening, as the Center welcomes Chris Augustin and Peter Robbins. Chris is an Alien/UFO/Paranormal Investigator who runs and operates, &lt;a href="http://www.aliensthetruth.com/"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;www.AliensTheTruth.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; . Chris will being sharing his abduction experiences with us. Peter Robbins is one of America's best known UFO investigative writers. Peter will be speaking on the importance of ufology, where we stand at this moment in history, and about things each of can do to advance the work, and share his observations on current cases. Directly following our guest speakers, our own Mike Stevens will be presenting his feature presentation “Predators on the Powwow”, the film is the true story of an New Hampshire abduction, and includes recordings from the abductees hypnotic regression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;About Chris:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I have always been interested in science fiction movies, books, etc; from HG Wells to Star Trek. After viewing Independence Day back in 1996, I decided to start doing online research on aliens, UFOs and the paranormal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Over the years, my knowledge in web design increased, as well as the collection of topics that I researched. I have a computer science degree, and work as a business systems analyst for a major food service company doing application development and technical support. You could say I have an alter ego, by day I am a programmer, developing software and websites. By night, I am recording and analyzing UFO sighting reports, abduction experiences, hauntings and anything else that qualifies as strange/unknown/weird. I have even had 2 UFO sightings, potential abductions and numerous paranormal experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;My site is online for one main reason, the truth. In our community, people who have had UFO sightings, abduction experiences, paranormal encounters, etc; need a place to go. They need a place to share what they have experienced without the fear of ridicule. This is truly an alternate reality for many people. The mainstream media rarely gives our community positive attention, unless it's some major event like the Roswell UFO crash anniversary, or when there's a mass sighting, where hundreds or thousands of people witness the event, like the Phoenix Lights in 1997.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;My site focuses on some very basic premises; there is life on this planet, which is one out of billions. Therefore, it is mathematically impossible for life not to exist on another.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With the vast amount of evidence collected over the years, going back to ancient times, up to today, from reports gathered by MUFON and other organizations; there is no way that we can be alone in the universe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;About Peter:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Peter Robbins is one of the America’s best known UFO investigative writers. He’s been involved in the field for more than thirty years, as a researcher, investigator, writer, lecturer, activist and author. A regular guest on radio shows around the country, he has also appeared as a guest on and been consultant to numerous television shows and documentaries. He is also is co-author of the British best-seller, &lt;em&gt;Left at East Gate: A First-Hand Account of the Rendlesham Forest UFO Incident, Its Cover-Up and Investigation&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Peter has lectured extensively both in the States and abroad at venues including Cambridge Hospital in Boston; The National Press Club in Washington, D.C.; Cornell University, The Julliard School; The School of Visual Arts in New York City; The Royal College of Science and Technology, London; University of Cardiff, Wales; Summerhill School in Suffolk UK; The UFO Organization of Japan, Tokyo; Leeds England International UFO Conferences, a fifteen-city book tour of the United Kingdom, and numerous UFO conferences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;His numerous credits include editorial assistant on requested papers for the United Nations 1978 initiative “for the establishment of a UN-UFO Department," and Parliament’s House of Lords 1980 Debate on UFOs. He is on the Advisory Board of Budd Hopkins’ Intruders Foundation, was Editor-in-Chief of the groundbreaking website, UFOcity.com, and Event Coordinator for the SCI FI Channel’s ‘Alien Abduction Phenomenon Symposium,’ to promote the release of the miniseries ‘Taken.’ Peter has written for numerous publications and websites, and is an advisor to the McMinnville Oregon UFO Festival, a producer and speaker of the Exeter New Hampshire UFO Conference, and was the consultant, Media Liaison, and UFO Symposium Coordinator for the City of Roswell, New Mexico. This summer (2012) he was made a member of the French Académie d'Ufologie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cost: 10$ per person. Pay at the door.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike </member_name><member_id>6862973</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347188449000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345488681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Abduction Experiences and The Importance of Ufology</name><id>78569692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347051600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/78569692/</event_url></item>