<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Tea parties are a wonderful way to introduce children to the ways of etiquette, entertaining, and even cooking. Tea parties for children give us a chance to have some simple and quiet fun with our sons and daughters.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tea Parties are not just for girls! Even if you have small boys, or both boys and girls, a tea party is a special activity that will become a treasured memory. Our children are bombarded daily with negative messages. They seem to be growing up faster all the time and their childhood innocence only last for so long. Activities such as tea parties, reading, family games nights, and craft time will stay with them forever as calming memories. Plan your tea party today, and enjoy an afternoon of magic and whimsy with your children.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tea parties will be held in the formal dining room of the Larches Inn. Children will enjoy fun and creative lessons on etiquette, delicious treats, and of course fabulous teas from around the world. Our in-house Chef Serena McLoughlin will educate the children on the history of tea and the process by which the teas come from nature to our tea cup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price includes Mother and Child - additional children are 25.00&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>7932349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245781035000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242068290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tea Parties are not just for Girls!</name><id>10387063</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245528000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/10387063/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/f/c/global_7505116.jpeg</photo_url></item>