<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/a/6/event_198776742.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and join us this Wednesday to share your stories, to bring your questions and to learn about the latest breakthroughs in healing approaches that can be effortless and lasting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you been frustrated by your inability to shake off persistent behavior patterns? Then come to discover this - the chance are they are these patterns or your depression and anxiety are not really yours! You may have absorbed this energy from someone else.  And now researchers are discovering that it could even be something you took on in the womb!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our personalities are molded by our mothers in a powerful way from the very beginnings of our lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;From w&lt;/span&gt;ithin placenta inside our mother we learn about life, but not the life that is our own. You may have never thought that your ADD to a large extent was connected to your pregnant mother’s depression, or your late night hunger tied to your mother starving during the Second World War. Or your fear of passing out and being suffocated was caused by your mother losing consciousness during anesthesia administered at birth.  We will sense these traumas as very real, as something that happened to us directly in our lives, yet find ourselves unable to recall an actual event to match that experience.  Consequently, much of  prenatal trauma remains unhealed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;While we are not&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;responsible&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;for trauma passed to us by our parents, we must be&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;responsive&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;to it. We must use it as a catalyst to facilitate not just our own healing, but that of our ancestral, and the traditional heritage as well. In this workshop you will be able to use the Energy Restructuring methodology to begin healing your prenatal trauma, repairing your mother’s wounding, and manifesting larger continuity and harmony within the tree.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary B</member_name><member_id>78201602</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363834167000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359187220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Breakthroughs in Healing - Trauma In the Womb</name><id>101458892</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363821300000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/101458892/</event_url></item>