<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the
established waiting list. A yes list will be provided as soon as
possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Criteria: NO WHINING, COMPLAINING, ETC. All hikers must be able
to maintain a minimum pace of three miles an hour for a minimum of
four hours. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along
with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods.
All attendees must read, understand and agree to the
waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;starting at Edmands Path Trailhead Back to here entering alpine
zone hike 2.90 mi/2 hr 42 min/+2405 ft on the Edmands Path From its
trailhead, the path runs nearly level across two small brooks, then
it crosses Abenaki Brook and turns sharp right onto an old logging
road on the far bank. The trail diverges left off the old road and
crosses a wet area. Soon it begins to climb steadily, undulating up
the west ridge of Mt. Eisenhower, carefully searching out the most
comfortable grades. The trail swings left and angles up the
mountainside on a footway supported by extensive rock cribbing,
then passes through a tiny stone gateway. It crosses a small brook
running over a ledge, and soon the grade becomes almost level as
the trail contours around the north slope of Mt. Eisenhower,
affording excellent views out through a fringe of trees. It breaks
into the open, crosses the nose of a ridge on a footway paved with
carefully placed stones, and reaches the Mt. Eisenhower Loop a few
yards from the Crawford Path. to the junction of Mt Eisenhower Loop
hike 0.38 mi/11 min/+330 ft on the Mt Eisenhower Loop It passes
through a grassy sag just to the right of Red Pond and then ascends
moderately from a ledge overlooking Red Pond. to Mt Eisenhower
Totals Distance 3.28 mi Time 2 hr 53 min Elev Gain +2826 ft Elev
Loss -91 ft Elev Change +2735 ft Driving Directions Show in Google
Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.38 mi/11 min/-330 ft on
the Mt Eisenhower Loop From there, it descends moderately to a
ledge overlooking Red Pond, then drops steeply over ledges, passes
through a grassy sag just to the left of Red Pond. to the junction
of Edmands Path hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+5 ft on the Mt Eisenhower Loop
It finally climbs briefly to a junction on the left with the
Edmands Path to rejoin the Crawford Path on a small, rocky knob. to
the junction of Crawford Path hike 0.20 mi/8 min/+24 ft on the
Crawford Path The Edmands Path can be reached from this junction by
following the Mt. Eisenhower Loop for a short distance. to the
junction of Mt Eisenhower Trail hike 1.20 mi/56 min/+595 ft on the
Crawford Path The Mt. Eisenhower Trail from the Dry River valley
enters right. The Crawford Path then begins the ascent of the
shoulder called Mt. Franklin, first moderately, then steeply for a
short distance near the top. The trail reaches the relatively level
shoulder and continues past an unmarked path on the right that
leads in 130 yd. to the barely noticeable summit of Mt. Franklin,
from which there are excellent views, particularly into Oakes Gulf.
to the junction of Mt Monroe Loop hike 0.40 mi/23 min/+305 ft on
the Mt Monroe Loop The trail diverges from the Crawford Path and
quickly ascends the minor crag called Little Monroe, then descends
into the shallow, grassy sag beyond. It then climbs steeply to the
summit of Mt. Monroe. to Mt Monroe Totals Distance 5.48 mi Time 4
hr 32 min Elev Gain +3935 ft Elev Loss -600 ft Elev Change +3335 ft
Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to
here hike 0.40 mi/23 min/-305 ft on the Mt Monroe Loop The trail
descends from the summit of Mt. Monroe and reaches a shallow,
grassy sag. It continues as it ascends the minor crag called Little
Monroe before reaching Crawford Path. to the junction of Crawford
Path hike 1.20 mi/56 min/-595 ft on the Crawford Path The Crawford
Path continues along the edge of the precipice that forms the
northwest wall of Oakes Gulf, the Mt. Monroe Loop rejoins on the
right, and the main path continues along the flat ridge, passing an
unmarked path on the left that leads in 130 yd. to the barely
noticeable summit of Mt. Franklin, from which there are excellent
views, particularly into Oakes Gulf. The trail drops rather steeply
off the end of the shoulder, then descends moderately to the sag,
passing the Mt. Eisenhower Trail. to the junction of Mt Eisenhower
Trail hike 0.20 mi/8 min/-24 ft on the Crawford Path The Mt.
Eisenhower Loop leaves on the right on a small ledge overlooking
Red Pond, a small alpine tarn of stagnant water. The Edmands Path
can be reached from this junction by following the Mt. Eisenhower
Loop for a short distance. to the junction of Mt Eisenhower Loop
hike 0.02 mi/1 min/-5 ft on the Mt Eisenhower Loop From the
Crawford Path, it descends briefly to a junction on the right with
the Edmands Path. to the junction of Edmands Path hike 2.90 mi/2 hr
42 min/-2405 ft on the Edmands Path From the Mt. Eisenhower Loop, a
few yards from the Crawford Path, the Edmands Path crosses the nose
of a ridge on a footway paved with carefully placed stones. It then
enters the scrub and contours around the north slope of Mt.
Eisenhower at a nearly level grade, affording excellent views
through a fringe of trees. It crosses a small brook running over a
ledge and descends to pass through a small stone gateway. It swings
right and angles down the mountainside on a footway supported by
extensive rock cribbing. It descends steadily, undulating down the
west ridge of Mt. Eisenhower, carefully searching out the most
comfortable grades. After a long descent, the trail crosses a wet
area and merges right with an old logging road. It turns sharp left
to cross Abenaki Brook on a bridge and runs nearly level across two
small brooks to the trailhead. to Edmands Path Trailhead Totals
Distance 10.20 mi Time 8 hr 42 min Elev Gain +4199 ft Elev Loss
-4199 ft Elev Change 0 ft &amp;#65279;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER FOUR DOOR SUBARU LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309135162000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308060841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT EISENHOWER &amp; MT MONROE VIA EDMANDS PATH</name><id>22150971</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309005000000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/22150971/</event_url></item>