<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Mt. Holyoke Range State Park is a little North of Springfield, MA with 3,000 acres! The exact length and path covered on this hike will depend on the weather conditions. We'll hike no more than approximatly 6 miles with less being the case if conditions require more effort given a 5 hour window for hiking. Most of the hike would be moderate in difficulty with some limited opportunity for high-moderate exertion. Streams, forest, and quiet solitude will dominate the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Those who wish to go need to have&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots (no sneakers!) - There could be snow or it could be wet/muddy! &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too. &lt;br /&gt;* Gloves &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket - BRIGHT color best given possibility of hunters &lt;br /&gt;* Hat &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water - MUST bring! &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food/lunch - (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advised equipment&lt;/b&gt; (depending on conditions):&lt;br /&gt;* Microspikes&lt;br /&gt;* Gators or snowpants or rainpants shell (over hiking pants)&lt;br /&gt;* Quickie Sled (for the very adventurous as some opportunity to use!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get cold after about 10 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 9 AM at the Notch Visitors Center at the west side of the park (see the park map). Directions are below. We'll likely relocate to another parking location for the hike (south or north side of the park). We will hike (with rest stops and sightseeing) about 5 hr. and get back to the vehicles at about 2 PM. Then the plan is to head out to eat an early dinner together back down MA-116 in South Hadley. We would finish up eating at about 4 PM and head home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;leaving&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; at a 8:15 AM for those interested. There will be a dark green Dodge Caravan. Please chip in for gas and the drive is about an hour. Return at about 5 PM. It is advised to call Kevin (number in RSVP) or e-mail him so he knows you plan to carpool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location/directions to meet at park&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=1540+West+St.&amp;amp;city=Amherst&amp;amp;state=MA" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location/directions for the carpool meet-up&lt;/b&gt; can be found at: &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?searchtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;searchtab=home&amp;amp;formtype=address&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=69+Prospect+Hill+rd.&amp;amp;city=East+Windsor&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;General park information&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/hksp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Park map&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/Holyoke.gif" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Can meet me in E. Windsor to join in a carpool or to follow up to hike location. Can also meet at hike location at Visitor's Center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260916604000</updated><rating><average>4.86999988556</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259334212000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at Mt. Holyoke Range SP in Amherst MA</name><id>11962757</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260626400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11962757/</event_url></item>