<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>17 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.2004</phone><name>Johnny D's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669354</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Date: Wednesday, January 14, 2009 &lt;br /&gt;Time: 8:00pm - 11:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Location: Johnny D's &lt;br /&gt;Street: 17 Holland St. &lt;br /&gt;City/Town: Somerville, MA &lt;br /&gt;  View MapGoogleMapQuestMicrosoftYahoo &lt;br /&gt;Contact Info Phone: 6175014902 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DescriptionWinter Warmer: A Benefit Concert for Mass Families in Need&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Wednesday, January 14 at 8pm, Johnny D's presents a musical fundraiser for the United Way Community Support Fund. The show features a stellar cast of Boston roots, rock, and folk artists, including Merrie Amsterburg, Mark Erelli, Meg Hutchinson, Jennifer Kimball, Todd Thibaud, Tim Gearan, Jimmy Ryan, Dinty Child, Jim Fitting, The Loomers, and host Alastair Moock. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Johnny D's is located at 17 Holland St, Somerville, MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 cover all goes to the Community Support Fund. For reservations and further info, contact the club at 617-776-2004 or visit www.johnnyds.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Community Support Fund is a joint effort by eighteen United Ways from across Massachusetts to provide emergency assistance to families and individuals struggling to afford basic needs this winter. This is the first time that United Ways from across the state have joined together under a singular community-wide response. Because so many families and individuals will need help this winter, United Ways across the state have agreed to distribute 100 percent of the funds raised to their local communities without overhead costs. More info at &lt;a href="http://csf.supportunitedway.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://csf.supportuni...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Johnny D's fundraiser was put together by Boston singer/songwriter Alastair Moock, with the support of the United Way and PARTNERS+simons. In November, PARTNERS+simons also created the print and television campaign for the Community Support Fund on a pro bono basis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info at &lt;a href="http://speakunited.org/blog/meghan+keaney/2008/12/live-united-heroes-tom-simons-and-todd-baird" target="_blank"&gt;http://speakunited.or...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232242387000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231269337000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Warmer: A Benefit Concert for Mass Families in Need</name><id>9460101</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231981200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/9460101/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/6/a/global_6849434.jpeg</photo_url></item>