<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Pierce Hall</address_2><address_1>Rt. 119</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03461</zip><lat>42.750000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Franklin Pierce College</name><city>Rindge</city><id>274339</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.019997</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What happened to William Rodriguez the morning of 9/11 is a miracle. What happened to his story after-the-fact is a tragedy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But with miracles and tragedies comes truth. And truth is exactly what Rodriguez brings to the whole mystery surrounding 9/11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Declared a hero for saving numerous lives at Ground Zero, he was the janitor on duty the morning of 9/11 who heard and felt explosions rock the basement sub-levels of the north tower just seconds before the jetliner struck the top floors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He not only claims he felt explosions coming from below the first sub-level while working in the basement, he says the walls were cracking around him and he pulled a man to safety by the name of Felipe David, who was severely burned from the basement explosions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All these events occurred only seconds before and during the jetliner strike above. And through it all, he now asks a simple question everybody should be asking? How could a jetliner hit 90 floors above and burn a man?s arms and face to a crisp in the basement below within seconds of impact?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[excerpted from: &lt;a href="http://bellaciao.org/en/article.php3?id_article=6625" target="_blank"&gt;http://bellaciao.org/...&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His eye witness account, ignored by the media and the government, points the finger squarely on an official cover-up at the highest levels since the government contends the WTC fell only from burning jet fuel. And after listening to Rodriguez, it?s easy to see why the Bush administration wants him kept quiet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bush wants him quiet because Rodriguez?s account is ?proof positive? the WTC was brought down by a controlled demolition, not burning jet fuel. And Bush knows if he?s caught lying about this or caught in a cover-up, it?s just a matter of time before the whole house of cards comes tumbling down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In fact, Rodriguez?s story is so damaging - so damning - it literally blows the lid off the government story, literally exposing the whole 9/11 investigation as a sham and a cover-up of the worst kind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And it appears the cover-up also extends to the media.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NBC news knew about his story several years ago, even spending a full day at his house taping his comments. But when push came to shove, his story was never aired. Why?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His eyewitness account, backed up by at least 14 people at the scene with him, isn?t speculation or conjecture. It isn?t a story that takes a network out on a journalistic limb. It?s a story that can be backed up, a story that can be verified with hospital records and testimony from many others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn't you like to hear and meet this man? You can at this event at Franklin Pierce College, May 18th, 6:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Carpool from Nashua leaves at 4:45 PM (exit 6 Park &amp;amp; Ride lot - we'll head over to join the Amherst carpool)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool leaves from the Amherst Library at 5:15PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool from Concord is not happening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool from Keene  is not happening.&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;William Rodriguez' own web site: &lt;a href="http://www.william911.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.william911...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wm. Rodriguez talk at scholars conference: &lt;a href="http://video.google.com/videoplay?docid=4380137365762802294" target="_blank"&gt;http://video.google.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy</member_name><member_id>3581956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181570706000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176832068000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening with September 11 Hero William Rodriguez</name><id>5679996</id><headcount>125</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179527400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/5679996/</event_url></item>