<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>With the new year we met with a group of new members, grateful for the greater diversity of our group as we grow. Jewish and Christian souls were present in the warm, rustic environment of the &lt;a href="http://www.peaceabbey.org" target="_blank"&gt;Peace Abbey, an Interfaith Retreat Center&lt;/a&gt;.  With the new members, we shared our expectations of the group, seeking to connect beyond our religious tradtions, celebrating diversity and plurality as a balm of healing in our divisive world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We chose as our next selection Jonathan Sack's, The Dignity of Difference: Avoiding the Clash of Civilization. We will read the first three chapters for our next meeting in February.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have spirited contributors in our group and I encourage all to continue to share our thoughts, inspirations and insights in our &lt;a href="http://www.interfaithbookclub.wordpress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Interfaith Book Club Blog&lt;/a&gt;. The blog provides this opportunity in between meeting times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also have a special blog dedicated to contemporary interfaith visual arts and poetry called &lt;a href="http://bookclub.meetup.com/912/pages/www.sacredartpoet.wordpress.com"&gt;Sacred Bearings&lt;/a&gt;. For those who may be interested, feel free to comment on the postings. If you wish to post art and/or poetry, send them me. I will post them for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Carl Chudy and Fr. Joe Matteucig&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;Our Lady of Fatima Shrine&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on Route 16, close to the Library and Town Hall Complex of Sherborn.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204082242000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200447083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club February Meetup</name><id>7125012</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203886800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/7125012/</event_url></item>