<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Tanager St. #2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.421910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 648 3737</phone><name>Herb Pearce</name><city>Arlington</city><id>900529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188564</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Greatest Game Ever Played&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2005  PG121 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a pint-sized caddie (Josh Flitter) at his side, amateur golfer Francis Ouimet (Shia LaBeouf) shocked the world at the 1913 U.S. Open when he outplayed defending British champ Harry Vardon in what was dubbed "The Greatest Game Ever Played." But Ouimet's rise to the top wasn't easy, with a hard-nosed father (Elias Koteas) and a hard-knock life to overcome. Actor Bill Paxton helms this inspiring true-life story based on actual events. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cast:Tyler Brody Stein, Shia LaBeouf, Elias Koteas, Josh Flitter, Max Kasch, Stephen Dillane, Peter Firth, Peyton List, Jackie Burroughs, Luke Askew, Len CariouDirector:Bill PaxtonGenres:Drama, Family Dramas, Sports Dramas, Dramas Based on Real Life, Sports Stories, Golf, Disney, Blu-rayThis movie is:Emotional, Sentimental&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ENNEAGRAM AT THE MOVIES &lt;br /&gt;

 Vegetarian dinner provided from 6:30 to 7pm. Movie at 7. Fine to show up anytime. It's helpful for me to know in advance if you are coming, particularly if you are eating, though if fine just to show up if you can't decide beforehand. You are welcome to bring additional items if you want. We stop the movie on occasion to talk about Enneagram types, subtypes and relationship dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The cost is $20-25 sliding scale. Please feel free to bring friends and I can help them learn the types if they don't know the Enneagram. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Herb Pearce is an Enneagram expert, having taught over 2000 Enneagram personality types workshops, as well as the Myers-Briggs and Astrology. He is an author of 2 books, a psychotherapist for individuals, couples and families and leads Personality Types Trainings for groups, organizations, churches, schools, colleges and yoga centers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;herb@herbpearce.com            781 648 3737      www.herbpearce.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Arlington Heights, Corner of Tanager St. and Wollaston Ave.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335742851000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Personality Types</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Personality-Types-Enneagram</urlname><id>1405281</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>Personality Types</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333027189000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enneagram at the Movies &amp; Dinner - The Greatest Game Ever Played</name><id>58366312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335738600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Personality-Types-Enneagram/events/58366312/</event_url></item>