<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>707867</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.817561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us to hear our guest speaker, Marc Adams, a former student of Jerry Falwell's Liberty Univeristy, who bills himself as running the only nonprofit with the sole mission of providing outreach to GLBT students terrorized at religious educational institutions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from his site:&lt;br /&gt;Marc Adams, Lambda Literary Award finalist and Silver Pen Award recipient for his autobiography, The Preacher’s Son will be speaking at a special community event sponsored by the Greater Worcester Humanists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Preacher’s Son chronicles Marc’s life growing up gay as the son of a fundamentalist Baptist minister in rural Pennsylvania where he endured a childhood of physical, emotional, and spiritual abuse. He went on to attend, by choice, Jerry Falwell’s Liberty University where he also was employed for 3 ½ years in the student recruiting/university relations department. His book articulately reveals life at Liberty and the struggle to conform to the standards for which he would have been a martyr. He shares about his years as an ex-gay. It culminates with his coming to terms with being gay, his coming out to his fundamentalist Baptist Christian family and his journey to become a Unitarian Universalist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since its release in 1996, The Preacher’s Son has garnered praise from bookstores, reviewers, the mainstream press, and the gay and lesbian media. Not to be discounted, Marc says, are the thousands of letters and e-mails he has received from men and women, gay and straight, who have read his books and found themselves changed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marc will share some of his life’s story, talk about his latest book, (lost)Found, as well as HeartStrong, Inc., the non-profit organization he co-founded. HeartStrong, Inc., is a non-profit educational organization for gay, lesbian, bisexual, and transgender students of religious schools, colleges, and universities. HeartStrong has provided hope and help to GLBT students who have endured faith-based anti-GLBT bullying in religious schools around the world since 1996. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of Marc’s books and resources will be available for purchase, including his latest book (the much anticipated follow up to The Preacher’s Son), (lost)Found. For more information about Marc Adams www.meetmarcadams.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park in the lot.  Through the double doors, hang a right.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266692629000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220751214000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GWH MEETING - October 2008 - Freethought Day Celebration</name><id>8705215</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224025200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/8705215/</event_url></item>