<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1019 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06405</zip><lat>41.281631</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Branford Green </name><city>Branford</city><id>963428</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.811409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Branford is once again hosting several talented and staged Jazz evenings for the next nine Thursdays&lt;br /&gt;following opening night of Thursday July 1st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The music is always good, the weather will change but can be so delicious when you catch one of those perfect balmy summer evenings . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your pic-i-nic basket or grab some take out on the way over,  your cooler ( discreet alcohol consumption is permitted), your chair, a friend or two and lets all laugh and breathe and enjoy . ..despite the stresses of the day . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starts at 6;30pm and does not go very late, but should be very fun and relaxing night,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you here!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glennn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the first act . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Walter Duda - Smooth Jazz - July 1!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bridgeport native Walter Duda was inspired by rock n roll vocalists Dion and Bobby Darin. He then became a fan of the vocal harmony arrangements of Brian Wilson (Beach Boys), The Beatles and The Hollies. While in Detroit, he was introduced to the rhythm and grooves of The Motown Sound. Next, progressive rock groups King Crimson and Yes caught his imagination. Eventually hearing jazz fusion keyboardists Brian Auger and George Duke inspired him to switch from playing guitar to piano.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a songwriter, he has been influenced by many artists, including Michael Franks, Mose Allison and Bobby Caldwell.  You'll hear those influences first hand as Walter Duda opens the 2010 Branford Jazz on the Green Series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out Blue Plate Radio to hear some of Duda's tracks!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>probably some type of purple balloon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glennn</member_name><member_id>8036405</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278161799000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275521165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday night JAZZ series on the Branford Green</name><id>wmwsnynkbcb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278022500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/13677657/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_3095463.jpeg</photo_url></item>