<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>April 13, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HI!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace and blessings! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am sure most of us are still basking in the great celebrations of Passover and Easter. I pray that these celebrations are truly a time of grace and spiritual growth; a time to deepen family and community bonds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A BLESSED PASSOVER AND A BLESSED EASTER TO ALL OF YOU.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaking about our last meeting (March 29), I would like to share some reflections. We read chapter 1 part 3: &amp;quot;LIGHT&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was quite interesting to see two things taking place during our interaction: first how LIGHT  is an integral part of the experience of world religions; secondly to notice how different descriptions - interpretations - feelings there are out there. During the sharing I felt like one who looks at a diamond. Depending from one's own position, the person experiences light and color in a different way from the one seated next to her/him. I continue to marvel at the beauty and creativity of God the Creator. And I wish we could enter deeper into this mystery which leads us to the LIGHT. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;God said: &amp;quot;Let there be Light&amp;quot; and there was light. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Ultimately, light is the mother of life. Where there is no light there is no life. Light is the secret presence of the divine.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The light that illuminates the sun is the light of Brahman; when Brahman shines everything shines, by Brahman's light everything is lighted.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The creator gave us the sun. And, as we see, the sun came up this morning and shines on us, keeping us warm. he's doing his duty, and for this we are very grateful.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;My God, how great you are! Clothed in majesty and glory, wrapped in a robe of light!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I am the Light of the world; anyone who follows me will not be walking in the dark; he/she will have the light of life.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;God says: I am the supreme fire; not deadly, but rather enkindling every spark of life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The soul not only unites to the fire that God is but also produces within a living flame. This flame of Love is the Holy Spirit.&amp;quot; Love takes on the characteristics of lire; it is highly active. Since love is never idle, but in continual motion, it is always emitting flames everywhere like a blazing fire... The soul is affected in its deepest center, for God does his work in the soul's depths. And the soul's center is God.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;God is the light of the heavens and the earth... God guides to his Light whom he wills.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I conclude with the last paragraph found on page 79: &amp;quot;One cannot talk about creation or its manifold periods of light and dark without talking about LIGHT. Nor can one talk about consciousness without alluding to light. Nor can we talk about love without recalling sparks and fire and flame. Thomas Aquinas observes that the first effect of love is melting. Perhaps our reintroducing awareness of light will allow us to revisit the warmth and melting of frozen hearts that occurs when we are less than enlightened.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let us continue to walk in the light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, coming to our next Interfaith Book Club Meeting, I want to remind all of you that: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR UPCOMING MEETING is going to be on Sunday May 3rd, at 4:00PM.&lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY - located at: Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770in Sherborn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you know the format of our meetings is quite simple: we gather to share our reflections and reactions on what we read at home. For our next meeting (MAY 3) we are going to share on chapter one: &amp;quot;COMMUNITY AND INTERDEPENDENCE&amp;quot; and on chapter 2: &amp;quot;NAMES FOR GOD&amp;quot; (pages 80-116). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if you not able to read the material &amp;quot;assigned&amp;quot;, don't worry and come anyway. It has been my belief that our simple presence can still foster deep and creative interaction. Hope to see all of you on May 3. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, mark your calendars and hope to see you at the meeting. Enjoy this book and enjoy this SPECIAL AND BLESSED SEASON. Blessings on you and your families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PEACE&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx &lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144&lt;br /&gt;e-mail: pino.ma@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on Route 16, close to the Library and Town Hall Complex of Sherborn.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246219488000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238361239000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club May Meetup</name><id>10064204</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241380800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/10064204/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/c/global_7393468.jpeg</photo_url></item>