<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>west hartford</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06119</zip><lat>41.764294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>caryl's house</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>462542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.727501</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Don't Ask, Don't tell, join us for an evening honoring those who have served and those who continue to serve. It will be a night of mystery, surprises, secrets and laughter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, the spaces are already filled.  Do RSVP though if you want to be on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations.  If nothing else, make up a great story to go behind the dish you're making.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292029449000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284352921000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes Monthly dinner Meetup</name><id>vmbmnynpbqb</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289606400000</time><rsvp_limit>29</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/14749378/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/6/global_17927606.jpeg</photo_url></item>