<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>98 rt.13 </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03033</zip><lat>42.723418</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Andres Institute of Art</name><city>Brookline </city><id>906249</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.662533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Easy Hike Sculpture Park &lt;br /&gt;

 (a Dog and Child friendly event)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday Nov. 12th.,1:00 pm. or anytime til around 3 pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 Andres Institute of Art &lt;br /&gt;

 #98, rt.13 Brookline NH 03033&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.andresinstitute.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RAIN, WIND OR, TOO WET, TOO COLD CANCELS THIS EVENT. &lt;br /&gt;

 RAIN DATE July, 8th. &lt;br /&gt;

 For all levels of hikers. RSVPs are incorrect. This event is listed with 10 other Groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host:: Steve Obermiller    ob@tds.net 603-491-1962 &lt;br /&gt;

 This an easy two to three hour hike. I have also ordered a great day for this event.  So, please bring something to drink, the dogs, the kids, and your friends. &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/b/3/event_7907539.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Join Steve Ob1. and his friends for an easy hike through 170 acres, up wooded trails with Art work to view on the way. This is Andreas' Sculpture Park with art work from sculptor from around the world, all along the trails. At the top of the trail is a spot with seats and a view of Mt. Manadnock 75 miles away. Where we can sit and take a short break. If you can not make it at 1:00 pm? Than meet us at anytime along the trail. The trail crisscrosses the main driveway to the top and the art studio. We park below at the start of the paved driveway. Please do not drive up the driveway.  Steve Ob1. will have his Ceil phone on to help you find us. Dress for changing weather and the woods, and remember the Deer Ticks. This is privet property. So, what we bring into the park. We must bring out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring plenty of fluids and to dress in layers so that you will be comfortable the whole time we are out on the trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone cares to, we can then go grab a bite to eat or enjoy a hot chocolate, at a nearby restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; - AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or tex Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352756289000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352484961000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Hike Sculptue Park</name><id>90698502</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352743200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/90698502/</event_url></item>