<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Faneuil Hall</address_2><address_1>148 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359501</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 227-5100</phone><name>McFadden's</name><city>Boston</city><id>753501</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Have you ever wondered what to do on a given night or just wanted to do something out of the ordinary? &lt;br /&gt;Well look no further – the premiere event planning company, Things To Do, is now in BOSTON!  We promise to provide unique social and cultural events that will allow you to meet other young professionals from the Boston area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you missed our summer events, here is your chance to kick off the fall at our next networking and social mixer for young professionals at McFadden’s. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you come alone or with friends, this event is the perfect opportunity to meet fun and interesting young professionals in a friendly environment.  You will also learn about the upcoming schedule of unique social events being planned by the Things To Do: BOSTON team and how you can get involved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free event - courtesy of the Things To Do: BOSTON team. We will all be on hand to personally greet you and help make your night a special one as we begin the start of an incredible new opportunity for Boston's young professionals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are looking for outgoing and imaginative young professional leaders who are interested in discussing ideas regarding the launch of this new company, future event ideas, over seas trips, etc. We would love your input on how we can create an exciting new young professional community unlike anything Boston has ever seen before with events worthy of attracting the top young leaders and entrepreneurs of the future from throughout the greater Boston area.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>7970205</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223135229000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1382</urlname><id>1275022</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Things To Do: BOSTON</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220475034000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Things To Do: Boston - Mixer at McFadden's</name><id>8681543</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222381800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1382/events/8681543/</event_url></item>