<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Gott Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01966</zip><lat>42.687389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 546-2997</phone><name>Halibut Point State Park</name><city>Rockport</city><id>744966</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.631871</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since attending the CAPE Group visit to the Chapters on a Quarry Wall exhibit last January, I thought it would be great to visit the quarries sometime in spring, now that leaves, ferns and mosses are peeping out from the rock crevices.  The entire area offers many photographic opportunities along one of the most spectacular coastlines of the North Shore.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the Halibut Point parking lot generally fills up by 11am, the new plan is to meet there at 10:30am (not Granite Pier!).  We'll spend an hour or two at Halibut Point admiring and photographing the astounding views.  After that we will drive over to Granite Pier, walk down to Flatledge Quarry and spend an hour or so there.  Time permitting we may also explore Little Parker quarry which is a short distance from Flat Ledge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking at Halibut Point is $2.  At Granite Pier it is $6 if there is an attendant on duty, free if there's none.  We can carpool there to reduce the charge per person.  Also there is street parking within a short walk of Granite Pier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After exploring the quarries, the plan is to head into Rockport, browse around and take a walk down Bearskin Neck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;General Info&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://halibutpoint.wordpress.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://halibutpoint.w...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.halibutpointstatepark.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.halibutpoi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the Halibut Point State Park parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen</member_name><member_id>2854002</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212592008000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><why>CAPE Group members are friendly, helpful, engaging and fun!  We have a mixture of photography experience, from novice to professional.</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211308622000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Event:  Granite Quarries, Rockport</name><id>7976112</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212330600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/7976112/</event_url></item>