<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Duchess of Langeais&lt;/b&gt; France 2007  137 min. &lt;br /&gt; originally released as  &amp;quot; Don't Touch the Axe&amp;quot;- guess they figured it wouldn't fare so well in the U.S. without a more proper  French sounding title.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The latest film from the remarkable 79-year-old French new-wave master Jacques Rivette is an adaptation of a Balzac novella, &lt;b&gt;La Duchesse de Langeais&lt;/b&gt;; the axe in question is that used to behead England's Charles I. The tortured romantic hero, Armand de Montriveau, on a visit to London, is warned not to touch it by his guide: a taboo symbol of violence, anarchy and revenge. In Restoration France of the 1820s, Montriveau (Guillaume Depardieu) falls in love with the coquettish Antoinette, wife of the Duke of Langeais, played by Jeanne Balibar. Antoinette is flattered and excited by his attentions, but considers the subservient role of a mistress beneath her: a socio-erotic game of cat-and-mouse ensues, fanning the flames of their mutual obsession. Rivette conceives the story in the highest and most classical style; the result is severe, sometimes subdued, but ultimately fascinating.  The Guardian&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rivette's cameraman William Lubtschansky transforms words and movement into installations of light and darkness, which seem to freeze periodically like paintings. Fires crackle incessantly in the salons' fireplaces, yet their calming effect is misleading. The passing of time is shown with titles, and Balzac's words accompany the development of events. Rivette dramatises nothing, he observes Balibar and Depardieu using words that are sharper than foils and rapiers, and watches them ? merciless as Balzac ? as they hope and suffer, fear and fight.  Signandsight Review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.slantmagazine.com/film/film_review.asp?ID=3480" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.slantmagaz...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then its off to a local cafe to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203555405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rivette's The Duchess of Langeais</name><id>7374424</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206298800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7374424/</event_url></item>