<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Greetings, thinkers everywhere...or at least in Boston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Ayn Rand meet up will take place on Sunday, March  5 at 5PM.  This meet-up, thus far, has been a conversational forum, which has gotten more interesting with each gathering.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While we occasionally turn to Q&amp;amp;A from Robert Mayhew's new book, Ayn Rand Answers, which is a compilation of her answers to questions from many speaking engagements over the years, the group conversation seems to flow in a variety of directions.  Feel free to come and throw out whatever questions or comments you wish.  My goal is not to act as a moderator, per se, but to just make sure we are growing in our understanding of Ayn Rand's philosophy, Objectivism, whether it be through discussions of current events, situations in our lives as viewed from an Objectivist perspective, or Q &amp;amp; A.  Come as you are, come inspired... just come with your brain turned on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll hope to see you on March 5.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have to pay meetup.com $19.00 per month to use their site, so if anyone is willing to donate a couple of green-backs to &amp;quot;the cause&amp;quot; I'd be most grateful.  At the last meeting several people put in a voluntary contribution at the end of the gathering. Oddly enough, it had overtones of passing the collection plate at church, but I enjoy that kind of irony, so we'll probably continue to collect money in that fashion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>2499401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1139180791000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Ayn Rand March Meetup</name><id>4848207</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1141596000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/4848207/</event_url></item>