<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>right at the T station</address_2><address_1>70 Union Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.329502</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>???</phone><name>Starbuck's Newton Center</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>73982</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192596</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>January's event will be a SUNDAY Meetup.  Topic:  bringing out the n00bs!  This month marks a new year and maybe, time for a fresh approach to an old problem.  Did you know our group has 72 members?  But I would guess that only about 25 of those have attended any of our events.  Is it the day/times of our events that's the problem?  The location?  What can we do to make our group useful and fun enough to lure these folks out of lurkerdom?  Or -- should we write the rest off as lazy bums and concentrate on the active membership?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newbies and lurkers -- talk to us.  Have you made a New Year's resolution to write something new, get published, or break some other writing milestone this year?  This is your chance to tell us how we can help you achieve that resolution!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This discussion will take place both on the message board and at the January meetup, so that those who can't attend can still get their $.02 in.  Be there (or be online) or be an irregular triskaidecagon!  =)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam Phillips</member_name><member_id>1902847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1168981677000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SF Writers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-SFandF-Writers</urlname><id>137807</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Science Fiction &amp; Fantasy Writers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1165701945000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Science Fiction Writers January Meetup</name><id>5317528</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1168808400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-SFandF-Writers/events/5317528/</event_url></item>