<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Join us this Thursday for a Bellydance Demonstration and Introduction to the upcoming classes starting Thursday, Feb 4th @ 6pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bringing the exotic mystique of Middle Eastern Dance (Belly Dance) on Thursday evenings to the Growing Green Wellness Center is a natural progression.  These classes are geared toward attracting beginners and/or advanced beginners who have had some training but would like to sharpen their skills and anyone who just loves the magic of dance!  We will not only explore basic belly dance movement (body isolations), but Middle Eastern music and rhythm and look into the history of this beautiful dance.  These classes will also focus on posture and muscle tone with a warm-up and cool down. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class Cards cover six-weekly sessions for $60, which includes one make-up class and a music cd of beautiful Middle Eastern music.  Students have the opportunity and are encouraged to continue with subsequent six week sessions because there is so much to discover!  These are considered ongoing classes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As both a Belly Dance instructor and student, I’ve seen how these classes have given women the opportunity to “get in touch with your inner spirit.”  It is also very comforting to know that this is the only dance form where each woman’s movement doesn’t have to be exactly the same as another’s and that weight is not a requirement or an issue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information or to contact me directly, go to:  www.Theharemdancer.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>danita thomas</member_name><member_id>11226615</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264893222000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264547204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Basic Bellydance Movement</name><id>12432370</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264719600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12432370/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/0/global_12411152.jpeg</photo_url></item>