<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kancamagus Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.043961</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Loon Mountain Ski Resort Parking Lot</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>3180271</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.553917</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm planning to hike/bushwhack(BW) to Scar Ridge.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This is located near Mt Osceola and south side from Kanc.&amp;nbsp; Scar Ridge has 2 peaks - West Peak (3774 ft) which is listed as NEHH(New England 100 Highest). Another one is East Peak (3620 ft).&amp;nbsp; Both E/W peaks are listed as NHHH (New Hampshire 100 Highest).&amp;nbsp; As West Peak has 2 bumps ahd both has white canister in each, we're planning to peakbag those 2 bumps on this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/a/9/event_50930601.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is "West Peak of West" white canister.&amp;nbsp; You can sign here on the small notebook in it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that Vose Spur and Scar Ridge are the 2 of the toughest bushwhacking in NH state, in NEHH list, I believe.&amp;nbsp; So please read the complete event description before signing up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Hiking/Bushwhacking Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We meet at Loon Mountain Ski Resort Parking Lot on Kancamagus Highway, Lincoln, NH at 8:00AM.&amp;nbsp; I'm thinking to camp one day before, but, haven't completely decided yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We will start hiking no later than 8:15AM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* This is less than 9 miles RT Hike/BW.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;NOTE:&lt;/span&gt; Since we'll be bushwhacking about 2/3 of total distance, there is no way to accurately describe total mileage of this hiking/BWing event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Again, this is not just hiking but including bushwhacking for considerable amount of distance in 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;very thick&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; spruce area.&amp;nbsp; If you don't want to be scratched by trees, please wear long sleeve, long pants.&amp;nbsp; Some people even prefer to wear protection eye glass. (I don't.)&amp;nbsp; Please bring smaller backpack as possible as you can to avoid stucking between tree branches. 
&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/1723755200050492932723/img/smileys/biggrin.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Rules to follow:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please don't bring your friends who are NOT the member of this meetup group as I need to make sure no liability as well as hikers capability who are going to join my hike in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* When you sign up this event, you'll be&amp;nbsp;asked several questions such that I can get to know your hiking experience if I haven't hiked with you yet.&amp;nbsp; If you've already hiked with me in past and you believe I know you, you may not have to answer...&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Otherwise, to answer to my questions are 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;NOT an optional.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* I do not prefer "No Show" after you signing up.&amp;nbsp; Please make sure to update your RSVP when your plan has changed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Weather Check Point:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather check point will be done on Sep 9th (Fri), 7PM.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I'll hike at Adirondacks High Peaks on Sep 10th, therefore, there is no email/phone access one day before this event. If you need to contact me, please do so by Friday, Sep 9th, 5PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Note:&amp;nbsp; At the higher elevation, temp might be colder than you assume.&amp;nbsp; Please don't underestimate the cold weather in higher elevation and make sure to bring appropriate gear such as waterproof jacket (in case of rain) etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please bring enough water, snack and lunch.&amp;nbsp; Needless to say, please bring your headlamp, although I'd like to come back to the parking lot before getting dark.&amp;nbsp; There is no access to brook etc. to retrieve water during this hike/BW.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, please feel free to drop me an email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assistant Organizer, (and 
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hiking-490/"&gt;Hike/Snowshoe in Vermont! Meetup&lt;/a&gt; Group Organizer)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomoko Nakajima&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My Car is Honda CR-V(Blue, VT plate)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1316005655000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314233835000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scar Ridge Bushwhacking (97/100 in NEHH)</name><id>30815591</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315742400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/30815591/</event_url></item>