<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Pleasant St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01833</zip><lat>42.724813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-352-6367</phone><name>The Georgetown Theatre Workshop </name><city>Georgetown</city><id>934995</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.988213</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of the cast is Robin Bornstein who you may know from this group.&lt;br /&gt;The last time she was in this type of production she stole the show and not just because she was in her underwear.&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is at The Georgetown Theatre Workshop &lt;a href="http://www.georgetowntheatreworkshop.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.georgetown...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ticket price is $10 and you will be responsible for getting your own ticket so get one soon as it will fill up fast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is enough interest I will try and find a local place to have dinner before hand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “There's a Burglar in My Bed” by Michael Parker&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;William Worthington III and his wife are both going to be away for the weekend from their two hundred acre Massachusetts estate with its twenty six bedroom mansion, he to Delaware to shoot ducks with the Duponts and she to her mother's in Boston. Both have, in fact, arranged trysts with their respective lovers in the estate's beach cottage. Inevitably their paths cross and divorce is in the air. Neither is willing to give up the world famous Worthington necklace, so each devises a plan to steal it. True to the laws of farce, both simulated burglaries are scheduled for same night. Fun filled chaos ensues: mistaken identities, unlikely romantic liaisons, a bumbling private detective, a fake necklace, one very determined nymphomaniac and two scantily clad pseudo nuns sharing a single skirt where did they come from? Confusion is piled on confusion until the mystery of who has the real necklace and who has the fake is revealed in a surprise ending.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the Loby the play starts at 8:00PM I will be there at 7:30PM</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>James Sawyer</member_name><member_id>9061363</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244909157000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240069990000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>See the play "There's a Burglar in My Bed"  </name><id>10212750</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242432000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10212750/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>