<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.367571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-723-2500</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>731371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070306</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come on Risk takers, lets watch together science movie of risk taking. Below is the link for trailer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RPqCpnd-2Xo" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't delay in making decision. Tickets for next Friday show are sold out. Make sure you buy ticket online or at counter if your rsvp is yes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You buy tickets here &lt;a href="https://store.mos.org/?action=showevent;event_id=273" target="_blank"&gt;https://store.mos.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;show timing : 5.00PM, Sat 30th Jan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the movie : This film takes audiences on a breathtaking journey from extraordinary heights, featuring spectacular footage of extreme skydiving while delving into both the biology of risktaking and the physics that make human flight possible.&lt;br /&gt;Skydiving teams bring audiences along on a secure yet death-defying ride, initiating their jumps from speeding aircraft miles above the immensity of Florida's Keys and California's Mojave Desert. The film also introduces audiences to the awesome sport of BASE jumping, with teams of jumpers leaping off spectacular cliffs and mountains, culminating in 4500-foot dives off the magnificent Fjords of Norway.&lt;br /&gt;More than a thrilling visual experience, the film educates audiences on the psychological and physiological forces that are at play in extreme risktaking and on the physics involved in skydiving, BASE jumping, parachuting, and their related activities.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email my phone number to people rsvp</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265060888000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264287992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Adrenaline Rush: The Science Of Risk </name><id>12403428</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264887900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/12403428/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/c/global_10053356.jpeg</photo_url></item>