<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Dorchester</address_2><address_1>934 Dorchester Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.318969</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 436 9747</phone><name>The Banshee Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>1011474</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056477</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Packers Boston,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;I hope you are having a great summer, enjoying the sunshine and looking forward to football season. I would also like to welcome the new members who have joined recently, hopefully we can grow even bigger this year, we are up to 156 members to date. I would also like to thank the group on behalf of the Banshee for the great year we had with you guys last season it was a pleasure to host the group, as you know the preseason games begin on August 13th, I am suggesting that we have the first meet up for the group on Thursday September 8th at 7.00pm New Orleans Saints @ Green Bay Packers. Ideally it would be great if the group can meet for a preseason game but in the past we have not got huge numbers, please give me some feed back and let me know if you guys want to arrange one. On September 8th we will be meeting on the 2nd floor (as usual) and Radeberger have agreed to host the first &amp;ldquo;Packers Boston Meetup&amp;rdquo; of the year, so if you like good food, cold beer and watching football with friends RSVP on the meetup site to give us an idea who is coming to the game, last year not many members RSVP&amp;rsquo;d each week but we did get huge crowds, it would be a huge help with staffing at the pub if the members could let us know who is coming. So any and all feedback is welcome, please join in and help grow the group, GO PACK.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Best,
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Ray Butler
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/a/b/event_45773931.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#65279; 
&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/b/0/event_9669904.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Located @ 934 Dorchester Ave, Dorchester, Ma, 02125 or take the Red Line to JFKUmass stop</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Packers Boston &amp; Ray Butler</member_name><member_id>9971064</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>ray butler</member_name><member_id>12777481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315615151000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Greenbaypackersboston</urlname><id>1489502</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Green Bay Packers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312562866000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Super Bowl World Champions Vs New Orleans Saints</name><id>28387611</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315522800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Greenbaypackersboston/events/28387611/</event_url></item>