<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Rogers Campground Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03584</zip><lat>44.468433</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-788-4885</phone><name>Rogers Campground</name><city>Lancaster</city><id>849387</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.544220</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>How would you solve a crime if the perpetrators managed to haul off all the evidence?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why did the Mayor of New York advise everyone to just hose off everything and wash off all the dust?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the clean-up, there seemed to be nothing left in any form of evidence in New York...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... but.... the dust .... yes, &lt;i&gt;the dust&lt;/i&gt;. How could it all have been washed down the drain?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, it wasn't! ... Years after the attacks, people still puzzled over the cause of the collapses of the WTC towers and especially of WTC 7, which wasn't hit by a plane. People began bringing samples of the steel and the dust to scientists and they may have solved one piece of the puzzle that is the World Trade Center collapses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Scientists solve the crime of the 21st Century&lt;/b&gt;, and one of those scientists is right here in New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark Basile has analyzed WTC dust taken from several locations and he confirms the results of other scientists in the US and elsewhere, such as Steven Jones of Utah and Neils Harret of Denmark. Mark will show workshop attenders slides of his detailed examination of particles in the WTC dust that could only come from a very high temperature reaction - hot enough to melt and atomize the steel in the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come hear Mark talk at the AltExpo tent (site #2) at the Porcupine Freedom Festival (PorcFest) up in Lancaster, New-Hampshire. Hopefully, a video will be available later if you can't attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at site#2, the AltExpo tent</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277583761000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276652045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scientists Solve the Crime of the 21st Century!</name><id>13814489</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277578800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/13814489/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/b/global_15757147.jpeg</photo_url></item>