<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Main St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nokia (12th Floor) </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>13010512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.080078</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please note our special meeting location for this event, hosted by Nokia. Link for directions: &lt;a href="http://here.com/cambridge%2C-ma-02142-usa/map=42.36225,-71.0803,17/title=1%20Main%20St"&gt;http://here.com/cambridge%2C-ma-02142-usa/map=42.36225,-71.0803,17/title=1%20Main%20St&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Thank you to Meetup member Keith Baker for helping to make this happen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendance is limited to the first 110 people. Due to Nokia security protocols, we will supply an RSVP list to Nokia, so that people can be checked off as they arrive. Please ensure your profile is up to date with your proper name. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and beverages for this Meetup to be provided by Clearpath Solutions - see our Sponsorship section. Thank you to Chris Emery!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Our guest speaker will be Chief AWS Evangelist Jeff Barr, who will make a stop in Boston as part of his 13 city, 5000 mile speaking tour with a presentation designed to introduce AWS and cloud computing to those who don’t know much about it, and to discuss the latest and great AWS developments for those who do. Topics to be covered include the latest EC2 instance types, the Relational Database Service, Amazon Glacier, Amazon Redshift, and the Virtual Private Cloud. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://aws.typepad.com/aws/2013/03/aws-user-group-road-trip-aka-hit-the-road-jeff.html"&gt;http://aws.typepad.com/aws/2013/03/aws-user-group-road-trip-aka-hit-the-road-jeff.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Please come armed with lots of questions; Jeff enjoys the interactive part of user group presentations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Jeff holds a BS degree in Computer Science from American University and is a part-time graduate student at the University of Washington. He’s father to 5 children and grandfather to 1. He’s a 10 year veteran of Amazon.com and has also worked on the Visual Studio team at Microsoft and at several startups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Also in attendance will be Tony Stephens with Amazon, Account Manager, New England. Tony is taking over for Mark Estes, who is now going to help build the enterprise market for AWS in Texas (good luck Mark!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Looking forward to our next Meetup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Mark&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Annati</member_name><member_id>9394912</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368733012000</updated><rating><average>4.57999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Web tech</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Boston-Amazon-Web-Services-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1367428</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Amazon Web Services Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>168</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365015915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Amazon Web Services Meetup Group</name><id>112500012</id><headcount>85</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368486000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Boston-Amazon-Web-Services-Meetup-Group/events/112500012/</event_url></item>