<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06320</zip><lat>41.354470</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>CT (860) 444-4624 </phone><name>Block Island Ferry Express</name><city>New London</city><id>1280342</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.095327</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt; Hi the round trip ticket is $43.00 for the day here is the websit to reserve your ticket. I moved up the trip from July because of the Music festival that is &amp;quot;Free to enjoy for all that visit the Island. We can meet at the ferry at 11:30 am in New London. and spend the day  on the Island Bring a picnic Lunch and we will do some wine tasting then go shopping or to the beach and hear some music. We will take the last ferry out at 7:50 pm that evening.                                   &lt;a href="https://www.goblockisland.com:444/bif/home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.goblockis...&lt;/a&gt; The Block Island Music Festival takes place the second week in June at Captain Nick’s Rock n’ Roll Bar (Block Island’s premiere nightclub and live music venue). This grassroots festival strives to push the envelope by erasing style barriers in order to create a truly unique and exciting musical atmosphere. The result is a six-day long musical gumbo where festival goers sample music performed by the most talented, “undiscovered” artists currently making music in the northeast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In accordance with the organic nature of The Block Island Music Festival, admission is FREE of charge. The festival is a 21+ years of age and proper identification is absolutely required.  Children will be admitted between the hours of 5pm-9pm ONLY under strict parental supervision.  To further our commitment to providing a unique experience- the music fest barbeque pit will provide FREE food to all festival goers starting at 5pm until supplies run out for the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each of the festival’s six days begins at 5pm outdoors on the Sunshine Stage. Four sets of music performed by solo artists and small acoustic ensembles provide the perfect ending to a day at the beach for visitors and locals alike. As the barbeque sizzles and the blender churns out frozen drinks, the audience slips easily into the mellow island atmosphere where flip flops and bikini tops constitute proper attire. As the sun sets on Block Island, the festival moves indoors to the Main Stage where four more bands perform through 1am.  By week’s end, the Block Island Music Festival has played host to 48 diverse musical acts.&lt;br /&gt;Saturday June 12:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:00pm-  Glenda Theuner &lt;br /&gt;6:00pm-  Shannon &amp;amp; Natalie &lt;br /&gt;7:00pm-  Harry Casper  &lt;br /&gt;8:00pm-  Steve &amp;quot;Lightnin&amp;quot; Lighty &lt;br /&gt;9:00pm-  Kagero &lt;br /&gt;10:00pm- VulGarrity &lt;br /&gt;11:00pm-  Stephanie White &lt;br /&gt;12:00am-  The Booze Beggars&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276406492000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274718262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"BLOCK ISLAND" Music Festival, Wine Tasting "EXTRAVAGANZA"</name><id>13578508</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276356600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/13578508/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/1/global_4236481.jpeg</photo_url></item>