<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>527  Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.344739</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BCA Theater</name><city>Boston</city><id>1181435</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070355</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How about a Saturday matinee (4pm) at the Black Box Theater at the Boston Center for the Arts in the South End, maybe followed by dinner.. I've bought 6 tix so hope 5 of you will join me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Looking forward, backward and sideways on his characters' lives, Alan Ayckbourn's latest play,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Life of Riley&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;, is a wry look at life, death and love. George Riley's closest friends have just discovered that he only has a few months to live, and that causes them to reflect and interpret the shocking news in their own way, with his final farewell affecting all of their futures. Ayckbourn is one of the world greatest living playwrights, and this is his 74th work, and the fourth which Zeitgeist has produced in the last four years. Don't miss this touching comic look at mortality and friendship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alan Ayckbourn is an Olivier and Tony Award winning English playwright who has written 77 plays, more than half of which have been produced in London's West End as well as around the world.As an acclaimed director, he has worked extensively in the West End and has also run his own company at the National Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the theater foyer at 3.30PM</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361674394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361113103000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Theater: Alan Ayckbourne's Life of Riley at 4pm</name><id>104999502</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361653200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/104999502/</event_url></item>