<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 French Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01505</zip><lat>42.359173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 508-869-0314 </phone><name>Tower Hill Botanical Gardens</name><city>Boylston</city><id>718941</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.727748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Camellia show runs Saturday, January 16 % Sunday, January 17 from 10am -5pm&lt;br /&gt;The cost of admission: $10.00 pr adult &lt;br /&gt;                                     (some discounts apply)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE MAGNIFICENT ORANGERIE&lt;br /&gt;New England's haven for Subtropical Plants&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Orangerie, an 18th century style greenhouse, provides a 4,000 square foot home to outstanding plants for winter display. A gallery with a northern exposure features ferns. The Orangerie is connected to the northeast end of the Stoddard Education and Visitors Center at a 90-degree angle. A growinghouse is attached to the eastern end of the Orangerie. This space is equipped with a &amp;quot;lift&amp;quot; to take plants to and from the pit greenhouse, a subterranean area where plants rest until the time is right to force them into growth. The pit house extends to the north. &lt;br /&gt;Lush foliage in the Orangerie &lt;br /&gt; Tower Hill's Orangerie Provides Your Year-Round Horticultural Experience &lt;br /&gt;Because the growing season is limited in New England, an Orangerie was incorporated as part of Tower Hill's Master Plan in 1986. The plants in this modern interpretation of an 18th century greenhouse provide the lush environment of an endless summer during the long, dormant winter months. A potting shed, growing house and pit house support this structure as a four-season growing space. Tower Hill Botanic Garden has become a year-round horticultural center for the education and enjoyment of their members and visiting public.&lt;br /&gt;Most of the plants chosen for the Orangerie are naturally winter-blooming or have outstanding features in the winter months. Large palms provide a canopy and are firmly anchored in beautifully handcrafted Versailles boxes. The middle layer of plants will include a selection of citrus trees. Among them are Meyer's Lemon (Citrus x meyeri 'Meyer'), Dancy Tangerine (Citrus reticulata 'Dancy'), Calamondin Orange (x Citrofortunella microcarpa) and Persian Lime (Citrus aurantiifolia). Currently, these trees are simultaneously in bud, bloom, and fruit, providing glorious fragrance.The understory is composed of an ever-changing, charming and colorful mix of flowering shrubs, perennials, annuals, and bulbs.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: This is just such a beautiful &amp;amp; peacefulo place to spend a Sunday afternoon. Leave the ice snow and cold weather for awhile and relax and enjoy!&lt;br /&gt;TWIG'S CAFE will be open (hrs. are 11am -3pm) if anyone is interested in lunch? &lt;br /&gt;reservations are recommended on days where there is an event in progress&lt;br /&gt;www.towerhillbg.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone interested?&lt;br /&gt;_Jo&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meetup inside the entrance to The Stoddard Education &amp; Visitors Center
(the main facility bldg) For those who may not know me, please look for the MEETUP LOGO</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203440998000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Anyone ready for Spring!</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199665932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camellia Show &amp; Orangerie at Peak Bloom @ Tower Hill Botanical Gardens</name><id>7048347</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203267600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7048347/</event_url></item>