<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The First Movie Night Event of 2011, Come visit the 360 State Street Screening Room, for a showing of:      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;13 Conversations About One Thing&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;  (2001 - Drama)     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0268690/" target="_blank"&gt;IMDB Description:&lt;/a&gt; The lives of a lawyer, an actuary, a housecleaner, a professor, and the people around them intersect as they ponder order and happiness in the face of life's cold unpredictability.     &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Alan Arkin, Matthew McConnaughey, Clea Duvall, Amy Irving, John Turturro     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AJ's Notes / Description:  One thing that seemed to come up often on the results of our Movie Night Survey (Thanks again to those whom participated and Lars for setting it up!) was films that may have been Art House, Foreign, and/or Off the Beaten Path.  This one was released in a few mainstream theaters, but at least from what I could see it was relegated to the Art Cinema's for the most part here in the US.  Roger Ebert gave it 4 Stars for a good reason though.  This is a movie that, though it may seem dreary throughout the story, manages to get it's point across and leave most viewers with just a shade of dark optimism that maybe one didn't begin with.  And personally I think this time of year I could use such an outlook and I doubt I'm alone.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I Set the time for 7pm, but we will not start showing the movie until shortly after 7:30. Don't plan to be any later than 7:30 though.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Important Notes:  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately I have to limit RSVP's to 18 for theater size. Please only respond Yes if you're sure you can make it.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're Coming, &lt;i&gt;I will need your full names&lt;/i&gt; if I don't already have (or remember) them &lt;i&gt;for the Concierge to let you in&lt;/i&gt;, and you may be asked for ID. Please either put your name in your RSVP or e-mail it to me. (If you live in the building just let me know that instead.)   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Other Notes:&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged! In the past we've ended up with quite the snack spread, so feel free to post if you're intending on bringing things and wish to coordinate.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are instructions near the call box and a bell button on it if the door is locked.  If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call AJ at 315-345-9348.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 7 pm (Adjusted-Confirmed with City.). If you don't mind a longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evenings (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street Starting at 4:30 or 5). 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only at $5 Daily Max from 5pm on Friday through Sunday, the entrance is on State street just to the right of the buildings main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The concierge should be able to let you in and direct you, make note of the directions near the call box. I will also try to post signs. My Cell if you have problems is 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1295129504000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294287937000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie:  "13 Conversations About One Thing"</name><id>15939356</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295049600000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15939356/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/f/c/global_20631836.jpeg</photo_url></item>