<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention: Actual screening time to be posted the week of the movie. Kendall evening screenings typically start around 7 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruno Dumont is one of the most divisive and controversial young directors out there. Traditional elements such as plot, dialogue and action don?t usually play a central role in his movies; the emphasis is rather on a naturalistic, visceral approach to observing ordinary people in mundane situations. There is usually a fair amount of nudity, violence and sex in his work, but they are not covered with layers of stylization as is the case with most other movies. They?re very blunt and they hit you straight in the face. There?s no buffer zone, which makes the experience more intense, disturbing, but possibly also very enriching and poetic. In fact a close-up on a man?s neck in a Dumont movie is about a hundred times more unsettling than all the carnage in all Tarantino?s movies combined :) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Here?s the movie synopsis:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dumont focuses on contemporary French culture beyond Paris. He bookends brutal experiences in an unnamed desert war with scenes of life among late teens outside of urban niceties? the population that fights our wars. André Demester and Barbe are neighbors and lovers. They part when he leaves to be a soldier in a far-off land. Can their attraction survive the barbarity of war?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be hosted by Jihad, who will be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater after the show. Then, we'll head off to a nearby restaurant for food and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sensesofcinema.com/contents/01/19/dumont_bodies.html" target="_blank"&gt;Article about Dumont's Movies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185231812000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184030197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flandres - Bruno Dumont's latest Movie</name><id>5998624</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185058800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5998624/</event_url></item>