<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hiking in Baxter State Park is unlike most of the hiking in the whites. Due to its location and geology its a lot different than the whites,its a lot closer to the hiking in the ADK's&amp;nbsp;The treeline is lower and its location in the Maine wilderness surrounded by lakes and not a lot of civilization make for great views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are comfortable on the more challenging hikes in the whites, like Caps ridge, Ammonosuc Ravine, Flume Slide, Wildcat D from Pinkham, Kings Ravine, and walking up over and around boulders, the trails on the east side of Katahdin will be a good fit for your abilities. Given the variable weather on Katahdin the two nights at the Park will allow the option of hiking either Saturday or Sunday. For those who drive up Thursday evening, they also have the option of hiking Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do note that I have confirmed reservations for one group site that holds 14 with 3 of those spaces currently reserved, so if you are accepted to the trip, you have a spot in the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Your experience level&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have hiked trails like Amonusuc Ravine, Caps Ridge, Flume Slide, the tripyramids slides, wildcat D from Pinkham, Kings Ravine in the whites, or many of the trails in the Adirondacks, then you are "ready" for Katahdin. Although not technical climbing, the trails do tend to have a lot more exposure than the whites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Hikes&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not booking a specific hike on a specific day. Although I would like that people hike together, there will be no formal group hike scheduled. As the event gets&amp;nbsp;closer&amp;nbsp;those attending will be in touch to decide what the interest level is. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Options are&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Helon Taylor to Knifes Edge to the summit and then down, either Saddle or Hamlin Ridge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cathedral to Summit then Knifes Edge (with an alternative down Saddle&amp;nbsp;or Hamlin in case of weather or experience issues).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those in excellent condition it is possible, but not advisable to climb all of the mountains on the New England 4 K list and also the 100 highest list in one weekend,&amp;nbsp;although&amp;nbsp;I plan to be backpacking in backcountry area north of the mountain after this weekend event so count me out :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baxter does have requirements for the minimum equipment allowed to climb the mountain, it is similiar to the hike safe requirements for NH. If you arent carrying the gear they recommend you are probably way over your ability level. I do&amp;nbsp;recomend picking up a Baxter state trails map, which is availlable just before the park gate at the visitors center or at the headquarters in Millinocket.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baxter State Park is primitive and has&amp;nbsp;many rules intended to keep&amp;nbsp;it looking and feeling wild.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No pets are allowed in the park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group site has no shelters so you must bring a tent (no campers allowed)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No motorcycles in the park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group site has a picnic table, places for tents and an outhouse. There is no running water or electricity or trash receptacles. The closest store is about a 1 hour drive one way out of the park. There is no cell phone coverage in most&amp;nbsp;of the park.&amp;nbsp;Most automotive GPS systems do not have the park roads in their database. Electronic devices are not allowed to be used in the park, which is enforced as no radios or cell phones in use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Portland Maine, Millinocket is about 3 hours via I 95. The trip into Roaring Brook is at least 1 hour from Millinocket. The roads in the park are rough but passable. I have driven a Honda civic and other compact cars in the park on the&amp;nbsp;roads with no&amp;nbsp;issues as long as I drive slow, although if there is anything loose hanging under the car&amp;nbsp;it may not be there when you leave. The speed limit on most roads are 25 and with most&amp;nbsp;cars, you wouldnt want to go much more than 25.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The park gate closes at&amp;nbsp;8:30 PM (NOTE THIS IS A NEW TIME, I HAD&amp;nbsp;PREVIOUSLY LISTED&amp;nbsp;6 PM)&amp;nbsp;therefore for most people, you will need to take Friday afternoon off and drive up during the day. There is great short day hike at Roaring Brook to South Turner Mtn if you get there before 3 PM. If you plan on a long hike on Friday, you will need to drive up Thursday evening. There are lots of options for motels and campgrounds outside the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Sign Up&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be wait listing the sign up, if you are interested in attending sign up and after reviewing the answers to the questions, I will be in touch. My intent is to figure out the interest and get firm commitments from everyone by then end of March. Baxter is very strict about reservations, once the group site reaches capacity of 14 they will not let anyone else in, so if a guest is coming with you, you need to make that known when you sign up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Costs&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do not intend to make a profit on this event. Dependent on the number of people attending, the costs will vary. Plan on $10 per night each person and once the sign ups are closed I will advise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every car with other than Maine license&amp;nbsp;plates will have to pay&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;"road fee"&amp;nbsp;at the&amp;nbsp;park gate, its around&amp;nbsp;$12&amp;nbsp;in addition to the&amp;nbsp;share&amp;nbsp;of the group site fee.&amp;nbsp;I will be driving&amp;nbsp;over from Gorham NH and will be backpacking after the trip so I&amp;nbsp;am not available to give rides. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Baxter State Park Bear Brook Group sites (adjacent to Roaring Brook)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis P</member_name><member_id>8579894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1314629640000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Hiking at BSP the weekend before Labor day. This may be alternative for those who want to hike Katahdin that are booked on labor day weekend and unable to attend the 4 season meetup up on Labor day weekend.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297604022000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Baxter State Park - Aug 26th 27th - Roaring Brook Group Campsite</name><id>16547553</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314356400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/16547553/</event_url></item>