<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>71 Avenue A, </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01376</zip><lat>42.608547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 863-2281 </phone><name>Shea Theater </name><city>Turners Falls</city><id>1238462</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.556431</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Hi Everyone, our friend Shawna has graciously researched the following play for us to see. If you plan on going please sign up early. Later this week I will be setting up a Paypal link so all payments can be made online. Based on payments I will reserve tickets so we can sit together. Thanks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Details&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arena Civic Theater presents To Kill a Mockingbird, Christopher Sergei's beautifully crafted adaptation of Harper Lee's Pulitzer Prize-winning novel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Production dates are Fridays and Saturdays, April 23, 24, 30 and May 1 at 8:00 p.m., and Sundays, April 25 and May 2 at 2 p.m. at the Shea Theater, Turners Falls, Mass. Following the matinee on April 15, Northampton Attorney William Newman of the ACLU will lead a talk-back with the actors and audience. Set in Macomb, Alabama, in 1935, the play features Alan Maynard (Greenfield) as Atticus, the lawyer faced with the daunting task of defending Tom Robinson, a black man accused of raping a white woman. Tom is played by Floyd Patterson II (Springfield). Emma Henderson (Southampton) and John McPhee (Amherst) portray Scout and Jem, Atticus' children, who learn some difficult and important lessons on understanding those who are different. Miss Maudie, played by Kay Lyons (Greenfield), assumes the role of narrator and commentator on life in Macomb County. Supporting roles include: Henry Hirschfeld (Shutesbury) as Dill, Halina Kusleika (Easthampton) and Jeff Hanson (Greenfield) as Mayella and Bob Ewell, Frank Lattuca (Amherst) as the prosecuting attorney, Kip Fonsh (Amherst) as Sheriff Tate, Penney Roberts (Northfield) and Susan Stark (Shelburne Falls) as Miss Stephanie and Mrs. DuBose. The role of Rev. Sykes will be played by Moonlight Davis (Erving). Also appearing are Jerry Marcano (Orange) as Boo Radley, John Darrow (Southampton) as the Judge, and Michael Motisi (Greenfield) as Cunningham. To Kill a Mockingbird is directed by Sondra Radosh (Amherst). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Production staff also includes Robert Freedman (Northampton), assistant director; Dave Stawasz (Holyoke), set design; Rachel Roy (Montague), lighting design; Karen Hinds (Florence), costume design; Carl Erikson (Amherst) and Jackie Walsh (Shelburne Falls), stage managers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket prices for To Kill a Mockingbird are $13 for adults, $11 for seniors and students, and $8 for children ages 12 and under. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shawna</member_name><member_id>10937608</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272310757000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270600002000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social: To Kill A Mockingbird</name><id>13108311</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272067200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/13108311/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/c/b/global_14194811.jpeg</photo_url></item>