<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>NH Route 113</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.762356</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rattlesnake Trailhead</name><city>Holderness</city><id>4510892</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.559120</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is for hikers aged 50-70+ (most of us are 55-65)  who haven't given up on their love of hiking and being in nature despite their age or level of physical conditioning. We hike at a pace 50% slower than the AMC Trailguide book time. Hike ratings: easy, moderate, strenuous,very strenuous.We start as a group,we hike as a group and we end as a group. There are three other hiking Meetup groups if you want a faster pace or more challenging hikes (The New England Hiking Meetup, 4 Seasons Hiking Group, New England Over 40 Hiking Group). The hiking Meetup group, (Fellowship Of The Tortoise) does easier,slower paced hikes than  this group.  Our goal is to stay fit while enjoying the camaraderie of hikers who have similar skills and goals.If you click on the PAGES button on the home page,there is a Winter Hiking Gear List. This is a dog free hiking group.Everybody must join the group and have a picture to be on a hike.If you are camera shy,print out a picture of yourself and give it to me at the trailhead.The picture is to show Fish and Game if you get separated from the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead: Take I93 North to Exit 24,take US3 to Holderness,make a left onto NH113 for 5.6 miles,Old Bridal Path parking lot on right (opposite parking lot on left side of road). We will hike the Morgan Trail to the summit of Morgan (2,220'),the Crawford-Ridgepole Trail to the summit of Percival (2,212') and the Percival Trail back to the cars. Beautiful views of Squam Lake.5.1 miles round trip,1,550' elevation gain,AMC book time 3.5, 5.0 hours estimated time for our group.----Steve----                                                                                                                                       Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue/Gray Chevy pick up truck NH2646423</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve A</member_name><member_id>6009756</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353250363000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1413769</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>New England Over 50 Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351639718000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MODERATE HIKE--MORGAN &amp; PERCIVAL MOUNTAINS</name><id>89245152</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353160800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group/events/89245152/</event_url></item>