<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Over the past year we have explored questions about faith, religion, purpose to life, what happens to us after we die, love, relationships, sex, and the missing piece. Dr. Nicholas Ribush, Kurukulla Center Founder, President and a former Tibetan Buddhist Monk, will teach us about the core beliefs of Buddhism and gives his religion’s perspective on the questions we have explored.  Venerable Geshe Tenley, a Tibetan Buddhist Monk born in Tibet and visiting from India will also be there.  Venerable Tenley has attained the highest degree within Buddhism.  However, he speaks very little English so Dr. Ribush will be leading the discussion and tour of the center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Dr. Nicholas Ribush (from the Kurukulla Center website) &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Nicholas Ribush received his medical degree from Melbourne University, Australia, in 1964. He first encountered Buddhism at Kopan Monastery, Nepal, in 1972, since when he has been a student of (the late) Lama Thubten Yeshe and Lama Zopa Rinpoche and a full time worker for the Foundation for the Preservation of the Mahayana Tradition (FPMT). He served on the FPMT board from its inception in 1983 to 2002. He was a monk in the Tibetan tradition from 1974 to 1986; established FPMT archiving and publishing activities at Kopan in 1973; and with Lama Yeshe founded Wisdom Publications in 1975.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between 1981 and 1996 he served variously as Wisdom's director, editorial director and director of development. In 1996 he founded the Lama Yeshe Wisdom Archive (www.lamayeshe.com), which he still directs. He founded Kurukulla Center in 1989, was center director for the next four years, and is currently director of Kurukulla Center once more. He lives with his wife Wendy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having given up a career in medicine to dedicate his life to an even more meaningful path, Nick imparts with great clarity and humor the wisdom of the Buddha's teachings. He has changed the course of many people's lives through his talk  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Venerable Geshe Tenley (from the Kurukulla Center website) &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Geshe Ngawang Tenley, born in 1969 as a nomad in Kham, Tibet escaped to India in 1989 to become a monk under the guidance of his uncle Geshe Tsulga. He was ordained by the late Gyume Khensur Geshe Urgyen Tseten Rinpoche in 1990 and began the program of studies to become a geshe at Sera Je Monastery. During the course of his studies, he has received many teachings from His Holiness the Dalai Lama as well as other highly qualified masters. In 1998, he received his full ordination (gelong) vows from His Holiness, and in November 2008, after eighteen years of rigorous studies, he completed his final exams to be conferred the geshe degree at Sera Je Monastery. In addition to serving as Geshe Tsulga's attendant at Kurukulla Center, Geshe Tenley also shares his knowledge and insights with the community through his teachings. His cheerfulness and humility endear him to everyone he meets.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259009589000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247205210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exploring Life's Deepest Questions with a Buddhist Monk</name><id>10844907</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258761600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/10844907/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/6/global_9579590.jpeg</photo_url></item>