<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Prospect St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366177</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-1253</phone><name>ImprovBoston</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>716773</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103333</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Geek Week has returned to Improv Boston, starting April 28 and lasting through May 2. I will be performing on opening night and invite you all to come see me perform in Science Fiction Novel and Dingopoly. My show is at 7:30 p.m. in the Studio of the theatre. Tickets are $10 each or $7 for students.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After my show, we can either catch another act (Red Alert! and FutureProv at 9 p.m. and/or Talk Nerdy to Me at 10 p.m.) or grab a bite to eat. At 11:30 p.m., there is a show called Deep Dish featuring improvisors from Improv Boston, Improv Asylum and Second City (Chicago) for a mere $5.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can communicate via email. You will be responsible for getting your own ticket either online or the night of the show. I can meet you in the lobby between 7 and 7:15 but then have to get ready. So if I don't see you before 7:15, I will meet up with all of you in the lobby after the show. I will provide my phone number to those who sign up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you cannot make it this night, be sure to partake of the various other shows throughout the week, including: The Dowry and Ethan; LOST - Blowing the Hatch; The Complete Works of Batman and Twitterprov:  Twitterprov, Red Alert and Continuum; Mythical Newsroom and Ninja Sex Party; Maximum Power and Swartzlander; Dungeon Master Guide and Epic Adventure; Lumber Knight and Benjamin Franklin: Dinosaur Hunter and many, many more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the website at: &lt;a href="http://www.improvboston.com/shows/geekweek.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.improvbost...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in lobby between 7 and 7:15. After that, just go into Studio and we'll meet after</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Giovanni</member_name><member_id>2402708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272669973000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271868603000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Geek Week Comedy Show</name><id>13248659</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272496500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13248659/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>