<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>ACROSS STREET from 261 Union St. (Crepes Tea House), Ground Floor; Park &amp; enter on the opposite side of the st. from Tea House</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.099113</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>A to Z Moving Company</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>698661</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.617401</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;FOR THIS OPEN MEN'S GROUP - We're going down a rabbit hole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/a/8/event_183869352.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;What gets you pissed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you ready to look at it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you tired of dealing with the consequences of your anger in the world?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Are you ready to commit to something else, and get some perspective on what's driving you? That's what we're going to do at this Open Men's Group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our whole night will be spent getting clear about what sets us off, takes us out, or lights us up ... in that old familiar way. And we're going to DO something about it - so we can take a new skill or two home for a test-drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anger is an emotion that men are both &lt;strong&gt;ENCOURAGED to express&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;EXPECTED to repress - at the SAME TIME.&lt;/strong&gt; It's the stuff of most of the good plot twists in the movies and shows we watch, it's the fuel that keeps many of us going some days. Yet when was the last time someone sat down with you to TALK ABOUT anger - how it shows up in you, how you express it, what's going on underneath it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you paying a price for how pissed you are - in your relationships, in your health, in your job?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you so cut off from your anger that people are "walking all over you?" Are you ready to find a healthy way to lay down some boundaries?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;This Open Men's Group will be a place to connect, share, and TRANSFORM our views about anger. Join us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Springfield Uprising Men's Group is holding an Open Men's Group from 6:30 until 9:00 pm in West Springfield, MA. &lt;strong&gt;Please bring these directions with you!&lt;/strong&gt; Many men have not found the place easily. The group meets in the ground floor of the A to Z Moving building (owned by a member of the group), which is [b]directly across the street[/b] from 261 Union Street, which is "Crepes Tea House". Park on the opposite side of the street from the Tea house, and in between Charlie's Diner (50's style silver and red diner) and A to Z Moving (there will probably be other men's cars in this parking lot; parking lot has a large white trailer in it).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entrance door to the A to Z Moving building is at the front (Northeast) corner of the building near the street. The door will have a white flag and sign on it. A Garmin GPS unit correctly got to the 261 Union Street address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park across street from Crepe's Tea House (261 Union Street), &amp; between Charlie's Diner and A to Z Movers. --Identify A to Z moving building (3 stories) by AtoZ Moving Trucks &amp; Sign. Entrance is on the ground floor, front (NE) corner of the building.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boysen </member_name><member_id>7527796</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354807445000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Men</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>openmen</urlname><id>1200732</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5500030518</group_lon><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354236434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Men's Group - F*ck You. Yeah, you heard me. A Night about MALE ANGER.</name><id>thsfnyqqbhb</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354750200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/events/93409402/</event_url></item>