<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Did someone say Breakfast?!?  It's been awhile since we have dined out for Breakfast (and it's a rarity on a Sunday since we usually go to Brunch on Sundays) so let's start off the month of August with a Sunday Breakfast.  If the weather is nice it will be agreat way for you to fill up before enjoying the summer sun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be dining at the Hearth'n Kettle in Weymouth, which is located on Route 18 just a short distance from Route 3.  They have a nice fireplace, a comfortable atmosphere and great food at reasonable prices.  Join the SSDOMG Members and their Guests for a Summer Sunday Breakfast! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summer Sunday Breakfast!&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, August 2nd @ 9:30am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hearth'n Kettle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;151 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Route 18&lt;br /&gt;Weymouth, MA 02188&lt;br /&gt;781-337-7007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hearthnkettle.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hearthnket...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting Place:&lt;/b&gt; Please meet outside the Front Door or in the Lobby if it's rainy.  If you arrive after we have been seated please tell the hostess you are with &amp;quot;Angela&amp;quot; and meet us at the table.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Angela &amp;amp; Jeanne &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; At least 6 Yes RSVP's by Noon on Thursday, July 30th.  There is currently no maximum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; One per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members and their Guest - Free, Group Members and all Other Guests - $2pp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Breakfast items range from $5.79 - $10.99. Side items, which cost less, are also available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps us to keep things simple for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Saturday, August 1st @ 11am ~ Anyone who changes from a Yes to No after this time will be considered a No-Show.  Anyone who is a Yes at this time who does not attend the event will be considered a No-Show.  For full details on our No-Show Policy please go to the About page. ~ If there are less than 5 Yes RSVP's within 3-4 hours (thereafter) the RSVP Deadline this event will be cancelled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview: Located on route 18 across from Building 19, McDonald's and the Hilltop Butcher, just south of the intersection of Route 53 (w/ CVS), just north of Dairy Queen and Route 3.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 18 towards Route 18 North.  Go straight thru the 1st light keeping Dairy Queen on your right.  Once you get to the top of the hill (less than 1/4 mi from the light), Hearth'n Kettle will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 53: At the intersection of Route 18, get on route 18 South and H'n K is about 1/2 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the Front Door or in the Lobby if it's rainy.  The reservation is under "Angela."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251414631000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248020034000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Sunday Breakfast!</name><id>10909035</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249219800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10909035/</event_url></item>