<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A fantastic opportunity to make some serious money with very little money down will be discussed on January 30th at 9:00pm. A little late I know, but WELL worth it.&lt;br /&gt;Our Speaker Blue-Moon Capital, will tell us how they offer Turn Key Investment opportunities to smaller investors like us (as opposed to D. Trump types).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will explain that for as little as $5000 Down, you can experience tremendous returns with their proven methods of turn-key rental Investment properties. No need to rehab, and management is taken care of.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In fact Metro West Investors is so blown away by this program, that we will offer to partner up with our members and put up the down-payment. How's that for confidence?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That means for you- No Money Down!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation you will hear how this will work. However, even if you don't want to partner with us, it really is a great way to invest in emerging markets for very little risk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow this link to register for the event:&lt;br /&gt;Remember you &lt;u&gt;MUST&lt;/u&gt; put &lt;b&gt;Metro West Investors&lt;/b&gt; as your representative/referral when registering&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow this link to register: &lt;a href="https://www1.gotomeeting.com/register/873756875" target="_blank"&gt;https://www1.gotomeet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Do NOT go to the Crowne Plaza - This seminar is a "Webinar"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Garian</member_name><member_id>2553452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202937755000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>This is a tremendous opportunity to make money in Real Estate. We will partner with you too!</why><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>InvestMetroWest</urlname><id>214680</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Metro West Investors - Boston area Real Estate Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198717856000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Low Money down Investment Webinar. Amazing Opportunity!!</name><id>6973333</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201744800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InvestMetroWest/events/6973333/</event_url></item>