<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;&lt;center&gt;SEPTEMBER 26, 1928: NEWSFLASH&lt;br /&gt;Coppone Released from Prison&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Chicago gang leader Harold &amp;quot;Hal&amp;quot; Coppone was released today from Awsume State Penitentiary near Philadelphia after serving a six-month term.  Coppone, who was jailed for carrying an unlicensed weapon, was met by a group of his men--among them was a Chicago gangster Joey &amp;quot;The Rattlesnake&amp;quot; Ratello, chief suspect in the recent killing of Marco &amp;quot;Machete&amp;quot; Molino--and departed quickly in a powerful seven-passenger Lincoln Touring car.  While he had nothing to say to the press, Coppone and his men were undoubtedly headed back to Chicago where, it is rumored, they have more than one score to settle.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;If youse want to learn da secret of &amp;quot;Hal&amp;quot; Coppone's whereabouts, &lt;br /&gt;then be in da &amp;quot;Back Room&amp;quot; at S.P. Keasy's Place, &lt;br /&gt;but don't tell nobody!  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Actually, youse is really invited ta da home of Liv and David &lt;br /&gt;on Friday, February 22nd at da hour of 7:30.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Youse best be prepared for a tale of &lt;br /&gt;blackmail, sex, larceny, deceit, and murder.  &lt;br /&gt;I also promise youse a fair deal of high jinks such as &lt;br /&gt;shady dealings, sordid affairs, and deceptive conduct.  &lt;br /&gt;But, be prepared to have such a good time that it should be criminal!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who RSVP to this event, I will send you information on your character--costumes requested--and information on a dish to bring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**This event has a very strict number of attendees.  There will be no &amp;quot;maybes&amp;quot; allowed and no tag-ons.  The game is limited to 8 players.  Because of the small number, this event did not have a mass Meetup e-mail sent and would require that you visit the webpage.  Should this event go well, there are companies that can customize murder mystery games for large groups and we may purchase one for a regular-sized Meetup.  So, if you didn't get in on this one in time, don't worry, there will be another one.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**There are two cats in the house that will be locked up during the evening.**&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203899910000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202834817000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Murder Mystery Dinner</name><id>7316948</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203726600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/7316948/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/c/a/global_3210458.jpeg</photo_url></item>