<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Allison St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.191335</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>223-0335</phone><name>Liberty Books</name><city>Concord</city><id>682917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.538397</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We have started up a monthly video screening &lt;b&gt;in Concord - on the 3rd Tuesday of every month&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have screenings every Tuesday somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: 1st Tuesday-Nashua; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; &lt;b&gt;3rd Tuesday-Concord&lt;/b&gt;; 4th Tuesday-Northerly (hopefully Plymouth - maybe Campton). If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, maybe we'll have a Truth Party somewhere!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have a discussion after the video regarding what we can do, including how each person can become more involved in this group and spread the workload of running a meetup like this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive at 6:30 if you can&lt;/b&gt;, in order to help set up and enjoy the pre-meeting conversations. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and then on to the video showing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS WEEK:    &lt;b&gt;Zeitgeist!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[from German: : &lt;i&gt;the general intellectual, moral, and cultural climate of an era&lt;/i&gt;]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zeitgeist took the internet by storm a little over a year ago - it caused quite a sensation and considerable controversy - WARNING: it is critical of modern religion (Christianity &amp;amp; others), so if that would offend you, proceed with caution - but, we do encourage you to proceed. With the sequel coming up in the Fall, we thought it would be a good time to review the original, or see it for the first time if you haven't already.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;i&gt;From &lt;a href="http://www.zeitgeistmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;the website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zeitgeist, produced by Peter Joseph, was created as a nonprofit expression to inspire people to start looking at the world from a more critical perspective and to understand that very often things are not what the population at large think they are. The information in Zeitgeist was established over a year long period of research and the current Source page on this site lists the basic sources used / referenced and the developing Interactive Transcript includes exact source references and further information. A Q &amp;amp; A page is also being developed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, it's important to point out that there is a tendency to simply disbelieve things that are counter to our understanding, without the necessary research performed. For example, some information contained in Part 1 and Part 3, specifically, is not obtained by simple keyword searches on the Internet. You have to dig deeper. For instance, very often people who look up &amp;quot;Horus&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;The Federal Reserve&amp;quot; on the Internet draw their conclusions from very general or biased sources. Online encyclopedias or text book Encyclopedias often do not contain the information contained in Zeitgeist. However, if one takes the time to read the sources provided, they will find that what is being presented is based on documented evidence. Non-Profit DVDs / Free Video Downloads are available through the Downloads page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Furthermore, in October 2008 the sequel to Zeitgeist will be presented for free online. This feature length work will address the solutions to the problems presented in the original work. This work is entitled: &amp;quot;Zeitgeist - Addendum&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That being said, It is my hope that people will not take what is said in the film as the truth, but find out for themselves, for truth is not told, it is realized. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth has set up a &lt;a href="http://mv911t.erideshare.com" target="_blank"&gt;carpooling group online at eRideShare.com&lt;/a&gt;. Carpooling arrangements can now be made by clicking on the link above to go to the online ridesharing group. It may take a little getting used to, but now that gas has gone over $4.00, it gets more interesting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you have to do is set up an individual username &amp;amp; password on eRideShare.com. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. Once you've figured out how the system works, just bookmark &lt;a href="http://mv911t.erideshare.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://mv911t.eridesh...&lt;/a&gt; and remember the password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. Then you can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, donations for the ride-sharing are always appreciated to cover gas costs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... and, contributions to the MV911T general fund help us pay for the Meetup site and for new materials for your viewing pleasure.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the meeting room in the back of the store.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy</member_name><member_id>3581956</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216334449000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214684330000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concord monthly video - Zeitgeist!</name><id>8235648</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216161000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/8235648/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/4/2/global_4736626.jpeg</photo_url></item>