<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Howe St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.311234</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kasbah Garden Cafe</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1011293</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.933937</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/d/3/event_36324531.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Want an Indiana Jones experience? well, read on...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;The Kasbah is a genuine Middle Eastern / Moroccan Restaurant .&amp;nbsp; It has good food and is reasonably priced, but its main draw is its unique garden atmosphere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Nestled in a little courtyard between houses and apartment buildings, this restaurant has outdoor seating in a beautiful and peaceful garden, shaded from the sun and insulated from the noise of the city.The indoor seating is still quite pleasant with Moroccan decor and has a few covered outdoor tables for rainy weather.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;The food is simple but good, middle eastern food with a Moroccan bent to it.&amp;nbsp; They have good vegetarian options as well as good desserts teas, coffees and especially home made Baklava.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;We are going there for a fabulous buffet dinner, created especially for us, and an entertaining belly dancing show! And all for the amazing price of $28.00&amp;nbsp;that includes both the show and the dinner entrees and desserts!!! BTW...if you are interested, you can partake in the Middle Eastern tradition of smoking Hookahs. Smoking Hookahs are at an additional charge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;They do not serve alcohol, but you are more than welcome to bring your own. Bring wine, beer, etc to complement your meal. The delicious food is reportedly a diverse Moroccan sampling of flavor for the senses, catering to both meat lovers and vegetarians. Mmmm...sounds terrific, doesn't it???&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;The outdoor location itself is worth the drive, but in case the weather does not comply, there is ample seating indoors. So come on out and join us...we welcome you and it will be worth the drive. Feed the adventure in your soul!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;You can pay the night of the event, but please, when you RSVP do it responsibly. In other words,&amp;nbsp;if you say yes, please show up. The venue is depending upon our numbers to&amp;nbsp;create this buffet, and show,for us.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Terri, Chuck,  or the Meetup sign...cell is 203-808-5829</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chuck</member_name><member_id>11483387</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310598175000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306443862000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join Us For A True Indie Experience @ The Kasbah Garden Cafe!!!</name><id>19864241</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310252400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/19864241/</event_url></item>