<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Beacon Hill</address_2><address_1>46 Joy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.359997</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 742-5415</phone><name>The African Meeting House on Smith Court at Museum of African American History</name><city>Boston</city><id>1400447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065239</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Here's your chance to get some exercise while learning and it's FREE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;If you want to be included in the lunch after the tour, you MUST RSVP &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/58391322/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bringing awareness of the African &amp;#8232;American &amp;nbsp;role during the Civil War period has been a passion of mine. I do this as a Civil War era re-enactor with the 54th Massachusetts Volunteer Regiment Company A and Colored Ladies Christian Relief Society. As such, I've had the pleasure and privilege of working with the Park Rangers, who will lead this interactive and enlightening tour. Bring your family and friends along on this special journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHAT: The Mothers of Freedom: An Historic Walk through 19th Century Beacon Hill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHEN: Saturday March 31, 2012 from Noon until 1 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHERE: Tour will start and end at the African Meeting House on Smith Court, just off 46 Joy Street, Boston, MA 02114, on Beacon Hill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DETAILS: Join rangers from Boston African American National Historic Site on this FREE Beacon Hill walking tour that highlights the vital role of African American women and their allies in the struggle for social justice and equality in the years preceding the Civil War. The tour will examine the critical role that these women played working on the Underground Railroad and in the Abolition Movement, and highlight their contributions to education and community and social services. Tour will begin and end in front of the African Meeting House on Smith Court on Beacon Hill. This 60 minute tour is free and open to the public on a first-come, first-served basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please call (617) 742-5415 for more information or visit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/boaf/index.htm"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/boaf/index.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on The Museum of African American History click on this link,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.afroammuseum.org/site14.htm"&gt;http://www.afroammuseum.org/site14.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333285361000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331980232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Be Tourists in Our City</name><id>56709692</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333208700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/56709692/</event_url></item>