<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lift Ticket Roll Back ~~ Ski all day for only $9 !!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/1/2/event_75825842.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We've gone the past two years and had a blast.  The tickets are almost free! And the mountain isn't very crowded because it's a weekday.  Let's ride up together.  It saves energy and it's much more fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool:&lt;/strong&gt; 7:30 am Dover Park &amp;amp; Ride - Spaulding Tpk to Exit 9. Left @ light. Then left again @ 2nd light.  Pull straight in and congregate in the rear by the fence.  Don't forget to share expenses with your driver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cranmore is a quick drive - about 1.5 hrs from Dover - in downtown North Conway.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release -&lt;/strong&gt; AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup including travel to and from. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357342885000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352750453000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ski Cranmore for only $9!</name><id>91094992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357302600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/91094992/</event_url></item>