<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0088178/" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;quot;Stop Making Sense&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; is a rockumentary about the 1980's rock band The Talking Heads. This is playing the air conditioned,  big room of the Somerville Theater. Tickets are $8.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 6:00pm, we are going to meet for dinner at the Tibetan restaurant &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=233A+Elm+Street%2C+Somerville%2C+MA%2C+02144" target="_blank"&gt;Marsta on Elm&lt;/a&gt;, located at 233 Elm Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner is not required. You can just meet us at the theater if dinner is not for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you will be joining us for dinner, please indicate so in the RSVP notes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ShaneO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+++++++++++++++&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Summary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Byrne walks onto the stage and does a solo &amp;quot;Psycho Killer.&amp;quot; Jerry Harrison, Tina Weymouth and Chris Frantz join him for two more songs. The crew is busy, still setting up. Then, three more musicians and two back-up singers join the band. Everybody sings, plays, harmonizes, dances, and runs. They change instruments and clothes. Bryne appears in the Big Suit. The backdrop is often black, but sometimes it displays words, images, or children's drawings. The band cooks for 18 songs, the lyrics are clear, the house rocks. In this concert film, the Talking Heads hardly talk, don't stop, and always make sense.  Written by  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be standing up against the colum that is to the left of the ticker taker. I'll be wearing a crimson colored Harvard baseball cap. I'll wait until 7:43 then you are on your own. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ShaneO</member_name><member_id>8134848</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825861000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276575144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Stop Making Sense" Talking Heads</name><id>13804413</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279237500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/13804413/</event_url></item>