<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Abigail Adams Room</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England R&amp;D Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1085070</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Joining us for this meeting is a very special guest from DotNetNule Corporation - Rob Chartier, Vice President of Engineering and Support.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.dnnboston.org/Portals/38/chartier.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join Rob for an open discussion on &amp;quot;DotNetNuke - A look inside&amp;quot;.  He will cover topics like how DotNetNuke is adopting the Agile methodologies at a corporate level, how they are best utilizing Scrum, a sneak peek at the roadmap for 2010, and how YOU can participate with the future direction of the product.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Chartier has developed IT solutions for more than 15 years with a diverse background in both software and hardware development. He is internationally recognized as an innovative thinker and leading IT architect with frequent speaking engagements showcasing his expertise. He's been an integral part of many open forums on cutting-edge technology, including the .NET Framework and Distributed Computing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He uses expertise with many Microsoft technologies, including .NET, and a strong background in Oracle, BEA Systems, Inc.'s BEA WebLogic, IBM, Java 2 Platform Enterprise Edition (J2EE), and similar technologies to support his award-winning writing. He frequently publishes to many of the leading developer and industry support Web sites and publications. He has a bachelor's degree in Computer Information Systems. He has been awarded the Microsoft MVP status in Asp/ASP.NET for the past 6 years and has been a member of the AspInsiders since its inception.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is sponsored by Red Gate Software. &lt;a href="http://www.red-gate.com/?utm_source=ug&amp;amp;utm_medium=uglogo&amp;amp;utm_content=dnnboston&amp;amp;utm_campaign=redgate" target="_blank"&gt;Red Gate Software makes ingeniously simple tools for over 500,000 Microsoft technology professionals working with SQL Server, .NET, and Exchange&lt;/a&gt;.  The company’s product line includes tools for comparing, synchronizing, backing up and recovering SQL Server databases; understanding and fixing .NET code problems; and email archiving for Exchange.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Swanzey</member_name><member_id>2473211</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274197613000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>DotNetNuke Users</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>DNNBoston</urlname><id>1372592</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>DotNetNuke Boston Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269429093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DotNetNuke Boston User Group</name><id>twtgnynhbwb</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274135400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/DNNBoston/events/12977084/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/8/global_11887848.jpeg</photo_url></item>