<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>***Note: There will be some parking issues for this Meetup.  It was just posted that our neighborhood from October 1 to November 1 will be resident parking only.  So, this will cause problems for our out-of-town members.  If anyone not in Salem or in an area of Salem not affected by parking would like to host this night, please let me know.  Otherwise, we are a 10-minute walk from the Salem Commuter Rail.  Anyone that knows they will have an issue with parking, please e-mail me at olivia.radue@gmail.com.  Hopefully we can set up a rideshare with other members.  Or, if everyone is willing to meet at one place where people can park (grocery parking lot, etc), then David or I can go pick up a carload.  Again, please let me know if parking will be an issue.  Also, let me know if you are a Salem resident willing to rideshare.  Thanks.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I decided to try a weeknight game night to try to appeal to some of the people who haven't  been able to do Friday nights.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if we have a small group this go around, we'll get a feel for who can meet on Wednesday.  So, let's plan to get together on Wednesday, October 24 from 7:30-10:30.  I do realize that this is getting close to Halloween for those who would need to drive into Salem.  I also thought driving would be slightly easier on a Wednesday as opposed to a Friday.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The house is at 21 Lemon St. and is pumpkin colored.  There is parking (non-resident) on Lemon St., Northey St., and Cross St.  The house is also within walking distance of most of downtown Salem and we're a short walk from the commuter rail.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who can't do either Wednesday or Fridays nights, if you have a night you prefer and are willing to host, please send me an e-mail and we'll set it up.  If you are willing to host regardless, please e-mail me with the dates that you would like to and how many people you can accommodate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We certainly hope to see you though.  The nights we have gotten together have been really fun, and we're looking forward to more.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244003154000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189829796000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Night Games</name><id>6362682</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193268600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/6362682/</event_url></item>