<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC's Cabot Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1487529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;04/16 Update: The start of this class was pushed back a week and it will now begin on April 23 and end on May 21. The start time and location remain unchanged.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Just because it's winter in the mountains it doesn't mean that you can't start looking ahead to the spring. Think about it - no snowshoes or crampons, lighter boots, and less "extra" clothing and gear to stuff in your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;If you are planning to become more active once the snow melts, or if you simply want to brush up on the knowledge, skills, and abilities that you already have, the Spring Hiking and Backpacking Program being offered by the Boston Chapter of the AMC is a great place to start.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Program Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Ever wanted to try hiking or backpacking and didn't know where to get started? Are you rusty and want to brush up on your knowledge and skills? Do you want to get involved with our organized hikes? Do you want to meet other hikers? Then the Hiking/Backpacking Committee's Annual 3-Season Hiking Program is for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;This interactive course consists of 5 instructional sessions to introduce the basics of spring, summer and fall day hiking and backpacking in New England. The program includes a series of lectures and demonstrations in Cabot Hall as well as guided hikes during April through and July weekends designed to increase and facilitate the safe enjoyment of the outdoors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;The instruction topics include: clothing, heat and energy management, nutrition, footwear, heat injuries/hypothermia, choosing the right gear, backcountry stewardship, physical conditioning, accident prevention, map and compass skills, weather hazards, sleeping bags, tents, and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The program runs on five Tuesday nights from 6:30 PM - 9:00 PM. The first three nights (04/16, 04/23, and 04/30) will focus on day hiking,&lt;/span&gt; the fourth night (05/07) will be a mix of different topics, and &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;the final night (05/14) will focus on overnight trips.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Program Registration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;The Program costs $50 for AMC members and $55 for non-members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;YOU MUST REGISTER FOR THIS PROGRAM DIRECTLY WITH THE AMC BY CLICKING &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hbbostonamc.org/regi/366"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;You can pay via Paypal when you register or you can send a check payable to "HB COMMITTEE" to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Chris McCarron &lt;br /&gt;

 c/o Phoenix Realty &lt;br /&gt;

 1318 Beacon St Unit #18 &lt;br /&gt;

 Brookline MA 02446.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;The program fee includes a comprehensive course manual and the current AMC White Mountain Guide book included.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;There will be weekend trips offered exclusively or preferentially to participants in this class so you can put your learning in practice (some additional costs may apply). Plus, this is a great opportunity to meet lots of other people who love the outdoors, and to make new friends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;The program takes place at AMC Cabot Auditorium located at 4 Joy Street in Boston, MA. It's near the Park Street T Station, the Massachusetts State House and the Boston Common. Discount parking passes are available for the Boston Common Garage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Questions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;If you have general questions about this program, you can either contact me, the program organizer Robert Knudsen (rknudsen@rcn.com) or the registrar Chris McCarron (chrishbamc@gmail.com).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366767717000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357701830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC's 2013 Introduction to Spring Hiking and Backpacking - Class 1 of 5</name><id>98674962</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366756200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/98674962/</event_url></item>