<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>151 W 46th St, Suite 1202</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10036</zip><lat>40.758416</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>This Activity is Done Remotely (there is not a physical meeting spot)</name><city>New York </city><id>1383122</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.984077</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;MEETUP OBE FLY-IN EXERCISE&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.iacworld.org/files/meetup/Fly-in.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Meetup members have a chance to put their projection skills to the test by attempting to have an out-of-body experience with the objective of identifying a mystery object hidden inside a red box in our New York office.  Members can use clairvoyance, intuition or lucid projection to find out information about the hidden object.  Periodically, the object will be revealed to help us to see how close we are with our perceptions.  Practice makes perfect, so if at first you don’t succeed, try and try again! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below are a few helpful hints, to help you to make the most of this project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturate your Mind with the idea of the Red Box&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The box we are attempting to reach is currently being held in the classroom of the IAC New York, which regularly offers classes on how to develop energetic sensitively and how to have out-of-body experiences.  Due to the energetic frequency of this room and the similarities of this event and the classes traditionally held at the IAC office, this location is the ideal destination to target outside of the body.  Since we are several states away, the best way to connect with the target object is to think about it, and look at photos of it (see above).  By connecting  our mind with the idea of the projective target (the place we plan to go) we naturally connect our energies to the target, facilitating  a greater chance to astral project there, once we are sleeping.  This connection is more important than distance or time and space. To optimize your chances of reaching the target box even more, try printing out a photo of the red box and posting it by your bed or the place you are planning to sleep.  Review the photo and ponder it for several minutes before finally resting or attempting a projective technique.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Write down your Perceptions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most people have better results when they write down their perceptions during their projective attempts.  Many times we could get a small glimpse of the object or an intuition about the object, before we even fully leave the body.  It is also possible to have a projection and then forget it after you wake up.  Due to this, the ideal scenario is to keep a notebook and small light near your bed in order to help you to capture any thoughts, ideas or perceptions which you may experience during your practice.  When the target objects are revealed every couple of weeks, go back to your notes and see which notes were more accurate and which were less accurate.  As self- knowledge is a large tool to help us to develop psychically, this procedure of keeping notes may serve as useful to you well after this project ends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;NOTE: In order to facilitate this, we have included an &amp;quot;Daily Projective Attempt Form&amp;quot; that you can download and use to record your experiences. Click &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/astralprojection-119/files"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt; to download the form:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;u&gt;Meetup members can use the following methods to view what is inside the box:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Out-of-Body Experience (when you physical body is resting and your astral body temporarily floats out of it to another place or dimension)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clairvoyance (the ability to visually perceive something while awake or asleep at a distance or that you otherwise would not be able to see only using your physical eyes)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Psychometry (the ability to send some of your energies while awake or asleep to an object and acquire information about the object during this process) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Although leaving the body is very natural and something that we are all capable of doing, full control of this phenomena takes time and practice.  Please see the page we posted with instructions for an OBE technique for you to try (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/astralprojection-119/pages/OBE_Technique"&gt;Click Here to see technique&lt;/a&gt;). We hope that this project can help you with your own self-study and projection attempts.  For questions, comments, additional instructions or to share your experience email us at &lt;b&gt;meetup@iacworld.org&lt;/b&gt; or call us at &lt;b&gt;212-867-0807&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Happy Projections and we hope to see you outside of the body!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>IAC  </member_name><member_id>1977812</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290475306000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Researchers of Consciousness</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-OBE</urlname><id>1258624</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Out-of-Body Experience Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286320390000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OBE Fly-in Exercise</name><id>llrppynpbdc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290470400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-OBE/events/15518013/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/c/global_18148604.jpeg</photo_url></item>