<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>187 Chelmsford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.608450</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-887-5677</phone><name>The Best Western</name><city>Chelmsford</city><id>334113</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340760</lon></venue><fee><label>Guest Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This month's speaker, Matthew Desrochers has to reschedule due to an unexpected family emergency.  Please keep him and his family in your thoughts and prayers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his place will be Annie Trajlinek, who is going to teach us all about College Rentals!  &lt;span&gt;Since we've had many people ask about this topic recently, and since we planned on discussing it at a later meeting, we thought we would talk about College Rentals this week instead!  Since Annie and Rhiannon spoke about college rentals almost three years ago now, we've had lots of interest, and we thought we'd have them teach what they know to our new members!  When Rhiannon was in college in 2005 she decided she wanted to move off campus, and Annie, her mother, decided that this was a great place to put her real estate knowledge to work.  After purchasing 5 houses, renting to tons of students, and learning the right and wrong things to do, Annie and Rhiannon have a College Rentals system that works for them and they are happy to share.  Annie will tell anyone who asks that she will "never rent to anyone but college students!"  If you have thought about the potential of college rentals and wondered the tricks to making it work, keeping it fun, and taking in profit you don't want to miss this meeting!  Learn how to make college rentals work from the renters' and landlord's perspectives!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;You Will Learn:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-The Pros and Cons of Renting to College Students&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-What to Look for in a College Rental Property&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-What College Students are Looking For&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-How to Marketing to Students and How to Find the Right Renters&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-How to Choose the Right School/Location&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-How to Avoid Costly Mistakes&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-What you Need to Know about College Rules&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-How to Set Your Price and What to Include in your Rental Agreement&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;-Tips on How to Keep Happy Renters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;See you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;SPEAKER BIO:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Annie Trajlinek lives in Sandown, NH and has been a real estate investor for 9 years in the NH/MA area.  She had been a member of the New England REIA for several years before taking ownership of it in 2005.   She and her daughter Rhiannon and son in law Peter have been running the REIA together since 2008.  In 2005, while Rhiannon and Peter were students at Plymouth State University and they all decided to jump into college rentals.  Since then, Annie has purchased 5 houses to rent to college students, and loves sharing her knowledge with others.  Annie specializes in networking and has worked for herself for over 35 years and loves meeting new people!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LOCATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The Best Western Hotel &lt;br /&gt;

 187 Chelsmford St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cheslmford, MA 01824 &lt;br /&gt;

 When:&lt;/strong&gt; 1st Wednesday of Each Month &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Admission Fees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; $20.00 at the Door&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ask about getting YOUR membership today!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newenglandreia.com"&gt;www.newenglandreia.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk into the front of the building, and straight ahead you will see our Welcome table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter and Rhiannon </member_name><member_id>6208546</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365041445000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nereia</urlname><id>593272</id><group_lat>42.6199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302578298000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Work College Rentals!</name><id>vxsvqyrgbfb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365030000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nereia/events/105023732/</event_url></item>