<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Life Alive Restaurant in Lowell has some great raw selections and they can convert other items to raw. They make their own delicious raw almond milk. This event is worth the trip out of the city if you're from close to Boston. This event is held on the first Saturday of every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LifeAlive's web site&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.LifeAlive.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.LifeAlive....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Live Alive sells only the highest quality, pure, organic products so taking care of yourself and your family is a true pleasure!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TO LIVE LIFE...ALIVE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Life Alive's intent is to fulfill their mission by infusing our community with a healthy, healing environment celebrating every aspect of our lives: BODY &amp;amp; MIND &amp;amp; SPIRIT. Our Mission is to personally feed you well with great food, healthy products &amp;amp; positive living options, so that you can truly know &amp;quot;healthy&amp;quot; can be a pleasure!  We encourage you to share your desires, explore your tastes, discover your hidden hungers, and wake up to the vibrancy of our earth's bounty and neighborhood's abundance.  Together, let us deepen our connection with nature &amp;amp; spirit, so that like us, future generations can celebrate the pleasure in being ALIVE. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MAY EVERYONE WHO COMES THROUGH THESE DOORS EXPERIENCE THE NOURISHMENT THEY SEEK.&lt;/b&gt; - Heidi Feinstein, Creator &amp;amp; Proprietor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Life Alive Restaurant is a vegetarian, mostly vegan restaurant with raw entrees. At this event, we will all be able to get 100% raw food.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Boston Raw Food Group posted files,&lt;/b&gt; please check the files section&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawfood.meetup.com/343/files/"&gt;http://rawfood.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To promote the BRFG,&lt;/b&gt; please print out and post our tear-strip flyer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/733136/BostonRawFoodMeetupTear-stripFlyer.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For upcoming events,&lt;/b&gt; please check the calendar&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawfood.meetup.com/343/calendar/"&gt;http://rawfood.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For other raw events&lt;/b&gt; around New England, please visit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.NewEnglandRawCommunity.com"&gt;http://www.NewEngland...&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may make an optional small donation to our Meetup group via &lt;a href="http://www.PayPal.com"&gt;http://www.PayPal.com...&lt;/a&gt; to elliott7 (at) comcast.net. Please email after your donation so we may send a thank you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226903084000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223625145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Life Alive</name><id>8935856</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225569600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/8935856/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/9/4/global_5357780.jpeg</photo_url></item>