<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1874 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02420</zip><lat>42.448071</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-862-6288</phone><name>Cary Memorial Library</name><city>Lexington</city><id>1056907</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.229634</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Explore and Discover Emotional Freedom Technique (EFT)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For years hypnotists and NLP practitioners have been including EFT as part of their arsenal in helping their clients overcome various issues. Perhaps because it is so easy to learn and tech their clients.&lt;br /&gt;Tapping (a descriptive word often used to refer to EFT) has been around for many years. It is highly kinesthetic in nature (the tapping part) and very strange to watch someone doing it.&lt;br /&gt;It can be highly effective however, in helping people overcome a myriad of thing.&lt;br /&gt;Come and learn this simple technique and learn resources available where you can further any practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;I am not a certified practitioner or trainer in EFT. I have been to trainings that have included this, learned and use this myself and have talked to many people who use this all the time. This will be a discovery workshop where we can learn from the complimentary manual offered by the originator of EFT.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Learning Center - Bottom Floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287148653000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286390525000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP Meetup - Lexington- Emotional Freedom Technique (EFT)</name><id>15023904</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287097200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/15023904/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/0/global_11885328.jpeg</photo_url></item>