<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Shore Rd</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>11766</zip><lat>40.943713</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>631 642 2200  ext 0</phone><name>Pathways To Health</name><city>Mount Sinai</city><id>939059</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.032907</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Dear Friends of &lt;br /&gt;Pathways and Mother Earth:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are holding a world peace prayer and prayer for our &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Bleeding Mother Earth&amp;quot; at our International Peace Pole here at Pathways. All are invited:&lt;br /&gt;Monday June 21, at 7 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please read the following request from Chief Arvol Looking Horse, &amp;quot;Present Chief and Keeper of the Sacred White Buffalo Calf Pipe of the Lakota, Dakota, Nakota Nation of the Sioux&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; *A Great Urgency **** To All World Religious and Spiritual Leaders*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               My Relatives,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               Time has come to speak to the hearts of our Nations and their Leaders. I ask you this from the bottom of my heart, to come together from the Spirit of your Nations in prayer. We, from the heart of Turtle Island , have a great message for the World; we are guided to speak from all the White Animals showing their sacred color, which have been signs for us to pray for the sacred life of all things. As I am sending this message to you, many Animal Nations are being threatened, those that swim, those that crawl, those that fly, and the plant Nations, eventually all will be affect from the oil disaster in the Gulf.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               The dangers we are faced with at this time are not of spirit. The catastrophe that has happened with the oil spill which looks like the bleeding of Grandmother Earth, is made by human mistakes, mistakes that we cannot afford to continue to make.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               I asked, as Spiritual Leaders, that we join together, united in prayer with the whole of our Global Communities. My concern is these serious issues will continue to worsen, as a domino effect that our Ancestors have warned us of in their Prophecies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               I know in my heart there are millions of people that feel our united prayers for the sake of our Grandmother Earth are long overdue. I believe we as Spiritual people must gather ourselves and focus our thoughts and prayers to allow the healing of the many wounds that have been inflicted on the Earth. As we honor the Cycle of Life, let us call for Prayer circles globally to assist in healing Grandmother Earth (our Unc'I Maka).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               We ask for prayers that the oil spill, this bleeding, will stop. That the winds stay calm to assist in the work. Pray for the people to be guided in repairing this mistake, and that we may also seek to live in harmony, as we make the choice to change the destructive path we are on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               As we pray, we will fully understand that we are all connected. And that what we create can have lasting effects on all life. So let us unite spiritually, All Nations, All Faiths, One Prayer. Along with this immediate effort, I also ask to please remember June 21st, World Peace and Prayer Day/Honoring Sacred Sites day. Whether it is a natural site, a temple, a church, a synagogue or just your own sacred space, let us make a prayer for all life, for good decision making by our Nations, for our children's future and well-being, and the generations to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Onipikte (that we shall live)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chief Arvol Looking Horse&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please join us Monday Night, &lt;br /&gt;June 21, at 7 pm&lt;br /&gt;by our Peace Pole.&lt;br /&gt;Pathways To Health&lt;br /&gt;77 Shore Rd&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Sinai, NY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;631 642 2200 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(If it rains, it will be indoors) &lt;br /&gt;Thank you &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;William and Judith&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at The Peace Pole in the Jeannie Stout Peace Garden at Pathways To Health</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>William Bezmen</member_name><member_id>8774813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277208726000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Holistic health &amp; Spiritualist</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Pathways-to-Health</urlname><id>1369837</id><group_lat>40.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-73.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pathways To Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276557605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Prayer for our Bleeding Mother Earth"</name><id>13801297</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277161200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Pathways-to-Health/events/13801297/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/0/global_7118880.jpeg</photo_url></item>