<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Little River Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03595</zip><lat>44.261257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hiker parking at the end of Little River Road</name><city>Twin Mountain</city><id>11278372</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.559708</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The former Firewardens Trail up Mt Hale is one of the best graded trails in the whites, which is odd as the trail has been officially abandoned for over 50 years. Despite the lack of official standing it is a popular approach to the mountain due to its long steady switchbacks and very mature birch glades. There is even an interesting view of the presidentials along the way. In the summer this route is fairly short but winter adds a few miles both ways as the road to the trailhead is not plowed. Rather than do a long somewhat boring roadwalk in from RT 3, the route we will be taking will be along the abandoned railroad grade (and former North Twin trail) that used to serve the area. This route is used in the winter and is accessed from the Little River road. Overall the distance is approximately 10 miles round trip, but at least 5 miles is hiking on an old railroad bed through a hardwood forest. This is still a 4000 footer so somewhere along the way we will still be gaining 2400 feet. This is an intermediate hike due to the distance. The pace in via the railroad bed could be brisk due to the conditions but once we start climbing the goal is a slow and steady pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail is also used extensively by skiers who enjoyed the birch glades and that means that if we get significant new snow prior to the hike, snowshoes will not be optional. Given the current hard icy conditions of the snowpack, microspikes will also be required. Please note snowshoes and microspikes are not optional. Dont sign up unless you have and plan to bring the gear to the trailhead. Worse case is you get to take your snowshoes out for a walk on the back of your pack so make sure you are comfortable carrying your snowshoes on your pack. If we get snow the trail is ideal for sliding in mnay spots but could be quite rough given the current lack of snow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In order to be signed up you must anwer the two questions. If you do not, you will be wait listed until you do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We plant to start as a group and leave the trailhead at 9:30 AM and stay together as a group unitl we return to the cars.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please make sure you check out hike safe NH and have the ten essentials&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=full-gear-list"&gt;http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=full-gear-list&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus make sure you have the " the add for winter gear" and place to stow extra gear if it gets warm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;Extra Warm Clothing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #434165"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;Insulated Parka&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #434165"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;Extra Mittens&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #434165"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;Balaclava&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #434165"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;Insulated Boots&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #434165"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;Overmitts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #434165"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;Snowshoes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;It is important g&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;iven the forecast that sunglasses may be a needed item!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #434165"&gt;I am driving south from Gorham NH for this event so I may not be of much use for carpooling. If you do carpool with someone make sure that you donate towards expenses.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The signups do not allow guests, if someone with the appropriate equipment and experience would like to join this hike have them sign up as a member.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Drive to Twin Mtn NH, look for the Little River Road with the large advertisement for the Seven Dwarves Motel, Drive south on the Little River road to the end</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360593409000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360067103000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mt Hale via the former Firewardens Trail</name><id>103111562</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360506600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/103111562/</event_url></item>