<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>449 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.349.4040</phone><name>Main Cambridge Public Library</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>767569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111112</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This lecture is part of a public lecture series (Evenings with Experts: 2011)&amp;nbsp;that is a collaboration between the Cambridge Public Library and Grow Native Massachusetts. It is free and, of course, open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href="http://www.grownativemass.org/"&gt;http://www.grownativemass.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*****Getting the Real Dirt on Soil Ecosystems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lecture by John Swallow Ph.D., Director of Environmental Sciences at Pine &amp;amp; Swallow Environmental&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If healthy, the earth beneath our feet is full of robust biological activity--with microbes, fungi, nematodes, and other life. Tonight, we explore the interconnection between soil ecosystems and the physical and chemical charateristits of soil. After this talk, you will have newfound awe for what you might have thought was just "dirt." Dr. Swallow is an internationally recognized pioneer in horticultural soil management and soil preparation for ecological restoration. His firm created the six unique soil types of Lusitania Meadow at Fresh Pond Reservation.*****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lecture will last about an hour, with about 30 minutes afterward for Q&amp;amp;A (total time about 90 minutes). Doors open at 6:30 p.m.; the lecture starts at 7:00 p.m. Seating is on a first-come, first-served basis. The closest T option is the Harvard Square stop on the Red Line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be at the library between 6:00 and 6:15. Meet me inside the library, inside the lecture room. We may not be able to sit together because seating is based on first come, first served, but if you can't find me, my bright red backpack, *and* my meetup sign inside the lecture room before the lecture, look for me afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for my bright red backpack *and* my meetup sign. I've been hearing&amp;nbsp;that a lot of people carry bright red backpacks, but how many of them are carrying meetup signs, too?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If people would like to go out in Harvard Square after the lecture, we can do that. We'll decide on Wednesday. Options for going out after the lecture:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Algiers Coffee House, 40 Brattle Street, 617.492.1557&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Harvard's Brew House, 33 Dunster Street, 617.868.3585&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you Wednesday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marianne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my bright red backpack *and* my meetup sign. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310003604000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308694658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lecture: Getting the Real Dirt on Soil Ecosystems</name><id>23031011</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309990500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/23031011/</event_url></item>