<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello:&lt;br /&gt;Two important parts of preparing and simplifying the holidays are 1) Letting go of things that are no longer part of our lives; 2) Economizing on gifts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may have a friend or family member who would love to receive that funky rhinestone pin from the 50's, or your vintage hat. Maybe you like the idea of passing along treasures that no longer suit you... but there is a mismatch between your treasures and the folks on your list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our group &amp;quot;Swap Meet&amp;quot; may be the answer! You bring nice things that no longer mean anything to you (think small - you'll need to carry it!), and swap them for things that you can utilize as gifts. An example - some of my friends used to collect coin silver spoons, vintage handkerchiefs, and costume jewelry from the 40s and 50s. After a time, they lost interest in those items. Then a funny thing happened: each one saw the other's stuff and loved it! they swapped and are very happy with their new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On December 6th, we'll set up tables at Trinity Church. This is not a yard sale, the idea is not to sell items, but rather to exchange things you don't want or need for things you do. Small or easy to transport items work best - costume jewelry, scarves, handbags, ties, cuff links, hats, gloves, small kitchen items, china, knick-knacks. Please be prepared to take home any items that are not swapped. Each person determines what a suitable swap is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What a fun way to let go of some treasures that are no longer quite so treasured! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marilyn&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230684766000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224640619000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December "SWAP MEET"</name><id>9007466</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228579200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/9007466/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/d/global_5119229.jpeg</photo_url></item>