<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sheri Winston is one of the country’s great sex teachers, and is bringing hot, fun, empowering erotic education to people throughout the country. She is the author of the award-winning book, Women’s Anatomy of Arousal: Secret Maps to Buried Pleasure, which prominent women’s health expert Dr. Christiane Northrup calls “the most comprehensive, user-friendly, practical and uplifting book on women’s sexuality I’ve ever read.” Women’s Anatomy of Arousal won the 2010 Book of the Year award from AASECT (the American Association of Sexuality Educators, Counselors and Therapists). Winston developed her expertise over 20 years as a certified nurse-midwife and gynecological practitioner, a holistic healing expert, and a student of the esoteric erotic arts. The result: a unique approach called Wholistic Sexuality™.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight's workshop will focus on FEMALE ANATOMY (open to women of all ages &amp;amp; men) &lt;br /&gt;In the Secrets of Female Pleasure you will discover just how much you’ve been missing! There’s more to the clitoris then meets the eye, and more to women’s arousal equipment then the clitoris. A largely unknown network of structures, the Female Erectile Network, is responsible for women’s arousal and orgasm. Learn the whole truth about what’s there, why, how it connects and how to make it work wonderfully. More accurate maps enable women &amp;amp; their lovers to experience their full pleasure potential. Lecture &amp;amp; Powerpoint presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investment:$35 or $25 before 11/31&lt;br /&gt;To register email Imani@thegreenvibration.com &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291425378000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289096017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Secrets of Female Pleasure</name><id>15364731</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291420800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/15364731/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/c/global_19429820.jpeg</photo_url></item>