<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366253</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-3721</phone><name>Pandemonium Books &amp; Games</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>875759</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105592</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**UPDATE**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As of 4/16, we have filled all of our available slots for this event. We would encourage you to still email us, and we can add your name as an alternate, in case one of the original players drops out. The email address to contact is aethan [AT] bloopwatch [dot] org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Andy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**ORIGINAL POST**&lt;br /&gt;Celebrating the launch of Dungeons and Dragons, 4th Edition, Pandemonium is proud to be a part of Worldwide D&amp;amp;D Game Day again! This free event will feature the chance to play 4th Edition D&amp;amp;D the day after it releases in stores! Dare the dangers of the plane of darkness in Into the Shadowhaunt.Characters are provided, and we'll be teaching the game as we go!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Materials are being provided for 25 people to play, so sign up early by emailing aethan [AT] bloopwatch [DOT] org with your name and when you'd like to play (Noon, 2 PM, 5 PM, or 6 PM.) Expect the game to take around 4 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on how many folks we have available to run the adventure, we may also have other special events, provided by Wizards of the Coast, such as Monster Charades, d20 Questions, 4th Edition Trivia, Dungeon Feud, and D&amp;amp;D Miniatures Events!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there! Remember to sign up as noted above!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be a short, roundish fellow with dark hair who'll likely be running games. I answer to Andy.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213053071000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>A chance to try 4th Edition D&amp;D in a fun and friendly atmosphere.</why><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207168137000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worldwide D&amp;D Game Day @ Pandemonium</name><id>7659844</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212879600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/7659844/</event_url></item>