<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The venue for our October gathering will be at Elmer's in gorgeous Ashfield! This place is so fun and quirky, I always love going there, and the drive itself will be worth the visit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I spoke to Nan, the owner, this evening and they are very excited that we may be coming. We still have to iron out the final details for you, but I have only heard GREAT things about dinner at Elmer's and I have been there several times for breakfast and that has always been fabulous. (In fact, I think they won some sort of prize for the best pancakes in New England).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the menu (it changes each week, so I am not sure what our choices will be): &lt;a href="http://www.elmersstore.com/s/es/newsb.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elmer's Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a review from Yelp!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nan, the owner/chef here, is a Katrina transplant, the place is beautiful (circa 1835), and I've been lucky enough to have had a few Friday night dinners here, which in my opinion are more fun than the breakfasts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everything is so freaking good, totally amazing food, friendly atmosphere and staff, absolutely one of the best dining experiences I've had in Massachusetts. The popovers here are possibly the greatest thing ever. EVER, people, EVER! Salads are made from fresh local farm greens, always a vegetarian option, lots of real love in the food. One Friday night they had Fish and Chips or Vegetarian Chili, once they had Thai Food, another time it was Fish Chowder or Mac and Cheese; they've had Local Dinners, with the entire menu consisting of from food grown by local farmers and gardeners.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if you are up for an adventure, please feel free to sign up now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, there is a $5.00 registration fee, which includes the appetizer plate that we will have for us at the table when we arrive and then each person will be responsible for their own dinner. At this moment, I am not certain of the price, but most likely it will be the usual $25.00 for soup/salad + entree + dessert. And this time, you are welcome to BYOB, if you wish. (we'd love to hear your recommendations on good, reasonably priced wines. I've been looking for &amp;quot;the best red under $10&amp;quot; and haven't found my perfect bottle yet, but I am very open to suggestions!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;can't wait to see you all next week! And hey, by the way, we are almost 100 strong in membership now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;warmly,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jessica&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS I will confirm that we will be meeting at Elmer's as soon as I have it sealed with the venue. Directions and everything to come.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will be the ones laughing the hardest!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>9683028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258325051000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255382697000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October EatUp!Thursday, Oct. 22nd, Elmer's in Ashfield</name><id>11610964</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256250600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/11610964/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/e/global_11197662.jpeg</photo_url></item>