<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>As tonight’s moderator, John Moore (Chilmark Research) says in his blog:  telehealth is a sector “in perpetual pilot phase … just waiting … the pending market breakthrough … the devices, sensors, software and services that will see rapid market growth and acceptance.  Four years on and we are still waiting.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s an issue that never goes away for those in the innovation business -- why proven ideas don’t get adopted faster.  Tonight’s session looks at telehealth as a lesson in technology adoption (or non-adoption, as the case may be).  Does it really matter if outcomes are better, costs are reduced and customers are happier?  What else must technologies (or their backers) do in order to prove themselves worthy?  What can telehealth’s lessons teach innovators in other areas? What lessons can successful innovators elsewhere teach telehealth?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll explore those questions with a panel of proven veterans in the telehealth battles, in technology adoption and in healthcare innovation in general -- four of whom are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adam Darkins, Chief Consulant, Veterans Health Administration&lt;/b&gt;. Adam leads the world's largest telehealth program -- the National Telehealth Programs for the US Department of Veterans Affairs (VA). Successful implementation of telehealth within the VA involves the use of health Informatics, telehealth and disease management technologies to enhance and extend care and case management. Under his leadership the VA has developed the clinical, technology and business underpinnings to successfully implement and sustain enterprise-wide telehealth-based services that have demonstrably improved access to care for patients, reduced utilization of healthcare resources and are associated with very high levels of patient satisfaction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The VA telehealth program cares for over 300,000 patients annually at more than 640 sites. There are over 1000 clinical videoconferencing end points providing telehealth services on the VA’s dedicated clinical enterprise videoconferencing network that links 140 VA Medical Centers and over 500 community based outpatient clinics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam has worked in health services development and has implemented enterprise information technology systems in the US and UK since 1991. He has a previous clinical background in neurosurgery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Naomi Fried, Ph.D., Chief Innovation Officer, Children’s Hospital Boston&lt;/b&gt;.  To say that Naomi Fried’s career is focused on the challenges of bringing innovation to healthcare would be an understatement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Children’s first-ever chief innovation officer, Naomi is responsible for assembling and leading a group of clinicians and staff to promote technological, clinical process and business model innovation across the primary pediatric teaching hospital of Harvard Medical School.  Prior to her current position, she was Vice President of Innovation and Advanced Technology at Kaiser Permanente, the nation’s largest not-for-profit health plan, where she built and managed a team of clinicians and technologists charged with identifying and assessing emerging clinical technologies and introducing them to operational leaders within Kaiser Permanente. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also while at Kaiser Permanente, she led the initiative to commercialize the plan’s Archimedes mathematical model for pharmaceutical and healthcare customers.  She wrote the business plan, developed the sales and marketing strategy, and negotiated most aspects of this complex spinout.  She has also been a key player at two healthcare venture capital firms — Paratech International and Capital Health -- and was herself responsible for the successful launch of of an e-clinical trial startup, 1747, Inc., where she directed technical development, marketing strategy and fund raising.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Naomi began her professional career as acting CEO of Shine, LLC, a spinout of the Stanford School of Medicine, formed to commercialize web-based medical information system developed by medical faculty.  She wrote the business plan created the revenue model, and initiated, negotiated and completed contracts with distribution partners, publishers, technology licensing office and drug database companies.  She also  spearheaded launch of the alpha version and planned and managed development of the beta version.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Naomi is an MIT Ph.D. in materials science and earned a B.S. summa cum laude in chemistry from the University of California at Berkley.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bruce Lehman, Co-founder and CEO, LehmanMillet.&lt;/b&gt; With offices in Boston, Mass. and Irvine, California, LehmanMillet  is the only healthcare marketing communications agency dedicated to serving companies seeking to change the standard of care. Clients range from start-ups to Fortune 100 and span the clinical spectrum across medical diagnostics, devices, biotechnology and specialty pharmaceuticals. Its core expertise is the use of communications to help drive the adoption of innovation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the firm's 31-year history, Bruce has worked with companies, large and small, whose successful commercializations of medical innovation have created the healthcare market we know today. He has been active in several industry associations including DxMA, the Harvard-MIT Division of Health Sciences and Technology (HST) Advisory Board, MassMEDIC, and HCMA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce graduated summa cum laude from Rutgers University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Steven E. Locke, MD, Associate Professor of Psychiatry, Harvard Medical School&lt;/b&gt;.  In addition to Harvard, Steven has directed a course in technology innovation and e-health at MIT since 1998 where he is an affiliated faculty member in the Division of Health Sciences and Technology.  He is also an entrepreneur as founder and CEO of Veritas Health Solutions LLC, a Boston-based behavioral telehealth consulting firm specializing in technology-supported self-care, behavioral health and disease management. His clients have included major disease management vendors, national health plans, managed behavioral health care companies and technology companies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven has held numerous leadership roles in professional organizations and has organized meeting programs in teleheatlh, behavioral medicine, clinical informatics, and disease management. He is past-President of the American Psychosomatic Society and was awarded the Stangler Prize for Innovation in 2008 by the American Association for Technology in Psychiatry. In 2009 he became a Distinguished Life Fellow of the American Psychiatric Association. A popular keynote speaker at events in the US, Europe and Asia, Steven chaired the annual Summit on Behavioral Telehealth held in Boston in 2007 and 2008. He also maintains a part-time practice of primary care psychiatry and behavioral medicine in Wayland, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;John Moore (moderator), Managing Partner, Chilmark Research.&lt;/b&gt; Chilmark is a Cambridge, Mass.-based healthcare industry analyst firm that performs market research and analysis on healthcare information technology (HIT) adoption and use. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two key factors that set Chilmark Research apart from other analyst firms are:  first, a deep technical and market expertise of IT adoption trends with particular emphasis on what drives successful market adoption of new technologies; and second, a singular focus on the growth of consumerism in healthcare, which Chilmark sees as one of healthcare’s most significant trends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John is an accomplished high-tech marketing executive, both nationally and internationally with over 15 years as an IT analyst, first in the manufacturing sector and later in the Healthcare IT (HIT) sector. Prior to becoming an analyst, he was senior VP of Marketing for a leading analytical instrumentation company, and prior to that a Research Associate at MIT where his area of focus was the diffusion of technologies into regulated markets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Edwin J. Simcox, Jr., Director, Healthcare Industry Solutions, AT&amp;amp;T.&lt;/b&gt;  Ed joined AT&amp;amp;T in July, 2010 as the director responsible for telehealth offer development as well as healthcare strategy and portfolio management in the newly-formed ForHealth team. AT&amp;amp;T created the ForHealth practice area to accelerate delivery of new wireless and advanced networking services to help the healthcare industry improve patient care and reduce costs nationwide. ForHealth services include wireless solutions that support disease management, remote patient monitoring, prescription adherence, and new cloud-based solutions that permit patients’ multiple health care providers to share medical data in near real time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In November 2010, the American Hospital Association (AHA) announced that it has exclusively endorsed AT&amp;amp;T’s Healthcare Information Exchange services.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to joining AT&amp;amp;T, Ed held multiple strategic positions at Clarian Health, a $5 Billion, integrated health system headquartered in Indianapolis, IN. Ed was tasked with assembling and chairing the Technology Architecture Committee, a governance committee comprised of clinicians and IT specialists who assessed and approved both clinical and administrative emerging technologies and standards. Ed was also responsible for the creating Clarian’s first comprehensive IT standards library and implementing policies to enforce the standards. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ed is a recipient of the Computerworld Laureate medal.  He holds a B.A. degree from DePauw University and a J.D. degree from Indiana University School of Law.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Cronk</member_name><member_id>465168</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Branigan</member_name><member_id>12277847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294766780000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279902833000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What Does Telehealth Say about Technology Adoption?</name><id>14191461</id><headcount>110</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294700400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/14191461/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/8/global_12538664.jpeg</photo_url></item>