<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Another Earth&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner of the 2011 Sundance Film Festival's Alfred P. Sloan Prize that recognizes a feature film with a central theme of science and/or technology, 
&lt;em&gt;Another Earth&lt;/em&gt; came out of nowhere at Sundance to catch big time attention from studios with its excellent weaving together of both human and scientific elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the sci-fi drama 
&lt;em&gt;Another Earth&lt;/em&gt;, Rhoda Williams (Brit Marling), a bright young woman accepted into MIT's astrophysics program, aspires to explore the cosmos. A brilliant composer, John Burroughs (William Mapother), has just reached the pinnacle of his profession and is about to have a second child with his loving wife. On the eve of the discovery of a duplicate Earth, tragedy strikes and the lives of these strangers become irrevocably intertwined. Estranged from the world and the selves they once knew, the two outsiders begin an unlikely love affair and reawaken to life. But when one is presented with the chance of a lifetime opportunity to travel to the other Earth and embrace an alternative reality, which new life will they choose?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This film is not for everyone as it one of those that you will either love or hate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will send an email on Sun Morning with my contact info.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Movie starts at 7:10 so will meet in lobby and go in at 7:05.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary</member_name><member_id>10329460</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312294828000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311913069000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie Another Earth at Landmark Cambridge</name><id>27457291</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312153200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/27457291/</event_url></item>