<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We should meet up at 6:30 so we can get good seats.  They are expecting it to be popular...it is showing in the downstairs theaters.   Movies showing downstairs always make things very hectic for us to meetup.  I will be in the area near the concessions on the first floor, as you enter the ticket taking area there.  I will be wearing my movie badge so newbies can find me. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In my experience, the movies showing downstairs tend to sell out and are very confusing since it is so near the ticket buying line.   I strongly sugguest that you buy your tickets ahead of time.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I tried all day yesterday to do this through Fandango, but finally they are available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like a nice comedy and I don't know what your weeks have been like, mine has been quite hectic and I could really use a good laugh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doreen &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The name of the movie is &amp;quot;Good Luck Chuck&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Dan Fogler, Dane Cook, Jessica Alba &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Website:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.goodluckchuckthemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.goodluckch...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: It all started when Charlie Logan was ten years old. Breaking the cardinal rules of spin-the-bottle, Charlie refused to lip-lock with a demented Goth girl ? and she put a hex on him. Now, twenty-five years later, Charlie (Dane Cook) is a successful dentist... and still cursed. While his plastic surgeon best friend, Stu (Dan Fogler), pursues as many of his patients as possible, Charlie can't seem to find the right girl. Even worse, he discovers at an ex-girlfriend's wedding that every woman he's ever slept with has found true love ? with the next guy after him. Before he knows it, Charlie's reputation as a &amp;quot;good luck charm&amp;quot; has women ? from sexy strangers to his overweight receptionist ? lining up for a quickie. But a life filled with all sex and no love has Charlie lonelier than ever ? that is, until he meets Cam (Jessica Alba). An accident-prone penguin specialist, Cam is as hard-to-get as she is beautiful. But when a genuine romance develops, Charlie realizes he's got to find a way to break his good-luck curse... before the girl of his dreams winds up with the next guy she meets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190730793000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188510448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Good Luck Chuck</name><id>6271643</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190500200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6271643/</event_url></item>