<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.infonewhaven.com/d/2008/06/06/311332" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.infonewhav...&lt;/a&gt; for more information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready for a wheel good time as New Haven holds its first Cycling Celebration.  East Rock Park will become a bikes only zone on July 19 with free activities for the whole family, including a ferris wheel, carousel, live music, street performers, bike jamboree and more! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On July 19th from 10am to 5pm at East Rock Park, the City of New Haven, Elm City Cycling and the Devil's Gear Bike shop will be programming a full day of activities to promote cycling in the City of New Haven.  East Rock Park will be closed to vehicles including Farnam Drive and English Drive to allow cyclists to enjoy full access of park roads. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some highlights:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10am to 12pm noon&lt;br /&gt;US Cycling Federation sanctioned race presented by Devil's Gear Bike Shop and the New Haven Cycling Club&lt;br /&gt;Orange Street and Farnam Drive.  Visit www.bikereg.com for details and registration information &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12pm&lt;br /&gt;Ferris wheel and carousel will begin turning at  on the top of the rock rewarding people who have made the climb to the top with a free ride and a great view of the area.  Residents are encouraged to walk or ride to the summit, which will feature free bicycle valet parking.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other attractions include:&lt;br /&gt;Bicycle jamboree&lt;br /&gt;Bicycle decorating and bicycle parade sponsored by Elm City Cycling.&lt;br /&gt;Kite-flying and guided hikes to the summit.&lt;br /&gt;Children's entertainment by Uncle Chip.&lt;br /&gt;Information about CT Transit's 'Bikes-on-Board' program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Neighborhood groups will be organizing group rides throughout the city to East Rock Park.  Yale University transit will provide a shuttle to the top for families with small children or those unable to walk or ride to the summit.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;All Ages&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hours:&lt;br /&gt;12pm (noon) to 4pm. Rain date Sunday, July 20th.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll meet you at the pavilion at 12:00</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine &amp; Melissa</member_name><member_id>3632860</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216656592000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213903731000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Ferris Wheel??? New Haven Summer Cycling Celebration</name><id>8174363</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216483200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8174363/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>