<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Update: The actual starting time is 1:55 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There has been a lot of press about this film, especially about Carey Mulligan's performance, and it looks like the quality actually lives up to the hype.  Lately I've been curious about the early sixties thanks to Mad Men, so anything from that era is very interesting to me right now.  And if you're a fan of Nick Hornby like I am, there's one more reason to see this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the film:&lt;br /&gt;An Education is the story of a teenage girl's coming-of-age set in 1961 London, a city caught between the drab, post-war 1950s and the glamorous, more liberated decade to come. Jenny (Carey Mulligan) stands on the brink of becoming a woman: a brilliantly witty and attractive 16-year-old whose suburban life is about to be blown apart by the utterly unsuitable 30-something David (Peter Sarsgaard). Urbane and witty, David manages to charm her conservative parents Jack (Alfred Molina) and Marjorie (Cara Seymour). David introduces Jenny to a glittering new world of classical concerts and late-night suppers with his attractive friend and business partner, Danny (Dominic Cooper) and Danny's girlfriend, the beautiful but vacuous Helen (Rosamund Pike). Just as Jenny's family's long-held dream of getting their brilliant daughter into Oxford seems within reach, Jenny is tempted by another kind of life. Written by Nick Hornby (About a Boy, High Fidelity) and directed by Lone Scherfig (Italian for Beginners). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An Education is the vivid story of how one girl became a woman — and how Olde England morphed into the youthquake center of '60s yeah yeah yeah. None of which would be quite so vivid without the beguiling performance of newcomer Mulligan. She's very much an It Girl, with her natural elegance in a brunet upsweep à la Audrey Hepburn. And she's protectively partnered by Sarsgaard in the tricky job of playing sweet yet suspect, a balance he sustains with nonchalance.&amp;quot; Grade: A-:  Entertainment Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;89% -- Certified Fresh on Rotten Tomatoes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(It was also a subject of Harlan Jacobson's Talk Cinema, which John hosted as Meetup a few weeks ago. I'm told the reaction was also very positive!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie we'll go to an area restaurant for a discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255889867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Education</name><id>11654444</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256406300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11654444/</event_url></item>