<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.367581</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1168541</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089590</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The votes are in! For those who would like to meet beforehand, we will be at The Friendly Toast at 1 Hampshire Street, Cambridge, which is in One Kendall Square. I'll try to get there by 5:40. It's a block away from the movie theater. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Otherwise I'll be in the lobby of the Landmark Theater by 6:30 with a Meetup sign. We'll send scouts ahead to grab seats together, and I'll be going in around 6:45.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;___________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SPOILER ALERT! Someone named John dies at the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meetup and see this gonzo sci-fi movie when they show it at the Kendall Square Cinema. Time is approximate, as the schedule has not been posted yet. We can meet beforehand for the necessary drink or two to steel ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Synopsis: It's a drug that promises an out-of-body experience with each hit. On the street they call it Soy Sauce, and users drift across time and dimensions. But some who come back are no longer human. Suddenly a silent otherworldly invasion is underway, and mankind needs a hero. What it gets instead is John and David, a pair of college dropouts who can barely hold down jobs. Can these two stop the oncoming horror in time to save humanity? No. No, they can't.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a hard R-rated movie. To get an idea, check out the VERY NSFW red band trailer: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://youtu.be/QDdJu2OUN38"&gt;http://youtu.be/QDdJu2OUN38&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie is already available on iTunes, Amazon Prime, and other download options, but let's see it on the big screen together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets finally available! We will be going to the 7PM showing, and meeting at the theater at 6:30. Please buy your tickets ASAP!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/%28S%28gb4dcmer3to0ry1ltn2lzaaa%29%29/Ticketing.aspx?ShowDate=2/22/2013&amp;amp;TheatreID=231"&gt;https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/%28S%28gb4dcmer3to0ry1ltn2lzaaa%29%29/Ticketing.aspx?ShowDate=2/22/2013&amp;amp;TheatreID=231&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerry</member_name><member_id>12227382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361656193000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359232427000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>John Dies at the End</name><id>101517102</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361577600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/101517102/</event_url></item>