<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1100 Lexington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.412483</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 547-5655</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739900</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.233269</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;With Halloween just around the corner, I thought a horror related book would be a logical choice to read.&amp;nbsp; And what's more horrific than zombies?&amp;nbsp; Besides, the book is being made into a movie, and I don't know about the rest of you, but I generally prefer to read a story before seeing it on the big screen.&amp;nbsp; Also, some of you, like me, may already be reading this for another book club, so I thought I would make things easier for those that are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/8/c/event_61258252.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Brooks, the author of the determinedly straight-faced parody &lt;em&gt;The Zombie Survival Guide&lt;/em&gt; (2003), returns in all seriousness to the zombie theme for his second outing, a future history in the style of Theodore Judson's &lt;em&gt;Fitzpatrick's War&lt;/em&gt;. Brooks tells the story of the world's desperate battle against the zombie threat with a series of first-person accounts "as told to the author" by various characters around the world. A Chinese doctor encounters one of the earliest zombie cases at a time when the Chinese government is ruthlessly suppressing any information about the outbreak that will soon spread across the globe. The tale then follows the outbreak via testimony of smugglers, intelligence officials, military personnel and many others who struggle to defeat the zombie menace. Despite its implausible premise and choppy delivery, the novel is surprisingly hard to put down. The subtle, and not so subtle, jabs at various contemporary politicians and policies are an added bonus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Publishers Weekly&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323307210000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317834382000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World War Z: An Oral History of the Zombie War</name><id>36256842</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320710400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/36256842/</event_url></item>