<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>260 Thayer Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.828943</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 421-0020</phone><name>AVON Cinema</name><city>Providence</city><id>1057628</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.401013</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/f/a/event_161187642.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hosted by Andrey, Julie, Brad, Heather, and Peter!  Get your tickets today! They always sell out. Click on the Buy Now link below, Get your ticket, And then RSVP here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skinet.com/warrenmiller/events/ri"&gt;Buy Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Warren Miller’s &lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The world’s leading winter sports film announces its 63rd annual feature film and U.S. tour.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fall, immerse yourself in the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; with Warren Miller Entertainment and experience the ultimate winter from a lens of absolute clarity. Warren Miller’s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a place of such singular focus and connection with the environment that, in this place, the faster you ride, the slower time passes. The&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; exists anywhere crisp winter air shocks your lungs and sunlight refracts off snowflakes, allowing you to emerge from this state improved – happier, more confident and more aware of your surroundings. So buckle up, because Warren Miller’s 63rd annual ski and snowboard film will take you into the zone…the moment…the groove…the center…the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warren Miller’s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; guides viewers to the top of the world’s most striking peaks, taking you on an exhilarating journey across the globe to Norway, Austria, California, Switzerland and beyond. The powder in Japan will send you scrambling to tune-up your gear, the gravity in Telluride will have you scheduling an avalanche refresher course, and the steeps in Alaska will drive you to push a little harder during your next preseason workout. Winter is right around the corner, and it is time to enter the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;…where the mountain meets the mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hosted by Jonny Moseley and showcasing celebrated athletes including Colby West, Chris Davenport, Jess McMillan and David Wise, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; throws down some of the most captivating footage ever shot by Warren Miller Entertainment. Olympic gold medalist Ted Ligety takes on Alaska’s mighty Chugach, Julian Carr bombs down Utah’s famed Wasatch, Jackie Paaso explores the Norwegian Arctic and Chris Anthony makes Warren Miller history on 70-year-old, 10th Mountain Division ski equipment. Roll-call winter’s finest athletes, because they are all here – embodying the essence of the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;and tackling the mountain with absolute attention and deep confidence&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, Warren Miller raises the bar with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flow State&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, offering filmgoers a magnitude of ski and snowboard action that can’t be matched anywhere else. When asked about the film, director Max Bervy said, &lt;em&gt;“The Flow State is a place where the impossible becomes possible – where time slows down and a perfect moment becomes attainable. This film reveals what it is like to be completely immersed in the present…completely immersed in the snow, in the mountains, and in the enjoyment of winter.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ticketholder Discounts &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sugarbush.com/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ticketholder Discounts &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sugarbush.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.skinet.com/warrenmiller/files/imagecache/sponsor_logo_offer/_sponsors/arc_4c_lockup_1.png" alt="image-arc 4c lockup 1" width="100" height="48" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.sugarbush.com/"&gt;FREE LIFT TICKET TO SUGARBUSH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone attending Flow State will receive a voucher good for One (1) FREE lift ticket to Sugarbush Resort, valid Monday through Friday during the 2012-13 winter season. Offer NOT VALID 12.22.12 through 1.01.13, 1.19.13 through 1.21.13, and 2.16.13 through 2.24.13. Not valid with any other offers. No refunds. Non-transferable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sugarloaf.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.skinet.com/warrenmiller/files/imagecache/sponsor_logo_offer/Sugarloaf.jpg" alt="image-Sugarloaf" width="100" height="99" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.sugarloaf.com/"&gt;BUY-ONE-GET-ONE FREE LIFT TICKET TO SUGARLOAF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone attending Flow State will receive a voucher good for One (1) 2-FOR-1 lift ticket to Sugarloaf, valid Sunday through Friday from Opening Day 2012 through Closing Day 2013. COUPON NOT VALID: Saturdays and the holiday periods of 11.23.12 through 11.24.12, 12.25.12 through 1.01.13, 1.19.13 through 1.21.13, 2.16.13 through 2.24.13 and 4.11.13 through 4.14.13. Offer cannot be combined with any other discounts or offers and holds no cash value. Vouchers can be redeemed at any lift ticket window. No refunds. Non-transferable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sundayriver.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.skinet.com/warrenmiller/files/imagecache/sponsor_logo_offer/SundayRiver.jpg" alt="image-SundayRiver" width="100" height="46" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.sundayriver.com/"&gt;BUY-ONE-GET-ONE FREE LIFT TICKET TO SUNDAY RIVER&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone attending Flow State will receive a voucher good for One (1) 2-FOR-1 lift ticket to Sunday River, valid Sunday through Friday from Opening Day 2012 through Closing Day 2013. COUPON NOT VALID: Saturdays and holiday periods of 11.23.12 through 11.24.12, 12.25.12 through 1.01.13, 1.19.13 through 1.21.13, 2.16.13 through 2.24.13 and 4.05.13 through 4.07.13. Offer cannot be combined with any other discounts or offers and holds no cash value. Vouchers can be redeemed at any lift ticket window. No refunds. Non-transferable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.theskishopplus.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.skinet.com/warrenmiller/files/imagecache/sponsor_logo_offer/_sponsors/the_ski_shop_plus_logo.png" alt="image-the ski shop plus logo" width="100" height="39" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.theskishopplus.com/"&gt;$25 OFF A PURCHASE OF $120 OR MORE AT THE SKI SHOP PLUS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone attending Flow State will receive a voucher good for $25 OFF a single purchase of $120 or more at The Ski Shop Plus. Print coupon to redeem savings. Offer valid for non-sale items only. Limit One (1) coupon per customer. Not valid in conjunction with other offers. Not valid for gift certificates, layaways, special orders, bus/lift tickets or prior purchases. OFFER EXPIRES 12.30.12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the English Cellar Alehouse (165 Angell Street) right around the corner from the AVON after 6pm on the night of the event.  Then we will meet in the AVON lobby by 7:30 - It fills up quickly!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Morrissey</member_name><member_id>9613620</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>heather cowen</member_name><member_id>11687483</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrey</member_name><member_id>12951891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352346014000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348406591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Providence RI - Avon Cinema- Warren Miller's Flow State</name><id>83682402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352334600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/83682402/</event_url></item>