<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>950 Cummings Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.576170</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>American BBQ</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1189816</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.871453</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Come on over to The American BBQ in Beverly, MA for a day of food, games and fun!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been to their other location and the food is awesome, let’s check out their Beverly site.  We will Meetup at 12:00 grab some lunch, chat and eat and play some games and most of all have some fun!!  There are booths and tables so we can move around as we need to for the games/the amount of people playing a particular game.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the American BBQ!:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;We’re proud and delighted to serve you our “Genuine Wood-Smoked BBQ”, prepared in the true Southern tradition, along with hospitality that‘ll make you feel this is your “home away from home”. First, we dry rub our premium meats with our own mix of spices and seasonings, then slow cook them (for 5-16 hours!) in our wood smokers right on the premises. The meat stays moist, “fall off the bone tender” and full of natural smokey flavor. Notice the reddish color near the bone, telling you its really slow-smoked. They serve beer and wine.  So, pull up a chair, roll up your sleeves and get ready for the best southern BBQ in the north! Make no mistake about it, you’ll come as a stranger but leave as family.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Games!:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Do you have a favorite non gambling card or board game(s) that you like to play?  Well bring it/them to this event.   We ask everyone to bring 1 or 2 games or decks of cards that you like to play, that you have around the house, if you don’t have a game then don’t worry we will have a few extra’s there that anyone can grab and play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fun!:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Everyone is open to move around the restaurant and play which ever game(s) you want, you don’t have to be stuck playing that one game, you can play as many or as few as you want.  Also this is an open event so if you are not able to come at 12:00 then come in anytime grab something to eat and get in a game or two.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;American BBQ&lt;br /&gt;950 Cummings Center Suite 96x&lt;br /&gt;Beverly, MA 01915&lt;br /&gt;978.921.1212&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of free parking in the Cummings Center Parking lot!&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come on in and we will be in the restaurant.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269522224000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266070256000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Food, Fun and Games at The American BBQ!!</name><id>12594964</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269187200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/12594964/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/3/global_12327475.jpeg</photo_url></item>