<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>61 Harvard Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.272047</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Visions by Baker</name><city>Worcester</city><id>918860</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.801932</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>ADDRESS HAS CHANGED PLEASE PLAN ACCORDINGLY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So quick question, who wants to be a member of the largest co-op photography studio in New England.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello, I’m writing to you because you are a local photographer and you fit the criteria that you live in or around Worcester and you are breathing and you make money with your photography occasionally or on a regular basis.  My friend and I have started working on a huge studio on Main Street in Worcester. We are holding a second membership meeting on January 15th. (link is below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/wphotostudio" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/wp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plan is to get 50 members to sign up and then we start construction; by construction I actually mean just minor construction. The studio space is an old department store and all we need to do is paint and the flooring is being redone for us and we are planning on building a cyclorama and updating some of the walls and building a few things here and there. All the construction should be done within 2 months with an opening date of March or April 1st depending on final member count. Anyways read on and I hope you’re Ainterested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.worcesterphotostudio.com       &lt;br /&gt;We are please to announce that we will be opening a huge photography studio in downtown Worcester. The studio will be set up in a co-op fashion, we will share the space with around 50 local photographers and loan our equipment for use during your time shooting at the studio.  &lt;br /&gt;To use our studio all you will have to do is obtain a membership and then login on our website for the studio and select a date and time and area to shoot in our studios.&lt;br /&gt;We will maintain light setups for you to use and also provide instruction for those not experienced with lighting. We will be using Cyber Sync and Pocket Wizard and Radio Poppers as well to trigger the lighting setups. We plan to have Alien Bee&amp;#146;s and an assortment of lighting equipment from continuous to strobe and also light rings.&lt;br /&gt;The goal of our studios is to provide an inexpensive artistic outlet to Worcester County and the surrounding area.  We plan to share our space with around 50 photographers and that will allow us to share expertise and artistic style with all of you. As a member you will be able to bring clients to the studio and run a photo shoot and afterward even process your photos there. The studio will also allow for walk in business from Main Street, so if you happen to be in the studio you will be able to take new clients.&lt;br /&gt;The studio will also have a board for posting jobs such as weddings or portraits. We want to encourage collaboration between photographers to help educate and encourage artistic growth.  We are also planning to showcase all members’ works on a big screen in the studio as well as on our website. We plan to host photography events and possibly a gallery as well in the future.  &lt;br /&gt;Worcester Photography Studio hopes to expand its membership over the months and years and with a growing membership we can expect the studio to grow in size. The building that we currently are renting also has additional floors which have been reserved by us to eventually include more shooting space and office space. Additionally each passing month that we are open we expect our equipment roster to grow and the members of our studio will be the ones who get to share it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Worcester Photography Studios&lt;br /&gt;381 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Worcester MA&lt;br /&gt;4th floor by secure Elevator access only&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6000 square feet.&lt;br /&gt;6 shooting areas&lt;br /&gt;(Each shooting area has different texture)&lt;br /&gt;Mill building, black room, metal finish + more&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cyclorama&lt;br /&gt;Lighting kits for each shooting area&lt;br /&gt;(Strobe, continuous, ring lights)&lt;br /&gt;Muslins, paper roll backdrop system&lt;br /&gt;Individual storage locker (4ft tall by 3ft deep and 2ft wide)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make-up room + models bathroom including shower&lt;br /&gt;Photographer’s bathroom&lt;br /&gt;Kitchenette with fridge and stove&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Online scheduler for registering shooting time&lt;br /&gt;16 camera security system with looped tape&lt;br /&gt;Keycard security system for entry into studio&lt;br /&gt;Work space for editing photos&lt;br /&gt;Common area for receiving clients&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly modeling events held at the studio&lt;br /&gt;Non Profit and charity events hosted by our studio.&lt;br /&gt;Monthly photography contests with varied topics of interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_______________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Construction news&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ve gotten a lot of questions regarding permits and construction.&lt;br /&gt;We are not doing any construction that is structure based. I’ve included a basic&lt;br /&gt;list of construction that we are planning for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brick walls and oak flooring for the mill room shooting area.&lt;br /&gt;Building out 2 walls an additional 4 feet in the front of the studio.&lt;br /&gt;Plumber will be working on 2 bathrooms, removing one toilet and adjusting sinks.&lt;br /&gt;Cropping a wall to allow for better fit cyclorama&lt;br /&gt;Storage lockers build along south wall&lt;br /&gt;Pre-finished finished flooring in one of the shooting areas &lt;br /&gt;White board put up in 2 of the shooting areas and painted&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The above construction should be completed within a month and the rest is minor cosmetic issues that we’ve already figured out.  We will be putting up a list for donating time to help us build this studio.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hendrickson</member_name><member_id>12134347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295140831000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294080428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Photography Studios membership drive</name><id>15899578</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295136000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/15899578/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/7/3/global_17237747.jpeg</photo_url></item>