<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_2><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 141</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1346807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091419</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note - to confirm your attendance at this event, you must register at the&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/dash7-wireless-sensor-networks/" target="_blank"&gt; MIT Enterprise Forum of Cambridge website.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mitforumca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The one device for all purposes is a dream held by most in the wireless and RFID world.  The DASH7 Alliance is focused on laying the ground work to make that dream a reality.&lt;br /&gt;Ann Grackin of ChainLink Research will host members of the alliance to discuss this important topic.&lt;br /&gt;What is the work of DASH7 and why is the work important?&lt;br /&gt;• Design better hardware for lower cost, interoperability, and rich in features that will  broaden the community of applications and users, thus catalyzing the market- not just defense, but the broader commercial markets.&lt;br /&gt;• Assure leverage of existing networks of passive and active RFID through standards and common set of API’s.&lt;br /&gt;• Create a safer world by incorporating  deep security  techniques for authentication, identity, privacy and secure transmission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lofty goals can be achieved, but the road ahead includes the often competing interests of business, government, end-users, standards bodies, and the tech companies themselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda topic will cover the DASH7 and its global alliance.&lt;br /&gt;• Introductions:  DASH7 and Lofty Goals- Ann Grackin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Panel Speakers:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• DASH7 – Technology and standards underpinning- JP Norair,  DASH7 Alliance&lt;br /&gt;• Interoperability in Software- Jayant Ramchandani, Novitaz&lt;br /&gt;• Making it Secure:  Louis Parks, SecureRF&lt;br /&gt;• Panel Discussion- &lt;br /&gt;o The panel will then discuss the Commercial Market opportunities beyond government the new standards alliance will enable- Mobile Apps, RTLS, Smart Card and Active on a single platform, Consumer Markets such as Retail, Healthcare, Hospitality, public applications such as Emergency response, etc.&lt;br /&gt;o The panel will also discuss these issues as well as the harmonizing of other RFID standards and frequencies- UHF, HF and LF as well as the mobile world. How does DASH7 work with epc global/GS1, the NFC and other standards groups?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPEAKERS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jayant Ramchandani, COO, Novitaz,&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.novitaz.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.novitaz.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jayant Ramchandani gained significant early stage start-up experience as vice president of engineering and chief technology officer at Shop911, as VP of engineering at Commerce Events, and as an early member of the Rasna Corporation team. Shop911 was acquired by SaleMinder, and Rasna was acquired by Parametric Technology Corporation (now PTC) (Nasdaq: PMTC). A graduate of Stanford University and the Indian Institutes of Technology, Jayant has more than 20 years of product development, software engineering, and management experience&lt;br /&gt;JP Norair, Leader of the Technical Working Group, DASH7 Alliance  &lt;a href="http://www.dash7.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dash7.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Louis Parks, President and CEO of  Secure RF&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.securerf.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.securerf.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Louis Parks is a co-founder of SecureRF. As CEO of SecureRF, Parks has helped guide the development of new cryptographic solutions and security tools for low-resource and embedded devices like radio frequency identification (RFID) and microcontrollers (MCU).&lt;br /&gt;Parks has consulted for Homeland Security on U.S. electronic border initiatives and has served as a resource to the White House on security issues related to the new electronic passports and passport cards. He is on the Board of Advisors of the National Center for Aerospace Leadership (NCAL), a partnership between US industry, academia and government teams, founded to respond to the critical needs of the US aerospace manufacturing supply chain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ann Grackin CEO ChainLink Research&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann has been a champion and catalyst for the RFID market through her firm ChainLink Research. Through research, writing, education and  workshops as well as her advisory role to Department of Defense, Walmart, industry associations such as CSCMP, ASPICS and many other leading firms, Ms. Grackin has been at the forefront of many industry-wide ventures to create one world with collaborative  business practices and safe and secure citizens. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register at &lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/dash7-wireless-sensor-networks/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/dash7-wireless-sensor-networks/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mitforumca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raghu Das</member_name><member_id>10876924</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Grackin</member_name><member_id>11301578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289956946000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279902737000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DASH 7  Alliance (ISO 18000-7)</name><id>14191442</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289862000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/14191442/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/6/global_19158870.jpeg</photo_url></item>