<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Interested in doing some hiking and seeing some of New England's beautiful fall foliage?  We'll drive from Alewife to Mount Monadnock, a 3,200 foot/1,000 m tall mountain in Southeast New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a very popular hike and the foliage should be near peak. For more information on Mount Monadnock, see: &lt;a href="http://monadnocktrails.com/"&gt;http://monadnocktrails.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The hike is average difficulty and takes about 4 hours roundtrip. The drive takes about 90 minutes each way. We expect to be back in Boston around 5 or 6 PM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring: water, lunch, and snacks for yourself; extra layers of warm clothing (it can be chilly on top of the mountain); and a camera if you like&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now we have only two cars, so the passenger limit is 12 people, including the 2 drivers. &lt;span&gt;If the trip fills up, please join the waiting list. If more people can drive, we will increase the limit of people who can come.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can drive and are willing to take passengers, please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it rains on the 20th, we will postpone the trip. If the weather is uncertain, please check here for updates around 8 AM on the 20th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet near the turnstiles about 9 AM on Saturday, 10/20.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob G</member_name><member_id>4202053</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350908498000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350087879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Foliage Hike: Mount Monadnock, NH</name><id>86757052</id><duration>30600000</duration><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350738000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/86757052/</event_url></item>