<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Newton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.309242</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Larz Anderson Auto/Transportation Museum</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1431177</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Join us for a tour of the night sky, constellations, and planets!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;The event is ON.  Jeff's excited, I'm excited, y'all sound excited.  It'll be cold--so bundle up!  I'll see you at 5pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A local expert I know (Jeff) will give a presentation on the constellations visible now to the naked eye, how the constellations move through the ecliptic over the course of the year, and other sundry celestial topics.  Some folks said they want to bring their telescopes, which would be great--Jeff will help us see the moons of Jupiter and possibly Uranus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will be held at Larz Anderson Park in Brookline, at the top of the hill where it's dark and away from the city lights.  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Turn into park at Larz Anderson Auto/Transportation Museum entrance on Newton Street, across from Dexter School, by St. Paul Street&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/photos/1156643/"&gt;A few photos&lt;/a&gt; of the entrance at night.    &lt;i&gt;More directions: from Jamaicaway/Pond Street -- pass Armenian Center (right), Avon Street (left), St. Paul St (left), then turn right at pole with park sign; from Brookline, up Goddard Street--turn left onto Newton, pass parking lot with 2 entrances; turn right at Dexter School --there's a low wall around the school across from the entrance.&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt; Once you turn in:&lt;/span&gt; Go up driveway, bear left, go up hill, past Auto Museum/castle building, keep going, jog right then turn left, there are parking spaces on your left and a concrete park-like fence (decorative)/looong gazebo structure on your right; keep going, turn right to the top of the hill --that's our meeting spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  there is a gala at the museum at 6pm, but we should be fine since we're starting at 5pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) &lt;b&gt; The event will be held even if it's cold.&lt;/b&gt;  If the temperature is low, wear thermal underwear and wool socks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2)  Jeff is doing this for free.   However, he does appreciate payment in the form of chocolate or cookies with chocolate. &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt; So please bring:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;chocolate/chocolate chip cookies or&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;a thermos of hot chocolate, coffee, or tea or&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;other snack food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for both Jeff, as a thank you, as well as to share with the group.&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to bring a mug/travel mug for the hot chocolate/coffee that folks will hopefully be bringing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Some people will need rides.  Please indicate if you can drive others--pickup at town X or MBTA station Y (&amp;quot;Malden T&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;North Shore-Beverly&amp;quot;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;A Yes RSVP means YES, you are coming.  It is rude to both the host (me) and the other attendees (you all) if you RSVP Yes, and then don't show.&lt;/span&gt;  People with high no-show rates will be removed from the RSVP list.  People who RSVP Maybe will be asked to change to Yes/No a few days before (if there's a waitlist, to allow those people to attend.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want more info on the constellations?  Check out: &lt;a href="http://www.skyandtelescope.com/observing/home/107510318.html"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skyandtelescope.com/observing/home/107510318.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.skyandtele...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's an optional dinner afterwards, which I'll post as a separate event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, since this is a social event, please make sure you have a photo of yourself in your profile.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>turn into park at Larz Anderson Auto / Transportation Museum on Newton St; turn in at museum sign, across from Dexter School, by St. Paul Street</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>6019932</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290453794000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289777519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Astronomy outdoors</name><id>15446362</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290290400000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15446362/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/5/global_19698725.jpeg</photo_url></item>