<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come meet the Wedelns or catch up with us if you're missing our company!&amp;nbsp; If you are curious in finding out what we do, we are an active, four season club and we'd love to tell you more about us!&amp;nbsp; There will be several Wedeln members at this event, full of answers to your questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If weather cooperates, we will be on the roofdeck for this event. Come as early as 5pm. Complimentary full food buffet starts at 6pm.&amp;nbsp; Cash bar.&amp;nbsp; Please note the dress code as they are strict and will refuse entry if you are wearing sneakers, shorts, t-shirts or hats. We don't make their rules but want to see you so please take note! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complimentary full food buffet (6-9) and free admission.  &lt;br /&gt;********************************************************    &lt;br /&gt;Sample menu (menu subject to change)  &lt;br /&gt;o Crab cakes, Buffalo  wings       &lt;br /&gt;o Marinated steak tips &lt;br /&gt;o Assorted Sliders                 &lt;br /&gt;o King Crab Lillipops &lt;br /&gt;o Delicious pastas &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dress code: &lt;br /&gt;Dress  to impress, NO Sneakers, shorts, t-shirts or hats &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Guest details:   &lt;br /&gt;All guests must be 21+ with proper ID. These events are geared  toward young professionals in their 20s, 30s, 40s. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;MBTA stop is  South Station or China Town &lt;br /&gt;Metered street is present and Valet  parking is $20&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Splash Lounge, 150 Kneeland Street, Boston  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.splash-boston.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.splash-boston.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>f weather cooperates, we will be on the roofdeck. Otherwise, we will be downstairs. Look for a group of smiling, friendly faces!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dani</member_name><member_id>10132142</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307115930000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304521486000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wedeln Happy Hour at Splash in Boston!!</name><id>17541150</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307048400000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/17541150/</event_url></item>