<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Doane Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01368</zip><lat>42.668553</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tully Lake Campground</name><city>Royalston</city><id>1380437</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.165308</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;This hike is on! Dress appropriately for a little breeze, and bring food and drink to snack on.  I will be at the kayak/canoe launch across the street from the Campground @9:45 in a silver Toyota Corolla with obscenities scratched into it (don't ask). Hope to see you all there.  978 821-9489 if you need to reach me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's spend some nice time walking the edge of Long Pond following mostly flat type terrain before we make our way up alongside Spirit Falls. The climb up (notice I didn't say walk) along the falls is rather strenuous, but luckily only about a quarter mile. From there we will walk along mostly flat terrain to Jacobs Ladder. As I have never been to the actual Jacobs Ladder, this part of the hike will be an adventure! &lt;br /&gt;

 If we feel up to it we can return the same way with a side trip to "the Ledges ". This adds about a mile to the 4 mile hike, give or take.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS &lt;br /&gt;

 In Massachusetts, take Route 2 to exit 17. Follow Route 32 North approximately 6 miles. &lt;br /&gt;

 From New Hampshire, follow Route 32 south about 8 miles from the intersection of Route 119 in Richmond. &lt;br /&gt;

 Route 32, also called Athol-Richmond Road, goes right over Tully Dam. The Recreation Area is at the north end of the dam. The Park Office is just south of the dam. &lt;br /&gt;

 To get to the Campground, take Doane Hill Road off of Route 32 north of the dam. Travel about 3/4 mile and the Campground will be on your right, just before the Tully River. &lt;br /&gt;

 WE WILL BE PARKING JUST PAST THE CAMPGROUND BUT ON THE OPPOSITE SIDE OF THE ROAD. This is a canoe/kayak launching area, but there is plenty of room. &lt;br /&gt;

 With rest stops and time to stand with our mouths agape admiring the views, this should take 3-4 hours. I am attending a Halloween party the night before, so I may walk a bit slower than normal!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry Rooney</member_name><member_id>43555442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351603954000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350777761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore Long Pond, Spirit Falls, and Jacobs Ladder in Royalston MA</name><id>87857662</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351432800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/87857662/</event_url></item>