<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a &lt;b&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/b&gt;.  Please be respectful of others who may want to RSVP and &lt;i&gt;only sign up for one or two mini-meetups a month&lt;/i&gt;.  See this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt; for more details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;Are you a word junkie that needs a fix?  Can't find people that enjoy words as much as you do?  This afternoon the place will be open for a couple hours for a potpourri of word games.  Whatever you got bring it along; if it involves words, we'll play it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing too complicated about this meetup. ;-)  Keep in mind while this does have a suggested end time of 5:30 to allow people to attend another meetup on this same day.  However, people still interested in just word games can continue for as long as they want.  &lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;Food theme:&lt;br /&gt;The theme for this event will be &amp;quot;food that can mix &amp;amp; match&amp;quot;.  Since we often mix and match letters to form words in these game, let's bring food that go well alone or when combined with something else.  For example, one person can bring graham  crackers and another person can bring chocolate.  Feel free to post ideas in your RSVP so others can find something that will compliment your item.  We will also have generic drinks and snacks on hand for people with dietary restrictions.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;About the location:&lt;br /&gt;This event will be guest-hosted by another member's home in Salem who is graciously donating their space.  Details will be sent out to the YES RSVP's a couple days before the event.  There will be plenty of room and should be a warm, comfortable place for all, I promise.  There are two cats on the premises but will be upstairs and away from people participating in the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297021384000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291579134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Word Game Potpourri</name><id>15649156</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296928800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15649156/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/1/global_11205793.jpeg</photo_url></item>