<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Providence Place Mall</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.826747</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Providence WaterFire</name><city>Providence</city><id>1089680</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416949</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Come lets us enjoy the mystical experience Of Providence Rhode Island Water fire, We will leave at 2pm that day and have dinner near the river, walk around and enjoy the shops then watch the water fire experience and perhaps sip a glass of wine and listen to some live music before heading home&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WaterFire is an experience that embraces all of the senses and all of the city!  Come to enjoy yourself, to relax, and to discover a remarkable new urban experience in a fascinating modern city. WaterFire is presented for free, but we need your donations to keep the fires burning! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress up, dress casual, or dress festive.  WaterFire is a celebration of community and beauty.  Everyone is welcome, and we encourage you to become a part of the event. There is often live dancing at the Sovereign Plaza Ballroom and live Jazz at the Verizon Jazz Stage; and an ever-changing, eclectic music program all along the rivers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WaterFire is an event to be explored and savored on foot as you wander around to discover its many surprises, folding chairs are not recommended and often interfere with your experience of the event.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please enjoy yourself at WaterFire! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279663550000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275455144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"River Water Fire"</name><id>13667972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279411200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/13667972/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/1/global_4236481.jpeg</photo_url></item>