<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Conway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>43.985138</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-447-2280</phone><name>World Fellowship Camp</name><city>Conway</city><id>992492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.267663</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>World Fellowship center in NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see link below. &lt;br /&gt;Season is not started yet. Opportunity to work together, and stay for free (your work). &lt;br /&gt;As well as a good time to see if you'd want to come back when its fully operated! &lt;br /&gt;I go to this center for more then a decade and its never enough! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directors of the center, Andy and Andrea updated me on details: please work 4 hrs/day, no pay for stay, kitchen is going to operate, and three meals a day are going to be provided for guests. Work options: gardening, cleaning, construction.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring with you: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. working cloth, gloves if you have &lt;br /&gt;2. water bottle &lt;br /&gt;3. bug spray &lt;br /&gt;4. sun screen, hat &lt;br /&gt;5. flush light &lt;br /&gt;6. sleeping bag, pad, or bed sheets &lt;br /&gt;7. swimming wear &lt;br /&gt;8. hiking shoes &lt;br /&gt;9. book to read &lt;br /&gt;10.good mood! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Absolutely fabulous and unique center! You''ll love it!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All kinds of stimulating pleasures! Physical activities, social, intellectual, spiritual-(nature)!  &lt;br /&gt;OK to come on Friday, May 28, till Mon, May 31st !  &lt;br /&gt;If it rains, still good to be there. Big house with fire place, Library, piano, games and great mountain view! There are few rustic cute lodges on a campus, garden, hiking trails around, lake, canoes, etc..  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call me if you have any question!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by Th., May 27th 10 am. I will inform Andy and Andrea on how many coming Fr., and Sat. To accommodate you best! They are looking forward meeting you all and thankful for your interest and willingness to work! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can drive people who need a ride! &lt;br /&gt;call me on details. Fri., Sat. and back. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.worldfellowship.org/index.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.worldfello...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maia  &lt;br /&gt;78-718-6203&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maia</member_name><member_id>3083598</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275067067000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271685081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Memorial weekend with friends at</name><id>13223541</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275062400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/13223541/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/9/global_9271705.jpeg</photo_url></item>