<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>92 Wattaquadock Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.431118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nashoba Valley Winery</name><city>Bolton</city><id>9085682</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.616920</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;BLUEGRASS AND BREWS FESTIVAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read the entire event's description. There have been changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, October 21, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The festival runs from : Noon - 5:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is everyone's favorite annual fall festival at Nashoba Valley Winery ! This festival highlights the hand crafted micro-brewed beers of our brewer. Relax, sit back, and enjoy some bluegrass music by Southern Rail. Stroll by the pavilion, visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;******&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;10/ 14 UPDDATE:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Due to the Popularity of this Event, to help pay for traffic and police detail requested by the Town and to help contribute to our farm for the bad apple crop this year, we are charging a $5.00 per person entrance fee to this year's Bluegrass &amp;amp; Brews event IF you pre-register! ONLY individuals 21 years of age or older can pre-register and purchase tickets prior to the event. If you DO NOT pre-register and are 21 years of age or older the entrance fee is $10 per person at the gate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;(NOTE: We will be accepting CASH ONLY AT ALL ADMISSIONS GATES, And CASH ONLY FOR FOOD AND BEER. We do have an ATM ON SITE BUT THE LINE COULD BE LONG)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Ages 15 to 20 will be charged $5.00 at the gate. Individuals under the age of 15 will be admitted free.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Pre-registration will be closed once 1500 tickets are sold and only on-site admission ticket purchases will be available. PRE-REGISTER @ &lt;a href="http://www.nashobavalleywinery.com"&gt;www.nashobavalleywinery.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Admission grants access to the picnic grounds, music grounds and beer garden. Food at the Pavilion and JAAS Snack Shack as well as the Wine Shoppe are open to the general public.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;The pre-purchase of a ticket does not guarantee parking at the winery. Parking is based on availability. We have made arrangements with a local church (approximately 800 yards) and the local school (approximately 1/2 mile) for satellite parking should our lots become full. &lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Shuttle buses are not provided from either of these locations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #462116"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #052501"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;PLEASE CAR POOL or MEET AT A REMOTE LOCATION AND CAR POOL IN.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***************************************************************************JAAS snack shack will be open to purchase a cider donut or a caramel apple, savor the smells of barbecue provided by the chef’s from the restaurant, J’s. And finally, take a tour of the winery or simply taste many of Nashoba Valley Winery's award winning wines Sign up for the winery tour in front of the wine shoppe at the information table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*There are plenty of picnic tables. Or, you may want to bring a chair or blanket. You are also welcome to bring your own cooler(s) Wine may be purchased in the shop to enhance your picnic. If unable to find the group, my contact # is: 978-289.7679&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SOUTHERN RAIL &lt;br /&gt;

 Southern Rail’s music is high energy exuberant fun, with riveting harmonies, irreverent humor and sparkling banjo and mandolin solo work. Their songs have graced Bluegrass Unlimited’s Top Thirty Singles Chart receiving heavy national airplay. Southern Rail has a loyal fan base that makes every concert an event that the whole family can enjoy. So relax, put down your blanket and enjoy the music&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*THIS IS A SHARED EVENT WITH OTHER MEETUP GROUPS &lt;br /&gt;

 This event is open to all&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be @ the closest possible table we can get to the Wine Shoppe- there will be a meetup sign on the table. I will also wear a meetup pin.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Johannah W</member_name><member_id>60834042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350850697000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>travel-575</urlname><id>418980</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Old and Not so Old Ladies Travel</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346860415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bluegrass &amp; Blues Festival- Nashoba Valley Winery</name><id>80955292</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350838800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/travel-575/events/80955292/</event_url></item>