<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1815 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.387146</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-354-7766</phone><name>Tavern in the Square - Porter</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>859456</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118996</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note that the originally scheduled talk by Chris Reddy of Woods Hole has been postponed to a later date.&amp;nbsp; In his place will be Welkin Johnson discussing replication of HIV-like viruses&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/9/b/event_11609339.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;It's the second Tuesday of April, and you know what that means - Science by the Pint!&amp;nbsp; Join us again at Tavern in the Square for suds and cutting edge research, as Welkin Johnson and his lab members discuss how viruses like HIV replicate.&amp;nbsp; And of course there'll be the usual one on one mingling and questions for the scientists. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This time the restaurant manager knows what we're up to (hopefully), so seating should be better managed.&amp;nbsp; But nonetheless, trying to reserve large blocks of space just doesn't seem to work at that place.&amp;nbsp; So just come by early if you can and look for folks.&amp;nbsp; I'll be there about 6:15 with a Meetup sign at one table at least, and whoever shows up early can help garner a few more.&amp;nbsp; Once again, curtain time is 7:00, and getting settled ahead of time gives you a chance to get food and foam in front of you :) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Again, T/SQ is just a few blocks south down Mass Ave from the Porter T Stop (in the direction of Harvard).&amp;nbsp; And if you must drive, you're responsible for your own parking search squad. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, and cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.taverninthesquare.com/tavporter/"&gt;http://www.taverninthesquare.com/tavporter/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From SITN: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Science by the Pint is back in full force for its second season  &lt;br /&gt;at a new venue, the Tavern in the Square in Porter Square.  &lt;br /&gt;Science by the Pint is SITN's own science cafe - a fun,  &lt;br /&gt;informal event where scientists mingle with the general public  &lt;br /&gt;to talk about their research, why they do it, and how it  &lt;br /&gt;affects the world. Join us the second Tuesday of each month  &lt;br /&gt;from 7-9pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302738960000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300646853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science by the Pint: Welkin Johnson on Virus Replication</name><id>16988031</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302647400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/16988031/</event_url></item>