<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Yawkey Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.346672</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 267-9440 </phone><name>Fenway Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>567754</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098885</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here's the &lt;strong&gt;"Post Run Meeting Spots"&lt;/strong&gt;- Since Craig and my last name are D and F, we can be found in &lt;strong&gt;Section 4 &lt;/strong&gt;after the race.&amp;nbsp; Below is a map of Fenway.&amp;nbsp; Looking forward to seeing everyone!&amp;nbsp; It's going to be an amazing day!&amp;nbsp; Mindy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;**************************************************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Post-Run Meet Spot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those trying to find friends and family after the race, we have designated areas in Fenway by RUNNERS LAST NAME. Avoid confusion after the Run! Review the ballpark map with MEET UP locations posted&amp;nbsp;below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://cache.trustedpartner.com/images/library/RedSoxRace/Content/Run/After-The-Race-Meet-Your-Runner-by-Last-Name.png" width="685" height="416" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;Family Fun Activities on Race Day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch the &lt;span&gt;opening ceremony&lt;/span&gt; inside &lt;span&gt;Fenway Park&lt;/span&gt; &amp;ndash; Arrive at Gate B or E and be sure to take a seat near the stage before 7:15AM. RUNNERS WILL BE SEATED ACCORDING TO STRIPE COLOR ON BIB by 7:20 AM TO START RACE ON TIME&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meet Wally the Green Monster&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take your photo with the 2004 and &lt;span&gt;2007 World Series&lt;/span&gt; Trophies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet Red Sox Legends &lt;/strong&gt;-While friends and family members wait for you to finish the race, they can say hello and take their picture with &lt;span&gt;Luis Tiant&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span&gt;Carlton Fisk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visit the Family Fun Zone Presented by Our Family for Families First &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to show your appreciation to a heroic service member currently deployed in &lt;span&gt;Iraq&lt;/span&gt; or &lt;span&gt;Afghanistan&lt;/span&gt;? &lt;strong&gt;Visit the Military Appreciation Area Presented by &lt;span&gt;BAE Systems&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;and assemble a &lt;span&gt;care package&lt;/span&gt; with provided supplies free of charge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visit Sponsor and Veteran informational tables&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take a self-guided tour of Fenway Park &lt;/strong&gt;&amp;ndash; see &lt;span&gt;Tour Guides&lt;/span&gt; with signs posted at select areas of the ballpark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Run to Home Base will end at NOON or earlier if weather requires.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;INFORMATION&lt;/span&gt; for the day of the&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"RUN TO HOME BASE" on Sunday May, 22nd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Here's updated information on &lt;strong&gt;parking, arrival gates at Fenway and activities&lt;/strong&gt; until noon for the &lt;strong&gt;"RUN&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TO HOME BASE"&lt;/strong&gt; on Sunday, May 22nd.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Opening ceremonies &lt;/strong&gt;with special guests start at&lt;strong&gt; 7:20am&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp; There will be road closures and delays on Sunday around Fenway, so people might want to take the &lt;strong&gt;GREEN line "T" to Kenmore Square, &lt;/strong&gt;or park in a different area and take the "T" in.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone at Fenway and thank you in advance for coming out to support a great cause!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Thanks,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Mindy Finkelstein&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;www.runtohomebase.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;RACE DAY, &lt;span&gt;SUNDAY MAY 22nd&lt;/span&gt; - ARRIVING AT &lt;span&gt;FENWAY&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Parking:&amp;nbsp; Lots&lt;/span&gt; around Fenway charge even &lt;span&gt;on Sunday&lt;/span&gt; and due to the Run, on street parking will NOT be available on most streets around the ballpark.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Lots in the area will be posted on the website &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;www.runtohomebase.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt; under the Heading &amp;ldquo;Run&amp;rdquo; in the next few days.&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please be sure to plan your route in advance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and expect &lt;span&gt;road closures&lt;/span&gt; and delays! &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We know from past experience that it will take much longer to get to Fenway on Race Day and the later you arrive, the more detours you will encounter, so please plan to arrive early.&lt;/span&gt; If you can, consider parking a short walk from Fenway as the lots closet to ballpark fill early or will have the longest lines. The closest T stop is the &lt;strong&gt;GREEN LINE &amp;ndash; &lt;span&gt;Kenmore Square&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and entrance is about 2- 3 blocks from Kenmore Square up Brookline Ave. Please check&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;SUNDAY MBTA schedules&lt;/strong&gt; as they often differ from weekday schedule.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opening Ceremonies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; This year, the opening ceremony will take place INSIDE Fenway Park so all runners and guests can see and hear the proceedings and&amp;nbsp; the &lt;strong&gt;very special guests&lt;/strong&gt; we will have to thank you for participating in this important salute to our military and wounded veterans.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;ALL runners will be seated in SPECIFIC ASSIGNED SECTIONS of Fenway by 7:15 AM&lt;/strong&gt; We encourage guests to arrive in time to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;attend the Opening Ceremonies and watch the start of the race and enjoy the exhibits and the Military Appreciation area by BAE Systems and Family Fun Zone by Families First inside the Fenway concourses for free.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;You are welcome to invite as many family and friends as you like!&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; The new exceptional video boards installed at Fenway will give sparkling views of the Run start from the comfort of seats at Fenway &amp;ndash; or after the Opening Ceremonies, fans can proceed to one of the designated areas behind the barriers on Yawkey Way or on the 2nd and 3rd levels of the ballpark.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;(Runners: You will be directed to sit in a specific section of Fenway&lt;/span&gt;). &lt;strong&gt;Family and friends are invited to sit in other designated sections of Fenway Park nearby and can enjoy the Opening Ceremonies&lt;/strong&gt; and can watch your start as indicated above.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;Following the opening ceremony, runners will be given instructions for each start on Yawkey Way. Each of the 3 waves will have an official race start on Yawkey Way. The 3-wave start, however, will help avoid a backlog at home plate. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activities for Family and Friends Before, During and After Your Run to Home Base&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please invite all of your friends and family to come watch your run at &lt;span&gt;Fenway Park!&amp;nbsp; There&lt;/span&gt; will be exhibits, family activities and a Military Appreciation area for all ages &amp;ndash; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;all for FREE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Select Concessions stands inside Fenway will be open for coffee, refreshments and snacks.&amp;nbsp; Gate B opens at 5:30AM and Gate E near the corner of Brookline Ave and Lansdowne Street (across from the Cask &amp;lsquo;n Flagon) opens at 6AM.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;WE ENCOURAGE FANS TO COME TO THE OPENING CEREMONIES&lt;/strong&gt;. Seating inside Fenway and near the field and stage will be on a first-come basis, so encourage them to arrive by 7:15am. Concessions will be open for breakfast! &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;We have lots of fun activities and exhibits in the Fenway concourse to keep friends and family busy while you are running and after you complete the race!&amp;nbsp; Activities will be available until NOON. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;Activities include: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;New Balance&lt;/span&gt; Interactive Family Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Military Appreciation Area sponsored by BAE Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; where guests can write a &amp;ldquo;thank-you&amp;rdquo; card or letter and assemble a care package to be sent to a service member now in Iraq or Afghanistan. PLEASE NOTE:&amp;nbsp; IF YOU KNOW SOMEONE SERVING IN IRAQ AND AFGHANISTAN WHO WILL BE STATIONED THERE THROUGH &lt;span&gt;JUNE 30, 2011&lt;/span&gt;, PLEASE SEND US THEIR FULL MAILING ADDRESS at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:military@redsox.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;military@redsox.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt; and we will add them to our list for &lt;span&gt;care packages&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;Free care package&lt;/span&gt; materials will be available on-site thanks to BAE&amp;rsquo;s generous support, but we welcome Runners and fans to bring NEW or GENTLY-USED recent DVDs. No other materials please. All packages will be mailed by Home Base/BAE staff. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family Fun Zone sponsored by Families First Foundation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that features carnival games, balloon animals, coloring and fun animals. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Opportunities to meet Red Sox Legends&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 16px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Say hello to&lt;/span&gt; Red &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Sox legends &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Luis Tiant and Carlton Fisk,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; who are tentatively scheduled to join us for part of the&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;morning festivities!&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;T&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ake your picture with &lt;span&gt;Wally the Green Monster&lt;/span&gt;, and with the &lt;span&gt;Red Sox&lt;/span&gt; 2004 and &lt;span&gt;2007 World Series&lt;/span&gt; Trophies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. BRING YOUR CAMERA or you may purchase pictures from Fan Photo. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self Guide Tours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; We will have Fenway Park&amp;rsquo;s &lt;span&gt;expert tour guides&lt;/span&gt; stationed at select points of interest throughout the ballpark.&amp;nbsp; Look for their large TOUR SIGNS and they will offer free, fascinating information about that area of the ballpark and the history of &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;America&amp;rsquo;s Most Beloved Ballpark&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walk Around the Warning Track:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; After the Run, and weather permitting, we hope to allow fans the chance to stroll around Fenway&amp;rsquo;s famous warning track. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information Tables about the Home Base Program and many veteran service organizations and sponsors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Send us names and addresses of servicemen and women deployed in Iraq and Afghanistan and bring new or gently used DVDs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; If you know someone who is now serving in Iraq or Afghanistan who will be there at least through JUNE 30, 2011, please email us their full name and military address to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:military@redsox.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;military@redsox.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;so we can send them a care package&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Have friends and family bring new and gently-used DVDs to Fenway Park on Sunday, May 22nd and we&amp;rsquo;ll include them in care packages. Please do not bring other materials. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet Up with Family and Friends After Your Run:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; We have assigned &amp;ldquo;Meet Spots&amp;rdquo; where Runners can meet friends and family members after the race, assigned by the letter of each Runner&amp;rsquo;s Last Name. A &amp;ldquo;meeting spot&amp;rdquo; diagram will be added to the Run website in the next several days. We suggest that you have family and friends download the diagram and bring&amp;nbsp; it with them since you won&amp;rsquo;t have a cell phone crossing the finish line!&amp;nbsp; After you Run, we&amp;nbsp;will have&amp;nbsp;water and a&amp;nbsp;snack available for runners and you can then proceed to your family and friends meeting area. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please note:&amp;nbsp; There is NO field access to anyone during the Run except Runners as they cross home plate and credentialed Race operations staff.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; However with Fenway&amp;rsquo;s new high definition video boards, &lt;strong&gt;the start, timed finish at the &lt;span&gt;Green Monster&lt;/span&gt; and runners crossing home plate will all be broadcast, larger than life and for easy viewing pleasure by all fans inside Fenway Park!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pre-Run Publicity You Can Share with Donors or Potential Supporters:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;The Run to Home Base presented by New Balance&lt;/strong&gt; has been receiving a lot of publicity &amp;ndash; check it out at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/homebaseprogram" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;www.facebook.com/homebaseprogram&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;. We welcome you to post links to the Run stories on your &lt;span&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt; and retweet stories that inspire you so they can inspire other runners and potential donors to your run!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arrival Gate: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Sunday, May 22nd&lt;/span&gt;, the main entrance to &lt;span&gt;Fenway Park&lt;/span&gt; will be Gate B&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; at the corner of Ipswich and Van Ness Streets (across from Fenway High School). &lt;strong&gt;GATE B will open at 5:30AM for runners and any guests you wish to invite.&lt;/strong&gt; Gate E near the corner of Brookline Ave and Lansdowne Street (across from the &lt;span&gt;Cask &amp;lsquo;n Flagon&lt;/span&gt;) opens at 6am.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note there will be security check before entry to Fenway Park for all who wish to carry any bags inside the ballpark, so please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 18px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&amp;#65279;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;RUN to HOME BASE 9K:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Sox Native Mindy Finkelstein will be running this years race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year our own Native Pinch Runner Lindsay ran the Run to Home Base road race in support of local servicemen and women returning from combat in Iraq and Afghanistan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Run to Home Base is a 9K race organized by the Red Sox Foundation  &lt;br /&gt;and Massachusetts General Hospital. The funds raised will go toward the  &lt;br /&gt;Home Base Program, a philanthropic partnership that is dedicated to  &lt;br /&gt;improving the lives of New England servicemen and women returning home  &lt;br /&gt;with combat stress disorders through clinical care, innovative research,  &lt;br /&gt;education, family support, and community outreach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This cause means a lot to many of us who know family and friends with men and and women that have willingly signed up to fight overseas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the race on the website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;www.runtohomebase.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be donating to and sponsoring Red Sox Native Mindy Finkelstein. Since a Native is running I will arrange for a group to enter Fenway Park, cheer and go on to the field weather and field conditions permitting. Last year this was a blast! See the 2010 event post comments and photographs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone wants to attend and go out on to the field please RSVP also with the comment "attending."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To donate, go to the home page, &lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.runtohomeb...&lt;/a&gt; and click on Support a Runner. Type in the first and last name (mindy finkelstein) in lower case letters and hit the search button; that will bring you to another page where you can click on the name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the next page, click on Make A Donation and follow the prompts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The deadline to donate is Wednesday, May18.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fenway frank&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post Script: Last year Lindsay did the math; 9 kilometers around home base equals  &lt;br /&gt;80.7 home runs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Section 18 Box Seats During Race, Meet at Pesky Pole After Race to Enter Field Weather &amp; Red Sox Permitting</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>3178870</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306209443000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>It is a great cause and a chance to be on the Fenway Park field. Priceless!</why><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293575742000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Info for the day of Mindy's Run to Home Base 9K -Help support our troops! May 22</name><id>15842018</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306065600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/15842018/</event_url></item>