<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>475 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.367938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 894-8755</phone><name>Little India</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739937</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.237468</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Brick-Lane-Novel-Monica-Ali/dp/B000WMOEUS/ref=pd_bbs_sr_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1230743643&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;Brick Lane on Amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon.com Review&lt;br /&gt;Wildly embraced by critics, readers, and contest judges (who put it on the short-list for the 2003 Man Booker Prize), Brick Lane is indeed a rare find: a book that lives up to its hype. Monica Ali's debut novel chronicles the life of Nazneen, a Bangladeshi girl so sickly at birth that the midwife at first declares her stillborn. At 18 her parents arrange a marriage to Chanu, a Bengali immigrant living in England. Although Chanu--who's twice Nazneen's age--turns out to be a foolish blowhard who &amp;quot;had a face like a frog,&amp;quot; Nazneen accepts her fate, which seems to be the main life lesson taught by the women in her family. &amp;quot;If God wanted us to ask questions,&amp;quot; her mother tells her, &amp;quot;he would have made us men.&amp;quot; Over the next decade-and-a-half Nazneen grows into a strong, confident woman who doesn't defy fate so much as bend it to her will. The great delight to be had in Brick Lane lies with Ali's characters, from Chanu the kindly fool to Mrs. Islam the elderly loan shark to Karim the political rabblerouser, all living in a hothouse of Bengali immigrants. Brick Lane combines the wide scope of a social novel about the struggles of Islamic immigrants in pre- and post-9/11 England with the intimate story of Nazneen, one of the more memorable heroines to come along in a long time. If Dickens or Trollope were loosed upon contemporary London, this is exactly the sort of novel they would cook up. --Claire Dederer --This text refers to the Hardcover edition.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256571569000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230743518000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February - Brick Lane by Monica Ali</name><id>9414109</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234630800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/9414109/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_5395668.jpeg</photo_url></item>