<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>242 E Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06787</zip><lat>41.673990</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-283-RAIL (7245)</phone><name>Railroad Museum of New England</name><city>Thomaston</city><id>175337</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.067440</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; Purchase tickets online or by calling 860-283-7245. Reservations only with deadline to purchase tickets no later than October 1. Enjoy this unique experience with the Haight-Brown Vineyard Express! Adults only. Spend the afternoon in old-time luxury! Meet at the Railroad Museum of New England's Thomaston train station by 1:30 PM before boarding your 1920s era vintage railroad car. Enjoy a scenic New England train ride while enjoying a glass of wine and light appetizer from Haight-Brown Vineyard. After your hour and 15 minute train ride, you will board a charter bus and head to Haight-Brown Vineyard for a winery tour, full wine tasting and plenty of culinary delights by a local caterer. Haight-Brown Vineyard will deliver you by bus back to Thomaston train station after the wine tastings. Pick up tickets at Thomaston Station's WILL CALL window on the day of the event. All tickets are non-refundable/non-exchangeable. Board your train at the Thomaston Station in Thomaston, CT. Please arrive at the Station 30 minutes before train departure time at 2:00. Trains run on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $75.00 a person.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call Me</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318156337000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315363512000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>" A Perfect Afternoon" Autumn Foliage &amp; Wine Tasting Train Ride</name><id>32544632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318095000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/32544632/</event_url></item>