<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.395172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sullivan Square T station</name><city>Charleston</city><id>2152511</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066521</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;UPDATED&amp;nbsp;07-20-11&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Last chance to attend our Totally Baller- bring tons of food- libations-and- friends-hike! All plans at the ready- just email Evan or myself (Emilie) at eheilig2@hotmail.com or call me at 773-746-3710. Sat night camp out and Sun morn hike the tallest mtn in NH! Conquer your 4k footers now :).&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Yes, I know, I'm sorry this is not a promotional hike to raise funds for scoliosis, rheumatoid arthritis, colon cancer, or breast implants. Nor have we advertised that we might give away free chocolate bars, marshmallows, and graham crackers, but we assumed that was par for the course! Come join in some moshing, campfire bonding, and hiking of the COOL summit of Mt. Washington, away from that nasty heat wave. Swimming and a complimentary post-hike glow free with your RSVP of "yes."&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summer months are scarce for meetups because a lot of people want to enjoy the weather and make the best of it. This meetup is for those who like hiking the white mountains and want to get to know other Godless hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a 2 day trip with the sole purpose of hiking/climbing Mt Washington. We are not trying to exclude anyone, but this is an experienced hike with interest in the group among some of the regular hikers. As a minimum, we&amp;nbsp;require that anyone signing up have at least 2&amp;nbsp;summits&amp;nbsp;on "four thousand footers" in the white mountains this year. Please take note that this is the highest peak, the most challenging terrain you are likely to encounter in the White Mountains, with incredibly variable and potentially dangerous conditions. This hike is difficult for even the best conditioned people. This hike is for advanced hikers only.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/recreation/hiking/hiking-mtwashington.cfm"&gt;http://www.outdoors.org/recreation/hiking/hiking-mtwashington.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Meetup Details (how we will get there)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet saturday afternoon at thirteen thirty (130pm)&amp;nbsp;in the&amp;nbsp;Sullivan Sq T Stop parking lot.&amp;nbsp;If you have a car, let us know in the RSVP (type and seats) so we can try and arrange car pooling. From the Sullivan Sq T stop we will get on the 93 and drive to Mt Washington for our&amp;nbsp;camp site (reserved sites are already booked so we will be using a public camp site on Old Cherry Mt Road just before Bretton Woods).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can't make the randevous at Sullivan Sq, or if you are already in the White Mountains Saturday morning and want to join the hike&amp;nbsp;then give Evan a call at 702-280-3583 so you can get progressive directions to the camp site, or the hike Sunday&amp;nbsp;morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;What you need to bring:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mount Washington&amp;nbsp;can be dangerous due to notoriously high winds and unpredictable weather. Please bring appropriate provisions and hiking gear in preparation. In addition to food, water, and camping gear be sure to bring the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Synthetic or wool base layer &amp;ndash; t-shirt, or underwear tops and bottoms&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Synthetic or wool long pants &amp;ndash; zip off pants and convert to shorts are popular during warm weather months&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wool sweater or synthetic pile jacket&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hat&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gloves or mittens&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bandanna or handkerchief&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Wind and rain gear&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; waterproof/breathable fabrics recommended&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Extra socks (a welcome treat for the feet at mid-hike, or if you inadvertently step in a stream. They also double as mittens)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Sturdy boots (a must)&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;2 liters of water minimum (a must)&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Food for two whole days (in the event we end up camping overnight, make sure you have enough)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stoves (reply in message below if you have one and can share)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Tent&lt;/strong&gt; (reply in message below if you have one and can share, also message if you need a tent/ tent-share)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sleeping bag and sleeping pad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;About the Hike:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since&amp;nbsp;Tuckerman's Ravine trail is currently closed, we will be hiking the west side loop (up Ammonoosuc Ravine and down Jewell trail) which is 9.6 miles, and will take approximately 7.5 to 8.0 hours to complete (to&amp;nbsp;include time at the summit).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/%7Eellozy/washington.html"&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Website with maps and information:&lt;/span&gt; http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/washington.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt Washington weather info: 
&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/recreation/tripplanner/go/pinkham-washington-weather.cfm"&gt;http://www.outdoors.org/recreation/tripplanner/go/pinkham-washington-weather.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: HIKING HAS INHERENT RISKS.&amp;nbsp;DO NOT ATTEND THIS MEETUP IF YOU ARE&amp;nbsp;UNSURE IF YOU ARE ADEQUATELY PREPARED. AS A GROUP WE CAN DECREASE RISK BY BUDDYING UP AND LOOKING OUT FOR EACH OTHER BUT NOBODY IS LIABLE FOR YOU.&amp;nbsp;THIS IS A VOLUNTARY HIKE AND IF YOU ATTEND YOU ARE ASSUMING THE RISK.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking lot of Sullivan Square T station</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>4427039</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311625366000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311012763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TOTALLY BALLER Once in a LIFETIME Camp and Hike Mt. Washington</name><id>26159621</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311442200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/26159621/</event_url></item>