<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>All around town!</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.345333</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ashmont/Peabody Square, Dudley Square, the Fenway, Fort Point Channel, Jackson Square and Maverick Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>589193</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100449</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Everyone is invited to Common Boston Weekend '08, a citywide architecture festival featuring open buildings, design displays and neighborhood tours led by design professionals, neighborhood residents, city officials, cyclists and even chefs. It's all free! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ashmont/Peabody Square&lt;br /&gt;*May 10, 12:30 pm: join Historic New England for a tour of the 1683 Pierce House.&lt;br /&gt;*May 11, 12:30 pm: view the changes underway around Dorchester's Peabody Square through the eyes of designers, residents, historians, chefs and more. Enjoy Ashmont Grill refreshments, a presentation by chef and owner Chris Douglass, and a bonus tour of All Saints Ashmont church at 4 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dudley Square&lt;br /&gt;*May 8, 6 pm: explore Roxbury's religious evolution at a talk by State Representative Byron Rushing at the Dudley Branch Library. &lt;br /&gt;The rest are on May 10:&lt;br /&gt;*10 am to noon: take a trolley tour of Dudley Square's churches, mosques and synagogues. &lt;br /&gt;*10 to 11:30 am: learn about Roxbury's role in U.S. history on a &amp;quot;From the Puritans to the Patriots&amp;quot; walking tour with WalkBoston.&lt;br /&gt;*Noon to 6 pm: view the results of the Dudley Square Community Charrette and Competition at Hibernian Hall (184 Dudley Street, Roxbury). Design teams have entered proposals for a mixed-use redevelopment of the B-2 police station site. Winners will be announced Saturday and present Sunday at 2 pm. &lt;br /&gt;*12:30 pm and 2:30 pm: tour Project Hope--the first LEED-certified building in Roxbury.&lt;br /&gt;*1 to 2:30 pm: attend a screening of Holding Ground: The Rebirth of Dudley Square at the Dudley Branch Library. &lt;br /&gt;*1 to 3 pm: explore the neighborhoods of Fountain Hill, Fort Hill and Mission Hill on the &amp;quot;Roxbury Peakbagging&amp;quot; tour to gain a fresh understanding of how natural and architectural forces shape our city.&lt;br /&gt;*2:45 to 4:45 pm: the Designery hosts an open studio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Fenway&lt;br /&gt;All on May 9:&lt;br /&gt;*11 am and noon: the Friends of Fenway Studios will give visitors an inside look into artists' studios and their National Historic Landmark building.&lt;br /&gt;*11 am: tour the Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum.&lt;br /&gt;*Noon to 1:30 pm: explore the Christian Science Center's Mary Baker Eddy Library, Mapparium, Hall of Ideas and Mother Church.&lt;br /&gt;*1:30 pm: tour Fenway Park.&lt;br /&gt;*1 to 2:30 pm: tour Brigham and Women's Carl J. and Ruth Shapiro Cardiovascular Center, which will be the first LEED-certified hospital facility in NE.&lt;br /&gt;*4 pm: visit Symphony Hall.&lt;br /&gt;*6 pm: hop on a bicycle for an Art + Architecture Tour. (Free for the first 20 people to pre-register; others may join the tour at a reduced rate.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fort Point Channel&lt;br /&gt;*May 9, noon to 1:30 pm: tour the Moakley Courthouse. &lt;br /&gt;*May 9, noon to 1:30 pm: tour the Macallen Building and its living green roof. &lt;br /&gt;*May 9, 1:30 to 3:00 pm: check out the Artists for Humanity EpiCenter--one of the AIA's top 10 sustainable buildings in the country.&lt;br /&gt;*May 10, 10 to 11:30 am: learn about the history and future of the neighborhood with the BSA's Urban Design Committee. &lt;br /&gt;*May 10, 11 to noon: Learning By Design leads a hands-on walking tour for children (ages 7 and up) and families. Observe, touch, draw and do texture rubbings. We depart from the Children's Museum.&lt;br /&gt;*May 11, 10 to 11:30 am: Urban AdvenTours holds a green buildings bike tour. (Free for the first 20 people to pre-register; others may join the tour at a reduced rate.)&lt;br /&gt;*May 11, noon to 1:30 pm: join the Fort Point Arts Community and experience the artists' studios and public art.&lt;br /&gt;*May 11, 2:30 to 4:30 pm: tour the Institute of Contemporary Art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jackson Square&lt;br /&gt;All on May 10: &lt;br /&gt;*11 am to 12:30 pm: local chef Nadine Nelson of Discerning Taste leads a neighborhood food tour of specialty food shops, ethnic eateries, independently owned coffee and tea shops, bakeries, cooperative markets and more. &lt;br /&gt;*12:30 to 1:30 pm: explore the Boston Neighborhood Network's new environmentally sustainable studios in the Egleston Power Station.&lt;br /&gt;*2 to 4 pm: tour Jackson Square and learn about its future from community members, designers and city officials.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maverick Square &lt;br /&gt;All on May 11: &lt;br /&gt;*11 am: local chef Nadine Nelson of Discerning Taste leads a neighborhood food tour. Munch your way through the best empanadas in the city, Vietnamese pho, old-world Italian food, Salvadorean enchiladas and Peruvian chicken brasas.&lt;br /&gt;*Noon to 2 pm: East Boston Savings Bank opens the building for self-guided tours. &lt;br /&gt;*Noon to 4:00 pm: visit the Atlantic Works Artists Lofts--Cultural Exchange Center &amp;amp; Galleries.&lt;br /&gt;*Noon to 4 pm: the East Boston YMCA hosts an open building. &lt;br /&gt;*1 pm: take a tour exploring &amp;quot;Immigration and Constant Change in East Boston.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;*1 pm: take a tour of Bremen Street Park.&lt;br /&gt;*1 pm: ZUMIX opens its building for self-guided tours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, contact Justin Crane (617-816-3777 or info@commonboston.org) or visit &lt;a href="http://www.commonboston.org/cb08" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.commonbost...&lt;/a&gt; for the latest event schedule. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**PLEASE NOTE: RSVP to &lt;a href="http://www.commonboston.org/cb08" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.commonbost...&lt;/a&gt;, not just at the Meetup site!**&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Moser-Booth</member_name><member_id>6447986</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210518463000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Celebrate our neighborhoods and communities at this free citywide architecture festival!</why><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209139038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Common Boston Weekend '08</name><id>7810746</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210345200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/7810746/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/3/b/global_3977435.jpeg</photo_url></item>