<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16-18 North Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.360541</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-742-3333</phone><name>Red Sky Restaurant and Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>847253</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056248</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us for a fun social mixer while raising money for a great cause! Our team is doing the 160 mile Bike Trek this October again and we need your support! Free food, drink specials from Dos Equis, free drink specials from 7-8PM from Absolut, and we will hold a huge silent auction with some fabulous items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be in the private room of Red Sky Restaurant to mix and mingle, in the back area. Come for a drink and munchies, see old friends, meet new ones and support an important cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5 cover at private room entrance-cash only. All proceeds from the party will be donated to the American Lung Association. We will be taking credit cards for the auction items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can stop by!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't make the party please take a moment and donate what you can to help us get to our goal: &lt;a href="http://www.mrsnv.com/evt/e01/team.jsp;jsessionid=a6301b8db96761221c7f?id=2210&amp;amp;tid=32717" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mrsnv.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, if you are up for the challenge, JOIN our team of guys and gals.  Last year was an amazing experience and it may sound difficult--but it wasn't that hard.  There are a ton of activities after each day including a lobster dinner--it makes it all worth it!  Come train with the team!&lt;br /&gt;Join here: &lt;a href="http://www.mrsnv.com/evt/e01/team.jsp;jsessionid=a6301b8db96761221c7f?id=2210&amp;amp;tid=32717" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mrsnv.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is posted on multiple meetup groups so please only RSVP once. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing angel wings-come meet the team</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314163313000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>47</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244988955000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social mixer to raise funds for the American Lung Association</name><id>10648601</id><headcount>47</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245366000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10648601/</event_url></item>