<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>249 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395308</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yoga In The Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>941611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121885</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>64.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Embody Your Authentic Masculine Power&lt;br /&gt;12:30-4:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've changed the time to 12:30 - 4:30. BTW- This MeetUp is definitely happening! (There are more registered than just through the meetup group.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm so excited to be bringing this workshop to Boston at last! Join me for a fresh perspective on gender dynamics, insights and aha-s into the language of women, experiential exercises to uncover unconscious limiting patterns, practical skills for enhanced verbal and physical intimacy, and energetic practices to access your core power!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a course for men who desire greater authenticity, ease and erotic fire in relating to women. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Don't worry women, I have a special empowerment workshop planned just for you!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Would you like to have a relationship that is full of passion, integrity and ease?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you want to know what works with women?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you want to understand women better - and have them understand you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This mini workshop is a unique opportunity to get compassionate, constructive feedback from a female expert on gender dynamics. You will be skillfully guided to uncover and convey core aspects of yourself that women want. Often the qualities that are most attractive are the ones we try to hide out of fear or shame. Allowing yourself to receive deep acceptance and honoring in those places can set you free to truly be the man you were meant to be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Get insight into the challenges you are facing in your intimate relations with women – and practical skills to address them.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Develop your authentic and compelling personal presence. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Discover the inner key to attracting the connections you desire.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Learn potent techniques to access your unique masculinity and sexual magnetism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Tantric Educator and Intimacy Coach. She has been studying and practicing in the fields of Somatics and Consciousness since 1988. Brynn guides individuals and couples in clearing emotional blocks, and awakening and harnessing their Vital Energy to experience the fullest range of Pleasure in their sexuality, Intimacy in their relationships, and Purpose and Passion in their lives.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>upstairs through the door to the left of the Burren.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246407291000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244920553000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Embody Your Authentic Masculine Power</name><id>10645002</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246120200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/10645002/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/global_9120349.jpeg</photo_url></item>