<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Walker Brook Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03262</zip><lat>44.013810</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt Waternomee crash site</name><city>Woodstock</city><id>1118804</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.746021</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In 1942, a US Army B-18 Bolo bomber crashed on the side of Mt Waternomee, part of Moosilauke's Blue Ridge.&lt;a href="http://www.logginginlincoln.com/Page2.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Crash Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.logginginlincoln.com/Page2.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.logginginlincoln.com/images/Img15.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The crash site can be reached by following an old trail up from a logging road off NH rt 118.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike starts on Walker Brook Road, then follows the unmaintained B18 Crash Trail part way up Mount Waternomee to the place where a Douglas B18-A bomber plane crashed in 1942. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remnants of the plane as well as a plaque are located at this site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start at the Walker brook road, near the bottom of 118 by the junction with 112. &lt;br /&gt;It's gated, so park there and walk to the end of the road, where it crosses a stream without a bridge. &lt;br /&gt;From there, follow the well established herd path to the crash site. It's pretty obvious these days, not much of a bush wack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Features:            Plane crash site, brooks, waterfall&lt;br /&gt;Distance:            4.6 miles  &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain:    1350 feet (cumulative)  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking Time:    Typical: 3:00  &lt;br /&gt;Outing Duration:    Typical: 4:30  &lt;br /&gt;We will end this trip at the Woodstock Brewery or other local eatery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We do not know what condition the trail will be in. Pack foot traction so you will be ready in case there is ice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.hikenewengland.com/images/WaternomeeB18Crash-Map.gif" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;i&gt;*  Walk past the gate and continue walking along Walker Brook Road for 0.9 mile until it ends at a circular field.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn right onto a trail that should be marked with a small cairn and/or surveyor's ribbon. This turn is at about the 1 o'clock position when you enter the field; or northwest if you prefer to use a compass.&lt;br /&gt;    * Walk for about 0.3 mile, then cross the brook (a tributary to Walker Brook) at a point where there is a metal stake with survey ribbon on the far side of the stream.&lt;br /&gt;    * You are now 1.1 miles away from the wreckage site. You will first parallel the stream, and then climb some, and then the trail levels out for a bit. At the end of this level area, be on the lookout for a tall waterfall that will only be partially visible through the woods. Then climb steeply up the trail, the rest of the way to the crash site.&lt;br /&gt;    * Be sure to keep walking in order to see all the plane remnants. You will first encounter the engines, then a boulder with a memorial plaque, and the wings will be farther up.&lt;br /&gt;    * After exploring, retrace your footsteps to return to your vehicle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leg gaitors in case the trail is wet/buggy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At trailhead. Trailhead is not far from hwy 112. if your early, watch for a small gated trailhead.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274105172000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269382270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Waternomee crash site</name><id>12972415</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274018400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12972415/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/5/global_11779317.jpeg</photo_url></item>