<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>171 Grove St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02466</zip><lat>42.340763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Walker Center</name><city>Auburndale</city><id>1445432</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.250944</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;CANCELLED DUE TO STORMY WEATHER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Note: Please note our different location this time. It should be very convenient for everyone - right off the Mass Pike or 128, and 2 blocks from the green line Riverside T stop, and free, easy parking! &lt;u&gt;Also, to keep our expenses and your fees down, snacks and drinks will not be provided this time.  Feel free to bring your own or some to share!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Note II: Thank you &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; much to those of you who have RSVP'd &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and showed up! PLEASE, PLEASE, be considerate by only signing up if you really intend to show up, or changing your RSVP if your plans change. We set up our space, and prepare snacks and handouts according to the number of RSVP s we have. Also, we have closed registration when we've reached our maximum capacity, and ended up doing so unnecessarily when people just didn't show up. Help us reach our goal of 100% attendance for those who rsvp &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;The topic this evening: Your &amp;quot;Ready for Take-off&amp;quot; Countdown Checklist!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;We'll be sharing this very powerful tool from our New Possibilities Group Coaching Program to help you successfully &amp;quot;take off&amp;quot; for your New Year!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you think about something, whether it’s something you want or don’t want, it’s like sending off a “rocket” of desire and creation. &lt;u&gt;Is your rocket ready for take-off - to create what you want vs. what you don't want?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've created a countdown checklist to use with your goals to uncover and alert you to any areas that need further attention to clear resistance, to make sure you're languaging and thinking about your goals in a way that will make them easier to achieve, and also to fuel your desire with extra positive attention and energy.  Once you have taken care of any resistance that shows up and have fully answered the questions, you will be “all systems go and ready for takeoff”!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun! Please join us and also stay &amp;quot;connected&amp;quot; by participating in our community's message board discussions and receiving our e-mails (which will include our &amp;quot;Good Vibrations&amp;quot; tips and news). To be able to do so, go to your account, and under &amp;quot;Your Groups&amp;quot;, each one has an &amp;quot;Edit email settings&amp;quot;. Set your preferences there. Hope to hear from you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&amp;quot;Ann and Mark know their stuff and how to deliver it! And as a bonus, they are kind, fun, and engaging. Comfortable and supportive group of participants, too - good energy. Great inspiration to get me to focus and gently practice.&amp;quot;  Diane&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295400153000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291758757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Your "Ready for Take-off" Countdown Checklist!</name><id>fvzspypcbxb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295395200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/15671019/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>