<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>151 Coliseum Ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.758167</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chunkys Cinema</name><city>Nashua</city><id>5595502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.500565</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I didn't get a chance to hike with Randy but I know quite a few of our members did and I thought some of you might be interested in seeing this movie. I watched the teaser and thought it was great. Watch the movie and support some worthy causes. Use this listing if you want to communicate and coordinate with other members of the group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT THE MOVIE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The information below is from Randy's website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This past winter, I set out to summit all 48 of New Hampshire’s peaks over 4,000 feet high in just one single winter season. Filmmaker Dina Sutin chose to capture this trek on film because she believed there was a compelling story for her to discover and share. The resulting documentary delivers a journey from exhilaration to exhaustion, and ultimately triumph! With a backdrop of the White Mountains’ most majestic winter moments, it showcases the experience shared by Quinn, Justin Fuller, myself, and many other hikers along the path.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We understood the challenge going into the quest: no blind person had ever climbed the 48 and only 46 people had ever achieved this feat in a single winter season. I would set out with Quinn and the support of some pretty incredible other hikers to demonstrate both canine and human potential. I’m very proud of the achievement and the support which made it possible but I think that Dina’s film has more than matched that accomplishment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The name “Four More Feet” is meaningful on several levels. It obviously refers to the four-paw drive of the Mighty Quinn who was a substantial part of the success. Then, he might look at it as the four feet of myself and Justin, who was unquestionably the most fundamental human element of my successful finish. But the most powerful part of the name, I think, is unveiled in the movie’s message about perseverance to accomplish difficult goals.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;For me, each time I share the experience of her film, I get to relive the “hikes” into history with some new friends along the trails. So I hope you’ll take a look at our homepage or the movie page for Four More Feet and come experience the journey with me and the Mighty Quinn!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GET YOUR TICKETS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Doors open at 6:00 PM. Film starts at 7:00 PM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;There will be a Question &amp;amp; Answer Session after the 50 minute film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;To order advance tickets please email &lt;a href="mailto:4morefeet@2020visionquest.org" target="_blank"&gt;4morefeet@2020visionquest.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Adults: $8 in advance – $10 at the door &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Children (12 years and under): $5 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Senior Citizens (65 years over): $5 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;*100% of ticket proceeds go to support the 2020 Vision Quest Charity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #222222"&gt;ABOUT THE THEATER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Chunky’s Cinema Pub &lt;br /&gt;

151 Coliseum Avenue &lt;br /&gt;

Nashua, NH 03063&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351127649000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349184928000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Four More Feet" (Movie Series)</name><id>85104302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351116000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/85104302/</event_url></item>