<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Redstone Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.801041</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rave Motion Pictures Buckland Hills</name><city>Manchester</city><id>664343</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.547752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There doesn't seem to be a lot of interest in seeing the Nature film so I thought I'd list an alternative. Let me know your preference if you RSVP Yes or Maybe.&lt;br /&gt;THanks,&lt;br /&gt;Lauren&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Earth: &lt;br /&gt;This just seems like some incredible footage that needs to be seen on the big screen. &lt;br /&gt;I listed Buckland Hills, but it's also showing in Plainville and Hartford so if there's a major preference I'm certainly flexible. I'll update if time and/or place changes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis:&lt;br /&gt;The first film in the Disneynature series, &amp;quot;earth&amp;quot;, narrated by James Earl Jones, tells the remarkable story of three animal families and their amazing journey across the planet we all call home.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;earth&amp;quot; combines rare action, unimaginable scale and impossible locations by capturing the most intimate moments of our planet's wildest and most elusive creatures. Directors Alastair Fothergill and Mark Linfield, the acclaimed creative team behind the Emmy Award®-winning &amp;quot;Planet Earth,&amp;quot; combine forces again to bring this epic adventure to the big screen, beginning Earth Day 2009....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Soloist:&lt;br /&gt;The Soloist is a biographical drama about real-life musical prodigy Nathaniel Anthony Ayers, who dropped out of Julliard after developing schizophrenia and became a homeless musician on the&lt;br /&gt;streets of Los Angeles. Journalist Steve Lopez discovers the former classical music prodigy, playing his violin on the streets. As Lopez endeavors to help the homeless man find his way back, a unique friendship is formed, one that transforms both their lives....&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet me  in the lobby. (I look like my pic)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lauren</member_name><member_id>1192026</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242517804000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241664418000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Earth" OR "The Soloist" </name><id>10357772</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241908200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/10357772/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/8/global_5165560.jpeg</photo_url></item>