<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As tradition goes, Wedeln will be hosting a new, and repeat, guest weekend up at the Lodge over Thanksgiving weekend! This is your chance to get some pre-season turns in, as most mountains are scheduled to open on or before November 26th! Hiking, x-country skiing, snow-shoeing, and shopping are always options around the lodge too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a couple of social events going on, apres ski, on Saturday November 27th at nearby ski clubs that we'll plan to attend together. More details will be provided to those who signup. Friday night, when you arrive at Wedeln, we'll hang out at the lodge, socialize and hopefully brag about the snow we found earlier that day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great opportunity to get to know more about the Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors club, whether you're interested in membership, or interested in just visiting a couple of times as a guest during the ski season or at other times during the year! Regular guest fees are $20 per night. &lt;b&gt;For new guests attending our New Guest Weekend, we'll offer 1/2 price guest fees!&lt;/b&gt; That's just $20 to stay with us two nights, in great accommodations! Check the lodge out at www.wedeln.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lodge is located in the North Conway, NH area, about 2.5 to 3 hours from Boston. Guests will need to bring their own linens/pillow/sleeping bag, as well as their toiletries. We have a full kitchen so you can bring up your breakfast/lunch stuff if you wish, or stop somewhere for sandwiches (Kringles is a wonderful stop off on the way to Wildcat! There's a great stop on the way to Attitash too, name is escaping me right now!). Typically people collaborate on dinner, whether it's going out, staying in to cook or ordering take out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions, and of course, please let us know if you plan to come up as soon as possible to help us in our planning! The Wedeln Ski House is always age 21+ only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THINK SNOW!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just come on in and say hello!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>7362850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291582647000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Adventurerists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak</urlname><id>1297030</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Ski, Snowboard, and Outdoor Adventurers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289873792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New (And Repeat) Guest Weekend @ Wedeln Ski &amp; Outdoors Club!</name><id>15460329</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290819600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak/events/15460329/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/b/f/global_6106799.jpeg</photo_url></item>