<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 90</address_2><address_1>45 S Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.759000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 523 5260</phone><name>SunDo Mountain Taoist Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>489318</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>After cultivating and circulating internal Qi energy within our chakras and meridian channels, join us for a Winter Solstice Tea Ceremony in which we will honor the five elements. Each element of water, wood, fire, metal and earth corresponds to a specific vital organ within the human body. During a guided meditation, The Inner Smile, we will visualize good health and energy for each of our organs while enjoying a detoxifying and cleansing tea. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This day, December 21, is the Winter Solstice and will be the shortest day and longest night of the year as the earth continues its journey around the sun. It is also a full moon night ... an excellent time to enhance our vital energy and good health.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please wear comfy clothing. No previous experience is necessary. All physical fitness levels are welcome as our practice can be adapted to suit individual needs. This event is a $5 suggested donation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Inner Smile Meditation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the most well-known of Taoist neidan (Inner Alchemy) practices is the &amp;quot;Inner Smile&amp;quot; - in which we smile inwardly to each of the major organs of our body, activating within us the energy of loving-kindness, and waking up the five elemental energies. This meditation will allow us to direct the healing energy of a smile into any part of our body that we would like healed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_ZkOG37q6YGU/SaUdFAC_mMI/AAAAAAAAAIA/TUCzmKC1rhM/s320/Meditation-1.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In ancient China, the Taoists taught that a constant inner smile, a smile to oneself, insured health, happiness and longevity. Why? Smiling to yourself is like basking in love: you become your own best friend. Living with an inner smile is to live in harmony with yourself.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ~ Mantak Chia&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292988137000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274735273000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taoist Yoga-Meditation Full Moon Solstice Tea</name><id>xxrrnynqbcc</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292974200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/15151662/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/5/global_12058597.jpeg</photo_url></item>