<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The BCM festival is a two day Celtic Music festival which features music and dancing from Irish, Scottich and other performers.  The 2009 Boston Celtic Music Fest (BCMFest) finale concert will spotlight dance from the &amp;quot;four corners&amp;quot; of Boston's most popular Celtic and Celtic-influenced&lt;br /&gt;traditions.  &amp;quot;BCMFest Dance Spotlight&amp;quot; will be the grand climax of the two day festival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BCMFest will celebrate its sixth year with an array of concerts and other&lt;br /&gt;special events at venues in Harvard Square and Medford, featuring some of Greater&lt;br /&gt;Boston's best performers of Irish, Scottish, Cape Breton, as well as Appalachian and&lt;br /&gt;other Celtic-influenced music.  For more informationabout the festival itself, visit the web site: &lt;a href="http://www.bcmfest.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bcmfest.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the course of the Spotlight Finale, the house band will welcome a bevy of guest&lt;br /&gt;performers for songs and tunes, with a special emphasis on featuring dance from the&lt;br /&gt;Irish, Scottish, Cape Breton and Appalachian/old-timey traditions.  For more information about the finale,visit the web site: &lt;a href="http://www.bcmfest.com/uploads/files/2009finale.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bcmfest.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $15 for the performance and can be bought at the following web site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://tickets.passimcenter.org/orderticketsarea.asp?p=179&amp;amp;a=25&amp;amp;backurl=%2Fdefault%2Easp%3FSearchMonth%3D1%26monthsubmit%3D%26SearchText%3D%26Go%2Ex%3D%26Go%2Ey%3D%26pg%3D1%23abc" target="_blank"&gt;http://tickets.passim...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets can also be purchased for Friday evening and Saturday daytime through the Club Passim web site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will send out an update Monday if we can get a group discount and if tickets can be bought at the door.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I willbe out front of the church with a meetup sign at 8:00</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234054029000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231044207000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Celtic Music Festival Dance Spotlight</name><id>9438388</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231635600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/9438388/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/3/global_1218899.jpeg</photo_url></item>