<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>545 Boylston St</address_2><address_1>Back Bay</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357231</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 638 -9699 </phone><name>Vlora Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>898612</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066116</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;France-US business: reports from the trenches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presentation by Amir Eldad, VP, Venator Partners&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amir Eldad will talk about US and Global market penetration and Issues facing a French company, such as:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;o   The US: a large market or also the place to reach global leadership?&lt;br /&gt;o   Building the right teams&lt;br /&gt;o   Bridging the business culture gap&lt;br /&gt;o   Hedging major bets and resource commitments&lt;br /&gt;o   Market penetration strategies&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BIO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amir Eldad is a serial entrepreneur and a global high-tech executive, now with Venator Partners – an executive search and advisory services firm. Prior to joining Venator Partners in 2007, Amir led the penetration of the U.S. market for non-U.S. headquartered start-ups. Acquiring tier-one customers and recruiting top-tier talent while bridging the multi-national cultural gap in order to build a global leadership position in new markets has been a corner stone of his mode of operation and a key element of his success. Amir lives in the greater Boston area, but spends a significant amount of time in Israel, France, and other countries to enable him to stay close to his clients.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presentation by Laurent de Bernede, CEO, Go To Market Consulting, LLC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laurent de Bernede will present how Go To Market Consulting, LLC, a management and marketing consulting firm specialized in helping European technology companies come to the US market, is partnering with Bimedia to deliver a strategic recommendation and a business plan to enter the US market in 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BIMEDIA is a leading French technology provider specialized in Point of Sale (POS) management hardware and software solutions. Bimedia’s solutions include innovative, state of the art cash register hardware with a complete web-based POS management solution. Bimedia’s offering comes with a suite of distribution agreements for dematerialized products that increases revenues of its clients by 40% on average. Bimedia has enjoyed an annual growth rate of 70% over the past five years and its entire organization is busy managing growth in France and other European countries. Recognizing that the timing is favorable to enter the US market, Bimedia has decided to outsource to a local consulting firm, the initial phases of its plan to move into the US market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BIO&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Originally from France, Laurent de Bernede has over 20 years of international experience heading multicultural Sales and Operations teams to manage complex projects. A creative mind and an entrepreneurial spirit have always driven his career in large corporations and start-up ventures. Laurent’s multidisciplinary profile allows him to provide tactical marketing, operational, and IT consulting services to leading European and US companies in a variety of sectors, ranging from ensures adaptability and top performance in a variety of sectors ranging from news media to financial services, VoIP and mobile telecom, Luxury consumer goods.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Asks for the InterFrench meeting</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gilberte Houbart</member_name><member_id>9857928</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259190511000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Membres</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Interfrench-Boston</urlname><id>1512639</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Interfrench Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257901265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Next InterFrench meeting on November 23</name><id>11846156</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259017200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Interfrench-Boston/events/11846156/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/5/f/global_10390447.jpeg</photo_url></item>