<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Marcy St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.075943</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Players Ring</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>671462</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.751850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;H&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/4/6/event_14364646.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;i Trailblazers!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Join us for an evening of theater at the Players Ring as we enjoy&amp;nbsp;a presentation of one of Neil Simon&amp;rsquo;s most-beloved comedies: Biloxi Blues. We will be meeting there around 6:45 pm as the show starts at 7 pm, we will go out for drinks afterwards!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in 1943, Biloxi Blues takes audiences on a hilarious journey through the final days of World War II &amp;mdash; as seen through the eyes of Eugene Morris Jerome: &amp;ldquo;There were three things I was determined to do in this war,&amp;rdquo; newly enlisted Army Private Jerome tells the crowd at the play&amp;rsquo;s outset: &amp;ldquo;Become a writer, not get killed, and lose my virginity. But first, we all had to get through Basic Training in the murky swamps of Mississippi.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biloxi Blues saw a remarkably successful run on Broadway back in the mid-1980s. It even took home the Tony Award for Best Play. That was before it became a major Hollywood motion picture in 1988, starring Matthew Broderick as Eugene; Christopher Walken as the tough-as-nails (yet off-his-rocker) Sgt. Toomey; and Penelope Ann Miller as the girl of Eugene&amp;rsquo;s dreams, Daisy Hannigan. The film, directed by Mike Nichols (of The Graduate), was #1 in theaters its opening weekend!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, as America is embroiled in a variety of simultaneous wars, and our armed services are in the middle of repealing a long-held &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Ask, Don&amp;rsquo;t Tell&amp;rdquo; policy, the themes explored in the 1940s-era Biloxi Blues are as quaint as they are cutting-edge and perfectly relevant to an entirely new generation of theatergoers. But the best part? It&amp;rsquo;s Neil Simon at his best, and just plain fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directed by Kathleen Cavalaro, and Biloxi Blues stars Will MacDonald, Jon Cilley, Elizabeth Locke O&amp;rsquo;Connell, Merlin Money Mason, Brandon Nigro, Laura Thomas, Samuel Bennett, Dan Stowell, and Brian Kelly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adult content and situations. Parental discretion advised.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305503906000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Everyone loves a good show!</why><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304807123000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Players Ring Theater Night -" Biloxi Blues"</name><id>17582043</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305499500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/17582043/</event_url></item>