<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>174 Lincoln Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.350536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-426-0180</phone><name>District Lounge </name><city>Boston</city><id>817282</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Singles Mingle in Boston @ The District Wed Dec, 10 5-9 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The district has agreed to let us have their place exclusively from 5-9 pm.  Read On&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is listed in a few locations here on Meetup and POF - please only post at one location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;District Restaurant &amp;amp; Lounge &lt;br /&gt;DISTRICT, is located in the Leather District, Boston’s industrial chic condo loft neighborhood. Designed by JFS Design Studio, this unique and aggressive design exudes an exotic tone with a hint of dangerous sensuality by combining ornate floral patterns and spherical shapes with birch tree trunks lined along the walls, behind the bar, and creatively used as door handles. White patent leather banquettes and comfy booths combined with gloss-white chandeliers radiate a vintage atmosphere that is edgy yet inviting.&lt;br /&gt;$10 Cover&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DJ &amp;amp; Cash Bar &lt;br /&gt;Trendy menu of salads, wraps, seafood &amp;amp; sandwiches from $6 - $15&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Easily found right of I 93 near South Station (take the T)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plenty of street parking and a garage on the same block&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;180 Lincoln St&lt;br /&gt;Boston MA 02111&lt;br /&gt;617-426-0180&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign Up Rules – Please post on this page to sign up for this event. The Venue is has a 200 person limit. Please – if you post your intention to go to this event – GO!  If you find that your circumstances change and can’t go – remove your post ASAP in order to make room for others.  I don’t want to sound like a hard-*ss but NO SHOWS WILL NOT BE ALLOWED TO SIGN UP FOR FUTURE EVENTS.  So make sure you attend if you sign up.  Thanks… &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please drink responsibly and make plans for safe transportation home. We want you to come to the next party!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Roger</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231646735000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227557549000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>After Work Singles Mingle in Boston @ The District 5-9 pm</name><id>9223616</id><headcount>65</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228946400000</time><rsvp_limit>200</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/9223616/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/global_6486134.jpeg</photo_url></item>