<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main ST/RTE 113</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03813</zip><lat>44.238182</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Baldface Circle Trail Head</name><city>Center Conway</city><id>9269122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.016050</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Bill Robichaud @ 207-332-8969&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Please take a moment to answer the RSVP questions when responding. It's for safety reasons this information be provided. Failure to furnish the requested information will result in removal from the activity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*** Alternate date will be Saturday, June 1st. ***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;The Baldface-Royce Range is a small but rugged range, running north to south along the Maine-New Hampshire border. While all well below 4000 feet, there are several peaks along the ridge that are above treeline, and provide fantastic views. Five of these peaks are on the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.nhmountainhiking.com/hike/lists/52view.html"&gt;52 With A View&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;peakbagging list, and this is your chance to get them all in one shot. The peaks on the list: Eastman Mountain (2939'), South Baldface (3570'), North Baldface (3610')&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, Mt. Meader (2782') (alternately Eagle Crag (3030')), and West Royce (3200'). The plan, if time and group fitness allows, will be to finish the traverse on East Royce (3114'), in Maine. We will need to start early, to allow for car spots at various planned bailout points. This is going to be a big hike, so I'm going to limit the group size to 10. Let's all plan to meet at 6:30am to spot cars, and hopefully be on trail by 7:15 or 7:30.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice:&lt;/strong&gt; We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you (in the colder months this can be particularly dangerous for the entire group if we have to wait around, getting cold). Please read the entire TRIP SUMMARY, below, before you RSVP. It is important, not only for your safety, but that of the entire group.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;TRIP SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This will be a &lt;strong&gt;MODERATELY FAST&lt;/strong&gt;-paced, &lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt;-distance 17.8 mile hike (one-way traverse) with an &lt;strong&gt;EXTREME&lt;/strong&gt;-7036-feet of elevation gain. The approximate hike time is 12 hours 24 minutes, based on "book time" math. It may take more or less time depending on trail conditions. Always plan for spending more time on the mountain than expected. We will be taking a variety of trails: We will start on the Baldface Circle Trail, and hike in to its junction with Slippery Brook Trail. We will then take Slippery Brook Trail to its junction with the Eastman Mountain, and Bald Knob trails. Up and back on the Eastman Mountain Trail, then up Bald Knob Trail to its junction with Baldface Circle Trail. Taking Baldface Circle Trail, we will pass over the open summits of South Baldface, and North Baldface, and on over several open knobs to the junction of Meader Ridge Trail. We'll take Meader Ridge Trail to Rim Junction, passing over Eagle Crag and Mt. Meader along the way. Following Basin Rim Trail, we'll ascend to West Royce, and continue down the Royce Trail to Royce Connector. We will then continue on Royce Connector to East Royce Trail to summit East Royce, and finish the traverse. Descent will be via the East Royce Trail. As we get closer to the date I'll know better as to what specific conditions we'll likely encounter and what you'll be expected to bring or able to leave behind and I'll be in touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bailouts:&lt;/strong&gt; I would like to have several bailout points along the ridge. The first and second being at the junction of the Meader Ridge Trail and Baldface Circle Trail, and &lt;span&gt;At the Meader Ridge Trail/Mt. Meader Trail junction&lt;/span&gt;. The Baldface Circle Trail (or alternately Bicknell Ridge Trail), will bring us back to the Baldface Circle trailhead. &lt;span&gt;Mt. Meader Trail comes out 0.5 miles north of the Baldface Circle Trailhead.&lt;/span&gt; The third and fourth bailouts will be centered around the Basin Trailhead off Rt. 113, where I'd like to spot one car. The bailouts are as follows: at Rim Junction, and at Royce Trail. Basin Trail takes you directly to the trailhead, and Royce Trail drops you a few 1/10ths north of the access road. The East Royce Trailhead on the other side of Evans Notch, is where we'll spot two cars for the return to Baldface Circle Trailhead, provided we have a successful traverse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Environment:&lt;/strong&gt; Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions so be prepared. If conditions will be or become dangerous on the trail (i.e., elevated likelihood of lightning, blizzard, dangerous winds, downpour, or dense fog, especially above treeline), I will cancel or terminate the hike - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. While reaching the summit is always our goal, we will not succumb to "summit fever" and risk our well-being in the process. The mountain will still be there another day. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Weather:&lt;/strong&gt; The &lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/summit_forecast.php"&gt;Mount Washington Observatory Higher Summits Forecast&lt;/a&gt; is always a good one to check, but we'll be nearly 3000 feet below that, so take it with a grain of salt. The &lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.240771877721&amp;amp;lon=-71.08600616455078"&gt;NWS point forecast&lt;/a&gt; for the area should give a good idea of what to expect. &lt;a href="http://www.mountain-forecast.com/"&gt;Mountain-forecast.com&lt;/a&gt; apparently has nothing for the Baldface Range. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Gear Info:&lt;/strong&gt; This gear is critical in the shoulder months. Like winter, there is no cheating here. If you mess up you put everyone in danger. Below is a list describing the minimum required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear:&lt;/strong&gt; Proper, well-soled hiking boots or shoes, with synthetic or wool socks with a spare pair in your pack, gaiters to keep any possible mud out of your boots. As previously stated, I'll know better as to what specific conditions we'll likely encounter and what you'll be expected to bring or able to leave behind and I'll be in touch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hands and Head:&lt;/strong&gt; A synthetic or wool cap that covers your ears and warm, non-cotton waterproof gloves. Your rain gear/shell, should feature a hood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Face and Eyes:&lt;/strong&gt; If the hike is above treeline: A face mask, balaclava or some other form of face protection. And for the eyes, glacier glasses with blinders and/or goggles with lightly tinted lenses. Sunglasses if it's a nice day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing:&lt;/strong&gt; Dress in layers with "wicking" synthetics next to the skin and wool over to easily regulate body temperature (clothing designed to deal with sweat during exertion and insulate even when wet). Also, it can be windy at the summit and it will typically be much colder at higher elevations so please be prepared. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON! While cotton is a great insulator when it's dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly conducts heat away from the body. Also consider bringing an extra layer in your pack just in case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear:&lt;/strong&gt; Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) as well as windproof/waterproof pants. Again, also consider bringing an extra layer. like a down or synthetic "puffy" just in case or if conditions above treeline warrant it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water:&lt;/strong&gt; Bring high-energy snacks making sure you have plenty of salts and sugars (this will help you make better use of your water), your choice of food for lunch, and pack extra just in case. Again, bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip (2-3 litres is what I suggest, even when it's cold). Use at least two Nalgene bottles or a hydration bladder to carry your water. It's a good idea to have a hearty meal the night before followed by a good night's sleep. Also, try to begin the hike well hydrated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter:&lt;/strong&gt; Be prepared to spend a night in the woods if you have to. Minimal options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket (which packs small and weighs just ounces). A pad or some way to get off the ground is also highly recommended (though pine boughs can work).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear:&lt;/strong&gt; Map and compass: don't just bring them, know how to use them. Also, a plastic whistle, headlamp with spare batteries (required, forget and you can't come), a first aid kit containing any medications you may need personally (please let me know if you have any applicable allergies, medical conditions, and special medications you may be carrying), a small knife or multipurpose tool, matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter, a toiletries kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items), sunscreen, lip balm, sunglasses, and a waterproof pack cover.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items:&lt;/strong&gt; Stowable trekking poles (personal preference) and camera.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailhead:&lt;/strong&gt; Here are &lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;daddr=44.238181,-71.016056(Baldface+Circle+Trailhead)"&gt;customizable directions&lt;/a&gt; to the Baldface Circle Trailhead. We will be spotting cars at the Basin Trailhead off of Rt. 113, and at the East Royce Trailhead on Rt. 113. There is the possibility that Evans Notch Road may not be open at the time of our hike. This will probably lead to us cutting the hike shorter, and only spotting cars at the Basin Trailhead. Please consult a map and/or contact me if you have questions. Elevation: 520' &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; You agree not to hold the Organizer, Event Organizers, Assistant Organizers, or any other members responsible for any injuries, mishaps, or any other situation that may happen at a planned event. You are responsible to research the event, know the area, and bring the proper gear and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>60417112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369012356000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363982795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Baldface-Royce Range Traverse (ADVANCED/EXTREME)</name><id>110566302</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368873000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/110566302/</event_url></item>