<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 2-day and 22.6 mile hike on the Appalachian Trail starting on Rte. 9, about 2.8 miles west of Woodford, VT and heading northbound. We'll be doing a generally upward trail assent most of the day with some up/downs with 2 of significance with 400 ft. losses. We'll start at 1,360 ft. and after 10.1 miles reach the Goddard Shelter (sleeps 12) for the night at 3,540 ft. The next day we start the 12.5 mile hike and reach the summit of Glastonbury Mtn. at 3,748 after only .3 mile with a firetower on top to explore sights. We then continue on the long ridgeline with a generally slow decent to the endpoint with one significant 1,000 ft. fall and rise in the first third of the day's hike. Six other lesser fall and rises are encountered but they are generally less than 200 ft. We'll take breaks at roughly thirds for the second day at Kid Gore and Story Spring shelters. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*6/26: Both days 81 high/60 low; 40% T-storm Sat, 60% showers Sun*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet 6/28/08 at 8 AM at the endpoint AT parking area on Stratton Arlington Rd. (called Arlington-West Wardsboro Rd. on the AT map/trail book), 7 miles west of West Wardsboro, VT. We'll shuttle to the starting point at the Rte. 9 AT parking area. We should be hiking by 9 AM. We'll hike with rest stops the 10.1 miles to the lean-to for the night. I figure we'll reach the lean-to at about 7 PM at the latest. We'll have dinner and set up for the night. We'll get up and ready somewhat early the second day given the 12.5 miles we need to cover and wanting to do that at a slower pace. We should be hiking by 7:00 AM and reach the endpoint by about 7:30 PM, 6/29/08. We'll stop at shelters 4.3 and 9.4 miles for the day for water/food. Hikers can leave for home or head back to the beginning for the shuttle vehicle and head home with a possible rest stop on the way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equipped we could come in earlier than I estimated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES == &lt;br /&gt;* Backpack -suitable to hold sleeping bag and all other gear and food, overall weight should be no more than about 40 lbs &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable &amp;amp; broken in  &lt;br /&gt;* 2 pair wool socks &lt;br /&gt;* Hat -something good in the rain and/or sun &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cool mornings &amp;amp; possibly hot afternoons, avoid cotton as it stays wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Comfortable underwear -no chaffing! &lt;br /&gt;* Rain poncho/jacket -essential! -rain pants optional &lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Bug spay -essential!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp -or flashlight, fresh batteries &lt;br /&gt;* 2 quart water min. -strongly suggest bringing a water filter to restock on water &lt;br /&gt;* Trail meals -2 lunches, 2 dinner, 1 breakfast. High energy meals should be planned. Only meal time to cook are dinner both days &amp;amp; breakfast 2nd day. &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks &amp;amp; electrolytes -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, GU energy gel, Gatoraide drink powder, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* Toilet paper -in plastic bag to keep dry &lt;br /&gt;* Hand soap/hand sanitizer -in plastic bag &lt;br /&gt;* Backpack First Aid kit &lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR == &lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries &lt;br /&gt;* Compass &lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking cookstove -if cooking &lt;br /&gt;* Matches -for cookstove &lt;br /&gt;* Something to sleep in -PJ's or shorts and T, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* Games or reading for night activity &lt;br /&gt;* Head net -keep bugs out &lt;br /&gt;* Tent &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so all questions should be directed to him. Kevin S can provide carpooling but it is advised to call Kevin S (number in RSVP) so he knows you would like to try to carpool. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the &lt;b&gt;Meetup&lt;/b&gt;/ending location on Stratton Arlington Rd. 7 miles west of West Wardsboro, VT: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/1250+Stratton+Arlington+Rd+West+Wardsboro+VT/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT trailhead start on Rte. 9 AT parking area about 2.8 miles west of Woodford, VT: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/2500+Vt+Route+9+woodford+vt/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not sure what vehicle I'll have at the starting point. Look for 6'2" guy &amp; you have my picture on the hiking site.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215290420000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>This segment of the AT is more of a challenge given distance as we head north and to higher altitudes. AT hiking with an overnight at a lean-to and the lovely Green Mountains of VT! :-)</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213025037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike/campout on the AT from Woodford Hollow VT to Arlington-West Wardsboro Rd VT</name><id>8108489</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214654400000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8108489/</event_url></item>