<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/(S(0qubocuh4snslviumxw1c0vt))/Ticketing.aspx?TheatreID=231&amp;amp;MovieID=14457&amp;amp;ShowDate=4/7/2013&amp;amp;ScheduleID=117529"&gt;THE PLACE BEYOND THE PINES ADVANCED TICKETS&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;Always better to have a ticket to a sparsely attended show than to not have a ticket to a Sold-Out show!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;The daring new movie from director Derek Cianfrance &lt;em&gt;(Blue Valentine)&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Place Beyond the Pines&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a sweeping emotional drama powerfully exploring the unbreakable bond between fathers and sons. Luke (Ryan Gosling), a high-wire motorcycle stunt performer with a carnival passing through Schenectady in upstate New York, tries to reconnect with a former lover, Romina (Eva Mendes), only to learn that she has given birth to their son in his absence. Luke decides to give up life on the road to try and provide for his newfound family by taking a job as a car mechanic. Noticing Luke's ambition and talents, his employer Robin (Ben Mendelsohn) proposes to partner with Luke in a string of spectacular bank robberies—which will place Luke on the radar of ambitious rookie cop Avery Cross (Bradley Cooper, &lt;em&gt;Silver Linings Playbook&lt;/em&gt;). Avery, who has to navigate a local police department ruled by the menacing and corrupt detective Deluca (Ray Liotta), is also struggling to balance his professional life with his family life, which includes his wife Jennifer (Rose Byrne) and their infant son. The consequences of Avery's confrontation with Luke will reverberate into the next generation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;a href="http://focusfeatures.com/the_place_beyond_the_pines"&gt;The Place Beyond The Pines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Rotten Tomatoes:  89% Critics (16 Fresh, 2 Rotten), 98% Viewers (9,963 Reviews)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From MovieDex:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The applause and standing ovation at the TIFF premiere lasted for minutes, and for good reason;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;The Place Beyond the Pines&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;is truly an exceptional film, boasting honest characters, terrific performances, and a daring, rule-breaking story that will leave you broken, breathless and gasping for more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When online tickets become available, we'll update the Meetup so that we can avoid a Sell-Out.  When the actual times are posted, we'll update the Meetup so that we can avoid sitting in the front row!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following the film, we'll go to a nearby eatery to discuss, dine, discuss, drink, discuss, dessert, discuss, and depart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will gather the group AFTER close of credits in the lobby area INSIDE the Kendall near the ticket taker holding an authentic, antique, Meetup Sign, so that we can use the restroom and go to a nearby eatery, hopefully West Bridge.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1365462971000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363386461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Place Beyond the Pines</name><id>109463872</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365367500000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/109463872/</event_url></item>