<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;This is a new print of  the German director Werner Herzog (one of my favorite directors for what its worth) classic  which is having its first screening at the Brattle in 15 years. I've been looking forward to seeing this film again, I probably saw it about 15 years  ago as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;German director Werner Herzog's internationally acclaimed &amp;quot;breakthrough&amp;quot; film is based on the famous story of mysterious 19th-century child genius Kasper Hauser. As played by Bruno S., Hauser shows up unannounced in the middle of a village square, frightening the populace with his bizarre behavior. He cannot talk, nor is there any indication of his parentage, thus Kaspar is immediately the object of close scrutiny from the authorities. When he finally does develop the power of speech, he reveals a highly advanced state of intelligence, as well as a seeming gift of prophecy. The winner of the 1975 Grand Jury prize at the Cannes Film Festival.&amp;quot; AllMovie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Eschewing traditional narrative, Herzog imbues his film with dreamlike images and symbolic language. One of the great films by a master of modern filmmaking. &amp;quot;  from the Brattle's description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.moviemartyr.com/1974/enigmaofkasparhauser.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.moviemarty...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the custom Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's end and then its off to a restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184635518000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182462948000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Mystery of Kaspar Hauser- German Cinema from the 1970's</name><id>5919239</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184454000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5919239/</event_url></item>