<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Plum Island Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.798267</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Plum Island Visitor Center</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1562390</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847076</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's go see if we can find the Snowy Owl at Plum Island/Parker River Wildlife Refuge. Bring binoculars and bird books if you have them. Bird experts are particularly welcome as I'm no expert!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I suggest we meet at the Plum Island visitor center and carpool into the wildlife reservation - there is a fee for entry to the reserve. This will be a combination walk and birdwatch...we might go around the Hellcat swamp, then drive to the end to walk on the beach and see what we can see. I hope we can do this in 3 cars max.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2-3 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a historic brochure of the Refuge written by Rachel Carson!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/pdf/parker_cia.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/pdf/parker_cia.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parker River National Wildlife Refuge was established in 1942 to provide feeding, resting, and nesting habitat for migratory birds. The refuge occupies 4,662 acres on the southern two-thirds of Plum Island, a barrier island on the Northeast coast of Massachusetts, and is administered by the US Fish and Wildlife Service, a federal agency. Parker River is one of over 550 Refuges in the National Wildlife Refuge System, a national network of lands dedicated to "wildlife first." &lt;br /&gt;

 Today, Parker River provides pristine coastal habitat for over 300 species of resident and migratory birds, as well as a large variety of mammals, insects, fish, reptiles and amphibians. The Refuge also provides critical habitat for the federally threatened Piping Plover. &lt;br /&gt;

 In addition to its mission of wildlife conservation, the Refuge provides a variety of excellent wildlife-dependent recreational activities, including surf fishing, wildlife observation and photography, guided nature programs, and seasonal waterfowl and deer hunting opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions to the Refuge &lt;br /&gt;

 The refuge is located ~35 miles north of Boston near the City of Newburyport. From Route 95 take exit 57 and travel east on Route 113, then continue straight onto Route 1A South to the intersection with Rolfe&amp;rsquo;s Lane for a total of 3.5 miles. Turn left onto Rolfe&amp;rsquo;s Lane and travel 0.5 miles to its end. Turn right onto the Plum Island Turnpike, and our visitor center will be shortly on the right. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(DO NOT PARK IN THE MASS AUDUBON LOT WHICH IS ON THE LEFT HAND SIDE!) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my red subaru with kayak holders on the top</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331589180000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331385433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Plum Island walk and birdwatch</name><id>55772482</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331478000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/55772482/</event_url></item>