<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>My wife and I  will be leading an overnight hike (AUGUST 23 &amp;amp; 24)to the Guyot Campsite.  I would like to make this hike enjoyable to experienced hikers, peak baggers and day hikers who have never overnighted before.  Therefore, this will be a fairly leisurely hike with an emphasis on fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike via the Zealand Trail to the Zealand Falls Hut (2.8 miles, 1:45 approximate hiking time), we will then follow the Twinway trail to the Bondcliff trail (4.2 miles, 2:20 approximate hiking time), we will then follow the Bondcliff trail to the Guyot Campsite ( .6 miles, :30 approximate hiking time).  We will set up camp at the Guyot Campsite and for anyone who would like, we will leave our packs and hike up to Mt. Bond (1.9 miles, 1:15 approximate hiking time one way).  This will make the total hiking for day one of 11.4 miles and approximate hiking time of 7:05.  On day two we will retrace our route back to the Zealand Falls Hut, where instead of hiking out the Zealand Trail we will follow the Lend-A-Hand trail over Mt. Hale and down the Hale Brook Trail.  This will make the total hiking for day two of 9.7 miles and approximate hiking time of 7:05.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that the cost to stay at the Guyot Campsite is approximately $8.00 and exact amount is required (therefore bring about $10.00 in one dollar bills). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a lean-to shelter at the Guyot Campsite, however there is no guarantee that there will be an opening in the shelter.  Therefore, everyone is required to bring a backpacking tent.  Since there is also a limited number of tent platforms, if anyone is going solo and bringing a two person tent, it would be nice (but not mandatory) to share with someone else.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone has any questions regarding this hike (e.g. what to bring), please feel free to contact me.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also be updating this information over the next couple of weeks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also note, the forecast of rain will not cancel this hike.  Unless it is a downpour on Saturday morning, we will be going.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>BLACK 4  DOOR ECHO WITH MAINE PLATES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220017474000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217947141000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OVERNIGHT HIKE TO GUYOT CAMPSITE</name><id>8481211</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219492800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8481211/</event_url></item>