<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1288 Boston Post Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06443</zip><lat>41.273888</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>2032452785</phone><name>Hammonasset Beach State Park</name><city>Madison</city><id>716824</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.559580</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Friday AND/OR Saturday night at Hammonassette Reservations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT IS STILL OPEN&amp;gt;&amp;gt;BUT I NOLONGER HAVE INTERNET ACCESS&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a yes and didnt reserve..just come on down to visit or reserve on your own....&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU ARE A MAYBEE&amp;gt;&amp;gt;just say so in the no area..i had to combine all info in this listing..&lt;br /&gt;BUT AS of now..im not taking any more reservatiosn..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rules:&lt;br /&gt;Camping site purchase times, 1:00 pm..for sites previously used, earlier for new sites. &lt;br /&gt;I will be there about 10:00 am friday morning for 2 sites only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im not sure if Steve has some singlesevent people..i have to let him do the reservations for them..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Locations: I asked for sites for 40-50's wild people @apx 13,&lt;br /&gt;they have some sites for us but they will fill adjacent sites with the public as they find they need..I asked for some trees...they give me what they can...all the more reason to reserve now.&lt;br /&gt;Party time: till 11:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;Guests: No guest cars in guest parking lot after 10:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Campers Reserved by me: Friday or Sat camping, go to camp office and state your name and/or mine (i have the group names on a list for them)&lt;br /&gt;Guests and Day Visitors: They pay the regular park entrance fee for the day. Then go to camp office for our location info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Finding us: Go to the camp office and use Al reigins or Steve Theriault party for the camp site location info. they will direct you to our location(s). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 tents per camp site limit : I got a spare tent and canopee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6 people per site limit : I dont think there is going to be tent checks at night..&lt;br /&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;Everything is ONLY being updated HERE for the reservation part..that means Yesses only for this camping event one..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So far i have real confirmed:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bob  and Jill put in $30 for one night or was it 2....im sure its defitnally saturday night, friday ??..write me to make sure..but dont matter..still reserving by # of cars anyway saturday only..&lt;br /&gt;Rob P..saturday only..&lt;br /&gt;Ok &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steve T for 2 nights + others ?????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dagny $15 for 2 nights&lt;br /&gt;Kathy G $10 for 2 nights          &lt;br /&gt;Janice M for 2 nights&lt;br /&gt;Me 2 nights&lt;br /&gt;= 4 cars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total, so far: only 2 sites are needed... BASED ON # of CARS ONLY at this time...&lt;br /&gt;Thats it..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; YOU ARE ON YOUR OWN..its easy to reserve your own site too..request you be near us if the area is still empty..&lt;br /&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On SEPT 14 apx 10:00 AM Me and Steve can only reserve camp sites for those that are really going..we cant just reserve and pay for sites that dont get used..or the other way..too many people for too few a sites..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 tents per camp site limit : I got a spare tent and canopee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6 people per site : I dont think there is going to be tent checks at night..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The CAMPING Fee is ; Cost per site is 15 per night per site..+ some silly process fee ($3?)&lt;br /&gt;ok thats pretty good..with 6 thats $3 each..but if only 2 its 8..ok you get the idea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JMay295766 writes:&lt;br /&gt;Hi Al,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     I wanted to let you know that breakfast preparations are going along.  Can you let the group know that I am cooking breakfast both day and have purchased the supplies to do it.  Omlettes made to order with bacon and muffins Saturday.  Sunday is pancakes and sausage with egges if one wants.  I also did some brownies.  I bought a bunch of sliced turkey if you want to do your hot sandwiches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh Yeh...sounding sizzeling already...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;Hammonasset Beach State Park&lt;br /&gt;1288 BOSTON POST RD (PO 271)&lt;br /&gt;Madison CT 06443&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camping area, same main entrance, say camping area or Park visitor (pay the entrance fee) or Reserved Camper....and divert off to right to camp area.&lt;br /&gt;stop at the office area..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north/Hartford area: Take I-91 south to Route 9 south. Off Route 9, take Exit 9. Turn right (south) onto Route 81; continue down Route 81 until you run into I-95. Turn right ont theo I-95 entrance ramp, and go approximately 1 mile to Exit 62, then turn left off the exit. Head south 1 mile down Hammonasset connector, and go straight through the light crossing Route 1 (Boston Post Road), into the park. From the south: Take I-95 north, Exit 62. Take a right off the exit ramp onto Hammonasset I-95 connector. Park entrance will be 1 mile ahead. From the east/Rhode Island: Take I-395 south onto I-95 south, Exit 62. Take a left off the exit and go approximately 1 mile. Go straight through the traffic light, crossing Route 1 (Boston Post Road). From the west/New York: Take I-95 north, Exit 62. Take a right off the exit and go approximately 1 mile. Go straight through the traffic light, crossing Route 1 (Boston Post Road), into the park. View Regional MapMap Driving Route&lt;br /&gt;Phone Park for More Information:&lt;br /&gt;Information: (203)245-1817&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Campsite layout :&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325210#map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190110799000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189022603000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>You are on your own for campsites at  Hammonassett</name><id>6303880</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189778400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6303880/</event_url></item>