<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>MT. JACKSON &amp;amp; PIERCE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be hiking Mt. Jackson &amp;amp; Mt. Pierce via the description below.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the hikers responsibility code and waiver on this Website.  All attendees are expected to be able to hike at a pace of two miles per hour and to hike for approximately two hours at a time without breaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance Time Elev&lt;br /&gt;Change&lt;br /&gt;Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude&lt;br /&gt;starting at Webster-Jackson Trailhead 44° 12' 55&amp;quot; 71° 24' 28&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;This trail connects US 302 at a small parking area just south of&lt;br /&gt;the Macomber Family Information Center (Crawford Depot) with&lt;br /&gt;the summits of both Mt. Webster and Mt. Jackson. The trail,&lt;br /&gt;blazed in blue, leaves the east side of US 302 0.1 mi. south of the&lt;br /&gt;Crawford Depot and 0.1 mi. north of the Gate of the Notch.&lt;br /&gt;0.10 mi 5 min +67 ft on Webster-Jackson Trail&lt;br /&gt;0.10 mi 5 min +67 ft This trail connects US 302 at a small parking area just south of&lt;br /&gt;the Macomber Family Information Center (Crawford Depot) with&lt;br /&gt;the summits of both Mt. Webster and Mt. Jackson, and provides&lt;br /&gt;the opportunity for an interesting loop trip, because the two&lt;br /&gt;summits are linked by the Webster Cliff Trail.&lt;br /&gt;The trail, blazed in blue, leaves the east side of US 302 between&lt;br /&gt;the Crawford Depot and the Gate of the Notch. It runs through a&lt;br /&gt;clearing, enters the woods, and passes the side path leading right&lt;br /&gt;to Elephant Head.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Elephant Head Spur 44° 12' 58&amp;quot; 71° 24' 24&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.50 mi 29 min +466 ft on Webster-Jackson Trail&lt;br /&gt;0.60 mi 34 min +533 ft The main trail climbs along the south bank of Elephant Head&lt;br /&gt;Brook, well above the stream, then turns right, away from the&lt;br /&gt;brook. Angling up the mountainside roughly parallel to the&lt;br /&gt;highway, nearly level stretches alternating with sharp uphill&lt;br /&gt;pitches, it crosses Little Mossy Brook, and a side path leads right&lt;br /&gt;60 yd. to Bugle Cliff. This is a massive ledge overlooking&lt;br /&gt;Crawford Notch, where the view is well worth the slight extra effort&lt;br /&gt;required; if ice is present, exercise extreme caution.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Bugle Cliff spur 44° 12' 44&amp;quot; 71° 24' 05&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.80 mi 39 min +329 ft on Webster-Jackson Trail&lt;br /&gt;1.40 mi 1 hr 13 min +862 ft The main trail rises fairly steeply and crosses Flume Cascade&lt;br /&gt;Brook. Within sound of Silver Cascade Brook, the trail divides, the&lt;br /&gt;left branch for Mt. Jackson and the right for Mt. Webster.&lt;br /&gt;1.20 mi 1 hr 15 min +1265 ft on Webster-Jackson Trail&lt;br /&gt;2.60 mi 2 hr 28 min +2128 ft The Jackson (left) branch ascends gradually until it comes within&lt;br /&gt;sight of Silver Cascade Brook, then begins to climb moderately.&lt;br /&gt;Above the junction, it crosses three branches of the brook in quick&lt;br /&gt;succession. A short distance below the base of the rocky summit&lt;br /&gt;cone, it passes Tisdale Spring (unreliable, often scanty and&lt;br /&gt;muddy). The trail soon swings right and ascends steep ledges to&lt;br /&gt;the open summit.&lt;br /&gt;to Mt Jackson 44° 12' 12&amp;quot; 71° 22' 32&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;1.60 mi 57 min -226 ft on Webster Cliff Trail&lt;br /&gt;4.20 mi 3 hr 25 min +1902 ft This trail, a part of the AT, leaves the east side of US 302. The&lt;br /&gt;parking area is a stop for the AMC’s Hiker Shuttle. The trail&lt;br /&gt;ascends along the edge of the spectacular cliffs that form the east&lt;br /&gt;wall of Crawford Notch, then leads over Mts. Webster, Jackson,&lt;br /&gt;and Pierce to the Crawford Path.&lt;br /&gt;The trail leaves the summit of Mt. Jackson toward Mt. Pierce,&lt;br /&gt;following a line of cairns running north, and descends the ledges&lt;br /&gt;at the north end of the cone quite rapidly into the scrub, then the&lt;br /&gt;grade eases. The trail enters and winds through open alpine&lt;br /&gt;meadows, with views of Mt. Washington and Mt. Jackson, then it&lt;br /&gt;turns sharp left and drops into the woods. It continues up and&lt;br /&gt;down along the ridge toward Mt. Pierce, then ascends gradually to&lt;br /&gt;the junction with the Mizpah Cutoff, which leads left (west) to the&lt;br /&gt;Crawford Path.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mizpah Cutoff 44° 13' 09&amp;quot; 71° 22' 15&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.10 mi 3 min -18 ft on Webster Cliff Trail&lt;br /&gt;4.30 mi 3 hr 28 min +1883 ft Mizpah Spring Hut (where there are also tentsites for&lt;br /&gt;backpackers) is reached, and the Mt. Clinton Trail to the Dry River&lt;br /&gt;valley diverges right (southeast), heading diagonally down the hut&lt;br /&gt;clearing.&lt;br /&gt;to AMC Mizpah Spring Hut 44° 13' 09&amp;quot; 71° 22' 11&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.80 mi 40 min +494 ft on Webster Cliff Trail&lt;br /&gt;2&lt;br /&gt;Distance Time Elev&lt;br /&gt;Change&lt;br /&gt;Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude&lt;br /&gt;5.10 mi 4 hr 8 min +2377 ft Continuing past the hut, the trail soon ascends a steep, rough&lt;br /&gt;section with two ladders, and reaches an open ledge with good&lt;br /&gt;views south and west. The grade lessens, and after a sharp right&lt;br /&gt;turn in a ledgy area the trail reaches the summit of the southwest&lt;br /&gt;knob of Mt. Pierce, which affords a view of the summit of Mt.&lt;br /&gt;Washington rising over Mt. Pierce.&lt;br /&gt;to Mt Pierce 44° 13' 37&amp;quot; 71° 21' 57&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.09 mi 3 min -56 ft on Webster Cliff Trail&lt;br /&gt;5.19 mi 4 hr 11 min +2321 ft The trail descends into a sag and ascends easily through scrub to&lt;br /&gt;the summit of Mt. Pierce, where it comes into the open. It then&lt;br /&gt;descends moderately in the open in the same direction&lt;br /&gt;(northeast) about 150 yd. to its junction with the Crawford Path.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Crawford Path 44° 13' 40&amp;quot; 71° 21' 53&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;1.20 mi 59 min -736 ft on Crawford Path&lt;br /&gt;6.39 mi 5 hr 10 min +1585 ft Caution: Parts of this trail are dangerous in bad weather. Several&lt;br /&gt;lives have been lost on the Crawford Path because of failure to&lt;br /&gt;observe proper precautions. Below Mt. Eisenhower, a number of&lt;br /&gt;ledges are exposed to the weather, but they are scattered, and&lt;br /&gt;shelter is usually available in nearby scrub. From the Eisenhower-&lt;br /&gt;Franklin col, the trail runs completely above treeline, exposed to&lt;br /&gt;the full force of all storms. The most dangerous part of the path is&lt;br /&gt;the section on the cone of Mt. Washington, beyond Lakes of the&lt;br /&gt;Clouds Hut. Always carry a compass and study the map before&lt;br /&gt;starting. If trouble arises on or above Mt. Monroe, take refuge at&lt;br /&gt;Lakes of the Clouds Hut or go down the Ammonoosuc Ravine&lt;br /&gt;Trail. The Crawford Path is well marked above treeline with large&lt;br /&gt;cairns; in poor visibility, great care should be exercised to stay on&lt;br /&gt;it because many of the other paths in the vicinity are much less&lt;br /&gt;clearly marked. If the path is lost in bad weather and cannot be&lt;br /&gt;found again after diligent effort, one should travel west,&lt;br /&gt;descending into the woods and following streams downhill to the&lt;br /&gt;roads. On the southeast, toward the Dry River valley, nearly all&lt;br /&gt;the slopes are more precipitous, the river crossings are potentially&lt;br /&gt;dangerous, and the distance to a highway is much greater.&lt;br /&gt;From here, the trail soon enters the scrub and then full woods,&lt;br /&gt;descends moderately past the Mizpah Cutoff and continues&lt;br /&gt;through the Gibbs Brook Scenic Area.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mizpah Cutoff 44° 13' 14&amp;quot; 71° 22' 57&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;1.30 mi 1 hr 17 min -1261 ft on Crawford Path&lt;br /&gt;7.69 mi 6 hr 27 min +324 ft The trail begins to descend towards Gibbs Brook, angling down&lt;br /&gt;the side of the valley. The Crawford Path follows the south bank&lt;br /&gt;of Gibbs Brook, and a side path leads 40 yd. right to Gibbs Falls.&lt;br /&gt;Soon the trail passes an information sign for the Gibbs Brook&lt;br /&gt;Scenic Area, then descends moderately but steadily.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Gibbs Falls spur 44° 13' 16&amp;quot; 71° 24' 13&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.20 mi 11 min -169 ft on Crawford Path&lt;br /&gt;7.89 mi 6 hr 38 min +156 ft The Crawford Path follows the south bank of Gibbs Brook, and a&lt;br /&gt;side path leads 40 yd. right to Gibbs Falls.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Crawford Connector 44° 13' 15&amp;quot; 71° 24' 23&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.20 mi 10 min -132 ft on Crawford Path&lt;br /&gt;8.09 mi 6 hr 48 min +24 ft The main parking area at the south end of this trail is now located&lt;br /&gt;on the west side of Mt. Clinton Rd. a short distance north of its&lt;br /&gt;junction with US 302.&lt;br /&gt;to Crawford Path Trailhead (HiCtr) 44° 13' 11&amp;quot; 71° 24' 36&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;The main parking area at the south end of this trail is now located&lt;br /&gt;on the west side of Mt. Clinton Rd. a short distance north of its&lt;br /&gt;junction with US 302. The former parking lot on US 302 has been&lt;br /&gt;closed, and Crawford Path hikers are requested to use the Mt.&lt;br /&gt;Clinton Rd. lot because the parking spaces at other lots in the&lt;br /&gt;area are needed for the trails that originate from them.&lt;br /&gt;8.09 mi 6 hr 48 min +24 ft Totals&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248784928000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248100515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOUNT JACKSON &amp; PIERCE</name><id>10915074</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248611400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10915074/</event_url></item>