<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ok i am going on Gloria's hike after the Bolton Walk, then after Gloria's hike, since its just down the street, I want to see the sun set and have dinner on top of mountain at Wickham park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe a pizza or grinder..not sure yet..depends..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOW I GUESS WE WILL FINISH UP ABOUT 4:00 / 4:30  so there is some time frame to think about, if you are on the hike, it wont matter..if you want just the sunset, well all i can say is we will be there when we can...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a simple walk to the top via the big grass hill for a peacefull sunset and dinner on the round rock above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Share conversation over some tasty beverage and dinner on the mountain top..and posibly a moonlight walk in other areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a chair and coat..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford take Interstate 84, take Exit 60 (Manchester-East Hartford). take a left ...The route is 44 Burnside Ave heading to East Hartford..The park begins about quarter mile west of the exit but DO NoT use the gate. The park actually locks the gate at sunset.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Gloria's hike, go back to East hartford on rte 44 east.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE WILL MEET on the side of the road (Vernon Road, east hartford, ct) between the MARCO POLO RESTARUANT and the bottom &amp;quot;hill&amp;quot;...  look for the orange traffic cones..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is road about 1 mile away from that exit going towards east hartford, as you just pass the hill on the right. you will see a citgo station and mack donalds to the left and marco polo restaurant on the right just before the street.... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Vernon/Rockville &lt;br /&gt;Im not sure exactly what exit number but as best i know of its the one that goes to the mall but its the one 3 miles before rte 44...Please look at your maps first... &lt;br /&gt;use the RTE 44 exit go towards east hartford&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;anyway..Vernon Street, East Hartford, CT is the destination.. use that for your GPS, or mapquest map info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have the dark blue toyota avalon and will put a orange cone somewhere to see..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193775077000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193502101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mountain Top Dinner and Sunset Event After Gloria's Hike</name><id>6626854</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193601600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6626854/</event_url></item>