<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Elizabeth Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.773520</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Connecticut Historical Society</name><city>Hartford</city><id>10951192</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.704890</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/a/4/event_192664772.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;First Saturdays at Connecticut Historical Society Museum are FREE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;www.chs.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Four Exhibits that sound interesting to me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two features for this month&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cats &amp;amp; Dogs in Art and Life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;September 27, 2012 - April 6, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portrait and landscape paintings, drawings, needlework, sculptures, decorative household items, and photographs--all from the collection of the Connecticut Historical Society and never before seen together--will be on display to illustrate the practical and emotional bonds between dogs, cats, and people and how those connections have changed or endured over time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art: Connecticut Poster Stamps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;September 27, 2012 - January 12, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Poster stamps, also known as "cinderellas," are posters shrunk to the size of stamps that became popular in the early twentieth century. They are non-denominated, meaning they cannot be used to mail anything, but they were used to advertise businesses and events or to make political statements. First created in Germany around 1907, these brightly-colored advertising labels were designed by both notable artists and anonymous illustrators. People often stuck them on envelopes, letterheads, invoices, or mail packages, or just collected them for fun. Poster stamps gave almost anyone the opportunity to collect art at a fraction of the price and size of a poster. Visitors will be able to create their own poster stamps and stick them on the wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two:  On going&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inn &amp;amp; Tavern Signs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between 1750 and 1850, there were more than 50,000 inn and tavern signs produced by American painters, creating a distinct visual language and offering a glimpse into tavern life, travel, and patriotic ideals in early America. Only a fraction of these signs survive. The Connecticut Historical Society's collection numbering more than 60 signs is by far the largest and most spectacular in the country. Learn more about the &lt;a href="http://www.chs.org/page.php?id=570"&gt;sign for Carter's Inn&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;a href="http://www.chs.org/page.php?id=515"&gt;Collection Highlights gallery&lt;/a&gt;. A book about our inn and tavern sign collection is also available on-site and online through our &lt;a href="http://store.chs.org/products/Lions-%26-Eagles-%26-Bulls%3A-Early-American-Tavern-%26-Inn-Signs-from-The-Connecticut-Historical-Society.html" target="_blank"&gt;museum store.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Making Connecticut&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't miss this exhibit 400+ years in the making! Colorful, interactive, and filled with more than 500 historic objects, images, and documents, &lt;span&gt;Making Connecticut&lt;/span&gt; is the story of all the people of Connecticut, from the 1500s through today. Themes of daily life, clothing, transportation, sports and leisure, work, and social change run throughout the exhibit. Hands-on activities for kids (and adults!) include working a World War II assembly line, hand stenciling designs for a 19th-century chair, sewing a Native American moccasin, replacing bobbins in a textile mill, and cooking a meal and setting the table in both a colonial and a 1980s kitchen. Come be surprised, inspired, and amused as you explore our state's past and your own place in "Making Connecticut."&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gabriele </member_name><member_id>11913420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357478669000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357229082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Saturday at CHS - Cats &amp; Dogs in Art and Life &amp; Connecticut Posters</name><id>97682362</id><headcount>4</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357399800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/97682362/</event_url></item>