<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 Audubon Way</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03032</zip><lat>42.983557</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 668-2045</phone><name>Massabesic Audubon Center</name><city>Auburn </city><id>762116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.365221</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come meet up at the Massabesic Audubon Center for a leisurely walk through the woods to Battery Point for a beautiful view of Lake Massabesic.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;About the Walk&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be wearing name tags and will greet you at the entrance to the visitor center at 10:00 AM.   There are restrooms at the starting point.  We will start the hike at 10:10.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be guiding the group on a gentle walk through a lovely wooded area. The entire walk should be about 4 - 4.5 miles long.  The trails are quite flat and easy to walk.  Sneakers or hiking shoes are recommended.  Sorry-  The sanctuary does not allow dogs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm not sure how many birds we'll see this time of year, but there are numerous feeders behind the Visitor Center.  We could stop and watch some of the birds from inside before heading to lunch.  I also love to stop and see some of the critters which are housed here.  The barred owl out front is quite lovely.  I'm asking for lunch suggestions for after the walk, if you have any.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hiker Code of Conduct&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please try not to get too far ahead of the group. I go to a lot of effort to organize these walks, and it's not enjoyable when people run ahead and create their own event. If you have an emergency, I completely understand. Otherwise, these are designed to be leisurely, social walks, with time to appreciate the critters around us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can always use more organizers, and if anyone feels that the pace of the walk is not appropriate for their needs, they should consider organizing their own event in the future. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Address&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address of the Massabesic Audubon Center is 26 Audubon Way in Auburn, NH. You should probably use mapquest or google maps to map out your route beforehand if you're not using a GPS- There are numerous options for driving here depending on where you're coming from. &lt;br /&gt;Here's a link for the Massabesic Audubon Center website: &lt;a href="http://www.nhaudubon.org/center_masa.php#" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhaudubon....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;How the Waiting List Works&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When someone from the hike drops, everyone on the waiting list is automatically emailed. The first person on the the waiting list to add themselves to the hike will get in. I realize that this doesn't seem fair for the first person on the waiting list, if someone lower on the list gets in. However, I found that the automatic waiting list resulted in a very high percentage of no-shows. A number of people didn't check their email, even days before the hike, and therefore didn't know they had gotten in to the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting some of you and seeing others again. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adrienne&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in front of the Visitor Center with name tags on.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1295280354000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290907035000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Walk at Massabesic Audubon Center- Many Stops- Followed by Lunch</name><id>15570472</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292079600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15570472/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/b/global_11010795.jpeg</photo_url></item>