<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Smith Neck Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06371</zip><lat>41.293165</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great Island Old Lyme Boat Ramp</name><city>Old Lyme</city><id>699545</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.323266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;Last Year we all found this to be a favourite spot for a Barbie-q and paddle event(s)..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an area that is good for both recreational and sea kayakers..&lt;br /&gt;But recreational kayaks should have a blow whistle, float bags, a paddle leash, a paddle float , pump and...shouldnt go out in the deep too far.&lt;br /&gt;You know why. you seen a recreational kayak sink before your eyes at Bolton lake..&lt;br /&gt;sea kayakers..well you know what its like out here..so i dont have to tell you anything,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is the place all of you liked last year and Edgar's famous roast..&lt;br /&gt;we will have a flotilla of stuff to bring out there..so if you fall in..good luck...&lt;br /&gt;you are on your own.. we will grabb the food and bugg juice though..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DISCLAIMER:&lt;br /&gt;IM OLD, HAVE NO ASSETTS, a big ass though, CANT HEAR OR SEE, AM WEAK AND THINK SHARKS ARE PETS..&lt;br /&gt;SO YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE TO DO SELF RESCUE.. YOU CAN PRACTICE THAT HERE ALSO..&lt;br /&gt;im not going in the water, i knowe there are giant blood suckers, piranahs, brain invading amebeas, and SHARKS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Saybrook Point starting with July 6, 2008. &lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Su   6     High   1:21 AM     4.1   5:23 AM    Rise  9:28 AM      10&lt;br /&gt;     6      Low   7:43 AM    -0.1   8:25 PM     Set 10:50 PM&lt;br /&gt;     6     High   1:53 PM     3.7&lt;br /&gt;     6      Low   8:03 PM     0.4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok tides look good,&lt;br /&gt;BUT THE OTHER WEATHER, RAIN, WIND, AND SEA CONDITIONS ARE A GUESS RIGHT NOW..&lt;br /&gt;thus the word &amp;quot;possible&amp;quot; and  might cancel if not good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lower Connecticut River: Great Island to Old Lyme&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Preview: The Great Island area provides paddling in the secluded back channels, side rivers, and coves that parallel the lower Connecticut River near the mouth on the east side. You wind through 10-foot-tall marsh reeds and generally avoid the voluminous summer boating traffic. Whereas deeper-draft boats have to pay attention to the charts, kayaks can wander all over the place in the shallow waters here. Another advantage of the lower Connecticut is that three-quarters of the 1-mile?wide mouth averages a few feet in depth, which serves to keep motorboats to a minimum or forces them into the west channel, which exits through two stone breakwaters beyond Saybrook Point Lighthouse. The water just off the breakwaters is also very shallow? even small boats sometimes get grounded. Great Island offers good summer sea kayaking amid marsh grass, seaside goldenrod, glasswort, sea lavender, and water hemp.&lt;br /&gt;This popular launch site, located less than 500 feet from the Great Island Wildlife Management Area, provides visitors with opportunities to explore tidal marshes and a barrier beach. It is important to note, however, that motorized vessels must remain a reasonable distance away from the Great Island Wildlife Management Area upon launching. A water trail map of the Great Island estuary is posted near the entrance of this site's parking lot, and offers descriptions of a car-top boat trail (which would take visitors approximately 1.5 hours to traverse south to Griswold Point and approximately 3 hours in duration to return to the launch for the average kayak or canoe user). The map also introduces the history, flora, and fauna of the area. PLEASE NOTE: Visitors should investigate tide tables before launching boats at this site, due to the extremely shallow depth of water at low tide. Some routes to this site are marked with brown and white boat launch signs. To help you reach Great Island State Boat Launch, some routes leading to this site are posted with the brown and white Long Island Sound Access sign .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; APX  415 Smith Neck Road&lt;br /&gt;Old Lyme, Connecticut for GPS users.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from hartford:&lt;br /&gt;I Take rte 9 south past essex to 95 north&lt;br /&gt; Take I-95 North to Exit 70. &lt;br /&gt;At the end of the exit ramp, turn right onto Route 156/Shore Road and continue 1.7 miles. Next, turn right onto Smith Neck Road, and proceed .7 miles (to its end).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have the Blue Avalon with the kayak trailer and most likely i put the orange cones somewhere visible.&lt;br /&gt;I dont expect this area to be filled..but dont know..our group SHOULD doubble park with each other to save room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather isnt great..BUT GOOD ENOUGH FOR A START..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or high wind.seas canceles the event.i dont have a backup for this one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub= Pungo 12'=  &lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper dipper= Riot Tourlite 15'=     al-r&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', =  Alex&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'=   Janice&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenland= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 10 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used or bring extra food for everyone..&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will drop off kayaks on the side of the boat ramp then park, THE ORANGE CONES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215537423000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214885498000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> *Great Island* Lyme ct   Kayak event</name><id>8251413</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215363600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8251413/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/global_3876204.jpeg</photo_url></item>