<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>The Hampton Inn</address_2><address_1>26 Mill River Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06902</zip><lat>41.053305</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Shelly's On The River</name><city>Stamford</city><id>1394716</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.546624</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come join us for a night of casual conversations, cool cocktails, and some dancing and romancing at, Shelly's On The River located in the Hampton Inn, Stamford, CT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;This will be our second time at this new venue and I guarantee you won't be disappointed! Shelly's has all the ingredients we need for a great evening of mixing and mingling. I can't think of a better atmosphere for people to meet and greet one another. The softly lit lounge offers a casual, jazzy backdrop for intimate conversation and the gentle sounds of your favorite standards in the background will have you swaying in anticipation for the DJ music soon to follow!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;DJ Radio personality MATT ZAKO from 95.5 The FOX will be spinning tunes for your pleasure all night inside the spacious dance floor located in the restaurant. This time we will start the music early at 8:30 PM and go til 12:30 AM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Also in appreciation for our patronage management will set out a COMPLIMENTARY CHEESE PLATTER AND EXTEND HAPPY HOUR UNTIL 10:pm ( $3 Beers, $5 House Wines and $6 Well Drinks) plus a bar menu for that quick bite! Now if you prefer dinner, then help yourself to a 15% discount off any of the main entrees on the dinner menu (note this does not include the bar menu or Tapas).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;REMEMBER, This will be a MULTI-GROUP EVENT so expect singles from all over Fairfield, and Westchester to attend!! Bring a friend, a neighbor, a fellow co-worker or grab an ex relationship and get down to one of the best MEET AND GREETS around!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;PLEASE NOTE: THERE IS A REQUIRED $1 MEETUP FEE FOR THIS EVENT SO COME SEE US AS SOON AS YOU ARRIVE, THANK YOU.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/7/d/600_18558557.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/8/c/600_18558572.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Shelly's On the River - Restaurant, Bar &amp;amp; Lounge located at 26 Mill River Street in Stamford, CT overlooking the Mill River Park is a perfect escape from the city’s chaos. Chef Gabriel Brandi created a menu of simple and rustic dishes focused on fresh, local and seasonal ingredients. Shelly’s On the River is a must-visit dining destination for those looking for inspired cuisine in a comfortable setting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dining Room is a relaxed dining space with dimmed lighting, and vaulted ceilings, ideal for an intimate dining experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bar &amp;amp; Lounge is a destination for meeting and socializing, the decor is jazz inspired with a classic bar atmosphere. With counter top seating or table seating. The Lounge is the perfect place for a pre-dinner cocktail or casual dining.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/b/d/600_18558621.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shellysontheriver.com/index.asp" target="_blank"&gt;CLICK HERE FOR A PEAK AT SHELLY'S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jose&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the meetup signs!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Minnie</member_name><member_id>2449349</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>OH NO!</member_name><member_id>4774025</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291054183000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>172</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290172145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DANCING and ROMANCING @ SHELLY'S ON THE RIVER</name><id>15498772</id><headcount>172</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290902400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/15498772/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/6/global_19736598.jpeg</photo_url></item>