<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Butterfly Place is located in Westford, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;The address is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;120 Tyngsboro Road, Westford, MA, 01886&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Phone number is .............  (978) 392-0955&lt;br /&gt;My cell phone is................  (207) 608-7715&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Butterfly Place is an indoor living environment which has been carefully designed for the propagation and development of some of nature's most colorful living creations. This wonderful man-made habitat is contained within a 3,100 sq. ft. glass atrium building towering to the height of over 27 feet at its peak. Within this atrium's living butterfly envronment can be found a variety of colorful plants and shrubs, each of which has been selected as a ource of nectar for the butterflies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At any given time, the atrium may contain up to 500 butterflies representing as many as 50 species from around the world, although butterflies which are native to the New England region are featured wherever possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may walk within the atrium itself on a winding pathway, or you may choose to view nature's guests through the windows of our observation room. Either way, be sure to take time to visit the convenient display cases which are interspersed within the observation area, each containing butterflies and moths at various stages of development. Designed to make you self guided visit all the more enlightening, each exhibit includes an explanation regarding the case's occupant(s). This area also includes a 15 minute video presentation featuring the life cycle of a butterfly, running continuously and also designed to further enhance your visit. Finally, if you still have questions or would simply like to learn more, we encourage you to stop by our &amp;quot;Show and Tell Bench, where a member of our staff is always available to be of help and to share his knowledge of these fascinating creatures.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Butterfly Place offers a truly unique opportunity to photograph or videotape butterflies in a natural environment. Please don't forget to bring your camera!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hours of operation for April 1st - September 30th are:  10 am - 5 pm&lt;br /&gt;I am thinking we should probably get there when the doors open at 10:00 am just so that we can have plenty of time to shoot before the darkness starts to settle in. Plus the flier says give yourself at LEAST an hour to really enjoy the butterflies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: Adults: $9.50 &lt;br /&gt;There are discounted tickets for groups of 10 or more and then of 20 and above. They are fairly decent discounts too. That is why I would really like to know who is coming before we go. Please RSVP quick as you can, okay??&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all for your attention.&lt;br /&gt;Deborah Wilson&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing  a FAN sign at the entrance.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220882735000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216841954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Event: The Butterfly Place</name><id>8397749</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220709600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8397749/</event_url></item>