<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>19 Warren Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02368</zip><lat>42.165508</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 961-7729</phone><name>Caffe Bella</name><city>Randolph</city><id>985857</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.044183</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Oh, yeah, that's in Rockland, isn't it?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is entirely possible that you'll get some variation of the above if you mention Cafe Bella in Randolph. Try it sometime, just for fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you may well know, people who respond that way are thinking of Bella's; a significantly larger Italian restaurant that sits quite close to an off-ramp for Route 3. It's a good restaurant that sees a lot of traffic in more than one sense of the word.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But take our word for it, the *other* Bella, in Randolph, gives up nothing to its brawnier namesake in terms of cuisine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to think of it, DON'T take our word for it! We're a DINING group! Come and see for yourself!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Specifically, come on Thursday, December 9th at 7:00 PM and join us as we investigate just why Cafe Bella is consistently mentioned in discussions of the South Shore's better restaurants, Italian or otherwise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special note:&lt;/b&gt; You'll probably recall that Mike recently posted this restaurant as an idea for the group and asked what time people could come at, because they apparently didn't take reservations. Well, as Confucius wisely said over two millenia ago, &amp;quot;Don't believe everything you read on Yelp!&amp;quot; We were in fact able to make a reservation, and so have scheduled this Meetup at what appears to be the time that will allow the largest number of our members to attend.&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Caffe Bella&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;19 Warren St (Route 139)&lt;br /&gt;Randolph, MA 02368&lt;br /&gt;(781) 961-7729&lt;br /&gt;Reviews on Yelp: &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/caffe-bella-randolph" target="_blank"&gt;Caffe Bella&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Two per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact Mike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Caffe Bella is on the spendy side for the South Shore: Fortunately it is not the kind of place where you pay over $20.00 for an entree and leave the table still hungry. They do offer pizza in addition to their entrees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Current Annual Members - None, Group Members - $2.00, Guests - $2.00; $12 to become a 2011 Annual Member ($10 if you are a 2010 Annual Member, a past 2-year Annual Member or Former AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over four years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, December 8th @ 7:00 pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer. Changes to &amp;quot;No&amp;quot; after the deadline will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Caffe Bella is located in a strip mall at the intersection of Warren Street (Route 139) and North Main Street (Route 28).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292097813000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290791211000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Other Bella!</name><id>15560302</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291939200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/15560302/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/3/global_18390867.jpeg</photo_url></item>