<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Holland Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397217</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Johnny D's Uptown Restaurant</name><city>Somerville</city><id>5690312</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122993</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/6/2/event_93750562.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;LIVE FOREVER!! &lt;br /&gt;

 Bob Marley Tribute Band the Duppy Conquerors perform Marley&amp;rsquo;s new recording "LIVE FOREVER" &lt;br /&gt;

 Saturday March 10, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 Johnny Ds &lt;br /&gt;

 17 Holland Street, Somerville, MA 02144-2730 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;(617) 776-2004 at 9:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.johnnyds.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Photos by Judy Johnson &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Recorded 30 years ago while Marley was touring in support of his album "Uprising", LIVE FOREVER is Bob Marley's last recorded concert. This never before released audio collection offers an incredible snapshot of one of music's most influential performers. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Uprising was released in 1980. As Marley died the following year, Uprising was to become the final studio album to be released during his lifetime. This album is one of Marley's most directly religious, with nearly every song addressing his Rastafarian beliefs, culminating in the acoustic folk classic, "Redemption Song". &lt;br /&gt;

 Bob Marley &amp;amp; The Wailers - LIVE FOREVER: The Stanley Theatre, Pittsburgh, PA, September 23, 1980 is a 2CD/3LP/digital collection that features many of Bob's most cherished songs, and is now available. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This unforgettable concert contains unique performances of "No Woman No Cry," "Jammin'," and "Is This Love," to name a few, and depicts a musical innovator and inspiration to people of many cultures and generations. This spectacular audio documentary LIVE FOREVER, also immortalizes the last song Marley ever performed live in concert: "Get Up Stand Up," his rally cry for equality. The Rolling Stone calls Marley's LIVE FOREVER "A final fierce account, onstage, of an honorable revolutionary life." &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Bob Marley was a hero figure, in the classic mythological sense. His departure from this planet came at a point when his vision of One World, One Love -- inspired by his belief in Rastafari -- was beginning to be heard and felt. The last Bob Marley and the Wailers tour in 1980 attracted the largest audiences at that time for any musical act in Europe. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 So, on March 10, 2012, the Bob Marley tribute band Duppy Conquerors will perform the entire recording "LIVE FOREVER" of Bob Marley and the Wailers that was performed at The Stanley Theatre, Pittsburgh, PA, September 23, 1980 at Johnny D&amp;rsquo;s located 17 Holland Street, Somerville, MA 02144-2730 (617) 776-2004 at 9:30pm ticket price $12. Advanced dinner Packages are available by calling for a reservation $25 + tax+ gratuity (includes shoe ticket) Dinner begins at 7:45 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331486672000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329253942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bob Marley Tribute Band</name><id>52354412</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331429400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/52354412/</event_url></item>