<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>363 Union Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02370</zip><lat>42.130001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Saddle Sores</name><city>Rockland</city><id>404948</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.910004</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SSFMG &amp;amp; SSDOMG Combined Meetup &amp;amp; More&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 10th, 2007 @ 5-8pm @ Saddle Sores&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join members of the South Shore Fitness Meetup Group (SSFMG) and the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group (SSDOMG) and their guests for this fabulous and fun Combined Meetup!  This Meetup will be full of food, fun, friends, festivities, and more!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here?s what we are featuring at tonight?s Combined Meetup and More!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Belley, of Belly Fitness, will be providing a Diet and Nutrition Workshop especially for our Groups!  Rob, who has been an active member of the SSFMG since April, has been providing us with Dynamic Stretching and Mini Boot Camps since August and he has agreed to put together a Diet and Nutrition Workshop for us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Organizer Team has put together an Event Organizer ?How To? Guide and Checklist which we will review with everyone.  This will be a great tool for those who would like to help organize Meetups and events with our Meetup Groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be planning events and Meetups for late November, December, and early 2008!  Be sure to check the Message Boards in your respective Meetup Groups for Restaurants and Event Ideas and be ready to let us know what you want to see on the calendar.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Country Line Dance Lessons!  We will have a member of a country music band teach us some basic country line dance steps so we can do some country line dancing while we listen to the band.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food!  Saddle Sores offers more than your ?typical? bar food.  Their food is delicious.  We will be savoring salad, pizza, calzones, nachos, chicken fingers, and more!  Now is your chance to try the food at Saddle Sores as there will be a little bit of just about everything for you to taste!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live Band!  Tonight the Greg Burroughs Band will be playing starting at 8pm.  While there is a cover charge, it is included in the event fee at a discount.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Billiards, Darts, Dancing and More!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is sure to be a fun night that you do not want to miss out on!  Be sure to arrive early so you don?t miss out on any of the fun.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here?s the scoop!&lt;br /&gt;November SSFMG and SSDOMG Combined Meetup and More!&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 10th&lt;br /&gt;5-8pm&lt;br /&gt;Doors open @ 4:45pm ~ Stay till the bar closes if you want!&lt;br /&gt;Saddle Sores&lt;br /&gt;363 Union Street&lt;br /&gt;Rockland, MA 02370&lt;br /&gt;(Across from the Fire Station in Rockland Center)&lt;br /&gt;781-878-0362&lt;br /&gt;www.saddlesores.com&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $20 per person, includes Food, Fun, Diet/Nutrition Workshop, Country Line Dance Lessons, Band, and Event Fee (Does not include the cost of drinks.)&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Angela, Rob, Kathy, Mike (SSFMG &amp;amp; SSDOMG Organizer Team)&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: We need at least 15 people by October 15th.  No maximum.  Up to 2 Guests per Group Member are welcome.  (If you want to bring more guests please email me.)&lt;br /&gt;Deadlines: See below.&lt;br /&gt;Ages: 21+ (Your ID will be checked.)&lt;br /&gt;Please see the Event Posting on the Message Board for full and complete details!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCE PAYMENT IS REQUIRED! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here?s how this will work.&lt;br /&gt;Once you RSVP Yes I will email you within a few days w/ my mailing address.&lt;br /&gt;Please mail me a Money Order and include the following information.  If any of this information is missing it may delay the process of your payment and RSVP.  &lt;br /&gt; Item      Example&lt;br /&gt; Name on Meetup Group   Angela N.&lt;br /&gt; First and Last Name    Angela Nuss&lt;br /&gt; Town      Braintree&lt;br /&gt; Email Address     email@server.xyz&lt;br /&gt; Which Meetup Group you RSVPed Yes SSFMG or SSDOMG&lt;br /&gt;Once your payment has been received I will mark you as ?Paid? on the Discussion Thread for the event on the Message Board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: You will be responsible for the payments of your guests.  They are subject to the same payment terms as you are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: If you belong to both Groups you only need to RSVP ?Yes? to one Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No personal checks.  Cash or Money Order Only!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Final Deadline: November 1st ~ All payments must be postmarked by this date and received by November 4th.  If payment is not received by this deadline and you have RSVPed ?Yes? then you will be subject to a $5 late charge (that?s a cost of $25) at the door.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see the Event Posting on the Message Board for full and complete details!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saddle Up!  Let?s get ready to have a fun, educational, and fantastic night w/ the SSFMG and SSDOMG!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542238000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190765909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SSDOMG &amp; SSFMG Combined Meetup and More!</name><id>6427865</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194732000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/6427865/</event_url></item>