<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Can you remember back when you were a child and your parents used to tell you stories?  Wasn't it the best?  Wouldn't it be cool if you could experience that all over again... as an adult, and with people who are truly amazing at it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If that sounds good to you, then come join us this coming Tuesday for an absolute GEM of an event.  One of our members, &lt;b&gt;Mike Sweeny&lt;/b&gt;, is going to be the featured storyteller at Brother Blue's Storytelling Event in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll get to sit back and watch as experienced storytellers dazzle and amaze you with their talent in short, 8-10 minute bursts of pure storytelling goodness.  And this event isn't just for the experienced craftsmen either.  Professionals and amateurs alike gather at Brother Blue's event to practice their craft, entertain the audience, or sometimes... just to bitch about their day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW MUCH DOES IT COST?&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Believe it or not, it's only a 3 dollar donation to get in the door for this 2.5 hour event that's loaded with all levels of talent.  Some of them will be amazing.  Some of them... not so much.  But I guarantee that you will enjoy yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One last reason to come.  If you've been to any of my workshops, then you've probably heard me say that the best way to convey your personality to someone is through conversational storytelling.  For example, you can't just say that you're a world traveler, because that's lame.  Instead, you would tell stories about your adventures, and the other person would GET that you're a world traveler on their own... and it will have a much greater impact.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So even though this event is meant to be entertaining (and it is), you will also learn something that will improve your social skills.  You will get to experience (on the receiving end) the power of really good storytelling, and it will give you a personal experience of what's possible for you if you decide to work on this skill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET THERE - IMPORTANT - READ THIS!&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This part is super important, so make sure you read it twice.  We're going to meet as a group in front of the &lt;b&gt;Out Of Town Newsstand just outside the Harvard Square T Stop&lt;/b&gt;.  I will be there starting at 6:00pm to greet you, and then we will all walk over together at 6:15pm.  Finding this library can be &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;really&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; confusing, so it's best if you come with us as a group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I strongly recommend that you do not try and find parking in Harvard Square (especially at that time of day) and that you just take the T in, and walk over with us.  If you have a car, then park at the Alewife train station and take the T over to Harvard Square.  It's only 3 stops in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just in case you can't make it on time, I will email everyone a set of walking directions from the newsstand so you can just meet us there if you need to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;COME JOIN US&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I really like this event, and I want you to come and experience it with me.  I also want you to come out and help support Mike Sweeny for his first time as a featured storyteller at Brother Blue's event.  I promise that this will be worth your time, so come on out and play with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell phone number in case you have any questions or in case you get lost.  It's 401-359-6685.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.P.S. - The guy in the picture for this event is Brother Blue in his earlier years.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet me in front of "Out Of Town News" just outside the Harvard Square T stop.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240777621000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237449505000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brother Blue's Storytelling</name><id>9986888</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237932000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/9986888/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/2/global_7742306.jpeg</photo_url></item>