<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1245 New Britain Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06110</zip><lat>41.731354</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-561-0180</phone><name>Szechuan Tokyo</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>823910</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Szechuan Tokyo started as an Asian-fusion restaurant in 1999. As popular as ever, additional to the restaurant the company has included in its operations a vast wholesale sushi group, a catering group, and the Entertainment Group, which provides products and consulting services associated with the music industry to a wide variety of clients. The Entertainment Group also offers products and services which exploit its vast resources (e.g., production, information technology, design).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What about the restaurant?&lt;br /&gt;Although the term &amp;quot;Asian-fusion&amp;quot; is used when describing the restaurant, Szechuan Tokyo never fuses the cuisine on the plate. Rather, we serve authentic home-style Sichuan cuisine, banquet-style delicacies, sushi and sashimi, and cooked Japanese specialties. No expense is spared when creating our dishes with authentic, premium ingredients that are impeccably fresh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Home of the &amp;quot;Jazz Bar;&amp;quot; our wine and liquor operation is eclectic yet complete. From a delicate foreign or domestic wine to the infamously &amp;quot;deadly&amp;quot; Scorpion Bowl, our signature cocktail for two, our beverage service has it all. Designated driver? Your soda or juice is on us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our mission is to serve great food and huge beverages at a value price; our variety empowers our customers to create the experience they desire; whether a quick, informal bite in the bar or a dress affair for a hundred persons -- &amp;quot;West Hartford's Asian Fusion Experience™&amp;quot; is here every day of the year (but for Thanksgiving) to serve luncheon and dinner in a unique, eclectic setting.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Large table in back room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stuart</member_name><member_id>4565209</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237333353000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-2183</urlname><id>1179521</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Connecticut Jewish Singles:  35+ Social Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228059697000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Asian Christmas Eve</name><id>9250495</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230163200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-2183/events/9250495/</event_url></item>