<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>FREE w/ promo T-shirt OR</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>14.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Event Description: NEW Event: "Wacky Wednesday".
Who: Combined MeetUp and Single Event "Wacky Wednesday" Group.
What: Comedian Joe Vega (see below). &lt;&lt;&lt; I heard this guy is VERY FUNNY!
&gt;&gt;&gt; Optional:  Following the show, you are invited to join us for a "Fire-Pit Under the Stars" after-party in the back-yard of one of our female group members! (see below). &lt;&lt;&lt;
When: Wednesday, September 19  - gather @ 6:15 PM.
Where: "FUNNY BONE" Comedy Club (within Manchester's Buckland Hills Mall).
Cost: $14.00, or FREE with promo Tee-shirt (see below) - Must be over 21.
Misc.:  Click the link below to RSVP, see who's attending, and/or for updated details!
Please read all details below and DO NOT hit reply or write directly.

I reserved 24 seats together on a first RSVP, first served basis via my FREE "FREE Live Outdoor Music" MeetUp online calendar reservation system:  &lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/" class="linkified"&gt;http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/&lt;/a&gt;

***

Rather than pay the $10-20 admission fee each time, almost everybody purchases a promo T-shirt (only $15) to gain admission to this and (almost) ALL WEDNESDAY performances for FREE by showing your promo T-shirt at the Box Office - FOREVER (whether attending as part of our irregularly scheduled group, or not).  Our group attends "Wacky Wednesday" at least twice per month - more during colder months.  Such a deal!

After RSVP'ing "yes", simply show up and gather in the "Funny Bone" BAR @ 6:15 (AFTER picking up your FREE ticket from the Box Office by buying and/or showing your promo T-shirt - telling the Box Office you have a reservation through "Rob's Wacky Wednesday" group).  This will give us a chance to gather, have a drink, chat, and enter as a "group", thus allowing us to sit together as their policy is "first come, first seated".  Ask the ticket-taker to point out "Rob's Wacky Wednesday" group, or simply look for a group of friendly 40/50-somethings wearing promo T-shirts and introduce yourself!  When the Club doors open at 6:30, THOSE PRESENT will enter together so we can be assigned good tables together and optionally have appetizers, dinner, drinks (no minimum; separate checks have been pre-approved) and get to know each other while waiting for the show to begin at 7:30 (lasting to @ 9:00).

&gt;&gt;&gt; If you do not RSVP "yes" and/or show up on time, there is no guarantee that you'll be able to sit with our group - but don't let that stop you as we can typically "squeeze you in"!  If entering after 6:30, please ask the ticket taker to assign you a seat with, or nearest to, "Rob's Wacky Wednesday" group, if still available.

All (over 21) are welcome to join us!  Invite your friends and encourage them to join the "Single Event" www.TheSingleEvent.com and "MeetUp" www.MeetUp.com to be invited to these, and MANY MORE fun activities of all sorts!

Please MapQuest directions to:
194 Buckland Hills Drive, Manchester, CT 06042.

The "Funny Bone" is located within the Buckland Hills Mall, on the first floor, between JC Penney and Barnes &amp; Noble, via the external "Blue Turtle" entryway.

Funny Regards,

- Rob

Rob Pudney

*** FOLLOWING THE SHOW: Weather permitting, rather than go to a bar, we typically gather around a propane-fueled ceramic "Fire Pit" and listen to some music, dance, chat, tell jokes, gaze at the stars, or just relax with friendly company at a nearby outdoor location.  THIS WEEK: We've been invited to after-party in the backyard of one of our female members, living @ 3 miles from the Funny Bone.  Directions will be provided at the show.  &lt;&lt;&lt;

&gt;&gt;&gt; PLEASE BRING SOME SNACKS AND/OR BEVERAGES OF CHOICE TO SHARE and a beach chair or blanket for this casual, fun gathering.

Please visit or call the Box Office (860) 432-8600 for info regarding the FREE "Wacky Wednesday" T-Shirt promo and/or check their web site:
www.HartfordFunnyBone.com for upcoming shows, general information, bios, etc.

***  THIS WEEK:  Joe Vega ...
"... has appeared in many feature films, most recently ROUNDERS, and ROW YOUR BOAT. He also worked on RYDER PI, AN EASTSIDE STORY, and PUNCHLINE with Tom Hanks. The acting is great, but performing in front of a live audience is my first love. Joe has made them laugh from coast to coast and everywhere in between. Whether its a packed house at TRUMP CASTLE in Atlantic City, or in front of 20,000 people at the famed MADISON SQUARE GARDEN; Joe has so much fun on stage that you cant help but have a great time watching him. Joe has logged some impressive time on radio shows, trading laughs with Howard Stern and others. He has appeared on all the major Comedy shows, including Comedy on the Road, Carolines, Comic Strip Live, and many others. He also hosted his own TV show called The Latin Connection on FOX. Whether its making people laugh in nightclubs or concert halls, JOE VEGA is motivating people all over the world. Youll be glad that he is on the job and loving it!"</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190785227000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190035476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEW Event: "Wacky Wednesday" &amp; "Fire-Pit" 09/19</name><id>6374512</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190240100000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6374512/</event_url></item>