<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>899 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363422</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-491-5877</phone><name>Toscanini's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669134</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099590</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>and 2 PM&lt;br /&gt;massmouth presents first annual February vacation 2010  folk tale slam!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Story: the world’s longest running family entertainment + “the world’s best ice cream” =sweet fun&lt;br /&gt;10 tales from world folk tradition “updated”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February 17th at 10am and 2pm. Two shows  Hosted by Stu Mendleson &lt;br /&gt;10-11AM &lt;br /&gt;short shorts ( 3 minute tales) geared toward the 3 years and up to 6yrs.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp; &lt;br /&gt;2-3:30 PM @Toscanini’s ( 5 minute tales) geared toward the 6 years and up folk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;massmouth presents~  Folk Tale Story Slams at Toscaninis @ &lt;a href="http://www.tosci.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tosci.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your $7 includes  admission and a ticket for an one ice cream and your donation to: &lt;br /&gt;Heading Home -  homeless families in Cambridge  @www.headinghomeinc.org&lt;br /&gt;Partners in Health- health care and emergency relief in Haiti @ &lt;a href="http://www.pih.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pih.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take an one award winning ice cream store, an audience's imagination , and several storytellers with the ability to weave word magic  and voilá - we have a sweet recipe for vacation fun.  Toscaninis Ice Cream on Main Street , Central Square, Cambridge,  will host two shows on Wednesday, February 17th. The first, for the &amp;quot;need a nap at noon&amp;quot; crowd is scheduled for 10am.  The second session will start at 2pm.  What is a story slam?  Award winning storytellers from massmouth.com will take the mic to tell their best 3 to 5 minute updated folk tale. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A panel of judges made of children's librarians and elementary aged students will grade the tellers, just as in a poetry or story slam for adults. Judges work in 3 teams of 3, two children on each. Every story is judged on it's form and how well it was told.  If 10 am is too early for ice cream, the ticket for a cone can be redeemed at any time within the vacation week. Come join us in a new twist on timeless family entertainment.  Your imagination can take you anywhere and a story will be the tour guide.&lt;br /&gt;899 Main Street Central Square, Cambridge MA (617) 491-5877&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Too early to eat ice cream? Save your ticket and Toscis will honor the ice cream part within a week of purchase. $7 = pays for tiny cone and $3 goes to Heading Home and Partners in Health&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266592072000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264424410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>folk tale slam</name><id>12415686</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266418800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/12415686/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_10410532.jpeg</photo_url></item>