<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Redstone Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.801041</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rave Motion Pictures Buckland Hills</name><city>Manchester</city><id>664343</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.547752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>To kick off the new year, let's go out to a  move that's been getting some of the best reviews of the season.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start with an early dinner at Carrabba's right near the movie at 6pm and then head over to the movie which starts at 8:00.  There are several other movies playing that start between 7 and 8 so if you're interested in another movie feel free to join us just for dinner  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carrabba's:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.carrabbas.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.carrabbas.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Manchester&lt;br /&gt;(860) 643-4100&lt;br /&gt;31 Red Stone Road&lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06042&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is at Rave Motion Pictures, 99 Red Stone Road, Manchester, CT.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;True Grit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A 14-year-old girl (Hailee Steinfeld) joins an aging U.S. marshal (Jeff Bridges) and another lawman (Matt Damon) in tracking her father's killer into hostile Indian territory in Joel and Ethan Coen's adaptation of Charles Portis' original novel. Sticking more closely to the source material than the 1969 feature adaptation starring Western icon John Wayne, the Coens' True Grit tells the story from the young girl's perspective, and re-teams the celebrated filmmaking duo with their No Country for Old Men screenwriting partner Scott Rudin. Josh Brolin co-stars. &lt;br /&gt;Cast: Jeff Bridges, Josh Brolin, Matt Damon, Hailee Steinfeld, Barry Pepper&lt;br /&gt;Director: Ethan Coen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.truegritmovie.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.truegritmovie.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New York Times | Manohla Dargis &lt;br /&gt;In some ways, much like Charles Laughton's &amp;quot;Night of the Hunter,&amp;quot; which the Coens quote both musically and visually, True Grit is a parable about good and evil. Only here, the lines between the two are so blurred as to be indistinguishable, making this a true picture of how the West was won, or - depending on your view - lost. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles Times | Kenneth Turan &lt;br /&gt;When Iris DeMent's impeccable version of the hymn is heard on the soundtrack as the final credits roll, it's the perfect touch to end a film whose aim is always true. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rolling Stone | Peter Travers &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes True Grit a new classic for the Coens is the way the brothers absorb the unfairly unsung Portis into their DNA, like they did with Cormac McCarthy in &amp;quot;No Country for Old Men.&amp;quot; True Grit is packed with action and laughs, plus a touching coda with an older Mattie, but it's the dialogue that really sings. Great filmmaking. Great acting. Great movie. Saddle up. Read full review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note in your RSVP whether you'll be a both dinner and the movie, just dinner or just the movie.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294197582000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293746152000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>True Grit - Dinner and a Movie</name><id>15862354</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294009200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/15862354/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/2/global_20510306.jpeg</photo_url></item>