<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>162 Winn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.504240</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>American Legion Hall</name><city>Burlington</city><id>486621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.185790</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please come to our previously postponed dance to celebrate the holidays with old friends and new at a special holiday party for meetup group members and their friends. There will be entertainment and dancing with Four on the Floor. We have rented the American Legion Hall in Burlington (right off of 128) from 7:30-11:30 PM with help of our good friend Brian. There is a $10.00 charge which should cover the expenses and some snacks. There will be a cash bar. You are welcome to invite family or friends, but please include their payment when you sign up (adults only, don't have to be single). Whether you already paid or not you will need to respond again at the new listing and mark &amp;quot;ALREADY PAID&amp;quot; or will pay by check or online. If you paid but cannot make this date please email me for a refund.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you wish to pay online please go to:&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/mvsinglefriends/calendar/9478898/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and indicate &amp;quot;PAID ONLINE&amp;quot; in your reply, it will help me keep track. I appreciate your help with this. If you prefer to send a check I will email you my address but indicate on your reply, &amp;quot;paying by check&amp;quot; and I will let you know when I receive it. The postponements and Mother Nature hasn't helped to get this organized. There is a limit of 125 people for the hall so please reply as soon as you know you can attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am sorry for all the previous confusion and look forward to a special night for all of us. I hope you will come. &lt;br /&gt;Sandy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>HALL IS RENTED TO US...COME ON IN.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235435770000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231447872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HOLIDAY DANCE PARTY</name><id>9478992</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235262600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9478992/</event_url></item>