<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03857</zip><lat>43.079918</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newmarket Mills LLC</name><city>Newmarket</city><id>12785102</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.935585</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstraction: Abstracts and Extracts through the Lens  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;An abstract photography exhibit by local seacoast photographers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We just can't celebrate our Abstract Show enough!  Please join us for a new opening reception at the new Newmarket Mill location.  For those who couldn't make it to the Exeter reception, this is your opportunity to see the show for the first time.  For those who did make the Exeter show, this is yet another opportunity to mix and mingle with some of your favorite photographers and to see the show in an entirely new light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, if you can bring a drink or finger food, your efforts will be welcome.  If you do intend to bring an item please make a note below so we know what additional items to pick up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gallery hours&lt;/strong&gt;: 2-4 pm each Saturday and Sunday through May 5th&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location info&lt;/strong&gt;:  55 Main Street, Newmarket, NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using the Main Street North entrance (near Poppers restaurant) at the Newmarket Mills, proceed upstairs to conference room suite 313.  Parking options: along the street, in the Mill parking lot directly across the street from the North Main entrance, or the municipal parking lot a little further up the hill (just off Main Street).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Handicap parking is available in back of the building (between the two gray stone buildings).  Enter through #55 Main entrance (Bloomin Cow &amp;amp; Creek Hill Upholstery signs nearby).  There is an elevator located down the hall and to the right.  Take the lift to the third floor, head left and the conference room is located on the left, just beyond the kitchen area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>tracy</member_name><member_id>11265621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366943386000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366030051000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opening Reception at The Mills</name><id>114420142</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366480800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/114420142/</event_url></item>