<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>232 Wooster Street </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.302810</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-773-0733</phone><name>Joker's Wild</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1029660</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919816</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Comedy?  Food?  Drinks?  I'm so in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello - I've never been to Joker's Wild, New Haven's comedy club.  A friend from high school is going to perform there (I assume as an opening act; he isn't billed on the website) so I thought it would be a good opportunity to check it out.  And you know me, the more the merrier, so I thought that I'd throw it out to ya'll and try to get a group to go  (www.jokerswildclub.com).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;21+ only. Tickets are $15, and shows are at 8pm and 10pm.  *NOTE* Two great NHC members brought it to my attention that if you call ahead and reserve tickets, they will be 'comped'. They said that I could update my reservation until 6pm on Friday - so please let me know by then if you're coming so that we can get free tickets!! (Note part deux - there is a two drink minimum). I have dinner plans, so  I'm going to the 10pm show.  I'll be there by 9:30pm. My phone # will be in my RSVP.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to an article about them in the Register (&lt;a href="http://www.nhregister.com/articles/2008/12/04/life/1204jokerswild.txt" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhregister...&lt;/a&gt;) parking is at 10 Olive St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 8pm show people, have a great time - but make sure that you call ahead so you don't have to pay a cover! 203 773 0733.  PS - I called and clarified the parking situation.  They said that they have a 30-spot lot, but if its full, they did confirm that there is free parking at 10 Olive st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: for the 10pm show, I currently have 11 yeses.  I called Joker's, and they made me promise that I'm really truely bringing that many people.  Because apparently, seats are included... and they have to move things around.  So please come if you RSVP'd yes so I don't look like a jerk : ) I'm really excited that people are coming, and if you want to come after this point I would definitely encourage you to come (and RSVP still) - (I haven't been there, but I'm sure we can figure out some way to all hang out). I know that I offered to call to get comped tickets until 6pm, but since we're already past 10 people (the amount their comfortable people calling ahead about per person), anyone who RSVPs 'yes' between now and 7pm (their dead-line), please call Joker's Wild and ask for tickets (203-773-0733).  If you're part of the 11 yeses, then your tickets are under the name &amp;quot;Kathryn Lynch.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm so glad people are coming ^_^ see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who don't know me and want help spotting me, I'm petite (aka... short), long chestnut hair, wearing a sort of blue-green top with different squares on it &amp;amp; jeans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there - couldn't we all use a good laugh?&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249946050000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249495738000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy Night!</name><id>11042988</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249695000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/11042988/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/5/0/global_10046640.jpeg</photo_url></item>