<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;RESCHEDULED from last month's rain-out! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of a series of hikes for those of us who want to start getting (back) into hiking and need to build up some stamina and endurance before attempting the rockier terrains and steeper inclines!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;I don't know how many of you have Thursday off due to Rosh Hashanah, but I do and I'll be celebrating by climbing this mountain!  I did two 5-ish mile hikes this past weekend and now I'm adding a mile.  Onward and upward, I say!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;North Pack Monadnock is a modest summit but the hike up the mountain is rewarding experience, with great views from the summit on the surrounding wooded hills of New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are looking for a reasonably challenging hike to get back in shape before more arduous climbs, look no further than North Pack Monadnock. Compared to nearby Mount Monadnock, the hike up North Pack is relatively easy, but the trail is steep in some places and will give you the flavor of longer hikes in the White Mountains: a consistently ascending trail under pine trees and birches, nice views and places to rest along the way, and a rewarding summit experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be taking a 6-mile loop, using Ted's Trail, Carolyn's Trail and the Cliff Trail. Description and pictures here: &lt;a href="http://www.hikeneweng.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Even though this hike is for those of us just starting out (or starting again) please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times! (I know it will feel strenuous to ME!) Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket and a hat) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some high-energy snacks! Weather permitting, I plan to sit and have a picnic lunch at the summit!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs and kids welcome!  &lt;b&gt;RAIN CANCELS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Wapack National Wildlife Refuge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wapack National Wildlife Refuge was New Hampshire's first refuge and was established through a donation in 1972. The 1,672-acre refuge is located about 20 miles west of Nashua, New Hampshire and encompasses the 2,278-foot North Pack Monadnock Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stone wall (photo by Mark Malnati) The refuge is a popular hawk migration area and provides nesting habitat for numerous migratory songbirds such as the tree sparrow, Swainson's thrush, magnolia warbler, crossbills, pine grosbeaks and white-throated sparrow. The refuge also supports a wide variety of upland wildlife including deer, bear, coyote, fisher, fox, mink and weasel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;The trailhead for Ted's and Carolyn's Trails is located on Old Mountain Road in Greenfield, NH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wapack Trailhead is marked by blue and white refuge boundary signs on the south side (right) of the road and there is a small pullout on the north side (left) of the road. (Wapack Trailhead is mentioned here only to give you a reference point for finding Ted's and Carolyn's Trails.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trailhead for Ted's and Carolyn's Trails is approximately a half mile east of (beyond) the trailhead for Wapack Trail. There is a trail sign as well as a one-car pullout, both located on the south side (right) of the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the east:&lt;br /&gt;* Go west on Rt. 101 over the top of Temple Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;* After the passing lane ends at the top of the hill, do not turn into the Miller State Park parking lot. Instead, continue 0.4 mile to the first right (Old Mountain Road in Peterborough), and turn right.&lt;br /&gt;* Proceed 0.6 mile to a three-way intersection, and bear right onto East Mountain Road.&lt;br /&gt;* Go another 2.8 miles until the road ends.&lt;br /&gt;* Turn right onto Sand Hill Road.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Sand Hill Road for approximately 2.2 miles (Sand Hill Road becomes Old Mountain Road at the Greenfield town line).&lt;br /&gt;* The signed trailhead and small pullout are both located on the south side (right) of the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north:&lt;br /&gt;* Go south on Rt. 202/Rt. 123.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Rt. 202/Rt. 123 south past the turnoff for Rt. 136 north (on the left).&lt;br /&gt;* Continue on Rt. 202/Rt. 123 south for 1.0 mile past the turnoff for Rt. 136, and then take your first left onto Sand Hill Road.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Sand Hill Road for approximately 4.5 miles (Sand Hill Road becomes Old Mountain Road at the Greenfield town line).&lt;br /&gt;* The signed trailhead and small pullout are both located on the south side (right) of the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the west:&lt;br /&gt;* Go east on Rt. 101.&lt;br /&gt;* In Peterborough, turn left at the junction with Rt. 202/Rt. 123 north (this will be the traffic light following the intersection that leads to downtown Peterborough).&lt;br /&gt;* Go 1.1 miles then bear right onto Sand Hill Road.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Sand Hill Road for approximately 4.5 miles (Sand Hill Road becomes Old Mountain Road at the Greenfield town line).&lt;br /&gt;* The signed trailhead and small pullout are both located on the south side (right) of the road.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there by 9:15.  I have a bright orange backpack, a blue-green Corolla and a big smile.  774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284120254000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283817846000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (Back) Into It Hike to North Pack Monadnock!</name><id>14677483</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284039000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14677483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/e/6/global_17763814.jpeg</photo_url></item>