<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of State and Pleasant Streets</address_2><address_1>26 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Richdale Food Store</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1126642</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Newburyport's Holiday Invitation Nights&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An annual can't-miss event! Enjoy merchant hospitality, live entertainment and the spirit of the holidays of a spectacular night in Newburyport. Do some shopping and grab a bite to eat - make it a great night out with your friends or that special someone.  We will walk around Newburyport to see the sites and sounds of the upcoming holiday, while we get some of that holiday shopping done.  The stores are open from 6:00-9:00pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward we can head into one of the restaurants and grab a bite to eat or a drink.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't meetup at 6:30, but want to attend anyways, still RSVP we can meetup at a later time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Downtown Newburyport, Winter Street &amp;amp; The Tannery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please note we will only wait for 15 minutes after scheduled meetup time to head out to where we will be sitting, if you think that you will be running late, please email me before hand so we can make other arrangements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There are 3 municipal lots downtown – parking is FREE in these 3 lots. &lt;br /&gt;They are located at Green &amp;amp; Merrimac Streets, State and Harris Streets (next to the Library) and on Prince Place. &lt;br /&gt;There are 2 lots run by the Newburyport Redevelopment Authority They are located at either side of Waterfront Park along Merrimac Street Between The Black Cow and Not Your Average Joe’s (West Lot) and Water Street (East Lot) You may also park in legal spots on the street. If you park in a nearby neighborhood, please be respectful of residents and all parking laws - do not block fire hydrants or driveways. Police will ticket or tow all cars which are parked in illegal spaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note snow may cancel this event!  Please check back for updates.&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you! &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside of the store.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260747548000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258935090000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Newburyport Invitation night!</name><id>11934624</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260574200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11934624/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/d/global_11939309.jpeg</photo_url></item>