<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For three decades, Charles Burnett's Killer of Sheep (Milestone Films) has been one of those legendary films passed around like a secret jewel among moviegoers lucky enough to have seen it. Made in 1977 as a thesis project at the UCLA film school and never commercially released because of legal battles over music rights, Killer of Sheep was declared a national treasure by the Library of Congress in 1990 and has been named one of the 100 essential films of all time by the National Society of Film Critics. Yet it's been shown only at small festivals, on the college circuit, and on low-quality bootlegs. Shot over a year of weekends in the Los Angeles ghetto of Watts on 16mm black-and-white film, Burnett's masterwork has now been restored and transferred to 35mm and is enjoying a limited release in theaters before coming out on DVD in the fall. &lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.calendarlive.com/printedition/calendar/cl-et-killer6apr06,0,4941969.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.calendarli...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film is playing a number of times at the MFA , this looks like the mostly likely time I can attend.&lt;br /&gt;As usual Tom wil be holding a meetup-sign near the front row and then its off to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181783295000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178587655000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Killer of Sheep- An American Film about Ghetto Life</name><id>5753733</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181404800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5753733/</event_url></item>