<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trinity College</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.748314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio</name><city>Hartford</city><id>291370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Yeah, its a holiday tradition.&amp;nbsp; And it will be playing at another theater in Hartford, but their version is a DVD and this version is 35MM.&amp;nbsp; One of my top 10 movies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;(1946) Directed by Frank Capra. Screenplay: Frances Goodrich, based on Philip Van Doren Stern&amp;iacute;s novel. Cast: James Stewart, Donna Reed, Henry Travers, Lionel Barrymore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While Frank Capra&amp;rsquo;s take on community values versus individual greed once seemed nostalgic, hard times have brought it back into our national dialogue - from Wall Street to Oakland. This holiday season, treat yourself and the people you care about to Capra&amp;rsquo;s powerful expression of populism and the inter-connectedness of us all. James Stewart plays an ordinary small town guy who puts his own dreams on hold to help others, only to see his optimism eroded by the greed of the privileged 1%. It takes an angel named Clarence to reveal what Stewart&amp;rsquo;s world would be like without his sacrifice, caring and commitment. Writers Dorothy Parker, Clifford Odets and the blacklisted Dalton Trumbo all worked (uncredited) on the brilliant script. Ranked as the #1 Most Powerful Movie of All Time by the American Film Institute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324594249000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321638716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's A Wonderful Life</name><id>41639712</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324512900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/41639712/</event_url></item>