<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi just want to let everyone know that we are combining a party we are having a &amp;quot;Hippie Party&amp;quot; come dressed up as a &amp;quot;hippie&amp;quot;, bring some 60's food from that era! Please no drugs or smokes! We will be dancing and socializing, so come out and have some fun! Please bring a potluck dinner from that time era.If you know of any good music let me know or bring some music that you would like to play. If you have any questions my number is 603-509-2907. What?s is a hippie you ask? What?s the difference between an old hippie and a new hippie? Once a hippie, always a hippie? These and similar questions are the source of much debate today. New subcategories like web-hippies, cyber-hippies, even zippies have become fashionable. But what is a hippie and are you one? &lt;br /&gt;To answer this question, let?s see what defines a hippie. Some say it?s the way people dress, and behave, a lifestyle. Others classify drug users and rock 'n' roll fans or those with certain radical political views as hippies. The dictionary defines a hippie as one who doesn?t conform to society?s standards and advocates a liberal attitude and lifestyle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To be a hippie you must believe in peace as the way to resolve differences among peoples, ideologies and religions. The way to peace is through love and tolerance. Loving means accepting others as they are, giving them freedom to express themselves and not judging them based on appearances. This is the core of the hippie philosophy &lt;br /&gt;I'm including a web site to give you some idea as to see if your a hippie! Enjoy. See you at the party! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://elitemrp.net/h.." target="_blank"&gt;http://elitemrp.net/h...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a really cool looking groovy dude!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201565411000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>You'll meet other people from "Trailblazers"</why><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200061323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hippie Party</name><id>7088578</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201392000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/7088578/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/5/e/global_2951726.jpeg</photo_url></item>