<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.227803</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.540063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The chance of rain diminishes as the day goes on, so let's keep our fingers crossed for some decent weather Saturday afternoon.  It's supposed to be to be warm and breezy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet in time to be in your kayak, ready to paddle at 2:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll paddle for 2-3 hours.  If we're lucky enough to see some sun, the light should be nice late in the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking and launch is on Route 135 between Hopkinton and Westborough centers, approx 42.24166 North and -71.57316 West.  Do not program "Whitehall State Park" into your GPS. That will not take you to the launch site.  The nearest side road is Dale Road in Hopkinton, just west of the parking lot entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a fishing tournament that ends at 3:00, so parking may be limited.  Double up in the spaces that are left, or park on the grass in the middle of the lot (I do it all the time and have not had a problem).  I'm limiting the attendance to 8 because of parking, but if you are bringing a guest in the same car, just sign up for 1 person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must have a whistle and wear a properly fastened PFD.  Although not required by law, it is a good idea to have a pump and paddle float with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350776318000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350603702000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle at Whitehall</name><id>87605912</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350756000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/87605912/</event_url></item>