<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Our gift to you and the community: &lt;br /&gt;

 Please Join Us for our FREE Evening of Guided Meditations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connecting to your Inner Wisdom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Tues. evening, October 23rd, 7:15 -8:45 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;(second date and location to choose from of this &lt;em&gt;same&lt;/em&gt; event: Friday. evening, Oct. 12th, Earthsong Yoga, Marlborough MA - see calendar to RSVP)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Note: Through mid November, we're collecting &lt;strong&gt;non-perishable foods and clean, in good condition clothing&lt;/strong&gt; to donate to A Place to Turn, which provides emergency food and clothing to those in need in about 30 towns in Metro West MA.  This is totally voluntary.  No pressure.  If you feel inclined, please bring what you'd like to donate.  We're &lt;strong&gt;accepting financial donations, as well&lt;/strong&gt;; as there is great need on all counts.  Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you ever feel stuck in your way of thinking, like you just wish you could think about some things differently?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you heard about your “inner wisdom”, but you have trouble connecting to it, or maybe even feel like you don’t have it?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are you struggling with any issues that you’d like some wisdom on, or would you just like to learn some ways to connect to your inner wisdom?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The evening will consist of 2-3 guided meditations. All you'll have to do is follow Ann’s voice as she guides you through the meditations, each one usually about 15 - 20 minutes long, with discussions in between. Ann’s intentions for your evening are that you will easily:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deeply relax and experience inner peace and harmony&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn and experience 3 different ways to powerfully connect to your inner wisdom&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect to inner resources that you might not tend to normally in your busy mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And to create greater possibilities for you by connecting to your greatest Self and Spirit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;So treat yourself to this wonderful free event for you. Please invite others to sign up and join you. Share this with your friends, family and groups. The evening is appropriate for everyone, and all are welcome! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Amazing guided meditations! Wow. Ann was incredible! I've been meditating for a few years but have been in a rut. Ann totally got me out of that! Ahhhhhh... ” Robyn C.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;“It was another great night of meditations with Ann. It's just so relaxing and rejuvenating. You owe it to yourself to give it a try. ” Rick N.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Space is limited, so registration is required. Please remember to be considerate and change your RSVP if your plans change. Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I really did enjoy your guided meditations tonight. I arrived feeling so exhausted and found an opening and energy and awakening inside. It was very healing for me to have this experience, and there were many tools I will leave here with. Thank you!” L.C.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., Spiritual Life Coach with www.NewPossibilitiesCoaching.com, certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann coaches people to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, clients become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness they want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;This non-meetup, public event is co-sponsored by Roots and Wings Healing Arts Center and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service and is being shared with you because of it's relevance to Law of Attraction and being a deliberate creator.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be on the first floor in the Wings studio</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351112345000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348248165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free community evening of guided meditations: Connecting to your Inner Wisdom</name><id>83463222</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351034100000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/83463222/</event_url></item>