<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>70.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m ANGRY (and I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to manage it).&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you know why you feel angry? Does something completely trivial make you jump off the deep end? Do you bottle up anger until you explode? Are you afraid your internal rage will consume you? Are you clueless how to react when someone else is angry with you?&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Then this is for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anger is a toxic emotion when it&amp;rsquo;s held inside or expressed in negative ways. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been yelled at, hit or threatened by someone who was angry, then you know how harmful inappropriate expression of anger is. Anger has a way of sapping our strength, our energy and our very ability to think rationally. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever said or done something in a rage and later regretted it, then you know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Here is something to help.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, we will spend four hours taking a deep look at our attitudes toward anger, how it can disempower us, and how we can express our anger in healthy, non-violent, and self-empowering ways. Don&amp;rsquo;t let anger have toxic control over your life!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attend my 4 hour workshop and you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to process anger peacefully, effectively and how to let it go&amp;hellip; so you can get back to the business of life and loving those in it. As part of this you&amp;rsquo;ll also learn how to channel your anger into a powerful, positive force that works for you, so you can put that bottled up fury (energy) towards creating the life you want.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This workshop is limited to only 12 participants, so hurry and RSVP "yes" now. For just $70, you can be one of those 12 participates and come away with the tools you need to be happier and have a healthier relationship with your anger and those you love.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you'd like more information about me, this workshop or how I work with anger feel free to call or email me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone: 617-462-6642&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Email: gbigonet@rcn.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glenn Bigonet, MA&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Compassionate Acceptance&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Counseling individuals, couples and families&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;www.glennbigonet.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PS. Remember, anger is a natural and normal emotion. Come to this workshop and learn how to harness your anger, so you feel better faster and create a life you love.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glenn Bigonet</member_name><member_id>9409368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299334879000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>There are positive ways of being with our anger and we will discuss many of them.</why><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Create-the-life-you-ve-always-wanted</urlname><id>1441068</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2300033569</group_lon><name>Get More Out of Life!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297111470000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taking Control of Anger</name><id>16478631</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299283200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Create-the-life-you-ve-always-wanted/events/16478631/</event_url></item>