<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Discover the diverse cultures and cuisines Boston-area restaurants have to offer at Cultural Café, hosted by Hostelling International USA.  On the first Tuesday of every month, enjoy a meal with members of the community, learn about a new culture and help support Cultural Kitchen, HI-USA’s premiere educational program for inner city youth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cafe Brazil in Allston is our one-night-vacation destination for April, on Tuesday April 6th.  Cafe Brazil has been served classic &amp;quot;home-style&amp;quot; Brazilian food since 1986 (bad year for the Sox - good year for eating!).  The family-style meal will include many of the restaurant's specialties including rice and beans, friend plantains, special mixed grill, and vegetable dishes.  You will enjoy Brazilian music in the background as the staff explains the food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by March 31st for this affordable and fun event.  You can reserve your place online at &lt;a href="http://culturalcafeapril.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://culturalcafeap...&lt;/a&gt; or sign up directly with Karin by e-mail kturer@usahostels.org or calling her at 617-718-7990 ext 23.  PLEASE NOTE - YOU MUST PAY IN ADVANCE IN ORDER TO HAVE A PLACE IN THIS MEETUP - it's a little different, I know :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***more about Cultural Kitchen and Cultural Café***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an afterschool activity, Cultural Kitchen teaches Boston and Somerville youth about culture and diversity using cooking as the primary vehicle - just like travelers at our hostels learn about one another while cooking together in the hostel kitchen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cultural Café gives us a chance to experience something similar to what the students experience in our program.  The setting is informal as we gather to build community, share a delicious meal, learn a bit about Brazilian culture, and support a great cause.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the big table!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270768624000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Culturalcafe</urlname><id>1554280</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Cultural Café - Dine Out for a Cause</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262983258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cultural Cafe - April in Brazil!</name><id>12263800</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270594800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Culturalcafe/events/12263800/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/5/4/global_12538436.jpeg</photo_url></item>