<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A long weekend means a full house of singles at the Gallery in Glastonbury!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eat to get content, drink to get happy, and dance to get sore feet!  Don't need a partner...a bunch of us just got up and danced together last January.  Not queer...the dance floor was crowded...nobody noticed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday the 19th is a holiday so that means there will be a lot of people here to party with and meet.  The next long weekend to party like this won't happen now until October!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need a minimum of 6 'YES' RSVPs for a reserved table with cake and champagne.  This is the way to go!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As before, pay $12 at the door.  Includes buffet 6:30 - 8:30 pm, dancing upstairs and downstairs, door prizes, cake, and champagne.  Band is &amp;quot;Mass-Conn Fusion.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go right after you pay and you will see the Meetup signs on the reserved table(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you responded 'MAYBE', please commit by Feb 17th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Springfield, MA- Take I 91 S, follow sign to I 84E ( a left exit).  Look to extreme right for Exit 55...follow rest of directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford- Take I 84 E to Exit 55 (Rt 2 E), Continue on Rt 2 E to Exit 8. At end of exit, take RIGHT at lite onto Hebron Ave and LEFT at next lite onto New London Tpke.  The Gallery is the second building on the LEFT.  Park in the rear of the building.  Enter at the side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1172012468000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169181405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Big, BIG Party! - Singles Dance!</name><id>5407000</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171839600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5407000/</event_url></item>