<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>307 Applebee Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03852</zip><lat>43.493721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Branch River</name><city>Milton MIlls</city><id>1669621</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.970337</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/d/6/event_116408662.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;In case you'd like to attend a low-impact paddle event:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the 8th successive year, a 4.5 mile group paddle down the pristine Branch River in Milton Mills, NH to the Salmon Falls River and Milton 3 Ponds will occur. A picnic lunch will be provided at the paddle destination on Branch Hill Farm property.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paddlers must bring their own kayaks or canoes and wear personal flotation devices; transportation for participants and their boats will be provided back to the parking/boat launch site. Children 10 years or older may attend if accompanied by an adult. &lt;strong&gt;Spaces are limited and must be reserved by May 23rd. To pre-register, send an email to: info@mmrg.info with your name, phone #, and the number of people you are registering for.&lt;/strong&gt; A $10 per person donation to Moose Mountains Regional Greenways is suggested to help cover lunch and event costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day begins at 10 am with a brief introduction to how we can help protect the Salmon Falls Watershed by Kira Jacobs of the US E.P.A. At a few paddle stops, Professor Jennifer Jacobs of UNH will point out changes in stream flow and how these impact food, oxygen and animals and plants living in and near the river. These planned educational moments allow paddlers to observe their scenic environment with enhanced appreciation along the way. &lt;br /&gt;

This event is extremely popular; last year there were approximately 60 attendees! There is no rain date and no pets, please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Websites: www.mmrg.info/PR_12_MMRG_BranchRiverPaddle_2012.html&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://calendar.fosters.com/calendar/events/event/8th_annual_Branch_River_Paddle/46409/dt/159975.aspx" class="linkified"&gt;http://calendar.fosters.com/calendar/events/event/8th_annual_Branch_River_Paddle/46409/dt/159975.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moose Mountains Regional Greenways (MMRG) and &lt;br /&gt;

Branch Hill Farm/the Carl Siemon Family Charitable Trust (CSFCT) &lt;br /&gt;

MMRG has worked to create conservation land in the Moose Mountains Region for over 10 years, serving the towns of Brookfield, Farmington, Middleton, Milton, New Durham, Wakefield and Wolfeboro. Branch Hill Farm/CSFCT is a private operating foundation whose mission is to purchase and protect land, to produce quality timber products, and to educate people about sound forestry practices and conservation. For more information on CSFCT, visit www.branchhillfarm.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP by May 23rd: email info@mmrg.info with your name, phone #, and # of people you are registering for</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338051403000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336227659000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Group Paddle down the Branch River with 60 people &amp; picnic lunch, 9:30 am - 2 pm</name><id>63533432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338039000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/63533432/</event_url></item>