<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2075 Mountain Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06093</zip><lat>41.992875</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sunrize Park</name><city>West Suffield</city><id>803465</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.713288</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;This is listed on my *Forever Young* Meetup site,&lt;br /&gt;look there also for other comments. attendies and that kind of thing..&lt;br /&gt;its at&lt;br /&gt;For more details, see the full listing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://friends.meetup.com/545/calendar/9061190/"&gt;http://friends.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im only listing this here since most of you have put away the kayaks, but still want to do things and   may want to attend an event like this..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Title&lt;br /&gt;    Lake House Picnic and Fireplace Relaxing Atmosphere at Sunrise Park's Pavillion &lt;br /&gt;When&lt;br /&gt;    Sunday, November 16, 2008 12:00 PM 20081116T170000Z &lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Lenore has suggested a walk and this place for our group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    This is a perfect location for our kind of Pot Luck Meals and Social activity, whether its walking, exploring, or just plain relaxing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Bring some CD's too if you want...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    There is a nice lawn area in front of the Lake House, and a great deck on the back facing the lake.&lt;br /&gt;Its also an indoor facility.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    So it really dosen't matter what the weather is like for a good event..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    BRING some Firewood for the indoor fireplace, some extra water..etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I will bring a few Duraflame logs. and surprise something food...&lt;br /&gt;    How do you make Sunrize Cake ?..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    There are tables inside and seating, but we usually like our own special chairs, so choose what you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I see there is walking trails here and at the nearby mountain overlooking the Old Newgate Prizon,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    so there is options wither its nice out or not, I have a feeling most will just want to explore the grounds and not do a long hike to the mountain....but heck thats an option for those interested....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I will most likely get here earlier..so we can do some walk or something..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Yet lets just waite till we know the weather... i/we can suggest modifications,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    but this event goes on Rain or Shine..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    check back for updates or whatever..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    The park is located quite near Bradley Airport so its only about 30 minutes from Wethersfield for a comparison.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Park Address: 2075 Mountain Road , West Suffield, CT 06078&lt;br /&gt;    for us GPS users.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Getting there from the south or north&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Take I 91 to exit #40, this is root 20 and goes to Bradley Airport,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Follow this connector past Hamilten Standard and take the exit for the continuation of rte 20,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Go past the airport runway, pass 2 streets on right and take the right onto East Street,&lt;br /&gt;    should see a sign that says Marks Auto Parts, follow this road 4 miles to its end at rte 168 = Mountain Rd,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Take a left on to Mountain Rd/ rte 168, heading west,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Go apx 1 mile you will see a sign that says Kurd Farm or something, from there in about 0.25 miles as you turn and go up hill there is a Diamond caution sign that says Park Entrance Ahead, The actual Sunrise sign isn't easy to see from the road while going fast...so&lt;br /&gt;    prepare for the turn at the Diamond Shape Sign then take the left into the park,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Bear left into the Sunrise entrance road, follow it along keeping to the right till you come to the top of the little hill and see the Lake,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    We will be inside the Lake House and Pavillion building,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;    Oh, Be Descret With THE ADULT BUG JUICE., well we usually are as a precaution but its just a reminder..LOL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    We should also leave the place clean, and take the trash away as we do for all our other events,&lt;br /&gt;    that way we keep up our good standing in all our events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    See you all there..&lt;br /&gt;    al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    From Lenore:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Tom's wife just called me back. We are confirmed for the 16th for the pavilion at Sunrise Park. Tom's wife said the water would probably be turned off before the 16th, but we can bring bottled water. I don't see a problem. I am psyched.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Ok see you all there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    al-r&lt;br /&gt;Where&lt;br /&gt;    Sunrize Park&lt;br /&gt;    2075 Mountain Rd&lt;br /&gt;    West Suffield, CT, 06093&lt;br /&gt;How will members find you there?&lt;br /&gt;    Look for the ORANGE cones on and near the cars, go into the Lake House Pavillion&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Orange Cones in the Parking Lot..</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229807285000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225811712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Invitation to My other Group Event, Sunrize Park, Suffield CT</name><id>9091894</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226854800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/9091894/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/9/global_5044665.jpeg</photo_url></item>