<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(behind Mohr &amp; McPherson)</address_2><address_1>460 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.342475</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 292-2822</phone><name>Galeria Cubana</name><city>Boston</city><id>1211056</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065602</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets are $25 in advance.  Its best to purchase your tickets before the event because I don't think that they will be selling tickets at the door.  You can purchase tickets at the following web site: &lt;a href="http://bostonmoxieinthecity.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonmoxieint...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After you have bought your ticket, please post a message with your RSVP saying you have a ticket.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ART, WINE &amp;amp; INTRODUCTIONS EVENT - MARCH 12&lt;br /&gt;Take a private, intimate art gallery and add a flowing open wine bar and delicious cheeses and chocolate desserts. To complete the scene, mix in about 35-50 professionals ages 25-45. What you have is a private affair for Moxie members, complete with 40+ bottles of wine, a table full of food and an art gallery rented for our exclusive use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress is trendy/upscale. No, guys, suits are not required. But when you see how fashionable the ladies look, you`ll be glad if you dressed to impress. Ladies, you can wear anything from your little black dress to what you wore to work that day. Light music will play and new friends will be made. Show up with your room mate, your life mate, your co-workers..or show up alone. There will be a staff of 3 or more volunteers on hand to help introduce you to other members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADMISSION INCLUDES:&lt;br /&gt;Open Wine Bar from 7-10pm (40+ Bottles of wine purchased)&lt;br /&gt;Desserts, Cheeses &amp;amp; Chocolates served at 7pm until gone&lt;br /&gt;Private art gallery rental (no blaring music!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THINGS TO KNOW:&lt;br /&gt;*Average age range of attendees varies. The majority of guests are between the ages of 24-44.&lt;br /&gt;*Dress code is trendy business casual.&lt;br /&gt;*Expect to meet people from all fields - Medical, Legal, Creative, Fashion, Entrepreneurs, Event Planning, Finance&lt;br /&gt;*Ethnically diverse crowd of professionals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT TONIGHT`S EXHIBIT &lt;br /&gt;Galería Cubana offers an exceptional collection of contemporary Cuban art gathered from artists living on the island of Cuba. Cuba's distinct cultural history has produced extraordinary art varying broadly in styles, methods and materials. After decades of anonymity, Cuban art has finally been gaining greater exposure and international recognition for its accomplishments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Galería Cubana is pleased to showcase the creative, technical, and experimental achievements of Cuban artwork by featuring a range of artists at various points in their career. We carry work of the highly-trained, self-taught and even street artists. Our collection includes oils and acrylics on canvas and paper, prints, drawings, watercolors and mixed media works. This range of work has been selected to encapsulate the cultural depth, aesthetic diversity, and political edge unique to Cuban art. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lagaleriac.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lagaleriac...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269105396000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267671280000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art, Wine &amp; Introductions - Art Exhibit &amp; Wine Social</name><id>12777480</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268438400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/12777480/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/2/3/global_7135059.jpeg</photo_url></item>