<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When:  Oct 17th&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Moultonborough, NH &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Red Hill Fire Tower&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Moultonborough, NH&lt;br /&gt;State Owned&lt;br /&gt;Elevation: about 2029 feet&lt;br /&gt;1.7 miles (each way)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the fourth in a series of short hikes and trips to various fire towers in NH.  I'm hoping for some great foliage. &lt;b&gt;On this date, the foliage is predicted to be AT PEAK in the Lakes Region!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday, October 17th, I am going to climb the Red Hill Fire Tower.  The trail is 3.4 miles round trip, making it a very manageable climb. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to the Trailhead&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Bean Road from near the junction of Rte. 25 and Rte. 25B in Center Harbor. After 1.4 mi. turn onto Sibley Rd. (fire tower sign) and follow to a parking lot at a gated jeep road. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Hill Trail leaves the upper parking lot on a gated road, and soon leaves the road R uphill on a narrower road. It ascends a narrow gully, crosses a brook on a bridge, and joins a snowmobile trail which enters R. At .3 miles it reaches a woods road junction with signboard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The woods road L descends (with switchback) to where the trail turned off it near the gate, while the woods road R is a snowmobile trail to the SE ridge.  The trail follows a road ahead past a gate, which angles up to the L for awhile before gaining a ridge and wandering in woods which have both been damaged by an ice storm and burned over. The tower is not visible until you are nearly there. The last part of the trail circles to the L, then the Eagle Cliff Trail enters L. The combined trail zags R a short distance to the warden's cabin and the fire tower. There are some small blueberry patches at the summit, and grassy areas for a picnic. You can climb to a platform on the fire tower for views, and if the observer isn't busy, they may invite you into the cab and explain how to detect fires. This tower is operated by the town of Moultonborough rather than the state. The actual summit is a rock ledge with survey marker beyond the tower.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Planning Details:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet us at the trail head at 10:00 AM.&lt;/b&gt; I want to leave plenty of time for everyone to make the drive north.  Moltonboro is a little over 1 hour north of Concord on I-93.  I am happy to meet up with anyone who wants to carpool from Concord.  After the descent, we can decide if we want to stop for late lunch/early dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a dog friendly hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional.  If you do not provide a phone number for follow-up (to confirm details as we get closer to the hike) I will remove your RSVP. &lt;/span&gt; I will only use your contact information for this meetup.  I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the NH Fire Tower Series:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So there are  the 48 White Mountain 4,000 footers and the NE 4,000 footers and then there are the New England 100 Highest....oh and there are the &amp;quot;52 With A View&amp;quot; in NH too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But what if you aren't quite ready for all that time and elevation gain? Or what if you just need some small worthwhile hikes and inspiring views in-between those trips to the Whites?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why not climb our State's fire towers for a little exercise?  The State of NH has a program to &amp;quot;increase the public's recognition of, and appreciation for, the critical roles that our fire towers play in the protection, stewardship and sustainable use of New Hampshire's forests.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who doesn't appreciate that?  And with all hikes less than 2 miles (and many less than 1 mile!), who wouldn't be willing to get a little workout for a guaranteed view?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There are 15 Fire Towers currently in use on public land in New Hampshire.  Ascending just 5 of these towers, some of which are accessible from State Parks and auto roads, qualifies you for a Tower Quest Patch.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Information about the Fire Tower program can be found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.nhdfl.org/fire-control-and-law-enforcement/fire-towers.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhdfl.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a series of short trips and hikes to visit these locations.  I'm hoping to do most of them in the fall, when the foliage will make the payoff even better. I hope you'll join me!  And if not, I hope you'll pass on the word about this program to others who might be interested!&lt;br /&gt;------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE.  I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda with two dogs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287347962000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286296492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH Fire Tower Series:  Red Hill in Moultonboro, NH (Day Hike)</name><id>15009093</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287324000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15009093/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/f/global_18516879.jpeg</photo_url></item>