<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Theater District</address_2><address_1>115 Stuart Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351166</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 742-2739</phone><name>Rock Bottom Restaurant &amp; Brewery</name><city>Boston</city><id>826578</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065674</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Anybody up for dinner after Alice in Wonderland? I was looking to get a rough headcount by Friday at 4:00 pm, so I can call the restaurant up at (617) 742-2739 to fine-tune the reservation of around twenty I made Thursday morning. The Alice in Wonderland 3-D movie is at 7:00 pm, lasts for an hour and forty five minutes, which might get us over to Rock Bottom at 9:00 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I made the reservation under &amp;quot;T.J. Maher&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Nerd Fun&amp;quot;. Can't find the group before, during, or after the movie? Just head on over. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I had been going to make a reservation at the Jacob Wirth Restaurant, but it is all booked up. Jacob's has a group sing-along every Friday, and they advised me that should I ever want to bring a party of 20 there on a Friday night, I would have to book with them a month in advance, it's that busy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Rock Bottom Restaurant:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rockbottom.com/boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rockbottom...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A lively and casual dining experience, we feature fresh, handcrafted beers brewed on premise and an innovative menu. Our beers range in style from IPAs and Light Lagers to a Golds and Amber Ales. We also brew many specialty and seasonal beers, all of which are handcrafted by our Brewmaster, Gerry O'Connell using his original recipes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The atmosphere is rich in woods and gleaming brewing vessels. Our service is friendly and upbeat. Our moderately priced menu features a medley of items ranging from Fish and Chips to Roasted Chicken and Beef Tenderloin, a variety of interesting salads, and our world famous white Cheddar mashed potatoes&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dinner Menu&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.rockbottom.com/sites/default/files/3001faxmenu110.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rockbottom...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Good burgers, great beer! ... both of which I gave up for Lent. Good thing that have a good spinach and cheese dip, seared ahi, and edamame. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Beer Menu&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.rockbottom.com/boston/beers" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rockbottom...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Here at Rock Bottom, we know the best-tasting beer is the freshest beer. That’s why we use the freshest ingredients and handpick the finest hops in the Yakima Valley. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our brewers add a professional touch, creating their own representations of the world's renowned beer and making sure they complement our flavorful food. It’s unique, fresh, handcrafted beer, brewed on site just for you, and it makes us proud&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Light beers, amber ales, india pale ales, and dark beers, all brewed on site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=175+Tremont+Street,+Boston,+MA+02111+(AMC+Loews+Boston+Common+19)&amp;amp;daddr=115+Stuart+Street,+boston&amp;amp;geocode=FVZChgIdQ6XD-yEpmRJPQD_lMymRZIrTd3rjiTFnzqsOXukPrA%3BFT86hgIduJ_D-ylpvb73dnrjiTECKhIf4Pajwg&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=cc&amp;amp;dirflg=w&amp;amp;sll=42.35219,-71.065&amp;amp;sspn=0.002922,0.004812&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=18" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit the front of the movie theater, take a left, heading into the Theater District down Tremont, and take a right onto Stuart. Rock Bottom is a couple of stores down on the right. A curved &amp;quot;Rock Bottom&amp;quot; sign is placed over the revolving doors of the entrance. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268079070000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267722762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner with Nerd Fun at Rock Bottom (not Jacob Wirth's), after Alice </name><id>12782656</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267840800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12782656/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>