<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://local.yahoo.com/info-10215422-victoria-seafood-restaurant-boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://local.yahoo.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A co-worker of mine, Mr. Sing Lee, anxiously awaits our group’s visit to the restaurant he has been working at on weekends for several years.  Sing is a fellow North Quincy resident who I have known for several years - he looks forward to meeting some folks from our group and is happy to know of our enthusiasm.&lt;br /&gt;****************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For people who like Chinese food, want to learn more Chinese culture, and meet friends. gives everyone an opportunity to come and make new friends, practice their Chinese or English, and enjoy dinner with us. Bring your friends, and come by, relax, practice in either language of your choice, and enjoy being part of our growing community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;IF WE WISH TO FOLLOW THIS WITH ANOTHER &amp;quot;KARAOKE NIGHT&amp;quot;, &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to member J. Spring Liu, we have actually two options for Karaoke, if we wish:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  She reminds us that a few blocks from the restaurant, there is &amp;quot;Do Re Mi Karoake&amp;quot;   - &lt;a href="http://www.doremikaraoke.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.doremikara...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.  If the group remains partial to Golden Leaf in Chinatown, this requires some extra travel time - the green line gets one back into Boston, Boylston Station in about 10 minutes - from there, it is perhaps a 10 minute walk to the Green Leaf on Hudson Street (Chinatown).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GETTING THERE BY MBTA:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from downtown Boston and using &amp;quot;T&amp;quot; (MBTA):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Line/Lu Xian, &amp;quot;B&amp;quot; Line -  Thanks to J. Spring Liu, we have some good directions!  She reminds us that Babcock St. station should be the closest.  The restaurant is a few blocks before Super 88 and on the same side where Boston meets Brighton.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask front dest where the Meetup group is...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248180059000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245689404000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FRIDAY NIGHT DINNER TABLE</name><id>10707960</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247869800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/10707960/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/2/global_9295154.jpeg</photo_url></item>