<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>UPDATE:  &gt;&gt;&gt; I just got the call from the concert organizers and TONIGHT's CONCERT is "officially" "ON"!!!

&gt;&gt;&gt; LOOK FOR: a large "Cheers" COCKTAIL-SHAPED BALLOON (see MeetUp photo).  Also, Al R. will be there with his four orange traffic cones.  

&gt;&gt;&gt; "Thanks" to Al, who's been doing "recon" of the area and has chosen a private, local location for our "POST-concert" outdoor PARTY, featuring two propane-fueled ceramic fire-pits and fun conversation with old and new friends!!!  Bring "extra" food, beverage, and a poncho!!!

&gt;&gt;&gt; NOT including all The Single Event, Parents Without Partners, etc. attendees, we have over 70 "YES" or "maybe" RSVP's per my "FREE Live Outdoor Music" MeetUp - go there (free) to check out who's coming, to RSVP, and/or to learn of upcoming events:  &lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/5907422/" class="linkified"&gt;http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/5907422/&lt;/a&gt;

- Rob Pudney

NOTE: ALL the info is contained within this email and also on my MeetUp site.  As I'm VERY busy at work, I will not be able to respond to ANY individual phone calls or emails.  Thanks for understanding.

***

Who:
Rob P.'s "FREE Live Outdoor Music" MeetUp and The Single Event's "Thirsty Thursday", as well as a couple of other groups combining into one huge free outdoor concert / dance party!

What:
JIMMY BUFFET tribute band: "Changes in Latitude".

When: 
Thursday, August 16 
Show: 7:00 - 9:00 ... &gt;&gt;&gt; Gather @ 6:00-6:30 so we can spread out a large enough area to party together! &lt;&lt;&lt;

Where: 
Promenade Shops at EVERGREEN WALK (NOT at Nevers Park!)
501 Evergreen Walk
South Windsor, CT 06074
860-648-6349 
recreation.southwindsor.org

LOCATE US:  To not interfere with the performers nor be blown out by loudspeakers, let's throw down our blankets/tarps and beach chairs BETWEEN STARBUCKS and BROOKS BROTHERS (centrally located, near the Fountain on the "Village Green").  

&gt;&gt;&gt; LOOK FOR: a large "Cheers" COCKTAIL-SHAPED BALLOON (see MeetUp photo).  Also, Al R. will be there with his four orange traffic cones.  

Please... NO OPEN ALCOHOL, use commuter mugs, etc. and we won't get harassed (I'm told).

Why:
We had 40 for the Billy Joel Tribute show and 60 at the Bushnell Park's Blues Fest from both "The Single Event" and "MeetUp" groups combined!   Weather permitting; we are going to push for our largest turnout yet for this dance/party music!!!  

Please feel free to forward this "open invitation" to your friends (particularly fun singles mostly in their 30's to 50's, but open to everyone!) to join us and encourage them to join "The Single Event" AND "FREE Live Outdoor Music" MeetUp social networking groups!

- Rob Pudney

***
&gt;&gt;&gt; NOTE: this South Windsor event is being held at the Promenade Shops at EVERGREEN WALK, NOT at Nevers Park! &lt;&lt;&lt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>24</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187476909000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182224536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TONIGHT's CONCERT is "officially" ON!!!  6:30 - ???</name><id>5907422</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187303400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5907422/</event_url></item>