<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Upper College Pond Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.858501</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Myles Standish Parking Lot #2</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>1248332</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.662430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome the NEW YEAR with &amp;quot;Bentley,' revisiting an old friend or making a new one.   We'll hike the Bentley Loop and maybe a side trail or two depending on the weather and conditions.  For those new to the forest, the Bentley is always a good hike and well marked for going on your own between group hikes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use the opportunity to see if those new boots are really waterproof, the high tech clothes are really wicking, or the trekking poles worth lugging along.  Footing should be moist while temperatures are moderate. Dress accordingly and hope the wettest weather is in the morning.  Two weeks ago I hiked the trail in dry conditions, last Sunday some side trails in the snow decorated with lots of deer, ski, and snowmobile tracks, and who knows what the 2nd will bring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So don't get too tired if you're going on one of the great DCR hikes on Saturday, but if you indulge a little too much to make a Saturday hike you should be back in form for Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buffett invites other dogs along but don't expect them to stay clean.  Even though there's no hunting, I can spot him in the greyness more easily when he wears hunter orange, if he just doesn't squirm out of it again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, donations are appreciated to cover website and other costs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Troll</member_name><member_id>11017991</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294006310000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293837585000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January First Sunday Hike</name><id>15871856</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293991200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/15871856/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/6/global_20498886.jpeg</photo_url></item>