<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bearsden Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01331</zip><lat>42.604958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bearsden Conservation Area</name><city>Athol</city><id>8983722</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.191895</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Come join us on a new adventurous hike led by NQTA President Bobby Curley and Trail leader Dan Bolton.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This will be a 6 mile moderate hike along the new Q+ M Trail from S.Royalston&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;along the Miller's River to the newly discovered Thousand Acre Waterfalls to Bearsden shelter with a stop to take a lunch break, at the just completed overnight shelter. Then following the freshly cut historic Red Bridge Trail in Bearsden Conservation Area back to the main parking lot in Bearsden (accessed via Bearsden Rd.) where we are meeting at 9 o'clock Saturday morning. We will then be spotting cars in South Royalston. Bobby Curley will bring the new Bearsden maps and Q+ M with him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Depending on the amount of people who RSVP for this hike, we may park cars at the Athol Hospital parking lot just at the base of Bearsden Road since the conservation parking area is very limited. If we do need to do that, I will post the directions to the hospital parking lot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;On the day of the hike, Bob and Dan can give us more information on this trail they've been blazing from the Quabbin to Mount Monadnock. It's been a huge project along with a few others they have been working on.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Very cool stuff and we can get involved too if anyone has an interest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From downtown Athol, go east on Main St. (Rte. 2A) approx. 1.5 mi. Take left onto Bearsden Rd. Go 1 mi., bear right to stay on Bearsden Rd and continue 0.5 mi. to entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;Bearsden Road has a big conservation area sign at the base of it from Main Street(rt 2A) in Athol. It may say Athol Conservation Area as it is referred to by both names. Bearsden Road is located across the street from Larry's Variety Meat and Produce market which is next to the Athol Hospital. There are signs to the hospital from rt 2 at the Athol exits to get you to that vicinity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;The conservation area is way out at the very end of Bearsden Road where it becomes a dirt road. Please take it slowly at this point as the road is rough but very doable. You'll pass by a red building at the top of the hill while still on the paved road then follow Bearsden Road until you see what looks like an intersection, bear right to stay on Bearsden Road then follow straight until the end. You'll pass Page Cabin and a small wetlands area. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://goo.gl/maps/uBiLA"&gt;http://goo.gl/maps/uBiLA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a maroon Chevy Monte Carlo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Bolton</member_name><member_id>11623335</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347138232000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346709171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Quabbin &amp; Monadnock(Q&amp;M) Trail Hike</name><id>80677012</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347109200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/80677012/</event_url></item>