<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The weather-beaten bluffs of Halibut Point comprise a low rocky coastal shelf covered in bayberry, greenbriar, and shadbush. During storms, waves crash over the rocky shore. Tidal pools harbor snails, hermit crabs, and sea stars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Above the reservation is the former Babson Farm Quarry, now filled by natural underground springs. Granite quarried here at the turn of the 20th century paved thousands of city streets and built bridges, tunnels, monuments, warehouses, and buildings, such as Boston's Custom House Tower.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halibut Point is cooperatively managed by The Trustees of Reservations and the Massachusetts Department of Environmental Management (DEM), which acquired an adjoining 54-acre state park in 1981 with the assistance of The Trustees. DEM operates a small visitor center and museum dedicated to telling the story of Cape Ann's historic granite industry. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Trails &lt;br /&gt;2.5 miles of trails. Moderate walking. The reservation is a link in Rockport's Atlantic Path. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Facilities &lt;br /&gt;The state park operates a small visitor center and museum devoted to Halibut Point's natural history and Cape Ann's historic granite quarrying industry, of which Halibut Point's Babson Farm Quarry was a major part. The visitor center has public restrooms.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to Get There:&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128 (Exit 9), take Route 127 north (Eastern Avenue) toward Rockport 3 mi. At 5-way intersection, turn left onto Railroad Avenue (remains Route 127) and follow for 2.4 mi. Turn right onto Gott Avenue. Entrance is opposite the state park's parking lot. To avoid traffic in Rockport Center (during summer), pick up Route 127 north at Gloucester Rotary (Exit 11) and follow through village of Lanesville. After crossing into Rockport, pass Folly Cove and look for &amp;quot;State Park&amp;quot; sign leading to Gott Avenue on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we'll have lunch at the &lt;a href="http://www.greenery-restaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Greenery Restaurant&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;15 Dock Square&lt;br /&gt;Rockport, MA 01966&lt;br /&gt;978-546-9593 &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1176129657000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174869768000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halibut State Park</name><id>5604742</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175956200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5604742/</event_url></item>