<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Walnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02460</zip><lat>42.346506</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>United Methodist Church</name><city>Newtonville</city><id>1280079</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.206274</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>$20@door+OPTfood/or$10</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thetruthaboutyourfood.com/images/tayf/drT-1.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.thetruthaboutyourfood.com/images/tayf/drT-1.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Adiel Tel-Oren (Dr. T), MD, DC, LN, CCN, DABFM, DACBN, FABDA Nutritional, Environmental &amp;amp; Functional Medicine; Public &amp;amp; Professional Lectures Worldwide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic: Aging Skin, Moles, Growths, Tags, Spots, &amp;amp; Blemishes: How &amp;amp; Why Do They Develop?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your diet, exposure, and general health create various skin growths, blemishes, and more serious lesions. Prevent risks and treat them safely, painlessly, and aesthetically - using nutritional methods and lifestyle, while improving your overall health and protecting your youthful skin!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;05:30PM: Registration (Optional)&lt;br /&gt;06:00PM: Potluck (Optional) bring raw vegan dish OR pay $10 for food (call 24 hours ahead to order)&lt;br /&gt;07:00PM: Speaker &amp;amp; FREE Individual Evaluation $15 online ($20 at door)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to &lt;a href="http://www.OptimumHealthSolution.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.OptimumHealthSolution.org&lt;/a&gt; to buy $15 ticket to lecture and free evaluation. All proceeds donated to Optimum Health Solution’s project of “Feeding Our Children A Healthy Future”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional Potluck 6 – 7 PM; Reg 5:30 PM - Bring raw vegan unprocessed dish for 8 or go to &lt;a href="http://www.OptimumHealthSolution.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.OptimumHealthSolution.org&lt;/a&gt; to buy a $10 ticket to potluck if you wish to have food prepared for you. Order must be placed 24 hours in advance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Tel-Oren, is a holistic scientist who educates doctors and the public about nutritional and environmental medicine, functional medicine (science-based holistic approaches to diagnosis and therapy), and disease prevention via truly natural lifestyle and dietary modification.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. T promotes &amp;quot;EcoRaw Living&amp;quot; as a model for optimal cellular health and the principles of sustainability.  He is the owner and manager of a raw, organic restaurant, Ecopolitan, in Minneapolis. Dr. T  offers nutritional medical care  in Africa, East and South Asia, Europe, the Americas, and the Tropics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He is the Founder and Co-Founder of several non-profit Health and Sustainability Programs Worldwide. This includes the Center for Community Development in Nepal (with its Community Health Program that cares for 200,000 Nepali villagers); The Israeli Center for Functional Medicine; The Eco-Sphere Green Community Project in Wisconsin; and the Ecopolitan Eco-Health Network with its numerous communities in the USA - supporting healthy lifestyle, Intensive Healing Retreats, Tropical Escapes, Foraging trips, Eco-Raw Restaurants, Clinics, University Degrees and Certification Programs, and Humanitarian Eco-Trekking adventures. Dr. T is also founder of the world's first hypoallergenic GF/DF vegan bakery (www.greenbakery.net).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;European &amp;amp; US-Trained MD&lt;br /&gt;• European Medical License 1996&lt;br /&gt;• USA Nutrition License 1997&lt;br /&gt;• MN Board of Nutrition &amp;amp; Dietetics&lt;br /&gt;• USA Doctor of Chiropractic, practiced 1990 through 2001&lt;br /&gt;• Professor &amp;amp; Board Certified Clinical Nutritionist with the IAACN &amp;amp; CNCB&lt;br /&gt;• Board Certified, American Board of Functional Medicine, American Clinical Board of Nutrition, American Board of Oxidative Medicine, American Board of Chelation Therapy; Fellow, American Board of Disability Analysts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President &amp;amp; Founder:&lt;br /&gt;• Ecopolitan Eco-Health Network, Ecopolitan Restaurant and Non-Profit Community (www.ecopolitan.com);&lt;br /&gt;• The Eco-Sphere Green Building Project&lt;br /&gt;• The Green Bakery (Beyond Gluten Free™ ) - The First Hypoallergenic Bread (www.greenbakery.net)&lt;br /&gt;• Co-Founder: CCODER Nepal's Health Plan (CCODER.org), caring for 200,000 villagers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President Emeritus &amp;amp; Professor of Nutrition and Functional Medicine:&lt;br /&gt;• University of Natural Medicine, Santa Fe, NM&lt;br /&gt;• Functional &amp;amp; Dental Health (FDH) Foundation, Founder&lt;br /&gt;• Bio-Mental Health Foundation, Founder&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ecopolitan.com/doctor-t" target="_blank"&gt;www.ecopolitan.com/doctor-t&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this lecture followed by FREE Individual Evaluations &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, January 14 at 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At United Methodist Church, 430 Walnut St., Newton &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.OptimumHealthSolution.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Betsy Bragg  617-835-2913&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Betsy@OptimumHealthSolution.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Bragg</member_name><member_id>5026531</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295216081000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294827302000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OHS Potluck / Speaker: Dr. Tel-Oren</name><id>16019915</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295044200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/16019915/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/1/global_12638257.jpeg</photo_url></item>