<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/hancock_112787/movietimes?date=7/3/2008" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.fandango.com/hancock_112787/movietimes?date=7/3/2008&lt;/a&gt;
^for advanced tix, click the link.^ i have mine already. it says auditorium#2 downstairs. That means this movie is showing on the same floor you get your tickets, don't go upstairs!

Runtime: ~2hrs | Rated PG-13 Some intense sequences of sci-fi action and violence, and language

Description: There are heroes? there are superheroes? and then there's Hancock (Will Smith). With great power comes great responsibility ? everyone knows that ? everyone, that is, but Hancock. Edgy, conflicted, sarcastic, and misunderstood, Hancock's well-intentioned heroics might get the job done and save countless lives, but always seem to leave jaw-dropping damage in their wake. The public has finally had enough ? as grateful as they are to have their local hero, the good citizens of Los Angeles are wondering what they ever did to deserve this guy. Hancock isn't the kind of man who cares what other people think ? until the day that he saves the life of PR executive Ray Embrey (Jason Bateman), and the sardonic superhero begins to realize that he may have a vulnerable side after all. Facing that will be Hancock's greatest challenge yet ? and a task that may prove impossible as Ray's wife, Mary (Charlize Theron), insists that he's a lost cause.

Director: Peter Berg (The Kingdom, Friday Night Lights, The Rundown, etc.)

Screenwriter: Vincent Ngo, Vince Gilligan

Starring: Will Smith, Charlize Theron, Jason Bateman, Eddie Marsan

Genre: Action Comedy, Comic-Book Superhero Film, Comedy

Reviews: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;id=9847" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;id=9847&lt;/a&gt;

Trailer: 
&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/pndUOvkiy2A&amp;hl=en" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

Notes: Please do not RSVP YES if you do not intend to come. Yes is not a MAYBE. If you can't figure out what you are going to do in the future, please do not burden us with that. Please buy your tix [b]AHEAD[/b] of time! This WILL BE SOLD OUT! I'm going to watch this regardless of people coming, but it will more fun with people.

How to find me: I"ll be wearing my trademark green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in front as usual. The movie is in auditorium#2, which is downstairs, I'll be in front of the popcorn stand behind the rope. This is on the same floor you bought your tickets.

The film begins @7PM. I'll be there @6:30PM and will wait for you until 6:45PM when we will all go inside.</description><how_to_find_us>I"ll be wearing my trademark green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in fr</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218889260000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Because we are the coolest cats on the planet.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213759794000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hancock</name><id>8163863</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215124200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8163863/</event_url></item>