<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research and Development Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1534447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As you are all obviously aware, we did not have a meetup in March as it was a hectic month and I was not able to get one together. However, I bring you some exciting news. A generous member reached out and put me in touch with a contact at the Microsoft New England Research &amp;amp; Development Center in Cambridge to host our next meetup (and hopefully future meetups to come).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I apologize in advance for the last minute notice, but I just received confirmation that we have a spot next Wednesday, April 15th at 7 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first two meetups were quite small, and took place at local restaurants and pubs. As you can see, our third meetup will be a significant upgrade. I don't have anything formal planned as it came together so quickly, but depending on the turnout we can hopefully begin to develop these monthly meetups into something more organized and informative.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am told there is plenty of space and parking, as well as Internet hookups, which are all undeniably awesome perks. Maybe the mystery man will give us more details via the group mailing list :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to meeting more WordPressers and thank you to all that have joined recently!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup will be held in the main hall of the new conf. center on the 1st floor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>James Coletti</member_name><member_id>7809368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259596523000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239114581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston WordPress @ Microsoft</name><id>10135020</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239836400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/10135020/</event_url></item>