<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>cross street Center between Chapel and Crown</address_2><address_1>76 Orange Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> (203) 562-2511</phone><name>Bentara</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1077533</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.924828</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As the age of convergence and convergent thinking is upon us; it's becoming more and more important for web professionals to understand video and multimedia production so they can have it become part of their site designs when appropriate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building an effective, results oriented video or multimedia project is like building a house. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It all starts with a well thought-out creative blueprint. Determining your client's present and future needs, discussing available visual construction materials and technology, and controlling costs are the key to a  successful multimedia project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seasoned writer/producer/director and non-linear editor Michael O'Keefe from AVITY in New Haven will share some of his experiences and knowledge about video and multimedia production and discuss how he has been incorporating video into his client's web work. He'll also talk about some of the new generation of digital cameras and discuss non-linear editing interfaces like Final Cut Pro. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this practical look at video production basics and what's new on the digital video scene and how video can enhance your site designs and work in the future.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Fischer</member_name><member_id>3013881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200102565000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197502598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater New Haven Design and Marketing January Meetup</name><id>6902787</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199918700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/6902787/</event_url></item>