<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi NLPers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First of all, a special reminder: the NLP meetup this month is free!  If you have been on the fence about checking out the meetup, here is your chance, and if you have someone you would like to introduce to NLP, here is a no-risk way to do it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, we will be starting the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP, those who want a review, and those who want to come early to socialize/network. At 7pm we will get rolling with the main event for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main event(s): Rapport and Metaphor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rapport&lt;/u&gt; is defined as &lt;i&gt;relation marked by harmony, conformity, accord, or affinity&lt;/i&gt;.  It turns out that if you do not have rapport with someone, it is almost impossible to do any counseling, coaching, or change work with them.  Thus, establishing and maintaining rapport is fundamental to the practice of NLP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will do several demonstrations of rapport (and non-rapport), and then will practice it ourselves. We will also introduce the NLP concepts of &lt;i&gt;pacing&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;leading&lt;/i&gt; with rapport.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Metaphor&lt;/u&gt; is a powerful concept, central to NLP.  Metaphors can be used as elaborate language patterns, as tools for understanding others maps of reality, and as powerful teaching tools. Metaphors are also an exceptionally powerful vehicle for solving problems in creative ways. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this months meetup, we will be exploring metaphorical problem solving. We will focus on visual metaphors, and we'll learn (and practice) the technique of &lt;i&gt;drawing solutions&lt;/i&gt;. I will provide the paper and markers - you provide the challenges.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also stay for a while after the meetup, if anyone wants to work on specific issues they are having that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adam Marx&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk straight ahead into the meeting room.  I'll probably be the one talking.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216258104000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210894392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP June Meetup - Rapport and Metaphor - Free!</name><id>7947407</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213914600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/7947407/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/9/2/global_4360498.jpeg</photo_url></item>