<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Will be provided to those who RSVP</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02132</zip><lat>42.279755</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stacy and Ingo's House</name><city>West Roxbury</city><id>1058865</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.162676</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wondering what new and different dishes you're going to be serving along side your bird for Thanksgiving dinner?  How about borrowing innovative ideas from friends?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be having a Thanksgiving Recipe Swap.  Here's how it works...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who attends will bring their favorite dish and printouts of the recipe.  Then we all share in tasting the food and everyone leaves with pages full of new recipes.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best recipes to bring....&lt;br /&gt;- Something unique that your family created&lt;br /&gt;- An recipe that your personal heritage/culture likes to enjoy on holidays&lt;br /&gt;- Your absolute favorite dish that you couldn't live without&lt;br /&gt;- A vegetarian specialty that wakes up a meatless plate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 5 pm - 7:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Place: Our home in West Roxbury (bordering Brookline and Jamaica Plain). &lt;br /&gt;***Note: I will provide the exact address and my phone number to those who RSVP.*** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's easy to get here from all over Boston - we're inside the 128 corridor. Also great for those in Boston not wanting to drive - we're just 1 block from the Commuter Rail Bellevue Station (13 minutes from Back Bay, 17 minutes from South Station)! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to take the Commuter Rail? Take the Needham Line to Bellevue Station. A train arrives here at 6:21pm which will get you here just in time. There are trains back to the city at 7:43 and 9:20. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Stacy and Ingo&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stacy Goodman</member_name><member_id>3216337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259101021000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255542479000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pre-Thanksgiving Recipe Swap </name><id>11626346</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258927200000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/11626346/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_9634902.jpeg</photo_url></item>