<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Please take a moment to answer the RSVP questions when responding. It's for safety reasons this information be provided. Failure to furnish the requested information may result in removal from the activity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Random's New York chapter is back in action!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will hike two of the Catskills 3500 footers, Cornell (3870 ft) and Wittenberg (3790 ft), via the Wittenberg-Cornell-Slide trail, starting from the Woodland Valley Campground. The roundtrip distance is 9.4 miles and approximate elevation gain is 3000 feet. Wittenberg's summit provides a view of the Devil's paths peaks and the Blackhead range. Book time for this hike is about 6 hours, not including stops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet at the trailhead for the Wittenberg-Cornell trail. Woodland Valley has a day use parking area (fee required) for those just joining us for the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be doing another Catskills hike on Saturday, and staying at the Woodland valley campground on Saturday night. If you would like to join us for the weekend, you can make campground reservations here: &lt;a href="http://www.dec.ny.gov/outdoor/24501.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.dec.ny.gov/outdoor/24501.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for a list of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;required items needed for a day hike&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Appalachian Mountain Club&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Directions to Woodland Valley Campground:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; From Thruway Exit 19, Kingston - first right from traffic circle after leaving the exit, on to Route 28 West. Proceed 20-25 miles to the village of Phoenicia, which will be on your right. Proceed on Rte. 28 across the bridge over the Esopus Creek In Phoenicia. Turn left at the small yellow "Woodland Valley Campground" sign onto Woodland Valley Road. Follow Woodland Valley Road back over the Esopus Creek. Turn right at the "T" after the bridge. Stay left at the first sharp bend and follow Woodland Valley Road approximately six miles to the campground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice:&lt;/strong&gt; We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you (in the cold winter months this can be particularly dangerous for the entire group if we have to wait around, getting cold). Please read the entire TRIP SUMMARY before you RSVP. It is important, not only for your safety, but that of the entire group.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not a trained guide, so you should be comfortable hiking and in the wilderness in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; You agree not to hold the Organizer, Event Organizers, Assistant Organizers, or any other members responsible for any injuries, mishaps, or any other situation that may happen at a planned event. You are responsible to research the event, know the area, and bring the proper gear and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.hikesafe.com"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emily Singer</member_name><member_id>7452900</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369098467000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364862861000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Catskills Hike - Cornell and Wittenberg</name><id>112178352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368968400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/112178352/</event_url></item>