<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>ICC members are meeting to start a success virus. Our June 23 meeting on Tips has been retooled as a discussion led by Kay Green, of Green Graphic Design, Chris Amorosino, of Amorosino Writing, and Laura Kolk, of Kolk Design. Come for a night of inspiration and motivation. This is a night to lift your spirits and your energy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Bring stories about a great photo shoot or a promotion campaign&lt;br /&gt;- Share a design you are really proud of or a client you helped &lt;br /&gt;- Share how you redid your invoicing system to save time or found a great web site for free stuff&lt;br /&gt;- Give us insight on how you remain positive&lt;br /&gt;- Let us know how you get yourself unstuck when your mind is a blank&lt;br /&gt;- What books or magazines are inspiring you?&lt;br /&gt;- How did you win that precious new client?&lt;br /&gt;- Tell us the highlight of work year to date&lt;br /&gt;- Gush about your favorite low cal desert&lt;br /&gt;- Sing praises for your favorite web site&lt;br /&gt;- Share how you reduce stress&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t have anything to share? Come, have a glass of wine and get inspired.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;TO RESERVE YOUR PLACE:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;- Go to: www.paypal.com and select the &amp;quot;Send Money&amp;quot; tab &lt;br /&gt;- Insert &amp;quot;kolkdesign@usa.net&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;Recipient's Email&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;- Type in the amount you wish to send. ($24 per person) &lt;br /&gt;- Select &amp;quot;Service&amp;quot; for &amp;quot;Type&amp;quot; (of money sent). &lt;br /&gt;- Put ICC meeting-June 23 in the &amp;quot;Subject&amp;quot; box. &lt;br /&gt;- Note: Use the PayPal message box to type in your meal preference. This time our meal choices are: Basa Sole; Chicken Marsala with Mushrooms; or Penne Roberto (vegetarian).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;OUR RESERVATION DEADLINE is Thursday, June 18th.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;To cancel your reservation, you must do so by 5pm June 18th or your payment will be forfeited.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For questions, please contact Kay Green: &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;kay.green@sbcglobal.net&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>ask for the ICC party</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Kolk</member_name><member_id>6023842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258673356000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Network Marketers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>networkmarket-792</urlname><id>818489</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4400024414</group_lon><name>Independent Creative Club of Greater Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244479993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Format: Tips &amp; Such ICC June Meeting</name><id>10604091</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245794400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/networkmarket-792/events/10604091/</event_url></item>