<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Weekend&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a disarmingly delicate and daring drama set in Nottingham, England and featuring breakout performances by Tom Cullen and Chris New. After hanging out with his straight mates on a Friday night, Russell (Cullen) heads out to a gay club. Just before closing time he picks up an artist named Glen (New) and unexpectedly spends most of the next 48 hours with him in bedrooms and bars, telling stories and having sex. As they spend more time together, sharing snippets of their lives, they begin to reveal the things that hold them back as much as push them forward and develop a connection that will resonate throughout their lives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Weekend&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;is an affecting and naturalistic romance, a beautiful exploration of how two people can come together only briefly, yet impact each other in a profound way. &lt;strong&gt;Winner of the Grand Jury Award for Outstanding International Dramatic Feature at the 2011 Outfest Film Festival and the Emerging Visions Audience Award for Best Film at the 2011 SXSW Film Festival.&lt;/strong&gt; Written and directed by Andrew Haigh&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;(Greek Pete)&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;From AVClub's 'A' Rating:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Weekend&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;is, simply, a great indie romance. Its small scale allows for detailed looks at two men who are likeable and flawed, and who connect on a level neither expected&amp;mdash;nor in one case, was even looking for....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
User Review &lt;span style="font-size : 14px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is the best low budget indie gay movie in years, and the best gay movie since BROKEBACK MOUNTAIN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/user/ur19146085/comments"&gt;aupairkansas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Saint Paul, MN) &amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/user/ur19146085/comments"&gt;See all my reviews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;I just watched WEEKEND at a screening at the Oslo LGBT film festival, and am still in shock. This is the most real cinematic version of guys falling in love in recent history. I'm a filmmaker myself, and was blown away by the caliber of the writing, directing, acting, cinematography, editing, and music of this fantastic film. There's not a false note in the movie--everything rings true, even the ending (no spoilers here.) It's the rare film, like WINTER'S BONE last year, that at every turning point takes what I call the elegant decision. WEEKEND is at a higher level than all other LGBT films playing the festival circuit this year (the only other film near this level is Tom Twyker's 3.) Actually, it's at a higher level than almost all films playing anywhere this year. Where did this film come from? Apparently the brilliant mind of Andrew Haigh (writer/director/editor), who, I noted on an IMDb search, started as an apprentice editor on GLADIATOR, and then assistant editor on BLACK HAWK DOWN (working with the master editor Pietro Scalia on both. Go UCLA!) I look forward to seeing more of Haigh's work. Do not, I repeat, DO NOT miss this movie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rotten Tomatoes Critcs Review: 93%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rotten Tomatoes Audience Review: &amp;nbsp;88%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We have two separate tables reserved at Tommy Doyle's so that we can have discussion with a small group and actually be able to hear one another.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hope to see you at the movie, and hope you can join us for discussion afterward,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will send an email during the weekend of the film with meetup plans, stand in the lobby near the ticket takers after the credits holding a sign, and ask anyone that seems to be looking for MEETUP if they are looking for us :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319754144000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317424673000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WEEKEND</name><id>35657922</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319324400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/35657922/</event_url></item>