<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>RM # M01-0417</address_2><address_1>100 William T Morrissey Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.313400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-287-5000</phone><name>UMass Boston (McCormack Building)</name><city>Dorchester</city><id>1299462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.038902</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;When:  August 7 from 3-5:30PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: UMASS Boston McCormack Building&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Have you ever had a flying dream?  Have you felt yourself “falling” just before waking up? Have you experienced Déjà vu’s or had a dream about the future that came true?  If so you may have had powerful, yet often undetected psychic experience called an out-of-body experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This lecture will provide an overview of the out-of-body experience (i.e. OBE, astral projection), a powerful psychic/spiritual  experience that can help us to understand our lives and “reality” from a more expanded sense of awareness.  The out-of-body experience is not a dream, but a real and natural phenomena that has been reported by people from around the world, throughout human history.  Despite being more widely experienced then commonly thought, it is often confused as a dream when it does occur, and therefore goes unrecognized and undetected by the majority of people in their day-to-day lives.  The OBE a powerful tool for self-knowledge and personal transformation and had many practical benefits in our daily life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Modern scientific research into the phenomena shows us that the OBE can provide us with access to our true psychic nature and the energy-based reality that surrounds us.  A powerful tool for personal growth and self-knowledge, it can help us to understand and verify for ourselves in an empirical manner, our life purpose, psychic ability, intuition, past lives, the period between lives, the human energy system, and even the existence of life after death.  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;This lecture will include the following topics among others:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;An introduction into what OBEs are and are not&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The mechanisms behind the OBE and how they work&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The latest research into out-of-body experiences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The benefits and applications of the OBE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How the OBE supports a consciousness-centered paradigm for scientific research&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The implications of the OBE on our life purpose and well being&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About The Presenter: Gabriel Sereni is a consciousness researcher and has given lectures worldwide for years on topics related to consciousness studies, human potential, personal growth, psychic awareness and scientific approaches to spirituality.  He is currently the director of the IAC New York Center which conducts educational and research based activities in the areas of consciousness studies and psychic phenomena.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This meetup is for people who are both new and experienced with the topic of out-of-body experiences.   The lecture will be followed by a question and answer period along with a description of an upcoming Fly-in project for Boston Meetup members. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;FLY-IN PROJECT:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lecture will be followed by a “fly-in” project presentation for meetup members and the public who want to participate.  This project involves setting up a target at IAC’s NY Education Center for people to see if they can have an OBE, fly into a room in the center, and see if they can perceive a mystery item which will be placed in a concealed box.  Results will be reported to the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:  There is no fee for this event, however, a $10 donation to help cover Gabe's travel expenses from New York would be greatly appreciated. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>IAC  </member_name><member_id>1977812</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281212166000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Researchers of Consciousness</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-OBE</urlname><id>1258624</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Out-of-Body Experience Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276091933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Out-of-Body Experiences and Psychic Reality </name><id>13747586</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281207600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-OBE/events/13747586/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/8/global_15615256.jpeg</photo_url></item>