<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I wanted to add another meet up time because many people have said that Wednesday evenings were not good for them.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, How about the first Sunday of every month at 12pm?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am putting it on the calendar but if you have desires for another time please let me know.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what it will be about... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My name is Reverend Gabrielle. I am a non- denominational mystical Christian priest. I have been meditating for over 14 years and taught yoga for a long time too. I am eager to meet others who are interested in meditation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will focus on learning skills to concentrate and relax so a connection can be made inside through quieting the mind .  Mysticism just means knowing through experience and what better way to experience peace and love and stillness inside than through meditation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The intention is to come together the first Sunday of every month for a Meditation and Mystical tea. This is what it will look like. We will start with a visualization or a short reading or subject to contemplate. After the meditation, we will discuss our experiences and talk about ways to deepen our practice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting you all and will be happy to see you there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh yes, delicious tea will also be served. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Light,  &lt;br /&gt;Rev Gabrielle  &lt;br /&gt;617-852-2822 &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541269000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176263100000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New meditation meet up day and time!</name><id>5658486</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178467200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/5658486/</event_url></item>