<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Rt. 9 Westbound-behind Chuck E. Cheese)</address_2><address_1>3 Vision Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.300643</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitney Place Assisted Living</name><city>Natick</city><id>766030</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354550</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Ever wonder if there's a better way to talk to your children about race &amp;ndash; what it means, why do people look different, where do your friends' families come from, etc.? &amp;nbsp;Research suggests that avoiding the topic of race (i.e., teaching your children to be "race blind") is not effective because as much as the media has hyped the term "post-racial world", there is still a great deal of racial prejudice and stereotyping and our children are constantly taking note of what they hear and see. &amp;nbsp;For this discussion, we invited cultural anthropologist Dr. Michael Baran of Harvard and Cambridge Diversity Consulting to come talk to our chapter about some of his&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;span&gt;research on how children learn about race, what we can do to start productive conversations with them about it, and what tools are out there to help, including two FREE apps that Dr. Baran developed. If you have an iPod touch, iPad, or iPhone, you can take a look at them before the discussion. "Who Am I? Race Awareness Game" and "Guess My Race?" are both available through the Apple iTunes store.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; This discussion is appropriate for parents of toddlers to teens. We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the Community Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne L.</member_name><member_id>8054993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310486091000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307972180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discussion: Talking with children about race and diversity</name><id>22001221</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310427000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/22001221/</event_url></item>