<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Writing for Well-Being&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience a fun, relaxing evening in which Fran shows you how to use writing as a tool for well-being and gets your creative juices flowing.  Add the subtitle of the workshop, Using Meditation, Guided Imagery, and Music to Open your Heart for Self-Expression “à la Pen,” and you will have a glimpse of what is in special store for you.  By workshop’s end, you will take home a vision of your personal, “magic” pen and use it often!  Bring your ink and lined paper or a journal.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When this workshop was offered in January 2006, it helped facilitate the writing of a participant in the quiet, safe space that Fran is known to provide in all her work.  “Mary’s” work was accepted in the premier edition of the Boston Harbor Island Review.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original workshop was presented by Fran in July 2004, at the Central Massachusetts Writing Project’s Summer Invitational Institute, held at Worcester State College.  The former executive director of this program shared at Fran's presentation that during one of the writing prompts, he wrote three pages beyond what he ever thought he would write for his memoir.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will greet them at the door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan gale</member_name><member_id>572960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243302985000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Families of Intuitive People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Paths-to-Light-in-Worcester</urlname><id>83587</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>Paths to Light</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240780906000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Writing from the Heart</name><id>10271881</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242511200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Paths-to-Light-in-Worcester/events/10271881/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/6/global_7518518.jpeg</photo_url></item>