<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Come out this Wednesday evening for an Afterwork Mixer at Minibar in the Back Bay!  This is a great venue to meet new friends and to enjoy a summer night in Boston!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I realize that this group has not been very active lately and, with your help, that is going to change.  If you are interested in organizing and running events for the Boston Nightlife Meetup Group, then I would like to meet you this Wednesday at the mixer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having organized over 100 events for this group, I can say that hosting events is absolutely the fastest way to meet many interesting and like-minded people in Boston.  If you are new to organizing events, that is OK, I can help guide you in making your events a success!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you all on Wednesday night!  New and current group members are welcome, and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minibar web site: &lt;a href="http://www.minibarboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.minibarbos...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: The event will start at 6pm at MiniBar (51 Huntington Ave, inside the Copley Square Hotel).  Come by anytime, but I recommend arriving earlier rather than later, especially if you are interested in becoming an organizer for our meetup group.  Minibar can get pretty busy, so if you cannot find the group, please give me a ring (646.541.0708). Cover: None.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, call my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as this is an upscale venue. If traveling by T, Copley Station (on the green line) and Back Bay Station (on the orange line) are the closest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279805490000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279598920000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Afterwork Mixer and Organizers Search this Wednesday, 6-9pm!</name><id>14154417</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279749600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/14154417/</event_url></item>