<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You are invited to join the Cardboard Players Club poker club for Home Games online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- If you don't already have it, download the free PokerStars software from www.pokerstars.net &lt;br /&gt;

 - Open the main poker lobby, then click on the Home Games tab &lt;br /&gt;

 - Click the 'Join a Poker Club' button &lt;br /&gt;

 - Enter our Club ID number: 650411 &lt;br /&gt;

 - Enter the Invitation Code: fouraceswins&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once your membership request is approved, you can sign up for the tournament and you'll be ready to play!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to ask if you have any questions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FAQ:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is there a charge for this?&lt;/strong&gt; No.  The software is free.  Membership in the club is free.  Your tournament entry is free.  Free, free, free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this legal?&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.  Because there's no money involved, it's completely legal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How many people can play?&lt;/strong&gt; As many as sign up!  The software will automatically configure the starting tables to accommodate everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do I get if I win?&lt;/strong&gt; Bragging rights.  Nothing more or less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long will the tournament last?&lt;/strong&gt; That depends on the number of players, but, like a home tournament, the blinds go up so the tournament will move fairly quickly.  Our inaugural tournament was over in under an hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why should I do this?&lt;/strong&gt; It's fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do I have to know how to play Texas Hold 'em?&lt;/strong&gt; No, in fact it's a great way to learn.  The software won't let you do anything that's against the rules, and it will automatically fold your hand if you don't make a different decision within a certain amount of time.  Plus, your friends will be there to help!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just be signed onto PokerStars a few minutes before 7:00 and you'll be taken directly to your table!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348625787000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346161304000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Online Texas Hold 'em Poker Tourney - for CPCoC Members Only!</name><id>dfmcddyqmbhc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348614000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/79717642/</event_url></item>