<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Downtown</address_2><address_1>49 Peck St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 272-1212</phone><name>Red Fez the</name><city>Providence</city><id>205815</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;SORRY EVERYONE!!!!! Spot Underground is having a poetry slam tonight, which would be cool, but they aren't opening until 6:30 and have a cover of $4 - so we're going to the RED FEZ instead!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So sorry for the last minute change! We'll have to try another time. I'm totally bummed. Hope you can still make it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to the Providence Collective Monday Meetup series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: The Spot Underground in the Jewelry District at the corner of Elbow &amp;amp; Chestnut st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Spot has been around on Thayer Street for quite awhile, make no mistake and do not be confused - THIS is The Spot UNDERGROUND. Same organization, DIFFERENT location! This is a venue that holds a variety of different events from bands to art openings. I went here for the first time last month for pecha kucha, and was very impressed. Its a huge place with different levels to watch the bands play, a large central bar and lots of lounge type areas for conversation. Its not uber hipster trendy, but comfortable and a little quirky. A good place to come for a beer or cocktail and listen to music or just hang out. It's pretty cool and one to know about! So let's check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.&lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm wearing a gray blue sweater, but we're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287708853000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287286077000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VENUE CHANGE!!!!!!!  Monday Night Meetup - The Red Fez!!!!!</name><id>15133904</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287439200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/15133904/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>