<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>319 Centre Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02370</zip><lat>42.113241</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-264-3787</phone><name>South Shore SportFighting</name><city>Rockland</city><id>1195866</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.926536</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You're invited to come train at Mixed Martial Arts school(think UFC or CageFighting)....&amp;quot;South Shore SportFighting and Fitness&amp;quot; at 319 Centre Ave in Rockland, MA.It's on route 123 in the Centre Crossing Plaza right by the Abington border. (near the Abington Target)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sssfighting.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sssfightin...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the best workout to get out aggression and stress! Throw on some gloves and punch it out!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bill Mahoney of South Shore Sportsfighting is offering this class to us for $5 a person!! (CASH ONLY and PLEASE bring exact change)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be trained like the beginner kickboxing and cardio classes. We'll have a brief warmup with some jogging, squats, jumping jacks... to get us moving and ready to go.  &lt;br /&gt;We'll have some instruction on how to properly kick and punch, then practice with holding mitts for each other and using bags. I've even learned how to a choke hold the right way and some grappling moves.  &lt;br /&gt;But don't worry you won't get punched in the face! It's just about fitness and fun.  &lt;br /&gt;You will sweat and this is a GREAT workout, but even more fun! And a very inexpensive way to try something new.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan on bringing:  &lt;br /&gt;Water  &lt;br /&gt;a towel (remember you WILL sweat!)  &lt;br /&gt;If you have them, gloves, wraps &amp;amp; shin pads, but they do have loaners if not  &lt;br /&gt;$5 CASH, exact change  &lt;br /&gt;A great attitude to have fun! :)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GUESTS ARE WELCOME!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to up to 45 members!  &lt;br /&gt;We will need at least 10 people for this event to be held.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please update your RSVP by Friday January 7th at 4pm so I can give a final count to Bill. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***South Shore SportFighting has a fight schedule for later that night.  Tickets will be available for purchase at this event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bonus for arriving on time!  World class UFC fighers will be at the gym leaving at 1pm for UFC fans!  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet inside.  NO OUTSIDE SHOES ON THE MATS PLEASE!!!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4336960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294740362000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292180227000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MMA Fitness Session (Mixed Martial Arts) </name><id>15713076</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294509600000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/15713076/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/4/global_17469620.jpeg</photo_url></item>