<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time approximate. &amp;nbsp;Meetup will be updated when start time is announced.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Le Quattro Volte&lt;/em&gt;, the nearly wordless second film from Italian director Michaelangelo Frammartino, compresses a year in a mountainous spot in the southern Italian region of Calabria into the length of a short feature. It&amp;rsquo;s a remote location, but Frammartino&amp;rsquo;s canny eye, wry humor, and careful sense of rhythm make it feel like the best possible spot to observe the workings of the world, from ashes to ashes. Literally: The film begins and ends with a group of men creating charcoal, then cycles through a series of connected vignettes filled with images of death and rebirth taken from everyday life in and around a centuries-old village.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 15px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;Le Quattro Volte&amp;rdquo; packs more life into 88 minutes than movies twice as long, patiently surveying the human and natural landscapes of a remote valley in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.calabria2010.com/" style="color : #004276 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;the southern Italian region of Calabria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 15px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;If you pay attention, you see what is going on and grasp the connections between the different things you see, none of which are terribly unfamiliar. But there is something startling, even shocking, about the angle of vision Mr. Frammartino imposes by juxtaposing apparently disparate elements and lingering on what seem at first to be insignificant details. &lt;strong&gt;You have never seen anything like this movie&lt;/strong&gt;, even though what it shows you has been there all along.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Though the film is wordless, we'll share plentyof words at &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Tommy Doyle's.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp;Plan on a rather enjoyable reflection of the wonders of life following a film we'll think about for a long time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 15px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you are new to the group, please look for me holding a priceless Meetup Sign as I exit the theater, and then immediately outside the door in the hallway.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303053139000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>“Le Quattro Volte,” an idiosyncratic and amazing new film by Michelangelo Frammartino, is so full of surprises — nearly every shot contains a revelation, sneaky or overt, cosmic or mundane — that even to describe it is to risk giving something away.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301692193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Le Quattro Volte</name><id>17147397</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302985800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/17147397/</event_url></item>