<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Pirates Month! I didn't&amp;nbsp;write&amp;nbsp;this month's yarn cuz another be doing it better afore me.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If ye be a pirate on a long journey across the Atlantic or in the Caribbean ye might likes to know what ye be eatin' at any moments notice. That is why I be here laddies and lassies to tell ye that at fir&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;st a pirate's grub be fresh and plentiful, but as ye journey ventures on longer this pirate food turns scarce and what is left be rotten to the core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pirate food, in fact, may not look like anything ye have been eatin' before. The journey may start out all joyous with barrels of salted meat, a cow down below, chickens for eggs, fresh vegetables, biskits, beans, milk and a variety of pickled foods not to mention rum and more rum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But a pirate's appetite be fierce and some journeys, they be long. So before a fortnight is gone, the supplies in the hull start to suffer. Ye may start to notice that our pirate cook in the ship's gall&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/8/5/event_47983141.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ey is using more spices than usual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This be the first sig&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;n that we be running out of pirate food. The spices and herbs are to cover up thee&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;taste of rotting meat and vegetables. Maggots crawl through thee meat and weevils get into thee biskits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we be out for months at sea, we pirates finally eat thee cow and then thee chickens for meat. Some of me pirates already got thee scurvy from not having enough to fill thee bellies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we are ne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ar a port, sure as the sunset we will fill thee vessel with as much meat and vegetables as we could get our hands and hooks onto. But, if we be out to sea, we need to raid another ship with fresh supplies. Otherwise they might just be in as dire straights in regard to pirate food as we Arrrrr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One problem with we pirates is that we ain't be good fishermen. Yea, occasionally we be bringing in a sea turtle or some other creature we could catch that wouldn't send us down to Davy Jones Locker, but our mainstay be whatever we brung with us from the habitat of landlubbers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we be havin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;' a lucky strike we might be bringing onboard dishes like sour kraut, bumboo, hard tack, bone soup, sweetbreads, meat pie, pirate's stew, honey cakes or even the occasional stuffed hen that thee captain and his first mate may enjoy in private beyond the prying eyes of the other mateys.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, if we had the luckiest strike of all and we pirates raided an English ship with fresh supplies we might be dining on sheep, ducks, turkey legs, boar, hogs and even goats. Of course we be eatin' our mutton with our hands, wiping our mouths on our sleeves and drinking rum while singing songs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That be the pirate way. "&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Above be the content from&amp;nbsp;
&lt;a href="http://www.piratetreasure.org/pirate-food.htm"&gt;http://www.piratetreasure.org/pirate-food.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Margo Lynn below shares some lore with ye maties!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.doverpublications.com/designsampler/0810/sample4.htm"&gt;http://www.doverpublications.com/designsampler/0810/sample4.htm&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.doverpublications.com/designsampler/0810/sample41.htm"&gt;http://www.doverpublications.com/designsampler/0810/sample41.htm&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.shutterstock.com/pic-9066925/stock-vector-computer-pirate.html"&gt;http://www.shutterstock.com/pic-9066925/stock-vector-computer-pirate.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This last one looks "gooey" or "gui"to me, guey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember there are no rules, especially for&amp;nbsp;pirates! I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn&amp;rsquo;t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the directions a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318637161000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312181343000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Fabulous Foodies Pirate Dinner RRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR u coming?</name><id>pkdkxypmbmb</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315609200000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/29092711/</event_url></item>