<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Upakar Boston invites you to a Fundraiser Happy Hour&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for Upakar- Boston’s First Fundraiser Happy Hour! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will be held at VINALIA, one of the trendiest lounge venues in the Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;Date: July 16, 2009 &lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:30 pm - 9:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Location: Vinalia, 99 Summer Street, Boston, MA 02110&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $10 &lt;br /&gt;All Proceeds from the event will be donated to Upakar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upakar was founded in 1997 and was created to assist Indian Americans who require financial assistance to pursue an undergraduate degree at a U.S. based college or university. Upakar is the only Indian American scholarship organization that awards scholarship for 4 years. Since 1997, Upakar has been able to give out 94 scholarships and hopes to increase that number with your support! So come join us to support Upakar’s mission to recognize and nurture excellence in all fields by Indo-Americans and to support those in financial need in their pursuit of higher education. This event is a great opportunity to learn more about Upakar and what you can do to support the cause of higher education!&lt;br /&gt;Visit www.upakar.org for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For any questions regarding this event, please e-mail Sonia Rai at sonia.rai86@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;So come join us on July 16th for a noble cause!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248449996000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-27</urlname><id>610218</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Group Closing - Indian Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245973083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Upakar Boston Happy Hour &amp; Fundraiser</name><id>10737374</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247783400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-27/events/10737374/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/4/8/global_9029704.jpeg</photo_url></item>