<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Meetup Date changed to Wednesday, March 7th at 7pm due to the snow**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at Chaibo in Fitchburg on the first Thursday night in March to discuss The Night Circus by Erin Morgenstern. Treat yourself to some decadent chocolate cake or gelato, try Chaibo's nachos or paninis, or just just enjoy some coffee or tea as we chat about the book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of the book from Amazon, along with a few reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The circus arrives without warning. No announcements precede it. It is simply there, when yesterday it was not. Within the black-and-white striped canvas tents is an utterly unique experience full of breathtaking amazements. It is called Le Cirque des R&amp;ecirc;ves, and it is only open at night.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;But behind the scenes, a fierce competition is underway&amp;mdash;a duel between two young magicians, Celia and Marco, who have been trained since childhood expressly for this purpose by their mercurial instructors. Unbeknownst to them, this is a game in which only one can be left standing, and the circus is but the stage for a remarkable battle of imagination and will. Despite themselves, however, Celia and Marco tumble headfirst into love&amp;mdash;a deep, magical love that makes the lights flicker and the room grow warm whenever they so much as brush hands.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;True love or not, the game must play out, and the fates of everyone involved, from the cast of extraordinary circus per&amp;shy;formers to the patrons, hang in the balance, suspended as precariously as the daring acrobats overhead.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Written in rich, seductive prose, this spell-casting novel is a feast for the senses and the heart.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "&lt;em&gt;The Night Circus&lt;/em&gt; made me happy. Playful and intensely imaginative, Erin Morgenstern has created the circus I have always longed for and she has populated it with dueling love-struck magicians, precocious kittens, hyper-elegant displays of beauty and complicated clocks. This is a marvelous book." &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;-- Audrey Niffenegger, author of &lt;em&gt;The Time Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Wife&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"[T]he world of The Night Circus is elaborately designed, fantastically imagined and instantly intoxicating -- as if the reader had downed a glass of absinthe and leapt into a hallucination." &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;--Rachel Syme for NPR.org&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;The Night Circus&lt;/em&gt; is a gorgeously imagined fable poised in the high latitudes of Hans Christian Anderson and Oscar Wilde, with a few degrees toward Hesse&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Steppenwolf&amp;rdquo; for dangerous spice. The tale is masterfully written and invites allegorical interpretations even as its leisurely but persistent suspense gives it compelling charm. An enchanting read.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;Katherine Dunn, author of &lt;em&gt;Geek Love&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Dark as soot and bright as sparks,&amp;rsquo; &lt;em&gt;The Night Circus&lt;/em&gt; still holds me willingly captive in a world of almost unbearable beauty. This is a love story on a grand scale: it creates, it destroys, it ultimately transcends. Take a bow, Erin Morgenstern. This is one of the best books I have ever read.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;Brunonia Barry, author of &lt;em&gt;The Lace Reader&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333065303000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328211427000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - The Night Circus by Erin Morgenstern</name><id>50761762</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331164800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/50761762/</event_url></item>