<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>860 Elm St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.990361</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-629-9383</phone><name>Z Food and Drink</name><city>Manchester</city><id>764890</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463061</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The new Restaurant of the Month is Z Food and Drink.  The owner promises me that we will have 4 tables that hold 6 people each, but cannot guarantee that all 4 tables will be cleared of previous diners at the same time, so patience is the order of the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chef/Owner Tom Puskarich&lt;br /&gt;If you've lived in Southern New Hampshire for any length of time, chances are Chef/Owner Tom Puskarich has cooked for you. His culinary path began in the late 80s at the Bedford Village Inn with stops along the way at Café Pavone and Villa Banca before a brief return to his native California.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In August, 2006, Puskarich arrived back in his adopted home of Manchester and set his sights on locating the perfect spot for the restaurant that's been in the making for almost 20 years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In March, 2007 that restaurant became Z, a venture Puskarich brought to life with his partner, Maureen Cidzik, a seasoned client and guest relations professional.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You Really Like Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best New Eatery, Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Hippo Press Reader's Choice Awards, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Platinum Plate&lt;br /&gt;NECN's TV Diner, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best Cuisine with a Twist&lt;br /&gt;New Hampshire Magazine, Editor's Choice, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.zfoodanddrink.com/menu.phtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.zfoodanddr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East: Take 101W to I-93 North toward Concord and follow to Exit 8/ Wellington Road/Bridge Street. Turn right off the exit and follow Bridge Street for approximately 1.5 miles to the intersection of Elm Street (the Bank of America building will be on your left). Turn left onto Elm Street and continue approximately .8 miles. Z is located on the right at 860 Elm Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: Take I-293 toward Manchester and follow to Exit 5 - Granite Street. Continue toward downtown Manchester and turn right onto Granite Street. Continue on Granite to the intersection of Elm Street (the Verizon Wireless Arena will be on your right). Turn left onto Elm Street and follow for .1 miles. Z is located on the left at 860 Elm Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: Take I-93 South toward Manchester and take Exit 8/Wellington Road/Bridge Street and continue as if From the East or merge onto I-293 South toward Manchester to Exit 4/Queen City Bridge. Turn right off the exit and right at the first set of lights (Queen City Bridge). At the second set of lights, turn left onto Elm Street and follow for .2 miles. Z is located on the left at 860 Elm Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Next Month:&lt;/b&gt; Manhattan on the Pearl&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222180454000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221600373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dining Event: Restaurant of the Month Club September Meetup</name><id>8770649</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221954300000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8770649/</event_url></item>