<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>Meetup.com Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>4.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to all who attended the February NLP meetup.  We had a great session, where we wrestled with the ever-present question &amp;quot;What is NLP&amp;quot;, discussed the 12 presuppositions of NLP, and ended up learning and applying the NLP technique 'Circle of Excellence&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, for March: We're going to continue on with the theme of 'changing the world with NLP'.  As we discussed in the February meeting, we first need to change ourselves before we can change the world.  The Circle of Excellence technique was one step in that direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then _next_ step in that direction is figuring out what you want to change in the world (specifically), and then how to change it.  We'll address this in our March meeting with the NLP concept of Well-Formed Outcomes.  When an outcome is well-formed (a linguistic term) it is almost guaranteed to be achievable.  It will also contain (by definition) the first step(s) to achieving it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in better goal-setting - personally or professionally, to change your world or change your clothes - then come on by on March 22.  Worksheets will also be distributed to attendees, to enable them to help others set well-formed outcomes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month's meetup does not depend on knowing Circle of Excellence, or having attended last month's meeting.  It also does not presuppose that you know anything about NLP.  Everyone is welcome, from beginners to experts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you.&lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS  A reminder that the venue has changed.  In response to feedback, we are changing to a quieter, non-restaurant forum.  Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking.&lt;br /&gt;You can get directions here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing two flights of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174777553000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172192633000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Changing the World with NLP - Setting Well-Formed Goals</name><id>5505554</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174604400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/5505554/</event_url></item>