<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>900 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02021</zip><lat>42.164787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Canton High School</name><city>Canton</city><id>1355229</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.147096</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Another chance to put that 5k training to work!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cantonai.org/race/CHRR_GreenFlyer2010.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cantonai.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 mile fun run 8:30am ($5)&lt;br /&gt;5k at 9am ($20)&lt;br /&gt;10k at 9:30am ($20)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.active.com/running/canton-ma/reebok-canton-homecoming-road-race-2010" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.active.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Canton Associations of Industries is pleased to announce our Sixth Annual Reebok Homecoming Road Race to be held on Saturday September 25, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each year as this event has grown, we have continued to raise our fund raising target.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 5th Annual Race had 448 registered runners and raised over $52,000 that is being awarded to many worthy non-profit organizations located in the Town of Canton. Some of organizations include Massachusetts Hospital School, Clark School for the Deaf, Canton Recreation Department, Canton Police and Fire Departments, the 4th of July Fireworks, Canton Block Party, Mass Audubon and many others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part of the charter of the CAI is to raise funds and resources for the many worthy charities in the Town of Canton. This road race is our main focus to accomplish this goal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is my hope that the many wonderful businesses and community members will show their support by becoming a sponsor of our event, purchasing an ad in our ad booklet, by volunteering to assist the road race, supporting our raffle for two fantastic tickets to the Reebok Luxury Box at Gillette Stadium for a Patriot Game and most importantly by running in our road race. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The road race is a great attraction for families to come out and enjoy the fun. There is a race opportunity for everyone, a1 mile fun run, 5K &amp;amp; 10K races and a 5K wheelchair race and the 2nd Corporate Team Challenge for the coveted Crystal Cup. There are also games for the children, the silent auction for adults, massages and stretching for the runners, DJ and free food and beverages for all. I hope you all get to join us on this eventful day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, thank you for the wonderful out pouring of support from the Town of Canton. May you all run with the wind at your back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warm Regards,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Howard Jay Goldman&lt;br /&gt;President Canton Association of Industries&lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp; Chairman of the Reebok/CAI Road Race&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the registration area by 8:30am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Katherine</member_name><member_id>9909044</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285424269000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282583301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>6th Annual Reebok Canton Homecoming 5k</name><id>14512823</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285419600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/14512823/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/7/global_4320375.jpeg</photo_url></item>