<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5400 Computer Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01581</zip><lat>42.289700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree Hotel</name><city>Westborough</city><id>1140338</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.572400</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Tea Party Patriot,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a very important and unprecedented invitation to share with you.  As a supporter of the Tea Party movement, you have taken the initiative in restoring our founding principles to our nation’s governance.  This is your invitation to an upcoming event that will hopefully inspire you to action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are surely aware of the Special Senate Election that will take place in Massachusetts on January 19, 2010.  While one of the candidates promises to deliver the crucial 60th vote to the Liberal Democrats, continuing our nation's slide into a socialist welfare state, there is another candidate that promises to stand up as Vote 41 and support our values of limited government, lower taxes, and individual liberty.  State Senator Scott Brown is that candidate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have an opportunity in Massachusetts at a time when the stakes are too high to remain complacent.  Imagine the reaction of Americans across the nation when they hear that we have elected a common-sense-conservative to the US Senate, into the so-called Ted Kennedy seat.  This would truly be the new shot heard ‘round the world.  We want our government to return to those values that made us the greatest nation ever known.  With the power and passion behind the Tea Party movement, we can make it happen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join Tea Party Patriots from across New England on Saturday, January 2nd, where Scott Brown will share with us his values and principles, answer our questions  - the ones Martha Coakley will not - and ask for our help in winning the “people’s seat”.  With the US Senate breaking rules and adding outrageous earmarks in order to pass healthcare reform and Martha Coakley flaunting election laws by using union labor and union resources to influence voters, Scott Brown needs a team of dedicated and enthusiastic supporters on his side, carrying his message across the state.  He is the only candidate asking to meet with us and I think you will decide he is a candidate you can support.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve your seat today and join us as we take back our country!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.icontribute.us/scottbrown/initiative/brownbreakfast" target="_blank"&gt;(click here to RSVP)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christen Varley&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President, Greater Boston Tea Party&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christen Varley</member_name><member_id>9247789</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262610505000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261265325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tea Party Breakfast with US Senate Candidate Scott Brown</name><id>12117485</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262437200000</time><rsvp_limit>200</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/12117485/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/a/4/global_8615540.jpeg</photo_url></item>