<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>In 1981, Jean-Michel Basquiat catapulted from being an unknown nineteen-year-old graffiti writer to becoming one of the most successful, controversial, glamorous artists in the world. His shows were anticipated as the big events of the New York season, and his paintings were bought by the most powerful collectors and museums. Every aspect of his life became a subject for the media. By 1988, he was dead at the age of 27. Basquiat was described by The New York Times as &amp;quot;the art world's closest equivalent to James Dean.&amp;quot; In spite of his success, this turbulent and talented young painter was also plagued by loneliness, self-destruction and the belief that people really did not accept him for who he was. As the first black contemporary artist to really succeed in the powerful white art world, his early death shows that he was a casualty as well as a phenomenal success.  (yahoo.movies.com)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to additional info about the movie:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://artlife.blogspot.com/2006/04/movie-of-week-basquiat.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://artlife.blogsp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A link to a review by the New York Times:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/review?res=9E07E4DF123EF93AA3575BC0A960958260" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to examples of his work:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.soho-art.com/Jean-Michel-Basquiat.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.soho-art.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie which lasts 1 hr. 48 min., we'll go to a local restaurant for dining and discussion.  Please ONLY rsvp YES if you are planning to go to the restaurant afterwards so I'll make the reservation for the appropiate number of people.  Also, if your plans change, please change your RSVP.  Thank-you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to an interesting discussion afterwards.  Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;Susan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be near the front row on the right side of the theatre at the end of the film with my MEETUP sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331085786000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252714510000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Basquiat</name><id>11351122</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253919600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11351122/</event_url></item>