<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Local (Locale) (LoCal) (loco-l) is the theme.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The local scene, that’s where you want to be known. You want a close following of jive loyalists, big fish little pond. What’s local, after all, but the place you are, the people you’re with…It’s what’s happening, my friend.&lt;br /&gt;You gotta scope out the local talent, and then see what you can score. This is how it was before you could order exotic mail order brides from Nova Scotia and have them shipped tax-free second-day-air over Amazon.com. Local is where it is at, Man!&lt;br /&gt;Step into the wayback bro and dig it. Local is knocking; look around it’s everywhere you be.&lt;br /&gt;Local is green, but it’s also orange and ruby red. It’s the whispered tip, the private rendezvous. Local baby is the house next door. You know what I’m talking 'bout? You get the drift of my riff? &lt;br /&gt;Cool Daddyo!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284844487000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281623110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes Monthly dinner Meetup</name><id>vmbmnynmbnb</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284159600000</time><rsvp_limit>36</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/14401247/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/0/4/global_17164356.jpeg</photo_url></item>