<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A member of the group requested that I send out a message about this fund raiser.  So, I thought that we should do it as an event.  The event is at Filippo's Restaurant in the North End, and asks for a $25 donation per person.  Below are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’re all invited to a great night of free food, good music and fun times at Filippo’s Restaurant in the North End all the while benefiting those who were severely effected by the catastrophic earthquake in L’Aquilla, Italy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spread the word that a new group has form: Commissione Giovani of New England—Young Italians of New England. A group created by Italians and Italian-Americans to promote and maintain Italian culture and language.  Who wouldn’t want to meet new people from a great cultural background that is known for its passion and celebrations.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:  Filippo’s Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;                283 Causeway St &lt;br /&gt;               North End, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:   Friday, May 15th 7:30-10:30  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To participate in this fundraiser a donation of $25.00 will be required for admission in support of the relief efforts. The proceeds will be handed over completely to ease the pains of those who currently are suffering.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For donations and other information please contact helpabruzzo@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send out an e-mail with more details</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243638970000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241660102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fund Raiser for the Victim of the L'Aquila Earthquake</name><id>10357199</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242429300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/10357199/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/2/3/global_7135059.jpeg</photo_url></item>