<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372444</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 491 9400</phone><name>Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>730460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's the 2012 AllStar Break and we will return to one of the Natives favorite venues by request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive early, during the game or when ever and leave when ever. Game time is 8:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natives Team Weatherman Scott says it will probably be a hazy, hot and humid night so we will venture outside to relax, take in the scene, and watch game at Legal Seafoods out door bar and patio at the Charles Hotel in Harvard Square. This is the raw bar at street level visible from the street, not the patio dining area in the courtyard. There are several Televisions at the bar. The bar menu is sufficient for most people. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be either at or around the bar and then move to a round table. Ask the bartenders if you can not find us or are a newbie. All members should wear Red Sox Baseball hats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendance at this is unlimited. Please RSVP and bring guests and other Sox fans. Come meet other members who share your interest, provide feedback on desired events and cheer on our Sox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay cash for your beverage and food and tip your server/bartender when paying your separate food and drink check before leaving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fenway Frank &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the bartenders, look for Natives wearing Red Sox Hats</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>6918204</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342023935000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339872745000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AllStar Break - Relax &amp; Watch The AllStar Game at Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar</name><id>69459272</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341961200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/69459272/</event_url></item>