<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A reporter from The Boston Globe will be joining our group for this movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 2006 German Film described as &amp;quot;an intricate, ambiguous and deeply satisfying movie, a tautly plotted tale of state surveillance and personal betrayal that ultimately becomes an ode to the transformative power of art&amp;quot;, is set in East Germany in the Orwellian year of 1984.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since it won the Oscar, it might be  a good idea to get there a bit early so that you can get a good seat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Georg Dreyman is a successful playwright whose works always remain within the bounds of political correctness. He is having an affair with  lead actress, Christa-Maria, who has also attracted the interest of a certain high-ranking East German Official. Georg must now be proven a traitor and in steps long-time surveillance expert Gerd Weisler.  Weisler, whose own bureaucratic life is  as dull as a cockroach's, however, is slowly drawn into these other people's lives- their humanity, passion, and idealism. The same traits he so sorely lacks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This movie swept the German equivalent of the Oscars. Here is a complete review:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.slate.com/id/2159360/fr/flyout" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.slate.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local eatery to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173208133000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172437919000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Lives of Others" Winner of Best Foreign Film</name><id>5513075</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1173034800000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5513075/</event_url></item>