<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>27 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373271</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)876-2700</phone><name>Crema Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>693403</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120426</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.25</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;The Nihilist, that strange martyr who has no faith, who goes to the stake without enthusiasm... is a purely literary product. He was invented by Turgenev, and completed by Dostoevsky.&amp;quot;--Oscar Wilde&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When a young graduate returns home he is accompanied, much to his father and uncle's disapproval, by a strange friend &amp;quot;who doesn't acknowledge any authorities, who doesn't accept a single principle on faith.&amp;quot; Turgenev's masterpiece of generational conflict shocked Russian society when it was published in 1862 and continues to seem as fresh and outspoken as it did to those who first encountered its spirited nihilistic hero, Bazarov. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fathers and Sons&amp;quot; juxtaposes two generations, &amp;quot;the fathers,&amp;quot; or the fading aristocracy, and &amp;quot;the sons,&amp;quot; or the new fresh blood of the middle class and the nihilists, against the backdrop of the Russian pre-revolutionary unrest.  While it is often described as a &amp;quot;novel of ideas&amp;quot;, few rival it in psychological insight into characters and their relationships.  At its heart lies the tragic aftermath of a flippant kiss and the havoc it wrecks in the cozy country gentry household. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was also the first Russian work to gain prominence abroad, enthusiastically received by Gustave Flaubert, Guy de Maupassant, and Henry James just to name a few. So, you Tolstoy and Dostoevsky devotees out there, don't forget that Russian literature, as we know it, begins with and owes much to Ivan Turgenev.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to put off buying the book, here is where you may access it online:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bartleby.com/319/2/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bartleby.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if you are lazier still:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://librivox.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://librivox.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1263167845000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258511073000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turgenev: Fathers and Sons</name><id>11900219</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260140400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/11900219/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/a/7/global_5819031.jpeg</photo_url></item>