<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>32 Vassar Street</address_2><address_1>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 155</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1119883</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For registration, please visit &lt;a href="https://alum.mit.edu/smarTrans/public/Register.dyn?eventID=38582&amp;amp;groupID=298" target="_blank"&gt;https://alum.mit.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Overview&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A smart card can be a key component in an identity management scheme, but it is the combination of this technology with biometric and wireless technology that is the backbone of proven mobile identity verification and identification schemes in the Government sector all over the world. The integration of these technologies allows for the identification and verification of individuals at border points, large public events, or spontaneous controls on the street. In addition to Government applications, the use of mobile biometric identification has value in commercial markets, with project ranging from mobile online banking and healthcare, to public safety and private workforce management solutions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MIT Auto ID &amp;amp; Sensing SIG session will provide a valuable introduction to biometrics and portability, and shed light on the future of mobile biometrics-based security.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are always interested in growing our group with volunteers and new topics. If you are interested in contributing please join the group or join us through Linkedin: &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/groups?home=&amp;amp;gid=1988827&amp;amp;trk=anet_ug_hm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.linkedin.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presenters:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Dave Machuga, CTO of Identity Management Operating Unit, Northrop Grumman&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dan Tuck, Vice President of Engineering and Operations, Datastrip, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A. Mizan Rahman - CEO &amp;amp; Chief Technology Officer, M2SYS Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator: Kai Imgenberg, Director Sales EMEA, Aware, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEAKER BIOGRAPHIES:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave Machuga, CTO of Identity Management Operating Unit, Northrop Grumman &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/2/a/thumb_12533290.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David W. Machuga received his B.S., M.S., and Ph.D. degrees in electrical engineering from Penn State University.  In 1997, he started with Northrop Grumman Corporation in Baltimore, MD as a Senior Engineer working on material development, microwave devices, and antenna systems.  In 2000, he became Manager, Device Technology responsible for internal R&amp;amp;D projects.  From 2001 – 2003, he served as a program manager in the Space Systems Division.  During 2004, he was Director of Distributed Engineering and Electronic Warfare Programs, supervising 7 sites with 850 employees and was responsible for EW programs for engineering and manufacturing.  In 2006, he assumed the position of Director, Homeland Security and Homeland Defense.  Since 2008, his current position is Chief Technology Officer of the Identity Management Operating Unit and Director, Identity Management Solutions Business Area.  As CTO, he is responsible for developing the technology solutions for the Identity Management Operating Unit and technical direction for advanced technology and strategic planning.   In addition, the identity management solutions business area provides state of the art smart card systems, RFID solutions, mobile computing, federated IdM solutions, and strategic identity platforms. Dr. Machuga has 12 journal publications, 20 invention / 2 trade secret awards from Northrop Grumman, is a Senior Member of IEEE, and maintains an appointment as an Adjunct Professor of Electrical Engineering at Penn State University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northrop Grumman Corporation is a leading global security company whose 120,000 employees provide innovative systems, products, and solutions in aerospace, electronics, information systems, shipbuilding and technical services to government and commercial customers worldwide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dan Tuck, Vice President of Engineering and Operations, Datastrip, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/c/2/thumb_12725570.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Vice President of Engineering and Operations at Datastrip Inc., Dan Tuck is responsible for the company’s product development, manufacturing operations, and strategic planning from their offices in Shelton, Conn.  Mr. Tuck joined Datastrip in January 2005, bringing with him more than 20 years of experience and leadership in senior management, engineering, and strategic planning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before coming to Datastrip, Mr. Tuck was General Manager at Microphase Corp.  Prior to that, he was Chief Technical Officer at Paragon Networks.  Earlier in his career, Mr. Tuck was a member of the founding team and led the engineering organization at Ascom Nexion.  He was also a co-founder and Vice President of Engineering of Teleos Communications.  Mr. Tuck holds a Master of Science degree in electrical engineering from Princeton University, and a Bachelor of Science in electrical engineering from the University of Texas, Austin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Datastrip is an innovative market leader in providing mobile personal identification and verification products for the government, military, law enforcement, travel, security, and Fortune 500 commercial markets.  Datastrip’s core focus is the development of mobile secure identification technologies which easily integrate with existing systems and applications to effectively reduce system implementation costs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A. Mizan Rahman - CEO &amp;amp; Chief Technology Officer, M2SYS Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/4/2/thumb_12538434.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mizan Rahman founded M2SYS in 1998. As a visionary, expert software engineer and seasoned entrepreneur, he combines his impressive background solving customers' problems and building companies with a natural intensity and commitment to excellence. While working on several different project designs at M2SYS, Mr. Rahman designed and developed a new generation Supply Chain sourcing automation technology that received strong market demand and interest. Recognizing the enormous potential for this application, in 1999 Mr Rahman leveraged the innovation to spin off a separate subsidiary from M2SYS and founded Net Research, Inc/BayBuilder. BayBuilder evolved into the marketing and distribution arm of M2SYS' strategic sourcing software and quickly matured into an extremely successful enterprise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;M2SYS is a recognized industry leader in fingerprint identity management technology. Anchored by our innovative, patent-pending solution called Bio-Plugin™, we deliver fully functional, turn-key fingerprint recognition software that instantly integrates into third party programs, in many cases with no additional development or system upgrades required. We also offer several stand-alone applications and desktop security products that leverage our biometrics engine. Our fingerprint software solutions are accelerating the growth of biometric technology adoption in the global marketplace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266883877000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258500086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Biometrics &amp; Wireless </name><id>11898617</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264460400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/11898617/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/9/global_12538665.jpeg</photo_url></item>