<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Forum Room (3rd floor)</address_2><address_1>Mass Ave and Quincy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-495-2452</phone><name>Lamont Library, Harvard University</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>927679</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114296</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Is your website hard to manage? Are you unable to easily update the pages yourself? Are you looking for a tool to manage your website that is easy-to-use, flexible and provides unlimited room for growth?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plone is a CMS that allows non-technical end-users to manage website content using nothing but a web browser. It has replaced products like SharePoint, Red Dot and Vignette for department intranets, document management systems, and public websites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Plone CMS [1] is used by thousands of non-profits, small businesses, universities, government agencies and corporations around the world. It supports over 35 languages out-of-the-box, includes plugins for blogging, wikis, membership directory, e-commerce and much more. It's open source software which means that you have complete control over the codebase and can get started quickly at little to no cost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The local Plone usergroup in Boston [2] is organizing an event on April 28, as part of World Plone Day [3], a global “follow the sun” initiative involving at least 29 countries around the world.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an opportunity to come and learn more about Plone and find out if it's the right CMS for your organization. If you're already using Plone, this is your chance to meet other Plone enthusiasts in the Boston/Cambridge area, and hear about the innovative ways they are using Plone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're excited to announce that for the 3rd annual World Plone Day Boston there will be a lineup of excellent speakers, free organic food &amp;amp; drinks and giveaway prizes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Registration:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is free but you must register in order to attend: &lt;a href="http://bostonworldploneday2010-plone.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonworldplo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome whether you are new to CMSes, new to Plone or an old pro.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:15 - 2:30: &lt;b&gt;Sign-in and welcoming&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:30 - 3:00: &lt;b&gt;CMS benefits for a university website and intranet&lt;/b&gt;: Reflections on our first year with Plone by Eliza Grinnell and Lesley Lam from Harvard School of Engineering and Applied Sciences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 4:00: &lt;b&gt;Theming websites effortlessly&lt;/b&gt;: How Deliverance saves us countless hours in the theming process by Aaron VanDerlip and Nate Aune from Jazkarta.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:00 - 4:30: &lt;b&gt;Catalyzing change through collaborative learning&lt;/b&gt;: Harnessing Plone as a platform for collaborative research and reflective learning at Columbia Law School, both within and beyond the classroom by Kyle Homstead from Chronicle Technologies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 5:00: &lt;b&gt;Lightning talks and Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/b&gt;. This is an opportunity to give a short 5 min talk about how you are using Plone, or a cool tool that you've found and want to share. Please prepare your talk in advance, and sign up at the door. Projector will be provided. For example, there will be a lightning talk about the next major release of Plone 4, and there will be some time to ask questions to a panel of experts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:00 - 5:30: &lt;b&gt;Drawing for prizes and socializing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 7:30: &lt;b&gt;Drinks and optional dinner at nearby watering hole&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sponsors:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Harvard School of Engineering and Applied Sciences for hosting this event, and thanks to Jazkarta for providing the excellent assortment of gourmet food. Thanks to Packt Publishing and O'Reilly for providing books to giveaway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions about the World Plone Day event, you can contact Nate Aune at (888) 756-6348 or natea (at) jazkarta (dot) com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free registration:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to register today!   &lt;a href="http://bostonworldploneday2010-plone.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonworldplo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;[1] About Plone:&lt;/b&gt; Plone is the leading Open Source Content Management System (CMS) freely available on the web today Since 2001 and worldwide, Plone has been enabling normal end users with no technical expertise to create and manage dynamic web sites. Corporations and non-profit entities using Plone and related technologies include Akamai Technologies, N.A.S.A., Oxfam America, Discover Magazine, Penn State University, Duke, Cornell, Harvard School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, and many others. Read more about Plone at &lt;a href="http://plone.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://plone.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;[2] About Boston Plone User Group:&lt;/b&gt; Since 2005, the Boston Plone User group has been organizing gatherings for Plone enthusiasts to come together to share experiences, ask questions and connect with others who are using and building Plone-based websites. The monthly meetings are free and open to the public. More information at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonplone/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;[3] About World Plone Day:&lt;/b&gt; The worldwide Plone community is staging World Plone Day 2010 – a series of events around the globe on April 28nd to spread awareness of the Plone CMS. This &amp;quot;follow the sun&amp;quot; event is a global initiative involving at least 29 countries around the world.  Plone integration companies, user groups and developers will hold seminars, training sessions, and meet-ups to show potential users the power of Plone technology and the many markets who are currently using it. Read more about World Plone Day at: &lt;a href="http://worldploneday.org"&gt;http://worldploneday....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sally Kleinfeldt</member_name><member_id>2175963</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272652530000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Plonista</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonplone</urlname><id>207992</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Plone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270041830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World Plone Day 2010</name><id>13046934</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272478500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonplone/events/13046934/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/8/global_14451368.jpeg</photo_url></item>