<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Charles Street Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.373840</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>My Home</name><city>Waltham</city><id>9754792</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.248917</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Alex is going to Foxwoods with the boys from work, so I feel the need to have a girl's night!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As many of you know I am a BeautiControl Consultant and a certified esthetician! I want to help you look and feel your best! Let's get ready for the holiday season together! Start by pampering yourself, and if you really get in the holiday spirit, you may find some great gift ideas along the way!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone who attends will get to try our fab line of skin care, get an amazing, nourishing hand treatment, and a wonderful lip treatment to help heal those dry, chapped lips that this chilly weather brings!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The evening will be based on our relaxation spa! On top of all the treatments mentioned above, each guest will also get to experience an amazing warming masque, soothing, nourishing eye pads, along with a guided relaxation session complete with aromatherapy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be giving away some of the incentives our hostesses have the chance to earn: a neckwrap, discounts, etc. **Bring a friend, and get an extra entry into the drawings for prizes!**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously, I will have some snacks and wine - Feel free to bring whatever you wish!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Please no kiddos! Tell Daddy that it’s Mommy’s night out, and come enjoy yourself!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah Dorris</member_name><member_id>11365855</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352517086000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351369125000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Feel Fab Friday!</name><id>88824912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352505600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/88824912/</event_url></item>