<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>350 Roberts Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.768691</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-289-7212</phone><name>Margaritas</name><city>east hartford</city><id>966812</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.621508</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Full Moon Margarita Madness &lt;br /&gt;Each Full Moon Margarita Madness runs from 4pm to 1am and is hosted by a Margaritas employee.  Throughout the event, the host promotes all participating businesses and organizations.  Businesses that contribute a grand prize are promoted in-house for the entire month leading up to the event as well as in any print or radio ads that run in the days leading up to the event.  The business and the grand prize are also promoted on every dinner check and all in-house flyers, handouts and posters.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The charity is encouraged to spread the word through their organization and network via newsletters, press releases and word of mouth. Representatives of the charity are often on hand during the evening to offer support, have fun and answer questions concerning their organization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Throughout the evening, many items are given away to the crowd. These items are donated by our distributors, local merchants and businesses as well as the charity itself. In return for their support, all businesses are promoted to a large audience throughout the event, and are placed on our prominently displayed &amp;quot;Donor Board.&amp;quot;  Participating businesses also have the satisfaction of being involved with a community effort to support a local charity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a truly unique, exciting event which benefits many wonderful, worthy causes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you know of any charitable organization that might benefit from our support, please feel free to contact the management of your local Margaritas and provide them with the charity's name, location and a contact name.  We will be happy to add them to our list.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Magarita's is fun I'll be at a  table in the bar.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206313474000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Margaritas is fun and you can win prizes!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</why><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203198497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fullmoon Madness</name><id>7344380</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206140400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/7344380/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/f/global_3242511.jpeg</photo_url></item>