<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Parallel Worlds, Parallel Lives&lt;/b&gt; will be our first group event at The Museum of Science and as it is something of a unique opportunity, please read all of the details before RSVP'ing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This BBC documentary will be be televised as part of the Nova series on PBS in November but at this special screening we will also get to hear Max Tegmark, Associate Professor, Department of Physics, MIT and Paula Apsell, Senior Executive Producer, NOVA, WGBH speak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Museum has allotted 15 tickets for our group. We will meet in the lobby at 6:30 and then we will go to the registration table and our group will be allowed admittance into the theater at 6:40, so we can sit together as a group. The theater will open to the public at 6:45 and the film starts at 7:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parallel Worlds, Parallel Lives&lt;/b&gt; follows Mark Oliver Everett, &lt;br /&gt;     lead singer of the cult band the EELS, on his quest to learn &lt;br /&gt;     about his father, Hugh Everett III, a physicist who gave birth &lt;br /&gt;    to one of science's most bizarre and influential theories. &lt;br /&gt;     Everett’s “many worlds” interpretation of quantum mechanics &lt;br /&gt;     predicts that parallel universes are constantly splitting off &lt;br /&gt;    from the one in which we all live. At first derided, Hugh &lt;br /&gt;    Everett’s theory has steadily gained traction among physicists &lt;br /&gt;     while Mark Everett has increasingly grown curious about his &lt;br /&gt;     emotionally distant father. In this intelligent and imaginative &lt;br /&gt;     film, the wry and charismatic Mark embarks on a journey back &lt;br /&gt;     into his father's life, meeting his old friends and colleagues, &lt;br /&gt;     and takes a crash course in the weird world of quantum &lt;br /&gt;    mechanics in order to understand his father's mind-blowing &lt;br /&gt;     theory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This happens to be a &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; event but please only RSVP if you are truly interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions for those of us who ride the T:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the M.B.T.A.'s Green Line subway to Science Park station. This will be the Green Line's Lechmere-bound &amp;quot;E&amp;quot; train. The Museum is diagonally across the street (O'Brien Highway), just over the Charles River Dam draw bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks so much to Andrea from the Museum of Science for inviting our group to this screening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a bright red Meet-up sign in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222213831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Parallel Worlds, Parallel Lives at Boston's Museum of Science</name><id>8819163</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224109800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8819163/</event_url></item>