<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>247 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395187</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617) 776-6896</phone><name>The Burren</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669350</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121796</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;*** ATTENTION: PLEASE READ THE NOTE ABOUT RSVPs BELOW ***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/5/6/event_207211062.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Join us at the Burren in Davis Square for the next Science by the Pint, as Dr. Gary Ruvkun and colleagues present A War Within Us: How Do Our Bodies Detect and Neutralize Microbial Assaults? Gary Ruvkun is a professor of genetics at Harvard Medical School, and heads up the &lt;a href="http://ccib.mgh.harvard.edu/ruvkun"&gt;Ruvkun Lab&lt;/a&gt; at MGH, which studies the genetic signaling pathways involved with metabolism, longevity, and detection of foreign microbes and substances in the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;For those who've never been, Science by the Pint is an event sponsored by an organization of Harvard graduate students called Science in the News.  In between their sleepless hours of hard work at Harvard Med School, they bring their cutting edge scientific research to the public in a fun and informal format.  The event goes like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The main speaker gives a &lt;strong&gt;short&lt;/strong&gt; 5-10 minute talk (&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; a full length lecture) about their research, then answers general questions from the audience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team of colleagues comes around to individual tables and spends one-on-one time answering questions over food and refreshments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of nerdy fun is had by all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Things officially start at 7:00, but arriving by 6:30 allows fellow nerds to find a place to sit together, order food and drinks, and be ready once things get going. Watch for greeters from the group, who will be wearing a Meetup sticker (see below if you're interested in greeting other members).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The Burren is located on Elm Street right in the heart of Davis Square, just a short walk from the Red Line stop.  If you prefer to drive, Davis Square is not known for its ample parking, but there are metered spots on the street and in nearby municipal lots (see link below).  Keep in mind that the meters are active until 8:00 PM. Municipal lot meters are good for three hours, and street spots are good for two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;ABOUT RSVPs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;First, this is a public event.  An RSVP is not required to attend. Anyone can walk into the Burren from off the street (including scientists/presenters, as they did last time) and check out what's going on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;What your RSVP does is this:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;It lets other Nerd Fun members and organizers know you'll be there, so they can look for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;It lets the Science in the News people know how many of us to expect, so they can plan on how many scientists they should drag away from their hard work to entertain us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;It helps your organizers work with the SITN people and the Burren staff to make this event as fun as possible for everyone &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;So &lt;em&gt;why is there a limit&lt;/em&gt;? It's because:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;The back room at the Burren seats about 75 people, and will allow for maybe 100+ with some standing or doubled up at tables&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;SITN's administrative staff estimates that about half of the SBTP attendees are from Meetup/Nerd Fun, with the other half coming from their own recruiting. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;They generally have about 6 presenters they can bring to these events, without jiggering their schedules at Harvard (which are pretty intensive, as you can well imagine). That means quality time with scientists for about 60 people (roughly those seated at the tables). &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;So this means... &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you RSVP YES and your plans change, please change your RSVP to NO, so we have an accurate list of who will be there&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you're on the waiting list, it just means that more staff will be needed to accommodate everyone who wants to go.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Some of the SITN staff are also members of Nerd Fun and are monitoring the event website for expected turnout (which BTW means they see the comments)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;.  You should keep an eye on your email in case you get bumped in (yes, we're going back to an automatic list).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;And of course remember that &lt;em&gt;everyone in the group is responsible for holding each other accountable for their RSVPs.&lt;/em&gt; People that say they're coming and then don't are taking up a spot that you could have. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;VOLUNTEERS NEEDED TO GREET PEOPLE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;No one likes to be a newcomer at an event where there are hundreds of strangers and they don't know who to approach.  But this is a huge event, and one person cannot possibly be the point of contact for everyone - especially when they're intermingled with other non-Meetup people. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;So we need volunteers who will be willing to greet people.  I'll have Meetup stickers on to hand for you to wear so folks can approach you. You'll be asked if you want to volunteer when you RSVP - you can indicate there if you're interested.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Let's have a great time, and hope to see you there :)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/science-by-the-pint/"&gt;SITN - Science by the Pint&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hms.harvard.edu/dms/BBS/fac/ruvkun.php"&gt;Gary Ruvkin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.burren.com/"&gt;The Burren&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.somervillema.gov/sites/default/files/documents/Davis%20Square%20Parking%20Map.pdf"&gt;Davis Square Parking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the back room starting at 6:30 (some of us may be at the bar in front beforehand)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363051886000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>59</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361459660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science by the Pint - How Our Bodies Detect and Neutralize Microbial Assaults</name><id>105682772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363041000000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/105682772/</event_url></item>