<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A reading to celebrate the launch of White Whale Review: an online journal of poetry, short fiction, and nonfiction. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Readers to include:&lt;br /&gt;GEORGE KALOGERIS teaches humanities and literature at Boston University and at Suffolk University in Boston, Massachusetts. He recently published a book of poems based on the notebooks of Albert Camus entitled Camus: Carnets (Pressed Wafer). His poems have appeared in Agni, Harvard Review, and Ploughshares.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUMITA CHAKRABORTY is the assistant poetry editor at AGNI Magazine, a Cambridge resident, and a graduate of Wellesley College. She writes poetry and critical nonfiction, and has studied with Lucie Brock-Broido, Dan Chiasson, Pankaj Mishra, and Frank Bidart. Most recently, a poem of hers appeared in BOXCAR Poetry Review.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DAN MURPHY began to speak when he was six years old, smoke when he was eight, drink when he was fourteen, and read when he was twenty-one. He has worked as a painter, carpenter, college English teacher, and a family therapist. He has published in numerous journals such as The Comstock Review, International Journal of Literature, Parnassus Literary Journal, Salmon Magazine, Soundings East and others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also featuring a short story by RACHEL COYE.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234049998000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233048852000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Launch Reading for White Whale Review</name><id>9610776</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233876600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/9610776/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/5/global_187765.jpeg</photo_url></item>