<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 North Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03303</zip><lat>43.287703</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Hampshire State House</name><city>Concord</city><id>1406437</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.604050</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is time for “We The People” to wake up and realize that we are about to lose everything! The current attack on our 2nd Amendment Rights by the Obama Administration is a precursor to total gun confiscation. The 2nd Amendment is the guarantor of our Constitution. Without it, we will have no Liberty. It is time for every New Hampshire citizen who values their Freedom and our Constitution to draw a line in granite, making it clear to our State and Federal Legislators who would dar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;e to violate their oath to uphold our Constitution. They have abandoned the Constitution for far too long and this lawless behavior cannot be allowed to continue. That is why Jerry DeLemus , Organizer of the Rochester 912 Project, and Jack Kimball, Chairman of the Granite State Patriots have teamed up and are sponsoring the “ Line in the Granite, 2nd Amendment Rally.” The rally will take place on Thursday, January 31st from Noon until 2:00 PM in front of the NH Statehouse in Concord, NH. This is a “Valley Forge” event and we will rally regardless of weather. Will you be there?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Todd Puterbaugh</member_name><member_id>4083337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359662426000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359601175000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Amendment Rally</name><id>102260662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359651600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/102260662/</event_url></item>