<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's June, and at our book club's hangout Chaibo, that means one thing. Gelato! Come and join us for an ice-creamy treat or enjoy a smoothy or iced latte or just some coffee and a sandwich as we discuss Toni Morrison's new book, &lt;em&gt;Home&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of the book by an Amazon reviewer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I read in a review that "Toni never puts language above story." I agree with that statement 100%, and the prioritizing of story is on full display in&lt;/em&gt; Home&lt;em&gt;. This is a short book, but very fertile. How can she pack so much, in so thin a volume. The themes she touches on, each could be a full novel on its' own. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Frank Money has returned from the Korean war, with a deep secret. He has covered this secret with mourning the lost of his two best friends, a "mourning..so thick it completely covered my shame." Frank and his sister Cee were close growing up, he four years older than her, acted as a big brother should. And his going off to war created a physical separation, but not a division of affection. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 So, after the war and despite his struggling with post traumatic stress and using alcohol to self heal and exorcise the war demons, when he hears his sister is in danger, he does not hesitate to make his way toward her and.... To say more would give away too much. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The use of Frank addressing not only the reader but the author as well was marvelous. This was done, a few times briefly to kind of comment on how the story was unfolding to illustrious effect. The language in this book is simply beautiful, and for some reason it doesn't feel unfinished, as most short novels do. And the ending is brought full circle back to the beginning, all this in under 150 pages. In fact, the reading guide at the end brings up so many good questions you will be astonished as to how one could create that many queries in a short book. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Can't think of a better way to spend a couple of hours. This may well be the best novel you read all year. You will be greatly rewarded for taking that time!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340933593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338559098000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Home by Toni Morrison</name><id>67263482</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340838000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/67263482/</event_url></item>