<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Reservation Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03037</zip><lat>43.104805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pawtuckaway State Park</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>632081</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.205055</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/7/d/event_23018013.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/0/6/event_23018406.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/0/7/event_23018407.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Here is 2 links to a trail map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.com/Maps/pawhiking.html"&gt;http://www.nhstateparks.com/Maps/pawhiking.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/PawtuckawayTrailMap_web.pdf"&gt;http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/PawtuckawayTrailMap_web.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that we are using a rear entrance to the park on Reservation Rd. off of Route 107 (Raymond Road) in Deerfield. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;We are not using the front entrance to the Park on Mountain Road off of Route 156 in Nottingham. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The 3 pictures show the start of Reservation Rd. The 3rd picture shows a mailbox across the street near Reservation Road (137 Raymond Road, Deerfield, NH).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One AMC trail guide describes the North Mountain Trail as the most scenic in the park. There are several drop offs in places on North Mountain if your dog is not "cliff smart". &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting off at number 12 on the map we will use the North Mountain Trail to hike along the ridge of North Mountain heading in a northerly direction. &amp;nbsp;At the south end of North Mountain there is a fairly steep section that is 0.3 miles in distance for an elevation gain of about 300 feet. &amp;nbsp;Then the traverse along the mountain ridge is much flatter even though there is some uphill and down hill. Having hiked 1.5 miles from the starting point we reach the summit for an elevation gain of 500 feet. Then from the summit we descend 600 ft over 1.2 miles. &amp;nbsp;At the northern end of North Mountain there are some steep downhill sections of trial lasting 0.4 miles. &amp;nbsp;Then at 10 we start heading south again each step getting us closer to the cars. On the way back we ascend 300 feet that is spread out over 2.7 miles as we use a small section of the Round Pond Road and North Mtn. Bypass Trail to return to the southern end of North Mtn. &amp;nbsp;Then at the southern end of North Mountain we &amp;nbsp;retrace the 0.5 mile route on the North Mtn. Trail down hill back to the starting point descending 100 feet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a photo of the hike route in the photo album with a comment on the hikes elevations gains and losses along the route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;You should&amp;nbsp;definitely bring some water along for your dog and some food and drink for yourself.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I thought considering the length of the hike we might try something for fun, a snack pot luck. &amp;nbsp;If you would like to, bring a snack to share with the group. &amp;nbsp;As I thought of this after a lot of you signed up for the hike already don't feel like you have to do this if you don't want to. &amp;nbsp;It could be something you make or buy depending on your inclination or how much time you want to spend doing it. &amp;nbsp;It could be any thing from say chips, brownies, cookies, muffins, bread, small boxes of raisins, or even something healthy. &amp;nbsp;If you choose to do it email me and I will post a list so people will know what is being brought so far without using any names of who is bringing what. &amp;nbsp;You might also want to bring some sort of container with you that you can store some of the goodies in while on the hike or take home with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Once you turn onto Reservation Road off of Route 107 proceed 1.8 miles at which point Reservation Rd intersects with North Mountain Trail.  Reservation Rd at this point is a dirt road. This is number 12 on the map.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320583515000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317958380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>N. Mountain - Pawtuckaway St. Park - 5 mile moderate loop hike - snack pot luck</name><id>36482672</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319896800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/36482672/</event_url></item>