<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Avery Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.352853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Sports Club LA</name><city>Boston</city><id>951253</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063453</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>True Red Sox Natives love to be outside during the longest days of our so short Boston summer.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one of the best parties and wine tastings of the year in Boston. I rarely miss it and it sells out every year. Three years ago it sold out in less than 2 days!  Purchase your ticket now as you have been warned.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is Summer Solstice: the date in late June marking the first official day of summer and the years longest day of sunlight. And then there is Summer Solstice: the much anticipated annual Boston Uncorked roofdeck wine soiree. Each celebrates the other. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Boston Uncorked for the Summer Solstice 6th Annual Roof Deck Wine Tasting at the Sports Club LA/Boston on Thursday, June 24 from 6:00-8:45 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The extensive list of great wines, hors d'oeuvres from Blu Restaurant, live jazz performed by Florencia Gonzales, balmy breezes, the sunset, rooftop views overlooking Boston Common and intriguing people creates an indescribable vibe. One must attend to experience it.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the event and the wines go to &lt;a href="http://www.bostonuncorked.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the event of inclement weather, the event will be held indoors at Blu Restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to attend you must purchase your tickets on line in advance. Yes RSVPs who have not purchased tickets before the event will be changed to no.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will meet on the roof deck.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.bostonuncorked.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fenway Frank&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277863070000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275926017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Uncorked Summer Solstice 6th Annual Roof Deck Wine Tasting at Sports Club</name><id>13724465</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277416800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/13724465/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/1/global_4236993.jpeg</photo_url></item>