<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>717784</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703319</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I've heard a number of good things about this movie.  Time to be confirmed once RAW posts them; most films are at 5:00pm and 7:00pm, I've chosen the later time since it's a summer Sunday and if the weather is good, who wants to be inside?  If more people would go on Monday, let me know and I'll move the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From their website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Twelve-year-old Koichi lives with his mother and retired grandparents in Kagoshima, in the southern region of Kyushu, Japan. His younger brother Ryunosuke lives with their father in Hakata, northern Kyushu. The brothers have been separated by their parents' divorce and Koichi's only wish is for his family to be reunited. When he learns that a new bullet train line will soon open, linking the two towns, he starts to believe that a miracle will take place the moment these new trains first pass each other at top speed. With help from the adults around him, Koichi sets out on a journey with a group of friends, each hoping to witness a miracle that will improve their difficult lives."   (Japan, 128 mins, Japanese with subtitles)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.realartways.org/cinema.htm#i-wish"&gt;http://www.realartways.org/cinema.htm#i-wish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the reviews for more information about the film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342448748000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338375982000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"I Wish" @ Real Art Ways</name><id>66914282</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342393200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/66914282/</event_url></item>