<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Neponset St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.298237</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greendale Mall</name><city>Worcester</city><id>669441</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802090</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join MARC and VegWorcester members in a peaceful protest against fur. Wearing the fur of dead animals is NOT fashionable and is rampant with cruelty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT: MARC Fur Protest, Worcester.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Massachusetts Animal Rights Coalition)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHEN: Saturday December 1st 2012, 1:00pm~2:30pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHERE:&lt;/strong&gt; Outside Greendale Mall, 7 Neponset Street, Worcester Meet on sidewalk at entrance to drive to the mall. This &lt;br /&gt;

 is a great location - thousands of people will see our signs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP:&lt;/strong&gt; RSVP/Info/Direction: rayshick@msn.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather dependent event. Check emails or call cell (978-257-7062) morning of event for weather-related notice. (If it's very cold we make break early. We will bring handwarmers/footwarmers, though.) Literature and banners also provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY: Farmed fur animals are kept in tiny, filthy cages and often go&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;insane. Fur bearing animals receive zero protections under the&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Humane Slaughter Act. They are killed by anal or vaginal&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;electrocution, stomping, having their necks broken, or poison&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;injected directly into their hearts to not spoil their fur. Animals&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;electrocuted through their genitals often convulse for two or more&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;minutes before succumbing to massive heart attack. Trapped animals suffer awful, slow deaths in body gripping traps. They often chew off their legs or other body parts in a failed attempt to escape. If still alive when traps are checked they are usually stomped or clubbed to death.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS/PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt; Greendale Mall is located off of I-190 (Exit 1) near the junction of I-190 and I-290 in Worcester, MA. You can park in the mall lot. We will be near the entrance - just look for us and our signs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Framingham/Boston, MA - Take Mass Pike (I-90) West to I-495 North. On I-495 take Exit 25B to I-290. Follow I-290 to Exit 19 (I-190) and take Exit 1, Goldstar Boulevard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Leominster, MA - Take Exit 1 (Route 12/West Boylston Street) on I-190 South. Stay straight to go onto West Boylston Street. Turn left onto Goldstar Boulevard. The mall is on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Worcester, MA - Take Exit 1 on I-190 (from I-290 take Exit 19 to I-190), or just follow Goldstar Boulevard to West Boylston &lt;br /&gt;

 Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From West of Worcester - Take the Pike to Exit 10. Take I-290 North to I-190 North. Take exit 1 toward Goldstar Blvd then stay to the right as if going to West Boylston St. Mall entrance is on the &lt;br /&gt;

 right.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Manda Rose</member_name><member_id>3673742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354390948000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354251800000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Fur Protest with MARC - Cancelled due to snow</name><id>93450362</id><duration>5400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354384800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/93450362/</event_url></item>