<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/4/1/event_48430561.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Show time is at 7, I will be at the theater by 6 and we will go in for seats at 6:30.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;I strongly advise that you buy tickets ahead of time for this movie with such a star cast I am sure it will be a popular choice this weekend.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you miss the group on the way in, catch us after.&amp;nbsp; We gather in the hallway, outside the theater we have watched the movie in to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out for drinks and munchies and more movie talk.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please bring cash if you are planning to go to the after event, it makes it easier for everyone.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Movie Details:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; November 4, 2011 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Universal Pictures &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt;Brett Ratner &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt;Adam Cooper, Bill Collage, Russell Gewirtz, Rawson Marshall Thurber, Ted Griffin, Leslie Dixon, Noah Baumbach, Jeff Nathanson &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt;Ben Stiller, Eddie Murphy, Matthew Broderick, T&amp;eacute;a Leoni, Gabourey Sidibe, Casey Affleck, Stephen Henderson, Judd Hirsch, Michael Pena, Alan Alda &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Comedy &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; Not Available &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.towerheist.net/" target="_blank"&gt;TowerHeist.net&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; Ben Stiller and Eddie Murphy lead an all-star cast in "Tower Heist," a comedy caper about working stiffs who seek revenge on the Wall Street swindler who stiffed them. After the workers at a luxury Central Park condominium discover the penthouse billionaire has stolen their retirement, they plot the ultimate revenge: a heist to reclaim what he took from them. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Queens native Josh Kovacs (Stiller) has managed one of the most luxurious and well-secured residences in New York City for more than a decade. Under his watchful eye, nothing goes undetected. In the swankiest unit atop Josh's building, Wall Street titan Arthur Shaw (Alan Alda) is under house arrest after being caught stealing two billion from his investors. The hardest hit among those he defrauded? The tower staffers whose pensions he was entrusted to manage. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

With only days before Arthur gets away with the perfect crime, Josh's crew turns to petty crook Slide (Murphy) to plan the nearly impossible...to steal what they are sure is hidden in Arthur's guarded condo. Though amateurs, these rookie thieves know the building better than anyone. Turns out they've been casing the place for years, they just didn't know it. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will snag a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If it is downstatirs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320595707000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313421381000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tower Heist (7PM Show)</name><id>29549501</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320530400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/29549501/</event_url></item>