<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>194 Cranberry Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.839191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-2526</phone><name>Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Carver</city><id>727813</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.691455</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Myles Standish State Forest Workshop &amp;ndash; Looking To the Future &amp;ndash; Infrastructure and Operations Tour and Workshop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;CARVER &amp;ndash; Everyone is invited to take part in the final Myles Standish State Forest (MSSF) Resource Management Plan (RMP) Workshop, &amp;ldquo;Looking to the Future: MSSF Infrastructure and Operations&amp;rdquo;, Saturday, Feb. 12, 2:00 p.m., at the MSSF Headquarters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Discussion leaders include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Peggy Baker, former Pilgrim Society Director and current member of the Plymouth 400th Committee; Randy Parker,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;President, Simes House Foundation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;; Captain John W. Rogers Jr., Plymouth Police Department;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Trooper Jeffrey Diotte, MA State Police;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Lt. Dean Belanger and Sgt. James Cullen, Massachusetts Environmental Police South Coastal Division;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 15px"&gt;and Melissa Guimont, Evelyn Strawn, and Sharl Heller, Friends of Myles Standish State Forest. Join the discussion. Bring your ideas for improving infrastructure, streamlining operations, or planning the future of MSSF.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior to the workshop, on Sat. Feb. 12 at 1 p.m., The Massachusetts Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR) Southeast Regional Director Brian Shanahan will conduct a tour of the facilities, highlighting the inner workings of forest maintenance and management. Meet Director Shanahan at the MSSF Headquarters&amp;rsquo; parking lot to begin the tour. The workshop will follow the tour at 2 p.m. at the MSSF Conference Building, across the street from the MSSF Headquarters. A &amp;ldquo;British style&amp;rdquo; tea will be served (tea, cocoa, cookies, crumpets, cream and jam). Children are welcome. The building is accessible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;For more information on the location of the tour or the workshop call MSSF headquarters at 508-866-2526.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The tour and the workshop are the final in a series of five workshops hosted by the Friends of MSSF and DCR to increase stakeholder input into the MSSF RMP. The RMP is critical to the future of the forest as the plan will guide planning and management of the forest for the next decade or more. If you care about the forest, now is the time to let DCR know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The DCR will continue to collect public comments on the MSSF RMP through February. Please send comments to Jim Baecker, Mass. Department of Conservation and Recreation Office of Regional Planning, 251 Causeway St., Suite 700, Boston, MA&amp;nbsp; 02114.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;For more information on the MSSF RMP, contact Jim Baecker at 617-626-1355,&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:jim.baecker@state.ma.us"&gt;jim.baecker@state.ma.us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;You may also visit the Friends of MSSF website at&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com/"&gt;www.friendsmssf.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, or the DCR Public Meetings Pages at&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/news/publicmeetings/rmppast.htm"&gt;www.mass.gov/dcr/news/publicmeetings/rmppast.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Brian Shanahan at the Headquarters parking lot at 1 PM.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharl</member_name><member_id>712534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301517905000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Please come. The DCR planners need to know you care about the forest. Plus, we have a great line-up of discussion leaders and "High Tea"! Come early, take a walk, join the tour, attend the workshop and have tea and crumpets with your friends.</why><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296734637000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Resource Management Plan Tour and Workshop- Infrastructure and Operations</name><id>16425817</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297533600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/16425817/</event_url></item>