<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Rosemont Ave</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04103</zip><lat>43.670372</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Dig-In/Plant-In Party Central</name><city>Portland</city><id>13716532</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.300537</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As part of their &lt;strong&gt;Great Rosemont Dig-In/Plant-In&lt;/strong&gt;, a group of your Rosemont Ave neighbors is offering &lt;strong&gt;35 fruit trees (apples, pears, plums and cherry) available at cost for adoption&lt;/strong&gt;, to help transform our yards into living edible landscapes. Any homeowner or renter with landlord’s permission can have up to three dwarf fruit trees to plant in your yard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why adopt a fruit tree?&lt;/strong&gt; Imagine the yards of our Rosemont homes as a living edible food forest that sustains us, gives us pleasure and a reason to be outside, or a reason to share food with our neighbor across the fence. Imagine the famous Rosemont Block Party including a Cider Press. Imagine paying less at the grocery check-out…increasing our local food resilience, increasing the value and desirability of the neighborhood…all the while reducing greenhouse gases, and oil dependency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the cost?&lt;/strong&gt; A $15 donation per tree will cover the cost of the tree, a bag of compost and delivery to your home. Any donations to this program beyond $15 are welcome and will be tax deductible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do we ask of you?&lt;/strong&gt; Fruit trees are a fun way of becoming involved in gardening. Adopting the tree includes proper planting, taking care of it, and agreeing to pick the fruit, or allow it to be picked by others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The trees can be viewed and reserved starting at 9AM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coffee/Tea/Muffins/Bagels will be available.  Mix with the Rosemont neighbors.  A planting demonstration will be given around 9:15AM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selling of the fruit trees will start at 9:30 AM when volunteers move out to plant in their yards.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not worry if the trees sell out early or if we don't have a specific tree.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;We will be collecting contact information for a similar, larger scale, systemic effort in Portland in October.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We also plan to provide education on pruning and fertilization as well as email reminders to the "hood", in collaboration with neighborhood partners.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;In addition, a Rosemont neighbor, Doug Malcom has expressed interest in forming a volunteer group to pick unused fruit in Portland, preserve it, and share it among owners and volunteers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are certainly many great ideas around!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Questions?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Contact Alastair at 521-6151 or email&lt;/span&gt; jlough1@maine.rr.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/4/event_241865252.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alastair</member_name><member_id>4963124</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370107034000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>TT'rs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>TI-Portland</urlname><id>1233823</id><group_lat>43.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2900009155</group_lon><name>Tohidu Transition - Portland Maine</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1369913537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>35 Fruit Trees for Adoption  ($15) Saturday June 1</name><id>121981582</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370093400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/TI-Portland/events/121981582/</event_url></item>