<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748050</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio (located on Trinity's campus)</name><city>Hartford</city><id>512896</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Written and directed by Marjane Satrapi and Vincent Paronnaud, based on the graphic novels by Marjane Satrapi. With the voices of: Chiara Mastroianni, Catherine Deneuve, Danielle Darrieux, Simon Abkarian.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In place of the usual ?girls night out,? we invite you to a mother, daughter, and grandmother movie that celebrates a young woman?s independence of thought, creativity and humor. Marjane Satrapi is an Iranian comic book artist - and now filmmaker - who uses animation to illustrate her coming of age, first under the corrupt Shah, followed by repressive mullahs. A natural rebel, Marjane is sent to live in Vienna, where her love for punk music can?t erase her longing for home. The daughter is voiced by Chiara Mastroianni, her mother is portrayed by Mastroianni?s real mother, Catherine Deneuve. As the grandmother, Danielle Darrieux (to quote A.O.Scott of the New York Times) ?...is a source of humor, advice and moral guidance, and an embodiment of the film?s no-nonsense feminism.? Academy Award® nomination, Best Animated Feature Film. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, visit the website.  &lt;a href="http://www.sonyclassics.com/persepolis/main.html" target="_blank"&gt;Persepolis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are several interesting reviews on the website.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film appeared on many critics' top ten lists of the best films of 2007.[7]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2nd - Stephen Hunter, The Washington Post &lt;br /&gt;3rd - Marc Savlov, The Austin Chronicle &lt;br /&gt;3rd - Marjorie Baumgarten, The Austin Chronicle &lt;br /&gt;4th - Claudia Puig, USA Today &lt;br /&gt;4th - Lisa Schwarzbaum, Entertainment Weekly &lt;br /&gt;4th - Mike Russell, The Oregonian &lt;br /&gt;4th - Stephanie Zacharek, Salon &lt;br /&gt;4th - Stephen Holden, The New York Times &lt;br /&gt;6th - Richard Corliss, TIME magazine &lt;br /&gt;7th - Ella Taylor, LA Weekly &lt;br /&gt;8th - Dana Stevens, Slate &lt;br /&gt;10th - Peter Rainer, The Christian Science Monitor&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Note:  Cinestudio is on the campus of Trinity.  

I'm not sure if I can make this one, so please make sure you look at the photos of other attendees and look for each other in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207696868000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>This movie has won several awards and made many top 10 lists for 2007.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207329843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PERSEPOLIS</name><id>7673375</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207523700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/7673375/</event_url></item>