<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 McCurdy Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06371</zip><lat>41.313089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Christ the King Church</name><city>Old Lyme</city><id>1251574</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.331333</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;   The NHC's very own Frank Martignetti, professional choral director and orchestra conductor, will be leading what promises to be an amazing performance this weekend! 82 singers and a 24-piece orchestra will play pieces including a rarely-heard epic written for the opening of the Kennedy Center. Please read his description below of the selected pieces and of the groups that will be performing them. Ticket information is available at &lt;a href="http://www.conbrio.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.conbrio.or...&lt;/a&gt;. I have seen Frank and his colleauges perform many times, and I can not recommend his shows highly enough, so I hope to see many of you there!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; My colleague Steve Bruce and I will be leading our auditioned community choirs, the Mystic River Chorale and the Con Brio Choral Society, as well the University of Bridgeport Chamber Singers, which I also direct (some 82 singers combined) and a 24-piece orchestra.  The concert includes music for double choir, including Bach's wonderful motet Singet dem Herrn ein neus Lied (Sing to the Lord a New Song), and the New England premiere of the NEW choral concert version of Leonard Bernstein's Mass.  This epic piece was written for the opening of the Kennedy Center in 1969, and has been hailed as &amp;quot;a moving, modern meditation on faith and doubt.&amp;quot;  It is not often performed (although a recording by the Baltimore Symphony was Grammy-nominated last year) due to its epic size and length.  This new concert version is a 35-minute reduction of the 2.5 hour work, for reduced performing forces.  We are proud to showcase the wonderful talents of Tiffany Jackson, soprano soloist, and Bill Sorensen, tenor soloist.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am very proud of this project and hope you can make it!&lt;br /&gt;A radio broadcast from Rhode Island classical radio regarding the performance can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;feed://classical959.podbean.com/feed/&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272398708000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271821416000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A very promising choral and orchestral performance</name><id>13244472</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272225600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/13244472/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>