<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Church St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374370</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>888-262-4386</phone><name>AMC Loews Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669120</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Don't talk to anyone. Don't touch anyone."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's have a discussion of some issues Anita raised. First we'll see the new thriller , Contagion.&amp;nbsp; Afterward we'll get go out for a drink and discuss the societal and ethical issues of a fast moving deadly epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Contagion is a "thriller centered on the threat posed by a deadly disease and an international team of doctors contracted by the CDC to deal with the outbreak."&amp;nbsp; Staring Matt Damon, Jude Law, Laurence Fishburne and Kate Winslet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the likelihood of a worldwide and deadly epidemic in the modern era?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How well would our interdependent societies continue to function when human contact is the deadly vector of a fast moving mutated virus?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : right"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will the impact be on civil liberties?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What can historical epidemics, such as the black plague, teach us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;"In 1918, the naturally-occurring H1N1 pandemic known as the Spanish Influenza pandemic killed up to 50 million people worldwide (about 3% of the world population). It is estimated that more than 25% of the world population was infected. This was before air travel, and it spread like rapid-fire. In his books The Hot Zone and The Cobra Event, Richard Preston describes outbreaks of deadly viruses -- the first about a true incident involving Ebola, and the second a fictionalized account of a bioterrorism attack that looks like the common cold but is really a version of Mad Cow disease. In the past ten years, fears of bioterrorism have been of major concern. Yet, the World Health Organization and scientists worldwide have been predicting that the most likely threat to civilization is a mutated virus that can't be stopped and that can travel around the world quickly due to our modern technologies. What are the chances? What aspects of human behavior would make such a situation worse? Better? Do we take such threats and worries seriously? Do you get a flu shot every year? Would you be willing to voluntarily quarantine yourself or your family? Let's watch the movie and think about deadly things we can't see...."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the lobby at 7pm, the showtime is 7:30pm. Discussion will be after the movie.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim B</member_name><member_id>1113365</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317821870000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316147349000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Contagion    ( movie &amp; discussion )</name><id>33765802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316818800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/33765802/</event_url></item>