<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;peace groups&amp;quot; conference March 27-29, 09 details to get involved for 9/11 truth. see info below to get involved and possibly have a 9/11 truth speaker attend in order to incorporate a fresh perspective on how to end the wars etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-mark WeAreChangeBoston.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medford&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AFSC, in association with Tufts University fs Peace and Justice Studies Program and other New England peace and justice organizations is in the process of organizing a New England Regional conference for the weekend of March 27-29.&amp;#8232;&amp;#8232;New Strategies for New Realities is a post-inauguration is being designed to help re-focus the movement for peace and social justice for our new era. Among those we anticipate serving as speakers are Noam Chomsky , Phyllis Bennis, Bill Fletcher, Zia Mian and others still to be invited..&amp;#8232;&amp;#8232;The conference will provide an opportunity for in depth exploration and campaign development for three priorities: U.S. foreign and military policies, the economic crisis, and energy and the environment. &amp;#8232;&amp;#8232;It will provide a venue for hundreds of activists from across New England to develop political and social change strategies, campaigns. And, it will allow us to build essential working relationships. Among topics to be examined will be the implications of the irreversible reduction of U.S. global power and influence – economic, military, and diplomatic; how we work for economic security and justice in our country fs worst economic crisis since the Great Depression, and the intersections of the economic, climate, energy and national security crises we face. The conference will feature stimulating panel discussions, thoughtful and challenging key note presentations and workshops centered around analysis and education, campaigns or specific constituencies. Whether you are just beginning to get involved in working for social change or have been involved for years or decades we at the AFSC would like to invite you to participate in this education and action oriented event at this critical time in our history. &amp;#8232;&amp;#8232;Save the date – March 27-29.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information or to get involved, contact Joseph Gerson at JGerson@afsc.org or Genevie Gold at GGold@afsc.org or phone: 617-661-6130.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238368466000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226696080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"peace groups" conference March 27-29, 09 details to get involved for 9/11 truth</name><id>9163937</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238194800000</time><rsvp_limit>439</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9163937/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>