<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Dartmouth St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.348477</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Back Bay Station</name><city>Boston</city><id>867318</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076669</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Not to be confused with South Boston, the &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/South_End" target="_blank"&gt;South End&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most vibrant neighborhoods in Boston. If you have visited it, you probably stopped by a wonderful restaurant, a funky boutique, maybe took in a show -- but there is a lot more to this neighborhood to see and explore.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The South End was Boston's first big landfill project designed to create terrain for new housing stock.  It's based on an English plan, with lovely parks and squares framed by rows of houses.  Some of the concept for this marvelous layout came from none other than Charles Bulfinch, the great architect of the MA State House.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will explore the original landmass of the South End,  what once constituted the &amp;quot;Neck&amp;quot; where British redoubts were positioned and William Dawes made his way out past their sentries on April 18, 1775.  &lt;br /&gt;In the 19th century, filling began and the waters of the South Bay gave way to new land for Boston. Envisioned as the finest of neighborhoods, we will see the remnants of the early 19th century grandeur that the best families created here.  Still one of the largest collections of Victorian architecture in the country, the latter parts of the 1800s brought a wonderful array of brick row houses in many different styles to the South End. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The South End eventually lost out to the Back Bay (in the race to be THE neighborhood) and it evolved into an area occupied by many different immigrant groups. Major institutions, like the Cathedral of the Holy Cross and Boston City Hospital, came into the area to cater to these new populations.  We will see those buildings and glimpse some vestiges of the former immigrant populations who called the South End home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not only is this tour full of wonderful buildings it offers the opportunity to discuss the sociological impact of the changing demographics of a neighborhood.  In the 1950s the South End was considered &amp;quot;Skid Row&amp;quot; with SROs and flop houses being the norm. As the 20th century progressed this neighborhood was transformed as a strong gay community created a niche for themselves in the fabric of the City.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As with many City neighborhoods there is the tension between long-term residents and those who have come more recently, who are accused of gentrification.  But everyone in the South End is living and trying to create community in an urban setting.  This tour poses questions about diversity and the dynamics of living together in a neighborhood that embraces that concept.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/South_End" target="_blank"&gt;South End tour&lt;/a&gt; costs $15 ($5 for &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot card holders&lt;/a&gt; -- see web site) and lasts 90 minutes.  It will start across from Back Bay station and end on Washington Street -- where many cafes, restaurants will cater to your post tour needs!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Boston By Foot badges, bags, hats and whatnot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen G</member_name><member_id>7594534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246474790000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233328746000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South End Tour</name><id>9634618</id><headcount>49</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240768800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/9634618/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/6/global_7122518.jpeg</photo_url></item>