<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are doing a lovely fall hike on Columbus Day weekend up the 3,165-ft. Mt. Monadnock to the bare rock summit. This is a hike becomes rather strenuous and difficult the higher we go. &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;This is not a beginner's hike!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are merging with Cheryl M's &lt;b&gt;Northern Central MA, Southern NH Walking/ Hiking Group&lt;/b&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group/calendar/14876369/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; ) for this hike. Up to 20 additional people will be going from her group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike starts at the Old Toll Road parking lot (southern parking area). It is located 2.9 miles beyond the entrance to the Headquarter's parking lot on Route 124, on the same side of the road. There may be a $4 fee for hiking per person. There are no facilities there (e.g. out house).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike through the woods on the Old Halfway House Trail to the White Arrow Trail to the summit. We will descend via the Dublin-Marlboro Trail to the Marlboro Trail, then turn onto the Marian Trail/ Mossy Brook Trail/ Cart Path, back onto the Old Halfway House Trail (or optional Old Toll Road, if really tired). The trail up is very rocky and has a lot of ledge with views. The Marlboro Trail is also bald rock with beautiful views. The Marian Trail/Mossy Brook Trail is more wooded and partially follows a mossy-banked, clear water, babbling stream. Time will be an estimated 5 and 1/2 hours. Be prepared for changes of temperature and strong winds on the summit (you will be wet from persperation so hypothermia is a concern).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No cotton is acceptable for this hike and sturdy hiking boots required. Hiking poles are advised. Please dress in layers and have a wind jacket. Bring plenty of water and some foods containing protein and carbohydrates. The wind at the summit is also very strong so the temperatures are much less at the summit, up to 15 degrees cooler than at the base. We will hike at a moderate pace with small breaks when folks need them. Once we are on the mountain, no facilities are available. Severe weather cancels this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pets are not permitted in the park or on the mountain. Please note that this law includes all trails and areas on Mount Monadnock. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It has been said that Mt. Monadnock is the second most hiked mountain in the world after Mt. Fuji in Japan. Whatever the case may be, if you look around the summit on a summer day, you'll see scores of kids and adults enjoying the fine views from this very popular peak. The top half of the mountain is characterized by big slabs and boulders of rock that are fun to climb over. There are many trails of varying levels of difficulty so there is something here for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Monadnock is the centerpiece of the 5,000 acre Monadnock State Park. There are 40 miles of hiking trails, a visitor center, a campground with 21 tent sites and 7 youth group sites, a camp store, bathrooms, and shower facilities. The park is open year-round although services are limited from November through April. Pets are not allowed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The word &amp;quot;monadnock&amp;quot; originally comes from the Abnacki Indian language meaning &amp;quot;mountain that stands alone.&amp;quot; Because Monadnock &amp;quot;stands alone&amp;quot;, views from the treeless summit stretch far into the distance into surrounding states like Vermont and Massachusetts. Boston and the White Mountains are visible on a clear day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Monadnock forms one end of the roughly 50-mile Monadnock-Sunapee Greenway Trail. It is also the terminus of the 117-mile Monadnock-Metacomet Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location/directions to approximate meetup location at parking lot at Old Toll Road gate (650 Mountain Rd./Rt. 124, Jaffrey, NH):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Jaffrey&amp;amp;state=NH&amp;amp;address=650+Mountain+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=03452-6031&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.83469&amp;amp;longitude=-72.113844&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Lat.=42.83469, Lon.=-72.113844)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Monadnock State Park:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Rt. 124 &lt;br /&gt;Jaffrey, NH 03452 &lt;br /&gt;(603) 532-8862&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhparks.state.nh.us/explore/state-parks/monadnock-state-park.aspx"&gt;http://www.nhparks.st...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhparks.state.nh.us/uploads/pdf/MonadnockHikingTrailsMap_All_2010.pdf"&gt;http://www.nhparks.st...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hiking safety and equipment for high peaks:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287082373000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285038980000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike up Mt. Monadnock in Jaffrey NH</name><id>14841165</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286632800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/14841165/</event_url></item>