<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Suppressed by China, this movie went on to win the best director award at Cannes and the Golden Hugo at Chicago, before being nominated at the Oscars in the foreign language category, over the official objections of the Chinese.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is a captivating melodrama set in 1920s China about a young and beautiful wife of a cruel and impotent landlord, and her affair with his nephew. Rita Kempley of Washington Post describes it &amp;quot;as sumptuously cinematic as it is woefully fatalistic, an Oedipal fable of an abusive husband, his luscious new bride and the adopted nephew who falls in love with her.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read the rest of her review &lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-srv/style/longterm/movies/videos/judounrkempley_a0a0f5.htm" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;And, the &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/070601.html" target="_blank"&gt;movie description&lt;/a&gt; from Brattle Theater's website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is on Friday, June 1 at the &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm" target="_blank"&gt;Brattle Theater&lt;/a&gt; in Harvard Square, and the show starts at 7:30pm. The movie was released in 1990 and is 95 minutes long (or short).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have seen quite a few movies of Zhang Yimou (and admire him as a director), and while his recent movies (Hero, House of Flying Daggers, Curse of the Golden Flower) have brought him much success, he is more critically acclaimed for his earlier movies (To Live, Ju Dou, Raise The Red Lantern, Shanghai Triad) with the beautiful Gong Li as his muse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom is holding a meetup on Sunday (June 3) for a Yimou double-feature. Since I have already seen &amp;quot;To Live&amp;quot;, and missed &amp;quot;Ju Dou&amp;quot; last time it was shown, I thought this would be a good opportunity to hold my first meetup and watch this movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the show is over, and we will head over to a local restaurant (TBA) for dinner and conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;-Amit&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180913965000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179888598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ju Dou - another Zhang Yimou movie at the Brattle</name><id>5808122</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180740600000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5808122/</event_url></item>