<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>567 Crawford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.557892</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 345-9580</phone><name>Fitchburg Municipal Airport</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>360080</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.754395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Astronaut Charlie Precourt is arriving at Fitchburg Airport Friday around noon.  He's flying in from Salt Lake City to appear as THE star attraction at an Aviation Day at the Boys &amp;amp; Girls Club in Leominster on Saturday April 24th.  A few members from FPA are staying home from Nantucket to host the aviation unit on Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd like as many of us as possible at Fitchburg Airport to greet Charlie when he arrives.  He grew up in Hudson, MA, has flown four missions and logged over 950 hours in space.  He's flying his Mooney M20KT (that's, um, a low-wing) and we can provide him a warm welcome when he arrives.  Bring your family, neighbors and friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event on Saturday at the Boys &amp;amp; Girls Club has been organized by the Groton-based non-profit One Giant Leap and will have displays, demos and discussions on Space (by guess who?), Rocketry and Aviation (that's us!).  Youngsters ages 5-15 will be there with their families.  And  of course, we'll have a Young Eagles booth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll have a laptop with flightaware in order to track hs flight, so we'll know when he's on the 45...&lt;br /&gt;See you there!  If an update is required I'll email all members who have responded yes or maybe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's Charlie's Bio.  Good reading and quite a guy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jsc.nasa.gov/Bios/htmlbios/precourt.html" target="_blank"&gt;Charlie Precourt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Terminal!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Louise Anderson</member_name><member_id>6714056</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272212330000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271709748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's welcome Charlie Precourt to KFIT!</name><id>13228365</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272038400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/13228365/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/2/5/global_14504085.jpeg</photo_url></item>