<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Kendall Square </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.367496</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>495181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;***PLEASE NOTE: This event has been postponed by one week. The new event date is December 9, 2010. The time is the same (6:30 p.m.). Please update your RSVPs, if necessary.***&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is my first event as assistant organizer for this group and what do I want to see? A French movie! With subtitles!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Claire Denis's &lt;i&gt;White Material&lt;/i&gt; stars Isabell Huppert and Christopher Lambert. Denis also directed &lt;i&gt;35 Shots of Rum&lt;/i&gt;, which is a favorite of mine. If you are already a fan of her work, you won't need much more encouragement, but here's what &lt;a href="http://www.ifcfilms.com/films/white-material" target="_blank"&gt;IFC Films&lt;/a&gt; has to say about her latest movie:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Master filmmaker Claire Denis returns with this evocative African-set film starring the electrifying Isabelle Huppert (THE PIANO TEACHER) as a woman fighting to save her family plantation, and way of life, in the face of rising civil unrest. Featured in the Venice, Toronto, New York and Los Angeles film festivals, WHITE MATERIAL is an extraordinarily visceral, potent and very personal rumination on a society turned upside down. In an unnamed African country in the throes of a volatile regime change, Maria Vial (Huppert) is trying to sustain the coffee plantation she runs with her ex-husband André (Christophe Lambert), but unknown to her, he has other plans. The country is tenuously under the control of a rebel militia whose leader (Isaach De Bankolé) is on the run. With the regular army preparing to regain control, French forces have moved out, warning the remaining white residents that they’re on their own if they stay behind. However, Maria refuses to be driven off the land, continuing to run the farm as the specter of impending tragedy looms.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for my bright red backpack (attached to moi!) at the top of the stairs, on the second floor balcony overlooking the lobby. I'll buy my ticket, then perch in this spot from 6:30 to 6:45. At that point, we'll move into the theater. The movie starts at 6:55: can't miss those previews!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, I'll head to the front of the auditorium to collect anyone who arrived late or missed me on the balcony. I'd like to go to the &lt;a href="http://www.thefriendlytoast.net" target="_blank"&gt;Friendly Toast&lt;/a&gt; for tea and conversation after the movie. Claire Denis's movies always inspire discussion. You will be able to eat a late dinner at the Friendly Toast, if you wish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the Kendall Square Cinema!&lt;br /&gt;Marianne&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See the event description. Look for my bright red backpack. I'll try to remember my Meetup sign, too.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825779000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291079593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Claire Denis's White Material</name><id>15589697</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291937400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/15589697/</event_url></item>