<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rte. 1A</address_2><address_1>275 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01969</zip><lat>42.720725</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Todd's Farm</name><city>Rowley</city><id>1025961</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870619</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As the saying goes 3 strikes and you are out. Seeing this will be the 3rd time I have scheduled this and the weather has NOT agreed w/the calendar.  I thought I would try it 1 more time and see if we can actually get this event a success it will be nice to walk around, enjoy the weather and see what everyone is selling! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Todd Farm Flea Market is open every Sunday from mid April (April 5, 2009) through late November (November 29, 2009). Peak months are May, September, and October. &lt;b&gt;Up to 240 flea market vendors&lt;/b&gt; can be found on any given week at Todd Farm. Merchandise varies from antique furniture, clocks, jewelery, recordings, and tools to fishing rods, golf accessories, honey products, cedar fencing, plants and flowers, vintage toys, etc. And the list goes on and on. It's the perfect New England way to spend some leisurely weekend time. We look forward to seeing you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Just take I-95 south to Exit 54. From there, you'll want to head east on 133, and then north at Route 1A for about one mile. Todd Farm will be on your right in Rowley. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is a pay as you go, there is plenty of free parking in the back of the farm, you will probably see the line of people trying to park, just follow them!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in front of the red house in the middle of the farm.  Please note we will only wait till 15 minutes past the meet up time, if you are running late please text/call me and I will let you know my phone #, and I we will wait for you.  If you don't have my cell phone just send me an email and I will give it to you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there and hope we are able to attend! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be out front of the red house in the middle of the farm.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251415609000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249125987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go to Todd's Farm</name><id>11007053</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250431200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/11007053/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/d/7/global_10030567.jpeg</photo_url></item>