<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What? You never saw any episodes of Monty Python's Flying Circus? We need to correct that! Come join Nerd Fun as we watch at the Brattle Theater in Harvard Square &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;And Now For Something Completely Different&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; this Saturday at 2:00 pm. We should get out at 3:30 pm. After we can grab coffee somewhere, and if you wish you can come with us to dinner and &amp;quot;Monty Python's The Holy Grail&amp;quot; at 7:00 pm. &lt;i&gt;Monty Python's Life of Brian&lt;/i&gt; is being shown around dinner time, but man can't live by Python alone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a good primer for you in case you have never seen this wacky British comedy troupe starring Graham Chapman, John Cleese, Terry Gilliam, Eric Idle, Terry Jones, and Michael Palin. According to Wikipedia: &amp;quot;The film, released in 1971, consists of 90 minutes of the best sketches seen in the first two series of the TV show. The sketches were remade on film without an audience, and were intended for an American audience which had not yet seen the series&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Some of the Sketches&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;* Dirty Hungarian Phrasebook&lt;br /&gt;* The &amp;quot;Dead Parrot&amp;quot; sketch&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;The Lumberjack Song&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Upperclass Twits&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Hell's Grannies&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Nudge Nudge&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting outside the lobby of the Brattle Theater by 1:30 pm. We can buy tickets and grab seats at 1:40 pm, preferrably somewhere in the second row. The screen is recessed, in the back of the stage. Tickets are $10.00. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel like coming to &lt;b&gt;Monty Python's Holy Grail&lt;/b&gt;? Sign up at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/11771861/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Python-a-Thon&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/091107.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As a celebration of the 40th anniversary of one of the greatest comedy troupes of all time, The Brattle is pleased to present our second PYTHON-A-THON! This Monty Python marathon features four of their comedic assaults on reality, plus to kick it all off we’re screening the not-official-but-might-aswell-be Python-icized, version of THE WIND IN THE WILLOWS. AND NOW FOR SOMETHING COMPLETELY DIFFERENT is the filmic version of many of their most memorable sketches from the immortal Monty Python’s Flying Circus. LIFE OF BRIAN is the blasphemously hilarious story of Brian, an unwilling and incompetent prophet during the time of Jesus. MEANING OF LIFE is an episodic film that explores, in a typically surreal fashion, the 'big questions' of life, death, sex, and 'wafer thin mints.' And, the crèmede-la-crème, a Quote-A-Long screening of MONTY PYTHON AND THE HOLY GRAIL brought to us by The Action Pack - the folks behind our recent 80s Singalong Prom!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The theatre entrance is on the left side of the building - look for our sidewalk poster case&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Take the MBTA Red Line to the Harvard Square stop. Use the Brattle Street exit through the bus way. When you reach the top of the stairs you will see Brattle Street ahead to the right. The Brattle Theatre is the second building on the left side of the street, next to Wainwright Bank and Eastern Mountain Sports&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258034575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257280550000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monty Python "And Now for Something Completely Different" @ Brattle Theater</name><id>11785211</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257620400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11785211/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/e/global_11631278.jpeg</photo_url></item>