<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Route 123)</address_2><address_1>14 Pond Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02061</zip><lat>42.174060</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-878-7878</phone><name>Strawberry Fair Restaurant</name><city>Norwell</city><id>201047</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.884870</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join 2012 Annual Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for our unprecedented 3rd visit to Strawberry Fair for Brunch! &amp;nbsp;This also will be our 1st Annual Members Only Event of 2012. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Strawberry Faire is so popular among our Group Members that we have dined here twice as a group, the Org Team met here once, and it was one of the top vote-getters in last Fall's Annual Members Survey Poll in terms of smaller venues for us to return to with our Annual Members. &amp;nbsp;If you are not yet an Annual Member please be sure to attend an event (Christina's will be your last opportunity, which is the week before this event on March 20th) and become an Annual Member for only $12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be dining out for Brunch at The Strawberry Fair Restaurant in Norwell on Saturday, March 31st. Located on Route 228, a few yards from Route 53 and less than a mile from Route 3 at Queen Anne's Corner, the Restaurant has grown from a store into a quaint 3-room restaurant appropriately decorated with strawberries. Strawberry Fair Restaurant offers a wide variety of food sure to please everyone's palate. Entrees range from $5-$12. For more information about The Strawberry Fair Restaurant please visit the website at www.thestrawberryfair.com.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meetup and get to know each other in a smaller group setting, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy. This will also be a great time to plan a future Dining Out event and have everyone involved in conversation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1st 2012 Annual Members Only Event: Brunch @ Strawberry Fair!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, March 31st @ 1pm&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strawberry Faire Restaurant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 14 Pond Street&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Route 228&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Norwell, MA 02061&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 781-878-7878&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.thestrawberryfair.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Please meet outside the door off the parking lot (the indoor waiting area is tiny). We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please Note&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;This restaurant does not accept reservations. We may have to wait up to 15-20 and possibly 30 minutes (in extreme circumstances). Incomplete parties may not be seated (but they may make an exception for one person). In addition to calling ahead, the Organizer plans to arrive 10-15 minutes early to get our name on the waitlist. We would appreciate having someone who can arrive a few minutes early to do so. If you will be more than 15 minutes late please call the restaurant or let us know in your RSVP Comments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. This event is for&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;2012 Annual Members Only. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;You MUST be a 2012 Annual Member PRIOR to this event in order to attend. &amp;nbsp;We have 3 events prior to this in March, thus 3 opportunities for you to become a 2012 Annual Member in order to attend this event. &amp;nbsp;Do not fret; there will be several more AMO events w/ the next one projected to be in May.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: None - Everyone in attendance is already an Annual Member&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: Minimum of 4 people by Tuesday, March 27th @ 6pm. &amp;nbsp;Maximum of 8. &amp;nbsp;(Event Maximum has been changed to 6 people for purposes of maintaining an accurate Wait List and will be changed back to 8 once we have more than 8 2012 Annual Members who have RSVPed for this event.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: None, this event is for 2012 Annual Members Only. &amp;nbsp;Not sure if you are a "2012 Annual Member?" &amp;nbsp;Simply check your Title (below your name). &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: 8pm on Friday, March 30th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event. &amp;nbsp;Also, this will be the number we call in and will determine our table seating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please bring cash.&lt;/em&gt; You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&amp;nbsp; This has been the SSDOMG's policy for over 5 years now and it helps avoid confusion when paying the bill. &amp;nbsp;Absolutely positively no credit card charges for the food. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; This event takes place rain, snow or shine.&amp;nbsp; In the case of an extreme weather forecast we will update this&amp;nbsp;information at least 24 hours prior to the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the Pages for more information about the SSDOMG's policies and procedures which help ensure a smoother, relaxed, fun&amp;nbsp;dining experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;From Rt 3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, take Exit 14 and head North on Rt 228 towards Hingham/Nantasket. Follow Rt 228 for 1/2 mile to the intersection with Rt 53. Just before you come to the intersection, you will see a Saab dealership on your left. Strawberry Fair is the very next business on your left; a light yellow building with white trim. The driveway is on the near side of the restaurant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Heading South on Route 53:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Driving through Hingham, heading towards Norwell, you will pass Asian C (Chinese/Asian restaurant), then a Firestone dealership (both will be on your right). The next traffic light is the intersection of Routes 53 and 228 - turn right onto Route 228 (Pond St.) As you turn onto Route 228, you will see a Chili's restaurant on your right. The next building (light yellow with white trim) on your right is Strawberry Fair. The driveway is on the far side of the restaurant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Heading North on Route 53:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Driving through Norwell, heading towards Hingham, you will pass a Taco Bell, then a Hannaford Supermarket on your left, followed by a Kentucky Fried Chicken restaurant on your right. The next traffic light is the intersection of Routes 53 and 228 - turn left onto Route 228 (Pond St.) As you turn onto Route 228, you will see a Chili's restaurant on your right. The next building (light yellow with white trim) on your right is Strawberry Fair. The driveway is on the far side of the restaurant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional Parking is available at the shopping plaza across the street.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the door nearest the parking lot or at our table after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1333326915000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329067552000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1st 2012 Annual Members Only Event: Brunch @ Strawberry Fair!</name><id>52058122</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333213200000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/52058122/</event_url></item>