<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>225.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I felt that last email was unclear and want to be clear this workshop costs 225.00 per person with a 100.00 deposit before March 31st. details below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Photographing the Fine Art Nude” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Workshop to be held on Saturday the 4th of April, 2009 from 9am to 5:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “This is a nude figure workshop for beginner through professional fine art photographers. We will be educating, playing with, and discussing “One Studio Light” techniques. We will be changing angles and using different modifiers on the lights to create a variety of lighting styles. We will explore the intensive or subtle use of the light in high or low contrast on a fine art nude palette. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When creating a dramatic fine art nude portrait, the decision of where to place the light, at what intensity and with what modifiers - all have a great impact on the mood the image will convey. Typically intense strong single light images are considered dramatic and convey a lot of contrast and tension. The photographers challenge during the workshop will be to explore these dramatic lighting alternatives. You will also learn about composition to optimize your imagery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Throughout the day we will also teach posing and communication with our models. Photographers will hear about how to find models, set expectations, and get answers to basic questions on dealing with models. Ultimately you will learn ways to become comfortable with the models and have the models be comfortable with you.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you should bring…&lt;br /&gt;35 mm or medium format camera&lt;br /&gt;Digital cameras only please.&lt;br /&gt;No Point and shoot cameras, these cameras do not synch with professional studio lighting.&lt;br /&gt;Flash (and extra batteries) with an adjustable head, which we may use to trigger the slaves on our studio lights, (not just the pop-up flash on the camera body)&lt;br /&gt;A lens hood for each lens you will be using to help eliminate flare.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pricing: Workshops are $225.00 per person&lt;br /&gt;Class size limited to 11 people and $100.00 non refundable deposit is required to hold your place.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We provide studio lighting, backdrops, model, makeup artist, assistant, and basic handout materials for your reference. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A $100.00 Deposit Payment to hold you place is required. – You can use paypal online or Can be made by check, money order, or cash and need to be received by March 31st, 2009. Checks should be made out to Scott Erb and sent to 380 Bridle Path, Worcester, MA 01604. Payments for the remainder of the workshop will be accepted the day of the Workshop. If Mailing a check please include your name, address, phone number and email address.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note that space for this workshop fills up fast - so please register as early as possible!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in the workshop models let me know and I can send you there information and MM numbers. Call or email me with any questions. donna@erbphoto.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see &lt;a href="http://www.theintimateportrait.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.theintimat...&lt;/a&gt; to view past workshop photos and information.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239485190000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234482504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fine Art Nude Lighting Workshop With Scott Erb</name><id>9731555</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238850000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9731555/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/b/2/global_7287506.jpeg</photo_url></item>