<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372578</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>5982742</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116348</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/b/2/event_159510642.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Attention all math nerds (and not-so-math nerds):  Join us at the Harvard Book Store for a lecture and book signing by Steven Strogatz, on his new book The Joy of X: A Guided Tour of Math, from One to Infinity.  Strogatz is an award winning math professor at Cornell University, and a regular contributor to the New York Times.  In his new book, he takes us on a fun journey through the mathematics of all kinds of things in the world around us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lecture starts at 7:00.  As usual for HBS events, it's best to get there as early as possible to get a good seat (sometimes these things are packed, and if you're late you may end up stuck in the aisles listening over the loudspeaker).  We'll get there around 6:15, and hang out in front until about 6:30 before we go in and grab seats. Afterwards, we'll head to Uno's for food, drinks and nerdy socializing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Harvard Book Store website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome world-class mathematician and regular contributor to the New York Times STEVEN STROGATZ for a discussion of his book The Joy of x: A Guided Tour of Math, from One to Infinity. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Strogatz hosts a delightful tour of the greatest ideas of math, revealing how it connects to literature, philosophy, law, medicine, art, business, even pop culture in ways we never imagined &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Did O.J. do it? How should you flip your mattress to get the maximum wear out of it? How does Google search the Internet? How many people should you date before settling down? Believe it or not, math plays a crucial role in answering all of these questions and more. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Math underpins everything in the cosmos, including us, yet too few of us understand this universal language well enough to revel in its wisdom, its beauty — and its joy. This deeply enlightening, vastly entertaining volume translates math in a way that is at once intelligible and thrilling. Each trenchant chapter of The Joy of x offers an “aha!” moment, starting with why numbers are so helpful, and progressing through the wondrous truths implicit in π, the Pythagorean theorem, irrational numbers, fat tails, even the rigors and surprising charms of calculus. Showing why he has won awards as a professor at Cornell and garnered extensive praise for his articles about math for the New York Times, Strogatz presumes of his readers only curiosity and common sense. And he rewards them with clear, ingenious, and often funny explanations of the most vital and exciting principles of his discipline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/event/steven_strogatz/"&gt;http://www.harvard.com/event/steven_strogatz/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside before the lecture, or look for us inside - we'll be wearing Meetup pins</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>34</waitlist_count><updated>1349486583000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347825390000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Steven Strogatz: The Joy of X - A Guided Tour of Math, from One to Infinity</name><id>82667632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349475300000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/82667632/</event_url></item>