<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizers - Monica Trust (978)877-1119 and Michael Blair (978)808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will be putting everyone on the waitlist and we will add people to the trip in September.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/strong&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;strong&gt;answer all questions that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip is meant for experienced hikers who have overnight backpacking experience and are conditioned for hiking many miles with a lot of elevation gain. Please do not sign up if you have never backpacked &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt; if you haven't hiked more than 12-14 miles per days. The plan is to backpack two days climbing eight 4000 footers. We will begin our trip at Hale Brook trailhead and hike 2.2 miles to the summit of Hale (4054 ft). We will head over to Zealand (4260 ft.) through some steep ups and downs ~5.5 miles. Be warned this part of the trip will be one of the more difficult. We will drop our packs at the junction of the Zealand spur trail and hike to Zealand Mountain. Then we will continue our trip over Mt. Guyot to the tentsite. We will stop at the Guyot tentsite unload and set up camp before going to the three Bonds. First we will summit Mt Bond (4698 ft), and then to Bondcliff (4265 ft.) and return to f West Bond (4540ft.) for a possible the first day. The first day will hike 16.2 miles with an elevation gain of 7233 ft. The book time for this hike 11 hours and 40 min, not including breaks and setting up our tents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The second day we will eat breakfast, pack up and hike 2.8 miles to South Twin (4902 ft.). We will then hike 2.6 miles roundtrip to North Twin (4761 ft.) and back to South Twin. We will hike 1.1 miles to Galehead hut, where we will drop our packs and hike 1 mile roundtrip to Galehead Mt. (4024 ft.) and then back to the hut. We will complete our trip by hiking out 4.8 miles out to the Gale River trailhead. Day two we will be hiking 12 miles with an elevation gain of 2304 ft. with a book time of 7 hours 9 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike provided they are experienced "hikers", well-behaved, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, and you have a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination. Be sure to indicate in your RSVP if you will be bringing a dog.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~1.5 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 28.2 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 7,537 feet&lt;/strong&gt; over the two days.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=43.93628735575264&amp;amp;lon=-71.40744209289551&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(noaa.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will finalize the details before the trip but be sure you have extra space in your backpack after you pack your gear. I will coordinate with everyone to make sure we have the necessary group gear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Moderate_Weather_Backpacking.pdf"&gt;Click for a list of required items needed for a cold weather backpacking trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://iles.meetup.com/492954/Cold_Weather_Backpacking.pdf"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click for an idea of the required group gear needed for a warm weather backpacking trip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;TENTS&lt;/span&gt;: This is not car camping – we won’t have unlimited space to set up our tents. Unless you will be using a one-person bivy sack or a one-person hammock you will need to share a tent with someone - use the comment section for this event to coordinate this among yourselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;WATER PURIFICATION &amp;amp; STORAGE&lt;/span&gt;: I have a water filter, a 10 liter &amp;amp; a 20 liter water buckets for bringing water back to camp, and a 10 liter water bag for storing clean water. We could use one more filter so let me know if you have one that you want to bring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;FOOD&lt;/span&gt;: Each person is responsible for his or her own food – you will need to carry it and cook it yourself. You will also need to bring a way to hang it (i.e. “Bear Bag”) or protect it (i.e. “Bear Canister”).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;STOVE &amp;amp; FUEL&lt;/span&gt;: We should bring at least two stoves and fuel. It would be good if we brought the same type so we could share fuel. I have two Jet Boils that I could bring and I have enough fuel canisters for the group. I also have a pot and a frying pan. Let me know if you have a stove that you want to bring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will finalize the details before the trip but be sure you have extra space in your backpack after you pack your gear. I will coordinate with everyone to make sure we have the necessary group gear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be meeting at the Gale River trailhead to car spot and then drive over to Hale Brook Trailhead.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;lick for&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=43.914150,-71.364632(Dicey's+Mill+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=43.91415,-71.364632&amp;amp;sspn=0.007404,0.019205&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFaYTngId6A-_-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=15"&gt;customizable driving directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;(google.com)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be driving a green or a white Toyota Highlander</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351096458000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343006610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Two-day Backpack Pemi Wilderness~ Eight 4k footers in the (Advanced level)</name><id>74473872</id><headcount>9</headcount><duration>120600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350730800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/74473872/</event_url></item>