<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Mandarin Conversation group Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Feel free to bring Snacks and Munchies, drinks or take out.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2nd Monday meetings to practice Mandarin conversation. Learners of all levels, and native speakers welcome! &lt;br /&gt;This is an opportunity to meet with other learners and practice whatever you'd like to work on. Bring any books or homework you would like to review, and ask a native speaker to help you with pronounciation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully we will try  translate and read a song or poem or something in Chinese with ping ying.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reece,  Adele and David.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--- &lt;br /&gt;------------ &lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: (a member says that Mapquest directions are confusing) &lt;br /&gt;BCNC is at 38 Ash St., off of Oak St. between Washington St. and Harrison Ave. &lt;br /&gt;Oak St. is between Kneeland St. and Marginal Way (alongside the Turnpike)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The closest T stop is Orange Line New England Medical Center. &lt;br /&gt;Walk toward the South End (away from Chinatown) on Washington St and take the first left onto Oak St. The entrance to the building is in Ash St., the first small street on the left. There's a sign for BCNC- Boston Chinatown Neighborhood Center. Sign in at the front desk and ask for the Meetup conversation group. &lt;br /&gt;Parking is limited in the area, due to the theater district, but sometimes you can find spaces on the surrounding blocks. There are pay lots on Kneeland and Tremont Streets. &lt;br /&gt;The phone number in case you get lost is 617-635-5129.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.bcnc.net....." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bcnc.net.....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adele</member_name><member_id>481803</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289263412000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281104740000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>gbcqpynpblb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289259000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/14339341/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/4/global_5967540.jpeg</photo_url></item>