<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Friend St</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364304</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The North Star</name><city>Boston</city><id>2542581</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060898</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Playing for Pups II! &lt;br /&gt;

Ultimate Freeze Dance Competition &lt;br /&gt;

To Benefit the Animal Rescue League of Boston&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North Star has once again agreed to host Playing for Pups to raise money for homeless animals in the Boston area! Playing for Pups II will delight your inner child with a combination of old school games into one mega awesome competition. Ultimate Freeze Dance is Freeze Dance meets Dance-A-Thon and dance floor boundaries are "hot lava". It is an ULTIMATE test of dance stamina, skills, and a will to win it! Dance attire is highly encouraged so dust of those leggings and get your flash dance on! The rules will be read before the competition which will begin promptly at 4pm. Check in starts at 3pm giving you plenty of time to grab a beverage and stretch it out before the madness commences .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information and tickets please check out our website at www.playing4pups.eventbrite.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All participants are eligible to win door prizes from Boloco, Zipcar, YardHouse, Social Boston Sports, and ARL! There will also be appetizer deals from North Star and of course lots of glow bracelets!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who wants to come dance for a cause? Get your day drink on and watch or play in what is surely to be a once in a lifetime competition. Did I mention first prize also gets a sweet trophy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers! &lt;br /&gt;

Jackie&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361661317000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360873695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ultimate Freeze Dance Competition?!</name><id>104633732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361649600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/104633732/</event_url></item>