<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday at 6B Martini Lounge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's Beacon Hill neighborhood. 6:30-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Afterwork mixer returns this Thursday February 21st. This time we are taking the party to 6B martini lounge in historic Beacon Hill! 6B lounge is one of the &amp;quot;hidden gems &amp;quot; among the Beacon nightlife scene and has been voted as having the best martinis in Boston! So what better way to come out this Thurs and have a few cocktails with the group as we gear up for a festive weekend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting details: The address of this venue is 6 BEACON ST near the state house and right across the street from the Federalist bar. If unsure of this location I highly recommend going online (google) to get a better idea for directions. Also check out the venue website for 6B at &lt;a href="http://www.6blounge.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.6blounge.c...&lt;/a&gt;   This will give you a better overall sense of the venue and provide pinpoint directions from your destination. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inside, we will meet at the bar area on the right hand side from the entrance. Please do not hesitate to call or text me upon arrival if you are having trouble finding the group. My picture is on the site under the Assistant Organizer section so I should not be hard to find. This place is packed on Thurs nites so I highly ENCOURAGE you to attend early as possible. My phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Line to Park St/Govt Center &lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to State St/Downtown Crossing &lt;br /&gt;Blue Line to State St/Govt Center &lt;br /&gt;Red Line to Park St/Downtown Crossing&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203809695000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><why>A great start to the weekend!!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203304643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thirsty Thursdays! Afterwork Mixer returns! 6B Lounge</name><id>7352580</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203636600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/7352580/</event_url></item>