<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Warwick</address_2><address_1>3376 Post Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02886</zip><lat>41.694550</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-736-8388</phone><name>The Remington House Inn</name><city>Warwick</city><id>600367</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.457170</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month's location will be The Remington House Inn in Warwick, Rhode Island.  I have heard this restaurant brought up in several conversations this month, so I thought we could give it a try.  Their menu seems fairly comprehensive, and very reasonably priced for the items they offer.  You can go to their website, &lt;a href="http://www.theremingtonhouseinn.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;The Remington House Inn&lt;/a&gt;, to view their menu and get directions.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have made a reservation for 15 people.  If the event is full and you are interested in attending, please RSVP No with a note to be wait listed.  I will do my best to accomidate people in the order they RSVP'd.   Please keep in mind that the new attendance policy will be in place, so please be sure to update your RSVP should your plans to attend change. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because it has seemed fairly successful overall, I think we are going to do the payment as we have the last few events.  There will be one check for food, divided equally by all members, then a second check for beverages, to be paid for by each member according to what they ordered.  This way we can order appetizers for the table for all to enjoy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has not attended previous events, please plan on bringing a dollar to help me defray the cost of posting on meetup. For everyone who has attended, I only ask that you contribute every other event. This would be such a big help to me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the one in my profile piccy with the red hair ;-)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217199762000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>We are a lot of fun and we have gotten to try some really great restaurants.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209490384000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Dine Out Group July Meetup- The Remington House Inn</name><id>7836193</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217026800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/7836193/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/f/7/global_4036343.jpeg</photo_url></item>