<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet at 10:00 in the parking lot of the Elsie Turner Field, there is a white sign for it on the north side of Trapelo Rd.  This baseball field/diamond is across the street from the Federal Archives building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A walk through a 240 acre parcel of land that will become an  MDC reservation and be aprt of the Western Greenway. Several miles of old carriage roads loop through a variety of habitats: cattail marshes, red maple swamps, mature oak-hickory forests, vernal pools, new forests, and open meadows. Because of the diverse ecosystems, this area is a good place to observe a variety of wildlife, including species of special concern: wood frogs and painted turtles. On the west side of the hospital at the end of Marguerite Avenue is West Meadow, a large &amp;quot;quaking&amp;quot; bog, which is criss-crossed with paths, enabling hikers to walk across what would otherwise be a dangerous trek.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Western Greenway is a swath of green space that stretches for six miles beginning in Belmont and Lexington, and looping through Waltham as far south as Beaver Street. For more information on the geenway go to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://walthamlandtrust.org/land/the-western-greenway/" target="_blank"&gt;http://walthamlandtru...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have a picnic lunch afterwards at the nearby Robert Treat Paine Estate (Stonehurst).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.stonehurstwaltham.org/info_s.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.stonehurst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Treat_Paine_Estate" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a dish of something to share with everyone.  If you have a cooler, put some ice in it to keep the food cool while we walk.  I have a cooler and will be able to store a couple of dishes from people who don't hacve coolers.  If its drizzling that day we walk and then have lunch somewhere on Moody St.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183990158000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179678715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Western Greenway walk &amp; pic-nic</name><id>5798514</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183816800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5798514/</event_url></item>