<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>604 Columbus Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.339771</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-536-6204</phone><name>Bob's Southern Bistro</name><city>Boston</city><id>427816</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082405</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**CHANGE IN PLANS: Please read the update message I sent out. The new arrival time is 8:45, per the restaurant's requirement that we all be seated together as a group at 9. We will meet outside, in front of the restaurant. If you are lost or running late, please call Tonya at (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost of this all-you-can-eat brunch is $24. 95. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because tomorrow is the restaurant's final day of operations, it's going to be a CIRCUS. Please allow yourself ample travel time, and be prepared for anything.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The brunch menu, as well as directions (both MBTA and driving) can be found on their website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bobssouthernbistro.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bobssouthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Say it isn't so! Boston's most beloved soul food/jazz brunch institution, Bob's Southern Bistro (formerly known as Bob the Chef's), is closing its doors in the South End forever. If you're not still full from your Thanksgiving feast just a few days earlier, and you'd like pay your last respects to this cultural icon, join us on its final day of operations, Sunday November 25th, on which they will go out with a bang with a New Orleans-style &amp;quot;Funeral&amp;quot; jazz brunch. Here's your last--or one and only!--chance to get your fill of their legendary &amp;quot;down home cookin'&amp;quot;, including macaroni &amp;amp; cheese, famous &amp;quot;Gloryfried&amp;quot; chicken, collard greens, and let's not forget the sweet potato pie! For more information, see this article from October 30th in the Boston Globe: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/news/local/articles/2007/10/30/bistro_" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston.com...&lt;/a&gt; ending_its_soulful_reign/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please be aware that for this particular event (because a credit card deposit had to be put down to secure our reservation at the restaurant), our attendance and cancellation policy will be strictly enforced. If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event or contacted our organizer, Tonya, by calling her at (617) 445-7549, it will be counted as if you NO-SHOWED three (3) times. Our standing policy is that if you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group. **&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196171528000</updated><rating><average>4.84999990463</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193950545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Farewell to Bob's Southern Bistro: New Orleans "Funeral" jazz brunch</name><id>6658028</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195998300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6658028/</event_url></item>