<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Downtown/Near Loring Theatre</address_2><address_1>19 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.241894</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-749-3999</phone><name>Nona's Homemade Ice Cream</name><city>Hingham</city><id>954773</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.888929</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join fellow members of the SSDOMG for a TGIF Ice Cream Social!  Who says you can't have dessert before dinner?  The SSDOMG certainly does not believe that!  We will be checking out this popular ice cream shop in Hingham Square, just a short distance from the Loring Hall Cinema.  Why not take a break on your commute home and join us?!  Arrive anytime between 6-6:30 and stay as long as you like.  For those who would like to continue socializing afterward, downtown Hingham is an appealing place to wander.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TGIF Ice Cream Social!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, May 15th, 2009 @ 6pm&lt;br /&gt;Nona's Homemade Ice Cream&lt;br /&gt;19 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-749-3999&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.nonashomemade.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nonashomem...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Angela and Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costs: Pay for your own ice cream.  Prices range from $2-7.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: None!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: No Maximum!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests:  None.  Members only for our first ice cream social of the season!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, May 15th @ 12pm/Noon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: TBD - Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on &amp;quot;weather&amp;quot;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions: From Route 3A heading south (coming from Weymouth):&lt;/b&gt; Follow Route 3A as it crosses the bridge at Broad Cove, turns right and begins running parallel to the water. Shortly before you reach the rotary, you will come to the intersection of Route 3A and North St. (Stars Diner is on your right). Turn right onto North St., driving past Tosca on your left as you start to head down North St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After just a short distance, you will see Saint Paul's Catholic Church on your right - At this point, turn left onto Main St. After just a few yards, go straight across South St., remaining on Main. Nona's is in the row of shops on your right, just after you cross South St. There are parking spaces along the street and on nearby streets within easy walking distance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3A heading north (coming from Cohasset):&lt;/b&gt; Follow Route 3A into Hingham. After about a mile, you will come to a rotary. Take the second right out of the rotary, remaining on Route 3A North.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn left at the next set of lights onto North St. (Stars Diner is on the far left), driving past Tosca on your left as you start to head down North St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After just a short distance, you will see Saint Paul's Catholic Church on your right - At this point, turn left onto Main St. After just a few yards, go straight across South St., remaining on Main. Nona's is in the row of shops on your right, just after you cross South St. There are parking spaces along the street and on nearby streets within easy walking distance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us out in front of Nona's, or inside if it's raining!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242774160000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241964266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TGIF Ice Cream Social!</name><id>10378705</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242424800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10378705/</event_url></item>