<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Wheaton College</address_2><address_1>Mary Lyon Building</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02766</zip><lat>41.970485</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Woolley Room</name><city>Norton</city><id>1193807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.168617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A talk at Wheaton College&lt;br /&gt;From ARI. I probably won't be there but please report back if you decide to go.&lt;br /&gt;---------------------&lt;br /&gt;Who: Andrew Bernstein, visiting professor of philosophy at Marist College; he also teaches at SUNY Purchase.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: A talk explaining why only laissez-faire capitalism on a global scale will solve the problem of world oppression and poverty. An open Q&amp;amp;A follows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Woolley Room, Mary Lyon Building, Wheaton College, Norton, Massachusetts 02766.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Monday, February 22, 2010, at 7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: The opponents of global capitalism overlook the key points in the debate. The capitalist nations of Europe, North America and Asia are by far the wealthiest societies in history—with per capita incomes in the range of at least $20,000–$30,000 annually. But capitalism is not merely the system of prosperity; fundamentally, it is the system of individual rights and freedom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Capitalist nations protect their citizens’ freedom of speech, of the press and of intellectual expression. Similarly, their citizens possess economic freedom, including the right to own property, to start their own businesses and to seek profit. By stark contrast, the pre-capitalist systems of history and the noncapitalist systems of the present are politically oppressive and economically destitute; their citizens have few or no rights and, consequently, little or no wealth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What deeper principles make possible the freedom and wealth enjoyed under capitalism—and are lacking in its political antipodes? How has capitalism already greatly enhanced the lives of millions of human beings in formerly impoverished Third World countries? What can the men of the free world do to further promote the spread of capitalism into the repressed nations of the globe? These are the questions Dr. Bernstein addresses in his talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: FREE. Open to students and the public. No RSVP required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Andrew Bernstein holds a Ph.D. in philosophy from the Graduate Center of the City University of New York. He is the author of The Capitalist Manifesto: The Historic, Economic and Philosophic Case for Laissez-Faire (University Press of America, 2005) and Objectivism in One Lesson: An Introduction to the Philosophy of Ayn Rand (Hamilton Books, 2008). His new book, Capitalism Unbound: The Incontestable Moral Case for Individual Rights is forthcoming from Hamilton Books in 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information: Please e-mail the host, the Wheaton College Objectivism Club, at ohara_steven@wheatonma.edu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: The above event is organized, hosted and sponsored by an individual campus club. Although ARI provides financial support, educational materials and speakers for eligible student clubs, campus clubs are organizations independent of ARI. ARI does not necessarily endorse the content of the lectures and sessions offered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope you will be able to attend.&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;The Ayn Rand Institute&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gavin Pitt</member_name><member_id>4194885</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267058517000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266458672000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Global Capitalism: The Solution to World Oppression and Poverty</name><id>12633770</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266885000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/12633770/</event_url></item>