<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for meetup expenses</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>**New Date:  September 18th**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month we will meet at *6:00* at Winnie's house in Freeport.  Tour first with potluck to follow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CARPOOL:  Meet at Marginal Way park-and-ride (across from Bally) at 5:30 to share rides to Freeport if desired. [I've opened a carpool thread on the message board so we know who will be meeting at the park-and-ride].&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winnie is in the process of designing her site for her online certification course and invites you all to Freeport to see the beginning stages and limitations inherent in a 'design retrofit'. Of interest is: her plans for re-designing her pre-existing garden into zones 1 &amp;amp; 2, fixing and winterizing her attached greenhouse (no work done yet) and beginning backyard beekeeping.  Since her design is not yet complete, ideas and suggestions will be very welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Winnie:&lt;br /&gt;Coming from the south: take exit 20 (Desert Road) off 295. Turn left at the intersection (crossing back over 295) and make the first right on to Hunter Road. Go ~ 2.75 miles. Look for a red house on the right, then 'Smith Lane', then my driveway( # 126). Come on up the driveway--there should be plenty of parking if we squeeze in tightly. Those who can stay the whole time should park to the left in front of the garage and those who need to leave early should pull straight up to the garden area and park single file along the split rail fence on the right leaving enough room between to get out.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190325808000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187176367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portland Maine Permaculture September Meetup</name><id>6183964</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190152800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/6183964/</event_url></item>