<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 302</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03812</zip><lat>44.147129</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Willey House Historic Site</name><city>Harts Location</city><id>2299651</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.365807</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mt Willey 4,285 feet. 2.5 miles to the summit from the Kendron Flume trail. We will meet at the Willey Home Site off 302 approximately two miles south of Crawford Notch. There is parking both at the log house and across the road. This hike will be in celebration of Carmen&amp;#146;s completion of her forty-eight! She saved the best for last as this is a relativity short hike in terms of miles, five miles round trip to allow plenty of time to celebrate. There is one particularly steep section at about the two mile mark and it is a difficult climb for .3 miles, but that section is enabled by ladders. At the conclusion of this hike we will hold a celebratory BBQ/party at Jeffrey&amp;#146;s house located approximately ten miles south of the trail head in North Conway. Everyone is welcome. Bring your own beverage and something to eat/ share with the rest of the group. Folding or portable chairs might come in handy also, but I have plenty of room. I am certain there will be plenty of food, beverages and music to go around. If anyone has any questions please contact me. Hope to see you out there. We will meet at the Willey House at nine a.m.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309702988000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308924166000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Willey &amp; Party to Celebrate Carmen's Completion of the 48!</name><id>23368551</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309698000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/23368551/</event_url></item>