<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1846 Daniel Webster Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03106</zip><lat>43.106396</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Heads Pond Hooksett</name><city>Hooksett</city><id>2686101</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449234</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Due to all the rain happening this week,on Saturday (today) and overnight the chance of slipping on wet steep trail sections at the hike for Lake Massabesic the ledges and beyond is to high and is being changed to Head Pond Rail Trail where the terrain most of the way is a nice flat wide trail where wet ground will be less likely to cause a slip and fall as there is relatively a much flatter slope in most places.  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The current Weather Channel forecast during the hike calls for a few showers, 30% chance of rain, temps 48-53 degrees F, winds 16-17 MPH.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This should be an easy hike for most people unless walking 5 miles is an issue for you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Head Pond Rail Trail in Hooksett is a flat, wide trail most of the way.   As this is a line hike most of the way (you come back the exact same way) on a easy to follow mostly straight trail any one getting  tired before we reach the turn around point can easily find their way back to the parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be aware that the third house down the trail has 2 vicious dogs with an electric fence but they can reach within 15 feet of the trail.  Fortunately that house is very near the start of the hike and won't take long to get past if the dogs are outside. Simply staying to the left on the trail with your dog should take care of that when you first pass that house.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The parking lot for Head Pond Rail Trail is opposite Green's Marine at the intersection of the Danial Webster Highway and Post Road.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369610075000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365910959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lake Massabesic Trails becomes Head Pond Rail Trail - 5 Mile- Easy Hike</name><id>114239322</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369576800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/114239322/</event_url></item>