<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Norfolk Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02124</zip><lat>42.289944</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Condman Square Great Hall</name><city>Dorchester</city><id>11637032</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071968</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/7/0/event_202884432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us on Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/264942180303850/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/264942180303850/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Join Boston Collaborative for Food and Fitness for a weekend of seafood at the winter farmers markets. Celebrate the Fruits of our Ocean, a year-long campaign promoting local seafood in the community. Both winter markets now offer fresh seafood from local dayboat fishermen procured by Red’s Best, a Boston based seafood distributor that offers seasonal dayboat and traceable seafood direct to consumers at farmers markets and as well as wholesalers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Dorchester Winter Farmers’ Market will feature local Chef Karen Henry Garrett of Dot 2 Dot Café and Chef Ananda Pokhrel of Shanti Taste of India&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;will prepare local seafood dishes based on the local catch of the day and fresh ingredients from vendors of the market.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Tastings will be available for pre-registered participants.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/6/8/event_202889032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While many market goers already trek to a variety of markets around the city to stock up on fresh vegetables, meats, eggs and cheeses, they can now shop for seafood from local New England fisheries all season long. This campaign is an educational platform to help the public understand what sustainable fishing means and why it is so important to our community and our ocean. Embracing the diversity of species caught by the local, dayboat, independent fishing boats is even more important now as fishing for the traditionally popular species is curtailed even further.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Boston Collaborative for Food and Fitness and its partners are striving to educate the community about the health benefits of seafood, what sustainable seafood is really all about, and the importance of supporting the community based fisheries, how to prepare, store and utilize the entire fish in their recipes, while encouraging people to explore the vast diversity of seafood in the Atlantic Ocean.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;care, government, public health, youth development and more. BCFF has partnered with The Northwest Atlantic Marine Alliance and Health Care Without Harm as they strive to improve the community health in similar ways. Through this collaboration, BCFF, NAMA and HCWH are raising awareness about the health benefits of seafood. The promotion of the responsible fishing practices will ensure the sustainability of New England seafood for generations to come.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicola Williams</member_name><member_id>9817670</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361131715000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360380761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate the Fruits of our Ocean-Sustainable Seafood Event in Dorchester</name><id>103770882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361120400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/103770882/</event_url></item>