<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Intersection of 133 and 1A</address_2><address_1>26 Main St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01969</zip><lat>42.707548</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stephanie's Village Pancake House</name><city>Rowley</city><id>862761</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.881822</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It’s that time of the year again to go to a great place for breakfast at Stephanie's Village pancake house!&lt;br /&gt;Stephanie's Village Pancake house has a great menu, with a variety of different breakfast items, something for everyone, great waffles and omelettes, they also have a huge special's board remember to check it out you may just find something you never thought of on it. Let’s hope they will still be serving their delicious pumpkin pancakes! You can check the site for directions and to check out the menu at www.villagepancakehouse.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one of our popular location/events and we always have a great time.  This event will fill up fast.  We may not be seated at exactly 10:15 seeing they don’t hold rooms for the big parties; we will have to wait for the amount of tables to be open for all of us, if that doesn’t work for you then please take that into consideration when you are responding for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; With this event there are a few important things to remember:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Please show up 10 minutes early, we will not be seated until we are all there.&lt;br /&gt;-If you RSVP for this event and you are a no-show for past events we have the right to remove you from this event.&lt;br /&gt;-They will NOT be able to do separate check for anyone in the group, unless they put us at separate tables then each table will get a check.  &lt;br /&gt;-Remember to bring cash and some small bills so when you are paying your portion of the check including tax and tip it is easier for the organizer’s to figure out the money you owe.&lt;br /&gt;-We ask that you don't leave until the check is figured out.&lt;br /&gt;-Only RSVP if you are definitely attending it wouldn’t be fair to someone else in the group for you to take a spot and not use it. &lt;br /&gt;-Depending on the amount of RSVP's and how they set us up, you may be sitting at a table with members that you may not know (yet), if you are uncomfortable then this event may not be for you, please take this into consideration when you respond to this event. &lt;br /&gt;-This event will be posted on 3 Meetup sites, please ONLY put your response on one of the sites.  We have the right to change your RSVP if you have responded on two sites!&lt;br /&gt;- If your plans change then please update your reservation as early as you are able to.&lt;br /&gt;-We will only wait until 10:15 for you to show up for this event, after that we will be sitting down and I will take the count and give it to the hostess.&lt;br /&gt;-Depending on how many people sign up for this event from this site we may add more people that can attend, we will be watching the waiting list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for all the important details on this event, but this will be the 5th time we have been to this restaurant and we just want everyone to enjoy a great breakfast, it to go as smoothly as possible and everyone to have a great time, be careful there may even be a test at breakfast! lol kidding?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is a warm day we will meet under the awning to the right as you walk in the door where they usually have free hot coffee.  If we are not there then we will be inside the doors to the left under the special’s board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;November 1-Dec 11 we will be collecting donations for the Lazarus House in Lawrence.  If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to having a great breakfast with you! &lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will either be under the awning or as you come in the door to the left.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289868736000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286754438000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast anyone?</name><id>15066200</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289746800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/15066200/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/c/global_12428716.jpeg</photo_url></item>