<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>87 Perkins Row</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01983</zip><lat>42.631830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-887-9264</phone><name>Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Topsfield</city><id>669386</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.925970</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>4.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We did this hike last January and everyone enjoyed it, even though we were wearing yaktrax on our boots and dressed for mid winter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary is Mass Audubon's largest sanctuary with over 10 miles of trails spread across 2265 acres. Over 8 miles of the Ipswich River run through the sanctuary, winding around the edge of the property. The wetlands around the river are home to many birds and wetland creatures such as otters and painted turtles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Much of the sanctuary rises above the wetlands situated on a drumlin where almost all of the trails are located. Wooden boardwalks cross the wetlands in several places giving excellent viewing areas. An observation tower and gazebo along the edge of the wetlands give more wildlife viewing possibilities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Rockery is a man-made rock garden constructed from large boulders. A variety of plants fills the spaces between the boulders. Tunnels and trails were built into, around, and on the Rockery - it even has chairs fashioned from the careful placement of boulders. The Rockery overlooks a small pond, and was once part of an arboretum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Features&lt;br /&gt;Wildlife, birds, reptiles, wooden boardwalks crossing wetlands, observation tower, gazebo, canoe rentals, stone bridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;There is an admission charge of $4 for the sanctuary payed at the Audubon office.  No dogs are allowed in the sanctuary. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have to look into a good place in the area for lunch, any suggestions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Boston and the south: Take Rt I-95 north to exit 50 and follow Rt 1 north. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97, turn right onto Rt 97 south (toward Beverly and Danvers). Follow Rt 97 south and take the third left onto Perkins Row. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north: Take Rt I-95 south to exit 53A and follow Rt 97 south. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97 in Topsfield, stay on Rt 97 south and take the third left onto Perkins Row. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the parking lot in my green Toyota 4Runner (I hope).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>12</waitlist_count><updated>1259462763000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257825043000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary walk, Topsfield</name><id>11838800</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258815600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/11838800/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/3/global_7735123.jpeg</photo_url></item>