<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>21 Oakridge Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06371</zip><lat>41.303398</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Four Mile River, Boat Launch to ocean</name><city>Old Lyme</city><id>712089</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.255570</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WEATHER: Saturday: Sunny, with a high near 78. Calm wind becoming south between 5 and 8 mph. &lt;br /&gt;SAT&lt;br /&gt; E WINDS AROUND 5 KT...BECOMING SE IN THE AFTERNOON. SEAS 1 FT&lt;br /&gt; OR LESS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh you are not Goober recreational kayakers..or novices annymore, RIGHT ???&lt;br /&gt;Entering and exiting your kayaks, ESPECIALLY if you are using my kayaks,&lt;br /&gt;please approach shore in a parallel fashion and use the paddle to stabilize your exit and avoid stepping on the floor of your yak. (make like getting on a horse (no water gets on the seat) then place paddle at back of cockpit long end toward point of lean, grip paddle in a way that it marries to boat, then  plop azz into seat, you have control of the boat now and to take off shoes, etc.&lt;br /&gt;You should know how to do this for safety and improved kayak skills in sea conditions and learn to modify this method.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can tell a novice paddler by the way they drive up on shore (or get in or out and grinding the bottom of them cheap things) and how they step on the floor of their yaks. If you had a Carbon 18 footer that just cost you about 4, 000 bucks, you might put a hole in the bottom, and also turn the yak into junk in a short time, would you want that ?&lt;br /&gt;Well you should learn the technique just in case you buy a 1,500-2,500 dollar yak and not have junk in a short time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have spent way too much money on the kayaks, and have to spend time and money repairing the gel coat on the bottoms of my fiberglass kayaks, and am not going to buy new plastic kayaks either because of premature bottom leaks from abrasion spots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN, WIND OVER 10 MPH AND SEAS 1-2 FEET IS MY SET MAX LIMIT  FOR REC &amp;amp; SEA YAKS ON OUR KIND OF TRIPS AND WILL CANCEL THE EVENT IF IT LOOKS LIKE IT WONT BE ENJOYABLE, PLEASE CHECK BACK CLOSER TO THE EVENT, AND THE LAST CALL OF CANCEL WILL BE BY 10 AM ON EVENT DAY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please have some safety gear... one of which should be a whistle, this is really something cheap and lets those know you are in trouble.. MOST OF US HAVE PUMPS, PADDLE FLOATS, PADDLE LEASHES AND STUFF, so there is enough of us to help you if you dont..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh i found out there is a kayak outfit in the area that holds tours in the areas we have gone..&lt;br /&gt;this is good for those not able to join us..&lt;br /&gt;But they have maps of the good areas.. good..&lt;br /&gt;Print the page... this is sort of the same route the ConnYak people do also, but not up to the end of the cove, we will modify the route as necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;check out the PADDLe ROUTE map: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctcoastalkayaking.com/files/pattagansetttourmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctcoastalkayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa  23     High   3:39 AM     3.3   6:07 AM     Set  1:51 PM      62&lt;br /&gt;    23      Low   9:45 AM     0.7   7:36 PM    Rise 10:59 PM&lt;br /&gt;    23     High   4:15 PM     4.5&lt;br /&gt;    23      Low  10:55 PM     0.4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a beach lunch, &lt;br /&gt;I thought go left, cut across the beach to some rocks and a cove, we can eat in the vicinity of the cove or better yet right on the outer bounds of the beach. We choose as we need..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The barbie q can be done later after the trip at our past spot of 7 Falls Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions will be printed with map at the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There..&lt;br /&gt;If you are in meetup, really you should get a GPS..LOL&lt;br /&gt;apx address#  20 Oakridge Drive, Old Lyme CT for boat launch signs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;take I 91 south to rte 9 south,&lt;br /&gt;go to end and take left onto I 95 North, go 2 exits&lt;br /&gt;take exit # 71 = 4 Mile River Road&lt;br /&gt;At end of exit take left, this is 4 Mile River Road going SOUTH to the shore.. (unless they moved the exit)..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay on 4 Mile River Road for apx 0.7 miles.&lt;br /&gt;You will meet rte 156 = Shore Road,&lt;br /&gt;Take the right onto Shore Road heading South.&lt;br /&gt;in apx 0.6 miles look left for OAKRIDGE DRIVE.&lt;br /&gt;TAKE THE LEFT ONTO OAKRIDGE DRIVE&lt;br /&gt;go about half way around the circle, look for the boat launch sign and a road off to the right going to the river..go to end and unload then go back to parking lot..walk back to water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I get there as fast as i can..BUT THIS IS BEACH TIME AND BEACH TRAFFIC IN MIDDLETOWN AND TO ROCKY NECK. so we will expect some delays from other members also..but by 12:45 or so, we go..cant wait much longer than that..LOL....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:    ALL KAYAKS ARE NOW RESERVED.&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics on maybe 1 to 2 or so foot waves..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub= Pungo 12' with floataion bags installed= KATHY`g&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= AL-r&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna Snake= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = JANICE&lt;br /&gt;The Red Wild Dancer= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= BILL&lt;br /&gt;The Red Flat Boat= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= ALEX&lt;br /&gt; Lisa's Necky is already loaded too.. no more room available on trailer for this trip/distance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 10 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used. &lt;br /&gt;Oh i dont rent to maybees.&lt;br /&gt;i cant leave the expensive yaks on the trailer.&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Blue Toyota Avalon with Kayak trailer and Orange cone on roof.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222131937000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219073093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Recreational &amp; Sea Kayaks--Four Mile River to the Ocean Islands, Lunch on beach</name><id>8568710</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219507200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8568710/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/global_5044522.jpeg</photo_url></item>