<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/4/event_71522692.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;January has the same theme every year. This is the month we started our group five years ago, and the theme is a tradition. Comfort Food is something every one understands but it is different for every culture and region. Bring your comfort food to share. Start the new year off with good friends, good comforting food. The rest of the year will follow in-kind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVPs open 30 days prior to the event and these dinners fill up quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember there are no rules. Caryl will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plan to cook on site,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>please park on the lawn or in driveway next to my house or at my house if possible.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>8</waitlist_count><updated>1361755977000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358217930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comfort Food #5 redux</name><id>99651152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361577600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/99651152/</event_url></item>