<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Chime in&amp;quot; from 8 - 9 pm on the Phone&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note: This is a long distance call; not toll-free. &lt;br /&gt;** Phone # &amp;amp; worksheet will be sent to you after you RSVP : YES&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******************************************************** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ann Ide, BostonLOA member and New Possibilities Life Coach,&lt;/b&gt; led us in a &lt;b&gt;guided meditation of Abundance &amp;amp; Prosperity&lt;/b&gt; at our celebration on 12/7.  It was a great way to wrap up 2009 and &amp;quot;step into&amp;quot; the New Year, &lt;i&gt;being thankful of our abundance, big and small.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our desire is to provide you folks who were not at our celebration an opportunity to experience this guided meditation.  How fortunate are we that Ann said YES to our request.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, for folks who were at the celebration, come join us.  Ann will also guide everybody with a more in-depth discussion of how to align this guided meditation with &lt;b&gt;a Mindset of Dreaming BIG&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're also welcome to bring any questions you might have.  Ann says she is delighted to &amp;quot;mastermind&amp;quot; with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;We want to thank Ann for her gift of love, time and availability for us during this joyful season.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*******************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Ann Ide:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;www.NewPossibilitiesCoaching.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann is a certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming (NLP) and Hypnotherapy, and a certified NLP Life Coach with over 15 years experience. She has trained and consulted people nationally. Her passion is helping people move beyond suffering and mere survival, and creating “New Possibilities” in their lives for greater harmony, happiness and success. She provides personal and group coaching, guided meditations, and business workshops.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262383468000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260597028000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TELE-Meetup: Abundance Guided Meditation &amp; Dreamin' Big with Ann Ide</name><id>12069517</id><headcount>36</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261098000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/12069517/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/a/global_10628618.jpeg</photo_url></item>