<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet at 10:00  launching at10:30. &lt;br /&gt;Trip organizer: Mark Roberts 401-533-1883 Cell email:  hrmmark@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;Flo and Laura will co leading this trip as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Changes and cancellations to trips will be posted on the flatwater message board. Please check the board before leaving for any trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bungay River is part of the Ten Mile River Water Shed. Heading north (against the current, which is all but non-existent), a large part of this river is flanked on both sides by about a half mile of protected open space. It is considered the best Southern Red Maple Swamp around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Painted turtles, gray herons, mallard ducks, swans and geese nesting and multiple other species of bird live here. This river twists and turns making for a very fun but relaxing paddle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the first mile or so you can't hear any of the hustle and bustle of the surrounding small city. For those who like to fish, this river also feeds the local fish hatchery, which leads to some good modest stock trout fishing in the springtime. There is one take-out up the river. After about 30 minutes of good paddling there is a little path that leads to a little makeshift campsite. While camping isn't allowed it makes a good stop for a mid day snack and stretch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The further you go down the more technical it gets. There is no possibility of portage, but with some good paddling you can usually get pretty far along. The river then spreads into about a mile of marshland, which is mostly impassable. But when the water is high you can paddle around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;GPS Coordinates: N 41 57 228  W071 16 822 GPS Address: 102 Holden St, Attleboro MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On I-95 take exit 5 (rt 152). Take a left off the exit and bear right. Your on 152 now. Go about 3/4 of a mile and on your left you'll see a sign for Holden street. Take that left. The put-in is 1/4 mile down on the left. Just before you come to the bridge crossing the river there is a state canoe launch and a parking area on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our trip organizers provide directions as a courtesy to paddlers however, you are responsible to refer to a map and familiarize yourself with the trip location.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280660792000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279104792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bungay River, Attleboro MA</name><id>14098384</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280584800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/14098384/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/c/global_16422572.jpeg</photo_url></item>