<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>161 Essex St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.521828</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-745-9500</phone><name>Peabody Essex Museum</name><city>Salem</city><id>669327</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.892640</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The museum opens at 10 a.m. and the Festival starts at 11 a.m. I may try to get there at 10 a.m. because all the exhibits look interesting. I will wear the meetup logo pinned to my backpack-purse. I plan to take the Adult Docent-Led Tour at 1 p.m. I think I won't want to stick around for the film at 4:45, but if you're interested in the film, you need to make a reservation for yourself by May 20. - Anna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weavers, dancers, puppet masters, hieroglyphics experts and artists illuminate the Maya culture of Guatemala and Mexico. Come see the ancient arts come to life! This event is 11 a.m.-4 p.m. but I am interested in all the exhibits too.&lt;br /&gt;DEMONSTRATIONS&lt;br /&gt;Maya Dugouts&lt;br /&gt;Boat builder Wade Smith reconstructs a large-scale, speculative model of a dugout canoe based on ancient Maya designs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weaving the Waterways&lt;br /&gt;Using back strap or stick looms, skilled weavers of Maya descent create a traditional huipil, a blouse with water motifs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guatemala Maya Sawdust Carpet&lt;br /&gt;Master artist Ubaldo Sanchez creates an alfombra from hand-dyed sawdust, rice, dried beans and flowers on the Atrium floor. Help make the border!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DOCENT-LED GALLERY TOURS&lt;br /&gt;Fiery Pool: The Maya and the Mythic Sea&lt;br /&gt;Family tour, 11:30 am | Adult tour, 1 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets available on the day of the tour at the admissions desk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DANCE&lt;br /&gt;Grupo Awal | noon and 3 pm | Atrium&lt;br /&gt;Young troupe members represent the Maya culture of Guatemala through folk dances, dress and cultural traditions. At PEM, see these 20-minute dance tributes to Maiz, or corn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PERFORMANCES&lt;br /&gt;Puppet Theater | 1:15 and 4 pm | Atrium&lt;br /&gt;Gustavo Boada and members of the dance troupe Grupo Awal perform the Maya creation story — El Popol Vuh — with life-size puppets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRESENTATION AND DEMONSTRATION&lt;br /&gt;Who Shall Read Them? The Decipherment of Maya Hieroglyphics&lt;br /&gt;Morse Auditorium and Art Studios&lt;br /&gt;Marc Zender, an eminent scholar of Maya hieroglyps, talks about the ancient writing system and deciphering techniques. From 3:45–4:45 pm, join a beginner's workshop and make your own glyphs! For adults and teens. Reservations for both programs by May 20.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FILM&lt;br /&gt;Breaking the Maya Code | 4:45–6:45 pm | Morse Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;2008, 116 minutes, directed by David Lebrun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pem.org/calendar/event/270-fiery_pool_the_maya_and_the_mythic_sea" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pem.org/ca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture and will wear the meetup logo pinned to my back-pack purse</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anna</member_name><member_id>404606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>28</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277277234000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270142275000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mayan Festival and Exhibit at Peabody Essex Museum</name><id>13059350</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274540400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13059350/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/5/global_14064357.jpeg</photo_url></item>