<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Beantown and Beyonders - Are you a paddler?  Well load up that canoe or kayak and join the &amp;quot;Spring on the Cocheco&amp;quot; river trip, Saturday, May 16 2009. The three-hour paddling expedition begins in Rochester site on Route 125, running down the Cocheco River and into the Isinglass river.  In addition to the paddling, the goal is to pick up litter on the river along the way.  After the trip there is a lunch, where you can munch on as many hamburgers and hot dogs and drink's (a small donation would be appricated $3.). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trip is cross-promoted with the Trailblazers Meetup of NH.  Peter, their organizer, has been on this trip every year for the last eight years -- it's a lot of fun, and for a great envoronmental cause!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your own kayak or canoe and post comments with your reservation. If you know of someone going who has a canoe you can ride with them or contact them from the &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; list.  There are other canoe and rental dealers in the area who rent them.  You can check that out online, but here's one that looks like it might work:     &lt;a href="http://www.superpages.com/bp/Barrington-NH/Therriens-RentAll-L2019887000.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.superpages...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****If you are planning on coming to the canoe trip you must register with:************ &lt;br /&gt;Lorie Chase &lt;br /&gt;Cocheco River Watershed Coalition &lt;br /&gt;268 County Farm Road &lt;br /&gt;Dover, NH 03820 &lt;br /&gt;603-516-8113 FAX 603-743-3431 &lt;br /&gt;lorie.chase@unh.edu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email Lori Chase as they need to know how much food to bring and to pre register you for their trip. You can also ask to receive a map of where we are going. Last year there were over a hundred and fifty paddlers who went. About 30 people come from the Trailblazers meetup group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This fun and informative workshop-on-the-water is sponsored by UNH Cooperative Extension in cooperation with N.H. Fish and Game, the Cocheco River Watershed Coalition and Waste Management of Rochester, New Hampshire. There is no charge for the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will have a shuttle bringing our kayaks and canoes back to the starting point for free.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rain date for this trip will be on May 23 (a week later). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants can bring their watercraft to the put-in site at 9:00 a.m. on Saturday, May 16th (the site will be marked with balloons).  Download the PDF file marked &amp;quot;Cocheco River Start/Finish Location&amp;quot; from the &amp;quot;Files&amp;quot; tab on the left side of this page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Periodic breaks will feature presentations on the subjects of &amp;quot;Fishing the Cocheco and Fish in the Cocheco&amp;quot; by Scott Decker of the N.H. Fish and Game Department; &amp;quot;Watching Birds and Other Wildlife on the Cocheco&amp;quot; by Darrel Covell of UNH Cooperative Extension; &amp;quot;Hunting as a Function of Wildlife Management&amp;quot; by Darrel Covell; and &amp;quot;Hunting on the Cocheco&amp;quot; by Alan Davis of Waste Management of Rochester. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, bags will be available for those who want to pick up trash in the Cocheco River that day. Waste Management will be at the Little Falls Bridge Road to take all of the trash bags to their dump site at the end of the tour. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;U.S. Coast Guard-approved life jackets must be worn on this trip.  If you are going, please make arrangements to have them with you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!  &amp;quot;Stroke!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rick M.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have on an Aussie-looking hat with a Meetup Sign on top</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242855049000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242094204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canoeing/Kayaking on the Cocheco River  this Saturday.</name><id>10390902</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242478800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10390902/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/b/global_8594731.jpeg</photo_url></item>