<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A loop hike up the lesser-used trails to the top of Wachusett Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;One of a series of hikes for those of us who want to start getting (back) into hiking and need to build up some stamina and endurance before attempting the rockier terrains and steeper inclines! Hikes will be taken at a slower pace, with gains of 1000 feet or less and most will be 3 - 4 miles and take about half a day.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 2,006ft Mount Wachusett in Central Massachusetts is more like a large hill than a mountain but is popular for hiking in the summer and fall, and skiing in the winter. Mount Wachusett is technically a glaciated Monadnock which is a term reserved for a single mountain carved out by glaciers and located in an otherwise flat terrain.  A little known fact about the mountain is that it is home to the oldest growth forest east of the Connecticut River in Massachusetts. A few hundred feet below the summit are trees over 350 years old – which means they were saplings just about 30 years after the Mayflower set anchor off Cape Cod.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/MapLarge-WachusettMA090518.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at Machais Pool at the end of Westminster Road, take the Stage Coach Trail to the Harrington Trail, then loop around the Semuhenna and West Side Trails before taking the Old Indian Trail to the Summit.  After hanging out at the summit and enjoying the view and some lunch, we'll head down the Mountain House Trail, pick up the Bicentennial Trail which spills into Echo Lake trail and back to our cars.  (NOTE: This is NOT the route marked in yellow on the map, but a variation!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Even though this hike is for those of us just starting out (or starting again) please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times! Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some snacks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: &lt;b&gt;These are directions to the main entrance on Mountain Road.  We will be meeting a bit further on, at a small parking lot off Westminster Road, where it intersects with Administration Road!  Continue down Mountain Road about a mile or so and Westminster Road will be on your right.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East/Northeast/Southeast&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Take I-495 to exit 29, Rt. 2 west.&lt;br /&gt;    * Take Rt. 2 west to exit 25, Rt. 140 south.&lt;br /&gt;    * At the top of the exit ramp take a right onto Rt. 140 south.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 2.1 miles on Rt. 140 south and take a right onto Mile Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road, take left fork onto Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Park entrance is on right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Take 1-90 (MA PIKE) west to exit 10, I-290 north.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 7.3 miles on I-290 north to exit 19, I-190 north.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 9 miles on I-190 north to exit 5, Rt. 140 north.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 9.3 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left onto Mile Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road, bear left at fork onto Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Park entrance is on right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West/Northwest&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Take I-91 to Exit 27, Rt. 2 east.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 31 miles on Rt. 2 east to exit 25, Rt. 140 south.&lt;br /&gt;    * Take Rt. 2 east to exit 25, Rt. 140 south.&lt;br /&gt;    *  At the top of the exit ramp take a left onto Rt. 140 south.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 2.1 miles on Rt. 140 south and take a right onto Mile Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road bear left at fork onto Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Park entrance is on right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Southwest&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Take I-90 (MA PIKE) east to Exit 10, I-290 north.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 7.3 miles on I-290 north to exit 19, I-190 north.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 9 miles on I-190 north to exit 5, Rt. 140 north.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 9.3 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left onto Mile Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 0.5 mile on Mile Hill Rd to a split in the road, bear left at fork onto Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Drive 1.25 miles on Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;    * Park entrance is on right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the trailhead by 9:15am.  I have a bright orange backpack and a big smile.  My cell phone is 774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284985369000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284555966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (Back) Into It Loop Hike to Wachusett Mountain</name><id>14777858</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284903000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14777858/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/f/global_17983135.jpeg</photo_url></item>