<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/8/8/event_73154472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://plainville-ct.toysfortots.org/local-coordinator-sites/lco-sites/default.asp"&gt;http://plainville-ct.toysfortots.org/local-coordinator-sites/lco-sites/default.asp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi Folks! I wanted to do this event last year but thought of it to late. This is something near and dear to my heart and I donate every year. Toys for Tots is a great foundation that takes donated toys and distributes them to needy children everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we are a game playing group...what better group of people to donate games to kids. Last year I learned that older kids often get forgotten for this charity and I want to focus on them this year. So here's how this will work.....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone attending this event is asked to bring a game that children ages 12+ can play. Whatever fits in your budget. TOYS MUST BE NEW IN ORIGINAL WRAPPING. (I assume for the families safety.) Do not wrap your toy in gift wrap. Other than that, have fun with it! Toys can be found cheap at Walmart, Ebay etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*If you can't make this event and still want to donate...&amp;nbsp;bring the toys to my house (leave by the back door and let me know you did it), give them to another member who is coming,&amp;nbsp;you can also donate cash online at the above website, various retailers accept donations (they have boxes by their front doors) Toys R Us, Babies R Us, Farmington Bank&amp;nbsp; etc, you can find a list on the T4T website also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will also collect money to donate to the charity if you could not get a toy. I will leave out a basket for donations and this money will NOT be th usual meetup fees donation. All money collected on this night will go to Toys for Tots!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toy donation are the only thing I ask anyone to bring this time. I will not take money&amp;nbsp;for meetup site fees this night.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However should you feel the need to bring a snack to share with attendees, or an alcoholic beverage for yourself that is more than fine. I'll have&amp;nbsp;some munchies&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;non-alcoholic beverages laid out. &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/1723755200050492932723/img/smileys/biggrin.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a game if you like, bring a friend, but most important BRING A TOY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTES: Doggie alert!&amp;nbsp;I ahve a super friendly barkless&amp;nbsp;25lb Basenji who WILL sit next to you on the couch. She is hypoallergenic but be warned anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking: Please park on my lawn (provided there is no snow) or on the cross street Englewood. DO NOT PARK ON PACKARD ST! You will lose a mirror or worse.&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/614102232183174521616/img/smileys/wink.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Mustard yellow house across form Englewood Ave</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4895998</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323215365000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321462515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Toys For Tots - Game Night</name><id>41387942</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322956800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/41387942/</event_url></item>