<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>127 Ocean Blvd               NH 03842 </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03842</zip><lat>42.908443</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sea Ketch Restaurant and Decks</name><city>Hampton Beach</city><id>8868922</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.811302</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;There's a lot happening on Wednesday evenings at Hampton Beach! The REMINISANTS, Boston's Best Oldies Band will be playing at the Seashell Stage from 7:00- 9:30 pm. After, a weekly FIRE WORKS display starts at 9:30 on the beach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AND, of course, there’s the boardwalk with all its’ arcades, games (e.g. laser tag!), shops, foods, and more for us to enjoy at anytime. ……….Oh, almost forgot, the beach is there for those wishing to take a romantic stroll in the light of the receding FULL, BLUE moon while listening to the soothing sound of the ocean surf!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally for anyone who may want to stay later- THE BREAKERS at THE ASHWORTH HOTEL has a DJ and lots of dancing until 12:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start the night off on one of the decks overlooking the beach at THE SEA KETCH restaurant for drinks (possibly apps). Then, we can, either stay and listen to music there- or head over to the SEA SHELL STAGE for the Reminisants Band. &lt;br /&gt;

 Those who wish can do the boardwalk, the beach, or whatever becomes interesting at the time. We'll stay for the FIRE WORKS which start at 9:30. &lt;br /&gt;

 After that – head over to THE ASHWORTH for dancing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*** If the time posted is too early, you are welcome to join us at anytime! I will be posting my contact # closer to the date. PARKING: Depending on the weather &amp;amp; time, parking can be tight- and costly. You may want to think about carpooling.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346310064000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345747444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening at Hampton Beach</name><id>79052302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346275800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/79052302/</event_url></item>