<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Middle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810561</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 465 8008</phone><name>The Grog</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>689907</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.869301</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>SHORT NOTICE!&lt;br /&gt;Another great night coming up at the Grog and NOTICE THE TIME CHANGE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join Parker Wheeler's Blues Party featuring the Fabulour CHRIS FITZ!&lt;br /&gt;For over thirty-nine years, The Grog has been the place to meet and to enjoy in Newburyport.  The tradition of presenting fresh food, refreshment and entertainment continues - ever changing as we strive to keep things lively for you.&lt;br /&gt;After returning from The Civil War, Alfred W. Thompson, the great-grandfather of Newburyport Yankee Whit Kimball, opened a &amp;quot;Ladies and Gents Eating and Oyster House&amp;quot; serving Newburyporters, sailors, statesmen and travelers until prohibition.  After repeal, Spud Leary opened the Pilot House, serving the public until 1964, when the McCarthys assumed stewardship.  &lt;br /&gt;In 1969 the business was rechristened &amp;quot;The Grog&amp;quot; after the English Navy's traditional ration of rum and water.  This tradition was started by Admiral Vernon, whose nickname was &amp;quot;Old Grog&amp;quot;, so called for the cloak he wore made of grogram.  We continue to salute you, Admiral Vernon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen</member_name><member_id>3330386</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289851394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>North shore Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Newburyport-Singles-30s-40s-and-50s</urlname><id>1554197</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>Newburyport Singles 30's 40's and 50's</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288711838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Great Night at The Grog in Newburyport</name><id>15310672</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289775600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Newburyport-Singles-30s-40s-and-50s/events/15310672/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/6/c/global_13033644.jpeg</photo_url></item>