<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 5th Ave New York NY 10111. Cross Streets 49th Street </address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10020</zip><lat>40.757685</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New York City </name><city>New York </city><id>1092242</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.978450</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>37.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE IRA SINGLES EVENT PRESENTS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;            New York City Holiday Sights and Attractions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                    Bus Trip (No worries about driving and parking in the City!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                      On Saturday December 12, 2009. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Beautiful Bus Ride to New York City.  Our gorgeous bus accommodates 52 Fun- Loving Folks.  Relax and enjoy the fun ride on comfy seats, with WIFI, DVD, and almost a bathroom, highlighted with Gold and Marble inlay flooring and faucets. (OK, maybe you have to use your imagination). Think no pit stops at crowded rest areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our trip will begin rain or shine at one of four convenient pick up places. Exact times, pick up/drop off locations will be announced. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 1. Springfield. South Side of the Basket Ball Hall of Fame. 8:00am. ish. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.  Windsor. Commuter Lot. Route 91. Exit Number 38. Route 75. Aprox: 8:45am ish &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.  Middletown. Commuter Lot. Route 91. Exit Number 20. Country Club Road 9:30am ish &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4  .Milford: Peter Pan Arrow Garage. Exit 40 from 95.Take a left at the end of the exit ramp and then 312 will be on your left look for sign that says Peter Pan Arrow. 312 Woodmont Road. 10:15am ish &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Norwalk. Commuter Lot. Route 95. Exit Number 16. Hendrics Avenue. 11:00am ish. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rockefeller Center Area arrival in the 12:15ish Range. (Depending on Traffic)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Bus will be leaving at 8:00PM, giving you a lot of great time in the Big Apple!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Big Print Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST:  Round Trip $33.00 per person. Check must be received on or before  11/14/09 to receive the $4.00 Savings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; After this date: $37.00. Round Trip $ 37.00 per person if check is received on or before 11/27/09. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A light snack to be served on the way to the City. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Limited to a total of 52 fun-loving folks.  Please share with friends so we can fill the bus for a fabulous, adventure-filled Holiday day trip. A second bus will be added if we get an additional 52 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP no later than November 27, Friday.   I need to have your check for a confirmed yes by this date as well.  Please include: First and Last Name, Cell Number, Pick up Location, if you are paying for a friend/s, please include the above information for them as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we do not meet the 52 needed to go, all checks will be shredded. All will be notified if the trip is canceled via email.  No refunds unless the trip is cancelled. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.                   RSVP to: Mistrchrming@aol.com  Questions- 860-604-5792.  Checks to be sent to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ira Wettenstein/New York,  44 Dibble Hollow Lane, Windsor Locks CT. 06096&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even with the cold wind blowing (&amp;amp; sometimes even snow falling) New York City is transformed into a winter wonderland -- from the Christmas tree at Rockefeller Center to the Christmas window displays at Macy's and Saks Fifth Avenue, there are endless Christmas sights to enjoy during the holiday season in New York City. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christmas in New York. Isn’t it romantic? The city is (hopefully) covered with a blanket of snow, the ice skating rinks are open, and Xmas lights twinkle everywhere to add to the festive mood. I didn’t appreciate the season in NYC until I moved across the country – isn’t that always the way? – but now I look back with fond memories at the wonderful activities and things to see and do in New York City during the Christmas holidays. Here, in no particular order, are the top 10 things to do in the city for the winter holiday season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                                             Ideas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Every day after Thanksgiving and up until Christmas, Santa Claus is at Macy’s in Herald Square. Anyone who’s seen that old movie, Miracle on 34th Street knows that Santa indeed lives at Macy’s. The lines may be long, but he’s considered the best Santa in NYC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.  Stroll around 5th Avenue, and admire the famous, elaborately designed window displays. Department stores like Bergdorf Goodman, Saks Fifth Avenue, Lord &amp;amp; Taylor, Macy’s, Barneys, and Bloomingdale’s participate in this visual fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.  Everyone can afford tickets to see Balanchine’s The Nutcracker. It’s performed by the New York City Ballet at Lincoln Center, and tickets range from a mere $10 to a splurge-worthy $215. This show is only around during the Xmas holiday season, and is iconic of Christmas in the city. Cute little children scurry and dance, the toy soldiers march, and a huge one-ton Christmas tree make for a wonderful show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4.  While we’re on the topic of traditional winter holiday shows in New York, the world famous Radio City Rockettes have been performing their Radio City Christmas Spectacular for over 75 years (with different actual Rockettes, needless to say). This year, The Rockettes kick in unison until December 30, and tickets range from $40 to $250. Anyone visiting NYC in the winter should consider trying to budget in seeing Christmas Spectacular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. The Time Warner Center at Columbus Circle has its annual “Under the Stars” light show, and (fake) snow falling in its entranceway. This show and experience is every weekend evening until January 2; good thing, too, since there isn’t always real snow in NYC for Christmas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. The Rockefeller Center Christmas Tree is the biggest in the city, and the annual tree lighting is nationally broadcast. The lighting is always at the beginning of December – this year it’s December 3 – and it stays lit through the first week of January.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7.  The ice skating rink at Rockefeller Center is cheap (skate rentals are less than $20)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8.  A romantic Horse Drawn Carriage Ride thru Central Park, maybe in the snow!!! How Romantic would this be?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9. A what ever day. You pick and choose how much you want to do. Great food/people watching/ getting into the Holiday Spirit.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A largre Peter Pan Bus will be there</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1260807173000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>52</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255438116000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira- December 12, Saturday Holiday New York City Bus Trip </name><id>11615623</id><headcount>53</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260622800000</time><rsvp_limit>52</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/11615623/</event_url></item>