<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(IF rain: Community Cultural Center across the street)</address_2><address_1>1047 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.779999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-282-8241</phone><name>East Hartford Green</name><city>East Hartford</city><id>304946</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.620003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FINAL UPDATE: We definitely WILL MEET / PARTY TONIGHT in downtown East Hartford - Rain or Shine!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; IF moved indoors (across the street from the Green, to the E.H. Community Cultural Center) BYO FOOD &amp;amp; ALCOHOL IS PERMITTED inside the BACK of the Auditorium as they'll have tables and chairs for such (but not in the front of the auditorium's permanent seating area).  As such, we'll be allowed to picnic, drink, listen to and dance to the great tunes of SANTANA!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; General Info: Gather @ 6:00. (Show starts @ 6:30).  (AFTER the show ends, some may likely go over to Margarita's in East Hartford to continue the fun).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; IF OUTDOORS, on the GREEN: Look for me/us under three shiny BLUE STAR-shaped BALLOONS (may or may not be fully inflated/deflated) attached to a white stick w/ red reflector - LOW TO THE GROUND so as not to block the view of those behind us!  At concerts, I traditionally stake out an area with 2-4 large blue-on-blue U-Haul moving blankets, likely fairly in the center, or farther, from the stage, not too close to loud speakers.  If in doubt, call my cell# from an easy-for-me-to-spot-you location and I can direct you to us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; BYO picnic dinner/snacks and beverages of choice. As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; We typically stay till after the crowd disperses enjoying the company of old and new friends.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; This event is also being posted on the &amp;quot;Singles Event&amp;quot;, but without RSVP's, so likely several (or more) people will be joining us than post on MeetUp.  For Hartford area concerts we typically gather 12-24... C'mon EAST OF THE RIVER - come out to meet new local friends and have fun!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob Pudney, organizer   &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;C: (860) 690-9595  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: The Single Event's &amp;quot;Thirsty Thursday&amp;quot; group is being invited to join us for this event. During the summer months, we are trying to do more casual, BYO type gatherings, featuring different types of outdoor musical entertainment, moving around to various towns to encourage new folks to join us and make new friends! Typically 8-24 come together each time. These new introductions lead to invitations to each other's events and the opportunity to enjoy varied activities and make even more new friends!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: We welcome, and encourage, suggestions for &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; (7 days a week!) and/or Thirsty Thursday MeetUps in the Greater New Haven and Shoreline communities... along with your offer to volunteer to help organize such outings!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI:  Upcoming East Hartford shows (NOT necessarily MeetUps)  &lt;br /&gt;07/12  Motown  &lt;br /&gt;07/19  SANTANA Tribute = &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; MeetUp &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;  &lt;br /&gt;07/26  Showband playing hits  &lt;br /&gt;(08/02 - free to E.H. residents only @ Martin Park = Podunk Bluegrass)  &lt;br /&gt;08/09  50's - 70's  &lt;br /&gt;08/16  Celtic &amp;amp; African blend  &lt;br /&gt;08/23  TBA  &lt;br /&gt;08/30  Livingston Taylor = Americana  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185055786000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182220930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FINAL UPDATE: Thirsty Thursday: "SANTANA" Tribute - East Hartford TONIGHT</name><id>5907103</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184882400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5907103/</event_url></item>