<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Common Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.395386</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-404-7261</phone><name>Belmont Lions Club</name><city>Belmont </city><id>1170360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.176365</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Free public Lecture:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling the Transpersonal Interstate:&lt;br /&gt;Rock and Roll, Fundamentalism, and the New Age Pursuit of Ecstasy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Lenny Gibson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leonard Gibson, Ph.D., graduated from Williams College and earned doctorates from Claremont Graduate School in philosophy and The University of Texas at Austin in psychology. Lenny has forty years of experience working with non-ordinary states of consciousness. He has taught at The University of Tulsa and Lesley College and served his clinical psychology internship at the Boston, Mass. V.A. Hospital. He currently teaches Transpersonal Psychology at Burlington College. Lenny is a Holotropic Breathwork™ Facilitator and serves on the board of the Association of Holotropic Breathwork International (AHBI). He also assists with town and regional planning in his Vermont hometown and plays clarinet in local bands. A survivor of throat cancer, he facilitates the head and neck cancer support group at Dartmouth Hitchcock Medical Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Light refreshments will be served.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This lecture is part of a weekend Holotropic Breathwork workshop, but also stands alone as a free public lecture. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For information on the workshop and to register, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/boston-energy-healers/pages/www.BostonHolotropic.com"&gt;www.BostonHolotropic.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, February 12, 2010&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 8:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Belmont Lions Club&lt;br /&gt;1 Common Street (former train station)&lt;br /&gt;Belmont Center, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Belmont Lions Club located at 1 Common Street is close to Belmont Center and is accessible from the MBTA Commuter Rail (Fitchburg line) out of North Station as well as the #74 bus out of Harvard Square. The building is in fact the old train station (solid stone, well insulated) so if you take the train, go through the pedestrian tunnel under the tracks and then turn left and walk up the ramp to the front door.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There is ample on-street parking in the neighborhood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/boston-energy-healers/pages/www.BostonHolotropic.com"&gt;www.BostonHolotropic.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Recommended by Ysgawen (Allen))&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266192843000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Healing Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-healers-network</urlname><id>511093</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Healers Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264259425000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A night with Breathwork Speaker: Lenny Gibson</name><id>12400172</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266019200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-healers-network/events/12400172/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/4/b/global_7529195.jpeg</photo_url></item>