<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry folks, this has been on the schedule for a long-time, without an actual date/location. What happened was this Meetup got promoted by member votes rather than a Meetup scheduled by an organizer, and I didn't realize that at first and didn't step in to make sure that it got scheduled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have gotten a hold of a copy and have it till early next week. So I am scheduling the Meetup for this Saturday at 7pm to watch on DVD at my house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*****************Come at 6pm if you would like to join us for Potluck******&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I will remove RSVP's made for this event that were made prior to right now, so I can get an actual count that is accurate,&lt;/strong&gt; now that there is an actual time/location. &lt;strong&gt;So if you are interested, please RSVP at www.meetup.com/filmgroup even if you did previously.&lt;/strong&gt; Hope you can make it. Sorry for the relatively short notice. If it doesn't work for a lot of people, we can try to get another showing sometime in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/e/2/event_133471202.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ifcfilms.com/films/cave-of-forgotten-dreams"&gt;CAVE OF FORGOTTEN DREAMS&lt;/a&gt;, a breathtaking documentary from the incomparable Werner Herzog (ENCOUNTERS AT THE END OF THE WORLD, GRIZZLY MAN) follows an exclusive expedition into the nearly inaccessible Chauvet Cave in France, home to the most ancient visual art known to have been created by man. A hit at this year’s Toronto Film Festival, CAVE OF FORGOTTEN DREAMS is an unforgettable cinematic experience that provides a unique glimpse of pristine artwork dating back to human hands over 30,000 years ago -- almost twice as old as any previous discovery. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 "If you're a member of the human race - you owe it to yourself to see this movie." &lt;br /&gt;

 Dana Stevens, Slate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "****! WONDERFUL. SEE THIS FILM. IT TAKES YOU TO A PLACE YOU WON'T SOON FORGET." &lt;br /&gt;

 Michael Phillips, Chicago Tribune&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "WHAT A GIFT...AN INSIDE LOOK AT THE ASTONISHING CAVE OF CHAUVET-PONT-d'ARC-AND IN 3-D TOO. IT'S A BLAST TO BE INSIDE THE CAVE." &lt;br /&gt;

 Manohla Dargis, The New York Times&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "*****! BLOWS YOU AWAY WITH ITS BEAUTY." &lt;br /&gt;

 Joe Neumaier, New York Daily News&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "A sacred space where the human and the mystical effortlessly intertwine, and we are in Werner Herzog's debt for that great gift." &lt;br /&gt;

 Kenneth Turan, Los Angeles Times&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341202012000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>filmgroup</urlname><id>1279822</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Western MA Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309400177000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Werner Herzog's Cave of Forgotten Dreams on video.</name><id>24051071</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341097200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/filmgroup/events/24051071/</event_url></item>