<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Rendition is a movie about the practice of interrogating suspected terrorists in a foreign country where laws against torture do not apply. This practice is called rendition and this film makes it real.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film opens in an American middle class suburb. Reese Witherspoon is playing with her small son when they get a phone call from her husband, Omar Metwally, an Egyptian citizen who has lived in America for 20 years. He tells his wife and son he is on the way home from a business trip and they plan on meeting him at the airport. All seems well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When he gets off the plane, however, he is detained at the airport and questioned. He is a chemical engineer and the questioners are asking questions about a terrorist bomb plot. He denies everything. He seems clean but Meryl Streep, playing a high powered Washington decision maker, orders him to be put into rendition and he is whisked away to an unnamed middle eastern country and his name erased from the plane's passenger log while his wife and son wait patiently at the airport for a husband and father who has disappeared. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The scene now shifts to an unnamed middle eastern country where Yagal Noor, an Israeli actor of Jewish Iraqi descent, is cast in the role of the interrogator. Jake Gyllenhaal is cast as an American diplomat, who has just lost a co-worker in a suicide bombing, and has been promoted to assist Yagal Noor with the questioning. It is awful. I am cringing now just writing about it as scenes of waterboarding and electric shock torture are shown in detail. There is also a subplot about the interrogator's daughter and a suicide bomber which expands the story. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the meantime Reese Witherspoon is trying desperately to find her husband. She seeks out an old boyfriend, played by Peter Sarsgaard who works for a senator, played by Alan Arkin. Even when they confront Meryl Streep, there is a blank wall of silence. Jake Gyllenhaal, however, is beginning to have a change of heart as the torturing goes on. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a serious film about a serious topic. It will open your eyes and raise your consciousness. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283041107000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Consciousness movie members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>consciousness-65</urlname><id>355065</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Conscious Movie Meetup!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281378505000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie:  Rendition</name><id>14368149</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283036400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/consciousness-65/events/14368149/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/e/b/global_17075099.jpeg</photo_url></item>