<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Day two: Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mon-Wed, February 18-20, 2008 at 7pm&lt;br /&gt;General Admission Tickets: $16.50 (includes $1.50 restoration fee) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TICKETS MUST BE PURCHASED IN ADVANCED. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Banff Mountain Film Festival is on the road across North America and around the world. Whether you are an experienced mountaineer or an armchair adventurer, this event is for everyone. Don?t miss the excitement!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hot on the heels of the largest, and one of the most prestigious, mountain festivals in the world, the Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour has hit the road, with stops planned in more than 275 communities and 30 countries across the globe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year?s tour features a collection of the most inspiring and thought-provoking action, environmental, and adventure mountain films. Traveling from remote landscapes and cultures to up close and personal with adrenaline-packed action sports, the 2007/2008 World Tour is an exhilarating and provocative exploration of the mountain world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour is produced by Mountain Culture at The Banff Centre, and features award-winning films and audience favorites from approximately 300 films entered in the annual festival in Banff. Join Hermitlake.com and chunkymonkey productions when the Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour brings the spirit of outdoor adventure to the Boston outdoors community, at the Regent Theatre&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/events/banff2007.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.regentthea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/general_info.html" target="_blank"&gt;Directions and parking information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>naturegirl</member_name><member_id>3135826</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203636930000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200364579000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Banff Mountain Film Festival  February 19 (Day 2)</name><id>7116720</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203463800000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7116720/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/1/global_2979473.jpeg</photo_url></item>