<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Level 2 - Sea kayaks or Rec. Kayaks with Bulkheads&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Click picture to the right to see and or print the planned route you may need to enlarge it to see more of the details&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the potential of wind and current this event is recommended for kayakers with sea-kayaks or 12+ ft. Rec. Kayaks with bulkheads and who also have experience in paddling in tidal areas as well as wet exit &amp;amp; capsize recoveries. Also you must have appropriate safety gear including PFD, Paddle Float &amp;amp; Pump.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll either put-in at the Plum Island Bridge or Parking Lot #1 inside the Parker River Wildlife Reserve depending on how many people RSVP to attend as the parking at the Bridge is limited.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The tide on the Plum Island River from the Plum Island bridge to the Parker river (4 miles) is not strong, and it is possible to paddle against the tide.  The best time to paddle this section is within 3 hours of high tide.&amp;quot; High Tide on Sat. Oct. 4th is approx 3pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From Rt.95 Hampton&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;saddr=Blue+Star+Memorial+Hwy%2FI-95+S&amp;amp;daddr=42.82789,-70.866108+to:Plum+Island+Turnpike+Bridge,+Merrimack+%26+Plum+Island+Sound+%4042.797243,-70.822613&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FTGAjwId0s3G-w%3B%3BFbsIjQIdK1XH-w&amp;amp;mra=dpe&amp;amp;mrcr=0&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=13&amp;amp;via=1&amp;amp;sll=42.831038,-70.876064&amp;amp;sspn=0.092277,0.128574&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.871938,-70.853233&amp;amp;spn=0.184432,0.257149&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=12" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Info...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLUM ISLAND RIVER AND PLUM ISLAND SOUND&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the best ways to explore the Parker River and its tributaries is by kayak. Varying tides, currents, depths, and shoreline environments offer a range of rewarding boating experiences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Plum Island River, which flows back and forth between  the waters of the Merrimack and Parker Rivers, is the river that makes Plum Island an island. At its southern end, it is joined by the Parker River, at which point it becomes known as Plum Island Sound.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At low tide, the Sound appears to be a river channel -- an extension of the Parker River.  At the highest tides, the Sound covers the high marshes and appears to be quite a large bay.  A number of tidal creeks perforate the marsh on both sides, and make for interesting exploration by canoe or kayak. The Rowley River and Ipswich River both empty into the southern portion of the Sound. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll Start our paddle at the North End of the Parker and paddle to Plum Island Sound then turn right and head up the Parker River towards Newbury we may go as far as Byfield before the tide changes. We'll then head back to Plum Island Sound then retrace our route back to the put-in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate Distance 12 miles, Duration approximately 5hrs. Sunset is at 6:20pm so it will likely be setting around the time we take-out.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After paddling we'll stop at Plum Island Grille right across the Bridge for our PPPO Post Paddling Pig Out. See the link below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.plumislandgrille.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.plumisland...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for kayakers - parking is limited to 15 vehicles</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223739559000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220896322000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers - Parker River Paddle Plum Island MA</name><id>8714873</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223137800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/8714873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/9/global_5465209.jpeg</photo_url></item>