<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.129517</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-473-6611</phone><name>PINZ Bowling</name><city>Milford</city><id>734836</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.518942</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>PART I  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;FUN FUN FUN.........BOWLING&lt;br /&gt;PART II  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;FUN FUN FUN........DINNER AT PINZ&lt;br /&gt;PART III.......&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;FUN FUN FUN ..... DANCING TO A LIVE BAND AT PINZ&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is in three parts................join us for any of the parts or better yet, join us for all THREE PARTS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With 20 lanes to choose from, there’s always fun to be found. Open bowling is offered so we can meet on Saturday, February 27th at 6 pm to start with PART I.   Each futuristic glow-in-the-dark bowling lane features the latest technology, while the seating at the lanes creates a perfect place to relax and enjoy the experience. This is for fun, doesn't matter your expertise level of bowling. If you don't want to bowl, come join the seating and watch us bowl, or at least try to.  Then join us for dinner! Pricing for bowling is an hourly rate (up to six people) or individual rate. We can decide that night what we would like to choose to split the payment. Shoe rental is available at the front desk.  Depending on the number of YES replies will determine how many lanes we will need. &lt;a href="http://www.pinzbowl.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pinzbowl.c...&lt;/a&gt; Website has location directions, easy to find PINZ! &lt;br /&gt;After bowling, starts PART II which is dinner in the Blue Dog Lounge right at PINZ, on the other side of the building.  After dinner, starts PART III which is dancing to one of their live bands.  This will be a Fun Time! So come on down! Sign up by clicking the YES and submit your rsvp to enjoy a THREE PART NIGHT! &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the front desk where the Meetup group is</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267920176000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262535538000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PART 1, PART 2, PART 3  - ALL IN ONE NIGHT!</name><id>12205477</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267311600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/12205477/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/b/global_12478747.jpeg</photo_url></item>