<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A mandolinist, violist, and composer, Richard "Zach" Baldwin-Way's musical interests tend to lie somewhere between the genres of Appalachian Folk, Classical, and Jazz. For tonight he has composed a series neo-folk/classical inspired pieces for string quartet. This concert will hopefully be a jumping point for a collaborative effort that follows in the footsteps of the Jazz Writers Collective in the form of string quartet writing with the intention of exposing young composers in the Boston area and creating music in a group atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded by composer and arranger Lorenzo Carrano, the Jazz Writers’ Collective has been lending its voice to some of the most talented emerging composers around Boston since 2010. Showcasing some of the finest young players the local Jazz scene has to offer, the band has been conquering the heart of its audiences since its inception thanks to its outstanding performances and unique collaborations with international artists. As a ten piece orchestra, Jazz Writers' Collective combines the power of a big band and the intimacy of a chamber ensemble; its ever growing repertoire ranges from post be-bop and cool to modern classical music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to these bands there will be a few additional musical goodies...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come for a great night of music! Support local writers!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353301233000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonjazz</urlname><id>87187</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Jazz Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352743144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jazz Writers' Collective and Folk Fusion String Quartet @ Lily Pad</name><id>91073682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353290400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonjazz/events/91073682/</event_url></item>