<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizational meeting&lt;/em&gt;, including discussion of decluttering assistance for either pay or a time trade (your choice - to exchange with anyone willing to engage with you under whatever terms are mutually agreeable) for 15 minutes, half an hour, or an hour or two of clearing service with or by another of our members under your supervision - to achieve rapid progress on a particular spot/area within your space of concern, to clear a "beach head" from which base you can expand your clearing operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...Some of our members have come to meetings especially to find a Decluttering Buddy, and mentioned that they are most motivated to declutter whenever someone - &lt;em&gt;anyone&lt;/em&gt; - is scheduled to arrive for any reason ... so, this strategy of arranging for someone to arrive at a given time with an expressed purpose of decluttering will hopefully provide such incentive to more of us, and help to accelerate our decluttering objectives on at least a one-time basis (or perhaps ongoing, depending on individuals' availability and interest).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What might work best to help &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; declutter more? Comments/ suggestions are very welcomed to help this group better meet the objectives of more members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If interest warrants, we can perhaps meet at a more spacious venue of your choice ... perhaps in a nearby library. If interest in an organizational meeting such as this for our group is INsufficient, I probably will release the organizing function of this Meetup group for anyone else who has ideas, time, energy, and other resources to better meet the needs of our group members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...Possibly you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup at the home of any sign-up who has registered for this service</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335404372000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317578874000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tools for Decluttering Organizational Meeting &amp; "Clearing Machine"</name><id>35833932</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335394800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/35833932/</event_url></item>