<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396908</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Davis Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>736913</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122910</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>30-35 Miles starting and ending at Davis Square in Somerville.  We will meet at the outdoor tables in front of JP Licks (Across the street from the Somerville Theater).  The ride kicks off at 9:10am, and we will take the Minuteman Bikeway to its other end in Bedford.  From Bedford, we will share the road with cars and pedal to Cambridge, go along the Charles River for a bit (on the section of Memorial Drive that is closed to cars on Sundays) and then cut through Harvard Square, then Porter Square, and on to finish at Davis Square.  Parts of this ride will be on busy streets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will aim to average 15mph, which should get us back to Davis Square by lunchtime.  If the whole group is comfortable going faster than 15, then that is fine with me. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Davis Square is a great place to get lunch.  You can find sandwiches, burritos, pizza, veggie friendly options, and lets not forget ice-cream all within one block.  So lets capitalize on the variety and get food wherever you want, bring it to the outdoor tables, and satisfy our hunger while being entertained by some kind of street performer (I hope a good one will be there). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Somerville, on Sunday's you can park at metered spaces for free, or on residential side streets without worring about parking tickets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, the $2 meet-up fee goes to Rob who pays for this group to exist.  Thanks Rob!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Jon&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have my brown bike with light blue wheels, and an orange messenger bag</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Ramos</member_name><member_id>4466935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219151212000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218731938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>32 Miles - Start and End at Davis Sq. in Somerville</name><id>8543873</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218978000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/8543873/</event_url></item>