<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>588 Franklin Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.732246</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 296-9646</phone><name>Carbones</name><city>Hartford</city><id>502618</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>They've extended the Taste of Hartford another week and when else can you get a three course meal at Carbone's for $20.11!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the menu selections [url=http://www.letsgoarts.org/Document.Doc?id=775[/url]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP by Wednesday evening so we can make a reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hartford Advocate and the Greater Hartford Arts Council present the Taste of Hartford®, a week-long, city-wide dining experience. Participating restaurants offer a special three-course, price fixed menu that gives you the opportunity to sample the best they have to offer for only $20.11*! Here's the perfect chance to try something new or return to an old favorite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taste of Hartford® helps kick-off our 2011 United Arts Campaign. The money we raise each year goes to support over 150 arts and heritage organizations in the Greater Hartford Area. As you enjoy your meal, we ask you to contribute just one additional dollar to our United Arts Campaign. This one dollar helps fund hundreds of jobs in our community and makes sure our arts organizations continue to stay active, productive and healthy. Just look for the special envelope in your check portfolio or ask your server. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296262217000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-28</urlname><id>364032</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Heights Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295621338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>More Time to Taste</name><id>16131406</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296171000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-28/events/16131406/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/4/e/global_1222686.jpeg</photo_url></item>