<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$10.00 at the door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You may have noticed that Socializing for Justice is not an issue-based organization. We host events that draw progressives of all stripes that are like-minded but not necessarily like-identified. Our philosophy focuses on creating social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections, discussion spaces that challenge our myopic view of the world and now we're introducing skillshares which will support all of us desiring to make a difference in the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're very excited that Mark McCurdy, The Nonprofit Career Coach, has agreed to facilitate this training. Below is the workshop description from his website: &lt;a href="http://www.thenonprofitcareercoach.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.thenonprofitcareercoach.org&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Volunteer to accelerate your career&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How mission-focused volunteer work will positively transform your world and career. Learn from a one-of-a-kind framework or recipe how to cook up a career for social impact.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Points covered:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   1. Three secret ingredients to help you find your dream job for social impact (social impact compass)&lt;br /&gt;   2. Why and how to leverage your volunteer or pro-bono experience into a job reality&lt;br /&gt;   3. Hear the “secret recipe” of how people just like YOU are living their dream job for social impact&lt;br /&gt;   4. What are the “Hot &amp;amp; Spicy” sectors in the nonprofit/social impact space&lt;br /&gt;   5. Social impact resume writing that will get nonprofits and social entrepreneur organizations to call you&lt;br /&gt;   6. How strategic internships and volunteering will help expand your network and get you hired&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark is a highly sought after speaker and receives rave reviews - check out his &lt;a href="http://thenonprofitcareercoach.org/testimonials" target="_blank"&gt;testimonials&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you'll join us for this and future skillshares. Is there a skill you want to learn? Is there one you can offer? Let us know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over 1400+ members and 4+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287857580000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284667284000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Strategic Volunteering to Accelerate Your Career</name><id>14794878</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286229600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/14794878/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/c/global_18003468.jpeg</photo_url></item>