<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Maudslay Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.828848</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Maudslay Arts Center</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1306722</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.927930</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;strong&gt;CREATE&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp; CELEBRATE&amp;hellip;YOUR VIBRANT LIFE!&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Join us for one day&amp;nbsp;surrounded&amp;nbsp;by beautiful&amp;nbsp;gardens, lush green trails&amp;nbsp;and relaxing at a&amp;nbsp;historic arts center in the park, engaged with wellness practitioners, health &amp;amp; lifestyle experts, nutritionists, spiritual&amp;nbsp;energy&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;colorful&amp;nbsp;artists. &amp;nbsp;On&amp;nbsp;Saturday May 7th, from 9 am-5&amp;nbsp;pm at the Maudslay Arts Center, you will experience a naturally,&amp;nbsp;vibrant, healthy day that is dedicated to you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;We want each and every attendee and guest to celebrate what makes them unique, what makes them feel good, what needs to heal&amp;nbsp;and celebrate ways they can connect&amp;nbsp;with more like minded people who truly are focused on living a healthy vibrant life!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="https://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/eventReg?oeidk=a07e3dd9kc1f0ed7ef2&amp;amp;oseq=" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/register-banner.jpg" width="304" height="98" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day Weekend, and what a perfect way to celebrate Mother Earth and spend&amp;nbsp;time with your Mother at this special event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$20 Expo ($25 at the door)&amp;nbsp;/$35 Expo &amp;amp; All Speakers ($45 at the door) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(A portion of the proceeds is donated to support the Maudslay Arts Center (501c3 non profit)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One Day Can Lead to a&amp;nbsp; Happier, Healthier and Revitalized New You!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;




About this Vibrant Community Based Event
&lt;p&gt;We have a unique opportunity for a talented and respected group of health and wellness practitioners and professionals to offer their insight , knowledge and tools to teach us new ways of living in the moment, shifting behaviors that have kept us stuck, understanding the mind body connection and how what you eat affects how you feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highlighted Speakers include fitness expert&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;MICHAEL GERRISH&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #99cc00"&gt;(THE SHIFT DOCTORS) DR. MARION ROSS, PhD&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #99cc00"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;and &lt;a href="http://www.shiftyourlife.com/"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #99cc00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DR. TRACY LATZ M.D., M.S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; who specialize in working with clients on ways to shift their&amp;nbsp;behaviors and transform their lives and Revitalive&amp;rsquo;s own Ccertified Raw &amp;amp; Living Foods Lifestyle Educator&lt;a target="_blank"&gt; KRISTEN OVERLOCK&lt;/a&gt;, for a day that will help you transform your mind, body and spirit presented by Revitalive Health and Wellness Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;In just one day&amp;nbsp;YOU will learn how to take care of&amp;nbsp;YOUR body through fitness and food&amp;hellip;embrace a positive mindset for a healthier lifestyle, celebrate a green environment&amp;hellip;and nurture&amp;nbsp;YOUR spirit. We are encouraging people to&amp;nbsp;schedule time&amp;nbsp;for themselves and join us for this transformational event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #403778"&gt;The Vibrant Life Expo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a day to connect with with expert speakers, wellness practitioners, raw food and farming demos, eco-friendly exhibits, sustainable living activities, speaker presentations, networking opportunities and a wide array of local vendors that embrace living a happy and healthy lifestyle right here on the North Shore.&lt;/p&gt;
The Speakers- Spend a Day with Us and Learn from the Best!
&lt;span style="color : #4925d9"&gt;The Mind Body Connection and Intuition!&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/michael.jpg" width="140" height="159" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px 5px 0px 0px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Michael Gerrish&lt;/strong&gt; is best known as the author of &lt;em&gt;The Mind-Body Makeover Project: A 12-Week Plan for Transforming Your Body and Your Life.&lt;/em&gt; He only discovered his amazing intuitive gift about four years ago after a long illness. It&amp;rsquo;s not something he had ever hoped for yet it is an ability that has launched him into a new calling with which to help people.&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Michael is an intuitive who has the rare ability to see directly inside your very being in order to identify your strengths, aspirations and gifts &amp;mdash; even those you might not yet recognize &amp;mdash; as well as the challenges and fears that need your attention. I have yet to see any psychic or channel equal the loving, non-judgmental emotion that pours out of Michael when giving readings.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bob Olson, editor, &lt;a href="http://ofspirit.com/"&gt;OfSpirit.com&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href="http://bestpsychicmediums.com/"&gt;BestPsychicMediums.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/divider.jpg" width="501" height="22" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Finding the Balance between Nutrition and a Busy Lifestyle!&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/Kristen.jpg" width="140" height="155" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px 5px 0px 0px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kristen Overlock &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;BS Nutrition, Certified Colon Hydrotherapist (CCHT), &lt;br /&gt;Certified Raw &amp;amp; Living Foods Lifestyle Educator, I-ACT Certified, Reiki Master &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.revitalive.com/"&gt;Revitalive Health &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Over the last fifteen years, Kristen has developed a unique and compassionate approach to helping clients achieve the health and vitality that is rightfully theirs!&amp;nbsp; As an expert in the field of raw and vegan nutrition, Kristen has helped her clients strike the nutritional balance that works best for them. Learn simple strategies to integrate a whole food approach to eating into your life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/divider.jpg" width="501" height="22" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #4925d9"&gt;The Shift Doctors- Self Healing with Color &amp;amp; Sound to Shift Your Life!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/2009-07-22-Tracy-14-e1298083275408.jpg" width="125" height="187" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/2009-07-22-Marion-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/2009-07-22-Marion-1-e1298083753451.jpg" width="125" height="187" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracy Latz, M.D., M.S.&lt;/strong&gt; is an Integrative Psychiatrist, Medical Intuitive and has served as an Associate Clinical Faculty member in the Department of Psychiatry at the Wake Forest University School of Medicine. She holds a Masters degree in Immunobiology, doctorates in Metaphysics &amp;amp; Holistic Healing, certifications in Mind-Body Medicine and is currently in private practice in a suburb of Charlotte, NC with over 19 years of clinical experience in shifting lives.&lt;a href="http://www.shiftyourlife.com/"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Shift Your Life&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/wp-content/uploads/2009-07-22-Marion-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marion Ross, Ph.D.&lt;/strong&gt; holds doctorates in Holistic Healing, Metaphysics, and Transpersonal Psychology as well as a certification in Mind Body Medicine. She has successful practices in Paris, France and New York City. &amp;nbsp;Tracy and Marion have created 2 guided meditation CDs for self-healing and have written two books including the latest bestseller titled &amp;ldquo;Shift: A Woman&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Transformation&amp;rdquo;. Their first book is &amp;ldquo;SHIFT: 12 Keys to Shift Your Life&amp;rdquo;. They are contributing authors to the collaborative book titled &amp;ldquo;2012: Creating Your Own Shift&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr.&amp;rsquo;s Latz and Ross have taught classes and seminars in vibrational medicine &amp;amp; personal transformation since 2002. They also teach courses in Reiki, Color and Sound Healing, Energy Psychology, Energy Medicine, Meditation and other Metaphysical Topics. Dr.&amp;rsquo;s Latz &amp;amp; Ross teach regularly at the L.A. County Jail, have been sponsored by the New York Public to teach in Harlem in 2010, are teaching in SHIFT Charlotte March 2011 , and teach private seminars and courses regularly. Our website is: &lt;a href="http://www.shiftyourlife.com/"&gt;www.shiftyourlife.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304785274000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>For those with an admitted yearning to be more in tune, please feast your eyes here:
http://www.vibrantlifeexpo.com/
I will be there, offering free demos. Of what you ask?.... Ah, magic, my friends, pure magic. sharie camren .com</why><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303858359000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual Vibrant Life Expo in Newburyport</name><id>17444696</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304780400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/17444696/</event_url></item>