<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's take the road less travelled. We'll ascend via Falling Waters (beginning at the Lafayette Place parking lot) to the peak of Little Haystack. Once we reach the peak of Little Haystack we will take the Franconia Ridge Trail north towards the peak of Lincoln and then Lafayette.  We will then descend by taking the Garfield Ridge trail over to the less often travelled Skookumchuck Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a lovely trail with lots of water features and it  is steep, so I intend to take my time and enjoy the climb.  My general rule of thumb is to take breaks a least every 1 hour or as needed.  And for this trail, I expect to take at least some some good pictures!  If the weather does not look like it will be good, I will reschedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Book time is 8 hr 30 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;  Plan on it taking this long +/- about an hour.  This hike is dog-friendly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the US 3 parking lot for the Skookumchuck Trail, .3 miles south of the junction of US3 and NH141, just north of the point where US 3 divides from I-93 and the Franconia Notch parkway (more specific directions to follow) and then carpool to the Lafayette Place Parking lot near the hiker information center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plagerized From the White Mountain Guide for Your Benefit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Falling Waters  to peak of Little Haystack (Ascent)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;3hr 5 min&lt;br /&gt;4760'&lt;br /&gt;3.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;3000 feet elevation gain&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail begins at the Lafayette Place parking lots and climbs to the Franconia Ridge trail at the summit of Little Haystack Mountain, passing numerous waterfalls in its lower part.  I&lt;b&gt;t is steep and rough in parts&lt;/b&gt; and better for ascent than descent...the trail begins in common with the Old Bridle Path and passes through a clarning into the woods.  At .2mi it turns sharp right from the Old Bridle Path and immediately crosses &lt;b&gt;Walker Brook&lt;/b&gt; on a bridge then leads away from the brook, heading southeast and east.  At .7 mi it crosses &lt;b&gt;Dry Brook&lt;/b&gt;, turns left and follows up the south bank to a beautiful cascade known as &lt;b&gt;Stairs Falls&lt;/b&gt;.  Above the falls, the trail passes beneath &lt;b&gt;Sawteeth Ledges&lt;/b&gt; and crosses the brook to the north bank just below &lt;b&gt;Swiftwater Falls&lt;/b&gt; which descend 60 ft into a shady glen.  Continuing on the north bank the trail climbs on graded switchbacks for a short distance to an old logging road that rises gradually in the narrow gorge of Dry Brook.  The trail leaves the old road at a steep embankment, ascends in graded sections to &lt;b&gt;Cloudland Falls&lt;/b&gt; (80 ft high) and climbs steeply to a viewpoint overlooking the head of the falls and out over the valley toward Mt. Moosilauke on the skyline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the head of Cloudland Falls are &lt;b&gt;two small (25 ft) falls&lt;/b&gt; practically facing each other.  The one to the south, which emerges from the woods, is on the branch of Dry Brook that runs down Little Haystack, while the other is on the Mt. Lincoln branch.  The trail continues steeply on the north bank of the Mt. Lincoln branch, soon crosses to the south bank, crosses back to the north side, climbs to and follows an old logging road and recrosses to the south bank at 1.6 mi.  Here it swigs to the right, away from the brook and angles uphill on an old logging road.  After a view (cut) to the west, the trail takes the left fork of the old road, then diverges to the left off the road and ascends the ridge via a series of switchbacks.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Franconia Ridge Trail (Section)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Book Time 1hr 10 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This section of the Franconia Ridge Trail ( Little Haystack to Lincoln and then Lafayette) is described as follows:  &amp;quot;...the trail follows a broad, nearly level ridgecrest in the open to the foot of Mt. Lincoln, then ascends sharply, keeping mostly to the east of the crest of the knife-edged ridge between Mt. Lincoln and Little Haystack Mtn, which has steep slopes on both sides.  After passing over the summit of Mt Lincoln, the trail descends to a sag, climbs across a prominent hump, then descends to another sag where it passes through a small scrub patch that might provide some shelter in bad weather.  The trail then climbs at a moderate grade to the Summit of Mt. Lafayette, where it meets the Greenleaf Trail on the left and the Garfield Ridge Trail which continues straigh ahead along the north ridge.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Garfield Ridge Trail (Section)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Book Time:  25 minutes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This section of the Garfield Ridge Trail (from the Peak of Lafayette to the Skookumchuck) is described as &amp;quot;the trail leaves the summit of Mt. Lafayette and runs north along the ridge of the north peak to a junction on the left with the Skookumchuck Trail on a shoulder at .8 mi.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Skookumchuck Trail (Descent)&lt;/span&gt;(We are doing this IN REVERSE from the way it is described)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;3hr 40 min&lt;br /&gt;4.3 miles&lt;br /&gt;3000 feet elevation loss&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Skookumchuck trail is an attractive and less frequently used route from the Franconia Notch area to the North ridge of Lafayette, .8 miles below the summit.  Leaving the parking lot, the trail runs south leading gradually away from the highway and crossing a grassy logging road three times.  At 1.1 miles, it reaches the old route at the edge of Skookumchuck Brook and follows the brook upstream.  At 1.8 miles it crosses a small tributary on a rock bridge, climbs steeply away from the brook on rock steps, continues up the valley well above the brook at a moderate grade through a fine stand of birch.  At 2.5 miles it passes a small brook (unreliable) and continues to a shoulder at 3.6 miles, where there is a glimpse ahead to Lafayette's north peak.  After a short gradual descent, the trail angles to the north at mostly easy grades then emerges above treeline just before reaching the junction with the Garfield Ridge Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL.  I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). &lt;b&gt;I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283304242000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280761115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lafayette, Lincoln and Little Haystack via Falling Waters to Skookumchuck</name><id>14290743</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283083200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14290743/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/a/global_16921818.jpeg</photo_url></item>