<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.347622</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-357-7387</phone><name>DoggieDay Playcenter</name><city>Boston</city><id>668961</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068500</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover fees and goodies</description><amount>4.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I'm changing our originally posted meetup on Saturday the 13th to Sunday the 14th to an indoor meetup at Doggie Day (2 blocks down from Peter's Park) to celebrate the holidays!  Bring some champagne, coffee or beverage of your choice (I'll have cups) or people goodies (I'll have the doggie goodies) It'll be at 10:00 AM since that seems to be working for most people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the place:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.doggieday.com/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.doggieday....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, DD is having a fundraiser for the Lowell Humane Society and the doggie meetup group that donates the most, wins a free party after the 1st.  They are taking everything from animal toys, clothes etc (all animals) to gift cards at Target (or similar) or grocery gift cards for employee needs.  Think about anything that would be of use to their wonderful cause. Oh and they take cash too!  So bring something for them on the 14th or when you go to have your dog's pic taken with Santa on the 6th or 7th at DD.  Just make sure they know what meetup you are from so we can get credit.  Hint hint; Old Navy has great doggie stuff for little $$$$. I know we are all tightening the belts but it's worth it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetups will continue at DD thru March as it's just too cold for all of us already.  We have the option of holding them 2 times a month (2nd Sunday and 4th Saturday at 10AM please let me know which you prefer or both) I know a bunch of our members can't join on Saturdays so this might be a nice change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doggie Day care does not charge us to use their faciity so I encourage you to make purchases at their boutique or use them for other services (grooming, sitting etc) as this is an awesome place!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Terri &amp;amp; Simon &amp;amp; Louie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation procedure: Unless there is a snowstorm we are on! I'll email around 8AM if the weather we cancel.  Please use your discretion driving in foul weather.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Meetup.com charges each group a $15 a month meetup fee. This is a GROUP fee and if not paid, our Boston French Bulldog meetups, would not exist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizer is in charge of paying this fee every month. It would be greatly appreciated if at each meetup, each member can submit a donation that goes towards the monthly $15 fee. Give $1, give $10. If at the end of the meetup, the organizer has not collected enough to meet the $15, she will pay the difference. If she receives more than $15, the extra would go towards the next meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll see you inside-just ask for the Frencie Meetup</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231712134000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226161033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Bulldog Holiday Party</name><id>9120341</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229266800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/9120341/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/3/global_6429059.jpeg</photo_url></item>