<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Mohegan Sun Boulevard</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06382</zip><lat>41.460000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mohegan Sun Casino</name><city>Uncasville</city><id>530065</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.110000</lon></venue><fee><label>Bus Trip</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;You Are a Winner and you know this!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an exciting day at Mohegan Sun Casino!&lt;/b&gt;  -- &lt;i&gt;One of the world's most amazing destinations with some of New England's finest dining, hotel accommodations, retail shopping, live entertainment, sporting events and luxurious day spa!!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip cost:  $25.00/PP&lt;br /&gt;You will receive a $10.00 Meal Coupon &amp;amp; 2 - $10.00 Free Bets on the big 6 wheel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tour Bus Schedule&lt;/u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Departure: 7:00AM Sharp&lt;br /&gt;Evening:Bus departs the Casino at 5:00pm Sharp                   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience more action and excitement than you ever thought possible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Play the games, shop til you drop or spend a day indulging yourself in the spa!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Surround yourself with a spectacle of sights and sounds. The Mohegan Sun's vast array of more than 6,000 slot machines will dazzle your senses, and with the great variety of table games there's something for everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A world at play and a world to its own, Mohegan Sun, created in 1996 by the Mohegan Tribe of Connecticut, is one of the world's most amazing destinations with some of New England's finest dining, hotel accommodations, retail shopping, live entertainment and sporting events. It is also host to a luxurious day spa, convention center and meeting facility, as well as three major entertainment venues with seating from 300 to 10,000. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohegan Sun serves up nearly 300,000 square feet of gambling action 24 hours a day, 365 days a year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Elemis Spa and Fitness Center Pass:&lt;/u&gt;  Spa Day Pass/Non-Hotel Guest ... 1 day / $25&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can purchase a pass to use our facilities...including relaxation area, jacuzzi bath, sauna, steam and gymnasium. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use of robes, slippers,herbal teas, refreshment and amenities are included in the price, along with selected&lt;br /&gt;exercise classes. If you are booked in for a spa treatment, use of the facilities are free of charge for the day including use of the gymnasium. Please contact the spa manager for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: coral"&gt;For more information on Mohegan Sun click this link:  &lt;a href="http://mohegansun.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://mohegansun.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mohegansun.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Spa treatments and pricing click this link: &lt;a href="http://mohegansun.com/spa/treatments.jsp" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://mohegansun.com/spa/treatments.jsp" target="_blank"&gt;http://mohegansun.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be parked at the Firestone Tire Co., Liberty Tree Mall -  Peabody - Blue Oldsmobile --meet at 6:15 am (Dunkin Doughnuts is really close by) **Get there before the bus fills up and leaves at 7AM SHARP!!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205185917000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>No driving!  Get discounts on this group trip!  It's only one day!  See an indoor 7-story waterfall, the world's largest planetarium dome and the awe-inspiring Wombi Rock, a glowing crystal mountain of imported stone in the Casino of the Sky!</why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>divorcesupport-249</urlname><id>368805</id><group_lat>42.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Boston/Burbs Life after Divorce Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204421933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"one day" - Mohegan Sun "Winners Trip"</name><id>7442955</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204974900000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/divorcesupport-249/events/7442955/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/3/e/global_3365438.jpeg</photo_url></item>