<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197-203 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.743869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 246-5700</phone><name>The Alchemy Juice Bar &amp; Growing Green Co-op</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1035078</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689453</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Special Community Ceremony for our Family &amp;amp; Friends ~ &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please join us in celebration of or accomplishment to choose love above all else! As many of you may know John and I are declaring our sovereignty from one another and to the world. It has been a beautiful and challenging decade walking side by side. Although our love for one another is immense, intense and passionate we recognize that is time for our journey to take us on dif&lt;span&gt;...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;ferent paths. This is not to say that we shall never weave in and out along the way&amp;hellip;.but it is time for us to fly solo and discover who we are and what we can do without the other.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In our enmeshment we have lost parts of ourselves. The overwhelming challenges, painful insights and harsh lessons along the way have enabled us to both grow in ways beyond what we each knew was possible. With one another we have revealed our most intimate and vulnerable selves and trusted more than most do in a lifetime. We have fulfilled our sacred agreement with one another to heal and transform. Releasing one another this past year from a place of power, respect and love is has been one of the most difficult and rewarding tasks. From it has blossomed greater admiration and appreciation than ever before.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We also recognize the impact that our relationship and the dream we manifested together has had on those around us - mostly our children, but all of you. We want to publicly vow our commitment to one another and ask that you serve as witnesses of this love of the highest order &amp;ndash; this new paradigm of the masculine and feminine that we are all ushering in. It is a time where limiting patterns, fear-based beliefs and outdated strategies are no longer tolerable. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As we all adjust to the new frequencies things are beginning to shatter around us. We are being asked to embrace our most authentic selves and communicate with others in the most loving ways possible. If we cannot honor and get along with the ones we love so dearly, how will there ever be peace on earth? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We are all One. And all of you are interwoven within the tapestry we have threaded together one string at a time. It has been even more precarious and laborious to dismantle the dream than it was to create it - but in doing so we are co-creating the world as we want it to be from a place of intention, awareness and consciousness never before realized.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Everything is possible in this new reality that is unfolding before us. Our commitment to ourselves, to our family and to our community is unchanged, yet different. Within it holds the possibility of what we have all been visioning all along. Please join me in this celebration of authentic abundance and the highest form of love attainable. We are all worthy and deserving of such a love. No more must we settle for less and sabotage true beauty for the sake of illusionary world we have all been living in. Together we will stand and hold this point for true love without limits. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Thank you for sharing in the journey ~ I love you all and am most grateful for your embrace, love &amp;amp; support. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Imani &amp;amp; John &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please bring an organic dish to share &amp;amp; any contributions to our altar that reflect our relationship&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#65279;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307410176000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306586915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Freedom Ceremony</name><id>20045211</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307304000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/20045211/</event_url></item>