<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(between Causeway St &amp; Traverse St) </address_2><address_1>262 Friend St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364685</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 367-0544</phone><name>The Greatest Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>706579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061333</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Boston Blazers are back at the Garden and are currently having an outstanding season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Never been to a professional lacrosse game? Why not come out and join Things To Do Boston on April 4th and find out what it’s all about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have put together an amazing package that won’t break the bank and all but guarantee a good time.&lt;br /&gt;We will kick off the evening at The Greatest Bar (across the street from the Garden) where your purchase of a ticket gets you a personal size pizza and beer to start the night off right. After that we’ll head over to the Garden for our private tour of the field. (Time permitting, we will be able to actually head out on the field for some impromptu wind sprints or to just say hi to a few of the Blazers.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following our tour its game time! We will be escorted to our seats where we can enjoy some quality lacrosse from one of the top teams in the National Lacrosse League. This game could have some serious implications on the team’s playoff chances given it’s the second to last home game of the season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the game, if you’re not to warn out, we are invited to Johnnies On The Side for the official players after party. Here we can relax from the long day with our group and mingle with the players when they arrive later in the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To purchase tickets go to:&lt;br /&gt;www.thingstodoboston.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click on &amp;quot;See the full calendar&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $30 until 5pm on 3/20.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>7970205</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240529816000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1382</urlname><id>1275022</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Things To Do: BOSTON</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236369554000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blazers game at The Garden</name><id>9897832</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238878800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1382/events/9897832/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/9/global_5450809.jpeg</photo_url></item>