<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>AGENDA for July 10th BostonLOA Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's July, mid point of 2007.....let's take a pause, reflect on what you're THANKFUL for in your LOA journey these past 6 months. Come share your small and big victories. Let's celebrate together!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you in DAILY GRATITUDE? Are you able to find the good in a situation and be thankful for your experience?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GRATITUDE is so very important in energizing the Law Of Attraction in your life. Why? Being Thankful and Appreciative is a very high energy, positive vibration of thought. It is powerfully attractive!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'The grateful mind is constantly fixed upon the best, therefore it will receive the best.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Wallace Wattles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By being grateful, it's a way of making sure we're putting the highest possible positive energy on our desires and withholding energy from doubts and fears that we don't want. We open ourselves up to receiving &amp;quot;exponentially&amp;quot; more of what we want in our lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suzy Spivey, Life Coach and BostonLOA member, will present recent research on the power of gratitude and the role gratitude plays in manifesting your dreams. She will share practical tips with us for incorporating gratitude into our lives and putting the POWER of GRATITUDE to work more easily and effortlessly everyday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you very much, Suzy, for your gift of time and facilitation at our July meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have a wonderful July 4th! and yes, everyone... come and &amp;quot;delight&amp;quot; us with your small and big manifestations next Tuesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ChewHoong and Dave&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Suzy Spivey&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suzy brings contagious enthusiasm and purpose to her coaching, speaking, consulting, and dance workshops. With 20+ years of corporate experience in marketing, editorial, and sales management, Suzy knows what it takes to succeed. She has worked with both small and large businesses to increase sales, build successful relationships and increase visibility through innovative marketing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In her coaching, she specializes in helping others realize their potential and create abundance in every area of their lives. Bringing clarity and laser focus to her clients, Suzy will help you get crystal clear about your dreams, believe in your potential to make them a reality, and stay focused on moving forward with positive action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suzy received her coach training from Coaches Training Institute (CTI), one of the first educational institutions to develop and offer coach training. Suzy is also a certified Dance Instructor of JourneyDance?, Shake Your Soul?, and Kripalu Dancekinetics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit www.suzyspivey.com for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>31</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184391336000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>59</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181088197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction July Meetup</name><id>5858008</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184108400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/5858008/</event_url></item>