<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;IMPORTANT: Please be sure to read the entire event listing before you RSVP - then answer the questions that are part of the RSVP process. While the objective of this event is to enjoy ourselves, your safety, and the safety of the others, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands, overestimate your skills and abilities, or come unprepared you may put yourself and/or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If I haven't yet hiked with you, I will contact you to ensure that this trip will indeed constitute an enjoyable and safe fit with your background and interests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIFFICULTY RATING:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Intermediate-Advanced/3+&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trip is somewhat more difficult than a typical Intermediate outing for two reasons.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; First, we will be slightly over the Intermediate elevation gain limit of 3,000', and second, we will be hiking in winter conditions.&amp;nbsp; On the flip side, though I personally am a fast hiker, I will be leading this trip at a &lt;strong&gt;moderate&lt;/strong&gt; pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What We Are Doing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North Twin Mountain Winter Gear Welcoming&amp;nbsp;Fest !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come the 26th, predictions are that significant snow will have fallen in the Whites - enough to enable some skiing and snowshoeing, but not so much as to render bare boots, MicroSpikes and crampons pointless.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; In short, this is the perfect Saturday to get the cobwebs out of whatever combination of winter touring options you're most interested in working on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The geographic objective of the day is the 4761-foot summit of North Twin Mountain via a 6.8 mile route (one way), with 3300' of elevation gain.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; The route includes the 2.5 mile length of Haystack Road, followed by the 4.3-mile North Twin Trail.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; If you would love an opportunity to unfurl your XC/BC skis for the season, the first 4 miles are level enough to let you go to town (well, in this case, to the mountain&amp;hellip;).&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Not interested in skiing?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Well then how about donning those snowshoes or giving yourself a bare boot workout?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Whatever option you choose, we'll stay generally together as a group.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the trail steepens , those of us who skied will dismount and switch to whatever combination of snowshoes, MicroSpikes and crampons we'd like.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; How long the ascent takes will depend on the exact conditions we encounter.&amp;nbsp; Once at the summit, we'll check the time and see if a quick out-and-back to nearby South Twin (4902') is an option.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; If so, and if group sentiment is unanimously in favor, we'll grab it before heading back down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we arrive back at parking lot, it will be with the satisfaction of knowing that we're now dialed back in for winter hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important Notes on Participation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I haven't hiked with you before, I will contact you as soon as I can to ensure that this trip will indeed constitute an enjoyable and safe fit with your background and interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests are permitted only if&amp;nbsp;you provide me with everyone's full name,&amp;nbsp;e-mail address, cell phone number, and responses to all the sign-up questions.&amp;nbsp; I can then follow up with people as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs are permitted on this hike provided they are well-behaved, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, you clean up after them, and you have a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, or other situations and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here - meaning we might not reach the summit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.20288163884399&amp;amp;lon=-71.55773162841797&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for the current weather conditions and forecast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full winter gear is required for this hike.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; If you are not sure what this means, please check out the winter day hike gear list at &lt;a href="http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Winter_Dayhike_equip.pdf"&gt;http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Winter_Dayhike_equip.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You do not need to bring the gear specified under "Above Tree Line".&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Also, as described above, nordic skis will be useful and fun, but are optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be meeting on Rt. 3 just west of Twin Mountain, NH.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; The exact spot is TBD and I'll update the confirmed participants once it's finalized.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; From Boston, you should allow 2 hours and 30 minutes of driving time, not counting coffee/gas/food/bathroom stops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While carpooling is encouraged, you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Legal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to being posted as a Random Group of Hikers meet-up, this trip is also an official AMC trip, and you will need to sign the AMC's standard release agreement when we meet.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; If you are not familiar with this agreement, you can see it here:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease-2.pdf"&gt;http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease-2.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Questions?&amp;nbsp; Don't hesitate to contact me as needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322881431000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322033925000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Twin Mountain Winter Gear Welcoming Fest! (Intermediate-Advanced/3+)</name><id>42144012</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322312400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/42144012/</event_url></item>