<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building E51, Room 335</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>376848</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please RSVP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special Notice:&lt;/b&gt; Basil Chapman, developer of the Chapman Wave, will be at the Tigers meeting - from 5:30 to 6:50. See the description in the Boston Tigers section below the feature talk description of Kieran's presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feature Talk: &lt;b&gt;Follow the Leaders - How to Search for Leading Companies Using Investors Business Daily and Investors.com by Kieran McDonough of McDonough Wealth Advisors, LLC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;b&gt;Kieran McDonough&lt;/b&gt; presents his 3rd IBD talk to us. He will show us how to find CANSLIM quality stocks. He will go through in detail the fundamental analysis he uses to screen for leading stocks. CAN SLIM is the IBD system of buying the best fundamental companies during up trending markets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: &lt;b&gt;Mr. McDonough&lt;/b&gt; manages money for high net-worth investors using this time proven strategy.  Find him at &lt;a href="http://www.raymondjames.com/Branches/c2c/4qx/mcdonough/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.raymondjam...&lt;/a&gt; or at www.canslimadvisor.com He is also an instructor at the Intermediate Strategies for Successful Investing workshop for Investors Business Daily: &lt;a href="http://www.investors.com/seminar/level2.asp?src=WSHPSMR" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.investors....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His firm is:&lt;br /&gt;McDonough Wealth Advisors, LLC.&lt;br /&gt;Registered Investment Adviser&lt;br /&gt;100 City Hall Plaza Suite 305&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02108&lt;br /&gt;(617) 720-5700&lt;br /&gt;(866) 388-0122(fax)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING Announcement:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 to 6:50 - Basil Chapman, developer of the Chapman Wave,  will be speaking at the Tiger's Meeting.  Basil will focus on a Chapman Wave chart analysis of the current IBD100 stocks - including projection as to where they are headed.  Come early as there is a social gathering at 5:30 as well. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; to see the full announcement. For questions, see Bob Pod at bpodd@softwareresults.com. The meeting is in the same room as the 7:00 meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda for the meetup will be:&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:50 Pre-Meeting with Boston Tigers, led by Bob Podd&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Market Talk, Virtual Trading and Insights from the New York Traders Expo, Feature Talk (see above)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Virtual Trading game is up and running!&lt;/b&gt; Directions are at:&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/browse_thread/thread/ff5e030eb15a6c7c/7dab7a5592adbc28?lnk=gst&amp;amp;q=simulator#7dab7a5592adbc28" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Please be sure to choose a name that we can identify with you! Otherwise it is anonymous!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204465164000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>75</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199140536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Investor's Business Daily February Meetup</name><id>7001800</id><headcount>76</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204156800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/7001800/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/e/global_938062.jpeg</photo_url></item>