<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Revere Beach Pkwy</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02151</zip><lat>42.400932</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Revere Beach, William G. Reinstein Bandstand</name><city>Revere</city><id>701555</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.997554</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Guys, the Sand Sculpting Festival is back in Revere, and we're headed there catch these transient works of art (and get a little beach time in the process)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festival runs from July 14-20th, and we're headed there on Saturday, to get a sense of the almost completed projects, while still getting a chance to see the sculptors at work.  Check out the website at :&lt;a href="http://www.reverebeachpartnership.com/nessf07/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.reverebeac...&lt;/a&gt; for an idea of what you're going to see.  Keep checking back to the site for details on the schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Revere Beach is easily accessible by T, and that's probably your best bet due to the nightmare parking can provide.  Revere Beach on the blue line, and you can either get off at the Revere Beach or Wonderland Station.  Parking spots are available at  the Wonderland station if ya wanna risk it.  The sand castle competition is closer to the Revere Beach Station, and that'll be my destination via T   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet between 11:30-11:45, as best the T allows:-) The competition is based at the William G. Reinstein Bandstand (gazebo looking thing...photo available at &lt;a href="http://www.beautyinrevere.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beautyinre...&lt;/a&gt;) and it's going to be mobscene, but shoot to localize around this landmark.  Will be sending my cell number to my yes's and maybe's both Thursday and Friday night prior in case there are any last minute additions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will plan on grabbing some lunch there, walking around the sculptures, maybe hanging on the beach a bit, and head out in time for any evening events you have scheduled.  There are a ton, from the Italian festival (&lt;a href="http://www.italiaunita.org/festivals/agenda.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.italiaunit...&lt;/a&gt;) to Shakespeare on the Commons (that's my planned destination  &lt;a href="http://www.citicenter.org/shows/lists/details.php?showID=423" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.citicenter...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.bostoncentral.com/events/free_shakespeare_on_the_common_boston/p1020.php;" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostoncent...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring funds for food, and, if ya want some beach time, bathing suit, beach towel, sunscreen (probably a good idea regardless) etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check back for details regarding rain changes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, contact Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>23</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216654433000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214245538000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Sand Sculpting Festival at Revere Beach</name><id>8198238</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216481400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8198238/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>