<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC's Cabot Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1487529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;While you can use this event listing to get together with other randomites who are going and to coordinate car pooling, you need to officially regsiter for this program on the AMC website by clicking &lt;a href="http://www.hbbostonamc.org/index.php/Table/Fall-Leadership-Program/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Would you like to plan and lead your own trips? If so, then AMC Leader Training is a great place to start. &amp;nbsp;I took this class several years ago and I often refer back to the information and materials that were part of the learning process - a process that includes lectures, workshops, and hands-on activities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This is a great way to get an learn more about putting together and leading your own trips - whether it's with the Random Group, the AMC, or just a bunch of your friends. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This training program provided by volunteer leaders emphasizes group dynamics, leader responsibilities, trip planning/management, decision-making skills, and how to handle accidents and emergencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;You will learn great skills in this supportive and fun environment by engaging in role playing, decision games, and group planning exercises. &amp;nbsp;Enrollment is limited and previous participation on AMC trips is required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The course consists of two evening classes (Tuesday October 25 and November 1) at AMC Headquarters and one weekend event (Friday November 11 to Sunday November 13).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The $50 registration fee covers training, materials, weekend lodging and meals (except lunches). Space is limited to 30 participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The program takes place at AMC Cabot Auditorium located at 4 Joy Street in Boston, MA. It's near the Park Street T Station, the Massachusetts State House and the Boston Common. Discount parking passes are available for the Boston Common Garage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;There are two kinds of people in this world: Leaders and followers. This is your opportunity to become a Leader.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TO REGISTER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Send and email the Registrar, Sonya Korabelnikova @&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:s_korabel@yahoo.com" target="_blank"&gt;s_korabel@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320784585000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315945828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC's 2011 Fall Leadership Program - Class 1 of 3</name><id>33422602</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319583600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/33422602/</event_url></item>