<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>48 Spring Street,</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02341</zip><lat>42.075536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 447-2592</phone><name>The Olde Hitching Post Restaurant </name><city>Hanson</city><id>1124830</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.883763</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;But there never seems to be enough time to do the things you wanna do once you find them...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh - Hi, everybody! You'll have to excuse Mike... Every once in awhile he just spontaneously starts channeling Jim Croce...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That particular song makes a good point, though. After all, isn't making the time to do some of the things that we'd really like to do but haven't been doing a big part of what Meetup is really about? Case in Point: When was the last time you went out for breakfast with a few friends? Yeah, we thought so. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, don't worry, fellow diners! Because once again, your friendly neighborhood Meetup group is here to make things not just ok, but delicious! Yes, on this month's last Saturday morning, when we all wake up with a case of the post-Thanksgiving, I-don't-want-to-cook-anything blues, we are heading to &lt;a href="http://www.oldehitchingpost.com/default.htm" target="_blank"&gt;The Olde Hitching Post&lt;/a&gt; in Hanson, to tie on the feedbag and congratulate each other on surviving yet another L-tryptophan overdose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Olde Hitching Post is something of a rarity in these parts; a fine dining establishment that serves all three meals. Mike has dined there over the years and always enjoyed the restaurant's comfortable atmosphere and seasonally changing menu. We'll be meeting there at 10:00 AM on Saturday, November 28th. We are looking forward to introducing the group to a restaurant worth knowing about in an area where the choices are somewhat sparse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Olde Hitching Post&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 28th, 2009 @ 10:00 AM&lt;br /&gt;48 Spring Street (Route 58)&lt;br /&gt;Hanson, MA&lt;br /&gt;(781) 447-2592&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.oldehitchingpost.com/Default.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Olde Hitching Post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up to 2 per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Their breakfast menu isn't online, but a quick phone conversation indicated that omellettes run in the $6.00 - $7.00 range, with more basic selections costing less. Not a budget-buster, in other words.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members - None. Group Members and Guests - $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Friday, November 27th @ 7:00 PM. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer. Changes to No after this point will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions (Credit to Hitching Post Website):&lt;/b&gt; The Olde Hitching Post is located at 48 Spring Street (Route 58) in Hanson. We are providing directions starting from Route 3, but many members wil be able to pick them up starting from local roads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3 North (Coming from Cape Cod):&lt;/b&gt; Take Route 3 to Exit 9 (Route 3A). Head North on Route 3A for about 1 mile to its intersection with Route 106. Turn left (West) onto Route 106 until the road forks, then bear right onto Route 27 North.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 27 for about 8 miles to its intersection with Route 58. Turn right (North) onto Route 58 and follow the road for about 3 miles. The Olde Hitching Post will be on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3 South (Coming from Braintree/Boston):&lt;/b&gt; Take Route 3 to Exit 16B (Route 18 South). Follow Route 18 for about 3 miles until its intersection with Route 58. Bear left onto Route 58 South. Follow Route 58 for about 7 miles. The Olde Hitching Post will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259641642000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258476604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tie up for breakfast!</name><id>11895287</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259420400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/11895287/</event_url></item>