<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;The Bystander Effect&amp;quot; has been in the news again.  Someone was mercilessly beat up after coming to the aid of a robbery victim.  No calls to the police were made for about an hour.  The victim died.  Also very recently, we all remember the horrifying video recording of a man getting run over by a car, and the subsequent scene of passing automobiles and pedestrians barely taking notice as they left the gravely injured man lying in the middle of the street.  The police weren't called until it was too late.  Is humanity as a whole this detestable?  In short, I’m afraid that the answer is largely, “Yes!” although I believe that we can still hope that our higher potential might yet be realized. &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Nietzsche is famous for his derision of the &amp;quot;herd mentality&amp;quot; that causes us, like sheep, to follow the latest fads or, worse, the horrors of mob rule.  Can philosophy save us from ourselves?  Psychology, as the science of human behavior, should not be castigated when it describes the various forms of weakness and moral depravity of which we as a species are capable.  Psychology only describes (and theorizes) human behavior, but a week or two ago when I watched a TV report on &amp;quot;the bystander effect&amp;quot;  the news anchor sort of casually said &amp;quot;psychologists have a name for this...,&amp;quot; and  I then got the feeling that the scientific explanation of &amp;quot;why&amp;quot; human beings can be lower than the lowest snake (and the snake as the symbol of evil is surely a self-reflective negative image of man himself) somehow acts to lessen the shame.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is a genetic redesigning of humankind (transhumanism) the only hope for evading the total demise of the human species.  I'm not sure of my own views on transhumanism but I am not prepared to give up the ship just yet. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Perhaps linking  &amp;quot;the bystander effect&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;herd mentality&amp;quot; is a bit of a stretch but I think not. Whistleblowers: you are my heroes!  Conformity can be a very good thing at times.  But so can nonconformity.  The distinction of when the one should be dominant over the other requires philosophy so that, as Nietzsche said, we might overcome ourselves.  What is your philosophy of overcoming?  And is overcoming human limitations the very essence of what it is to be human? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278977631000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273721184000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Bystander Effect," Herd Mentality and Philosophy as Antidote for Psychology</name><id>13469098</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276297200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/13469098/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/5/global_15069333.jpeg</photo_url></item>