<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356970</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Park Street Church</name><city>Boston</city><id>866187</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062172</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The holiday season is fast approaching, and you are likely experiencing a jumble of emotions that you've yet to sort out. Facing a holiday after a separation or divorce can be more difficult than your friends and family members may realize. The Surviving the Holidays video, discussion group and devotional material will help you not only to survive the holidays, but to find strength, healing and tools to move forward in your daily walk through these painful emotions. On the video you will meet experts who have experienced separation, divorce or another life tragedy. These people share honestly about: -Being prepared for surprising emotions that may hit over the holidays -What to do about family traditions and other coming changes -How to survive potentially awkward moments at holiday events -How to help your children have a good holiday experience -Where to find comfort, strength and hope in a seemingly hopeless time In your discussion group, you'll have the chance to talk with others in separation or divorce, discuss what you've learned on the video and ask questions about any concerns you have.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gregory R</member_name><member_id>10379020</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323533791000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Divorced-and-Separated</urlname><id>1521209</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Divorced and Separated</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317695571000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Surviving the Holidays</name><id>36039052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323529200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Divorced-and-Separated/events/36039052/</event_url></item>