<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>From: chris.gruener@comcast.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;911 Truth - Tuesday, 12/1 at 6:30 PM is when the next Meeting of the Greater Boston Alliance for 9/11 Truth and Justice is scheduled&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hello friends.   This note is to remind you that the next planning and organizing meeting of the Boston/Cambridge Chapter of The Greater Boston Alliance for 9/11 Truth and Justice (formerly the Boston 911 Truth Committee) will be this Tuesday (12/1) at 6:15.  This meeting's location is at Encuentro Cinco (E5), at 33 Harrison Avenue, 5th floor, in the Chinatown district of Boston.  This meeting generally lasts till 9PM so if you need to arrive a little late or leave a little early to accommodate your work or family needs that is fine.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the Boston/Cambridge Chapter meeting take the Orange Line to the Chinatown T Stop or take the Green Line to the Boylston Street T Stop.  Encuentro Cinco is located on Harrison Ave at the corner of Harrison and Beach Street. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To view a map of the meeting site, click on the link below or copy and paste it to your browser: &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Boston&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=33+Harrison+" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; -------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The next Newton Chapter of The Greater Boston Alliance for 9/11 Truth and Justice will be Thursday (12/10), from 4:15 - 6 PM.  The meeting will be at the Parish of Saint Paul in Newton Highlands.  Directions are below.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For the Newton meeting, by train, take the D train on the Green line to Newton Highlands.  Walk up the ramp and turn right on to Walnut Street.  Walk one block, and across the street,  to 1135 Walnut Street.   Enter at the Parish Hall door (to the left as you are facing the church). &lt;br /&gt;To view a map of the meeting site, click on the link below or copy and paste it to your browser: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Newton&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=1135+Walnut+St&amp;amp;zipcode=02461" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By car take the turnpike to 128 south.  After 1+ miles you  will see the sign for Route 9, which you take East toward Boston. About 1/4 mile after the first light you come to on route 9 you will see a poorly marked exit to Center Street.  Take that exit and loop around under Route 9, now going north on Center street.  At the first light turn left onto Walnut Street.  Two blocks up you will go through a light at Lincoln Street.  The Parish of Saint Paul is one block further on your left, # 1135 Walnut Street.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at [Chris Gruener] one of these meetings.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I can be reached on my cell phone at 617-965-6552 .  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259883784000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259386049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>911 Truth - Tuesday, 12/1 at 6:30 PMGreater Boston Alliance for 9/11 Truth meeti</name><id>11966353</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259710200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/11966353/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/5/global_7275445.jpeg</photo_url></item>