<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 County Rd </address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02806</zip><lat>41.737339</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Barrington Books- Shaws Plaza</name><city>Barrington</city><id>1071131</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.304153</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will ride south from the middle of the path, starting in Barrington, RI, for about 45 minutes, stop at the Bristol end of the path along the ocean boardwalk, eat lunch/ice cream (if people are interested), then head back to Barrington. This should be about 13 miles round-trip.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who prefer a longer ride may choose to continue north from Barrington on to the Providence end of the path and back (this will add another 16 miles round trip). Rain will cancel the ride. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-95 North and South:  &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 195 East to Exit 7, Route 114, towards Barrington. Follow route 114 until it narrows to a single lane road. You will come to a stop light (there will be a white church on the left and high school field on the right). Continue through this light straight into town. You'll pass through a couple more lights and you'll eventually see a large shopping center on your right (look for a Talbot's, Staples, and Shaws Supermarket). The bike trail runs along the side of the shopping center parking lot. Park in a spot near the trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please consider carpooling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dot.state..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dot.state....&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total Bike Path Length: 14.5 miles of paved bike path with connection to 3 miles of paved path in  &lt;br /&gt;Colt State Park in Bristol. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grade: Predominately flat with one steep hill in East Providence. Path exposed to  &lt;br /&gt;Narragansett Bay on upper and lower stretches, making for occasional stiff head winds. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail condition: Good to average. This is the state's oldest major bike path. A long  &lt;br /&gt;section in Barrington was resurfaced in 2001. Narrower than most newer bike paths. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special characteristics: This path provides a vision for all other bike paths in  &lt;br /&gt;Rhode Island, connecting five communities. Terrain is very diverse from city to urban  &lt;br /&gt;waterfront to bayfront to forested areas to neighborhoods and villages centers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Natural attractions nearby: Boating and fishing in Narragansett Bay. Passive  &lt;br /&gt;recreation in Colt State Park. Wildlife viewing at Audubon Society of Rhode Island  &lt;br /&gt;Education Center in Bristol, with long boardwalk bisecting the path. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Historical attractions nearby: Historic homes and shopping districts in East  &lt;br /&gt;side of Providence, Warren center, Bristol.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park behind Staples in the spots along the bike trail. We'll meet there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ilana</member_name><member_id>4194841</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1274581871000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Leisure Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-235</urlname><id>527341</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Boston Leisure Bicycling</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269785610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>East Bay Bike Path</name><id>13013861</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274540400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-235/events/13013861/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/1/global_1549089.jpeg</photo_url></item>