<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Na9bY9gmhw4"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Na9bY9gmhw4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Everyone needs to believe in something, I believe I'll have another beer."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/6/a/event_118593642.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day after our June dinner, I’ll Have Another, will try for the Belmont Stakes win. He wants “another” win for sure. Should this horse win this third and final spring stakes race, he will be the first horse since 1978 to win the Triple Crown. This is the most prestigious title in horseracing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blood horses are amazing creatures whose entire joy and reason for being is running and competing against other horses. People who have never been around these horses cannot conceive of the intelligence and focus they possess. These horses, which are not your everyday racehorses, come to the track to win. They push themselves to the point of bursting their own hearts just to be in front of the other horses. The jockey’s job in the race is to actually time the horse’s race, holding them back, judging their strength and energy, style and temperament so that they do not overrun themselves. Together they form a tactical team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Horseracing, like every sport in the world, has unethical people who participate and sometimes create bad headlines. This is especially true at the lower end of the racing community but for the most part racehorses, blood horses, are treated with respect and an amazing amount of very expensive care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that as cooks we are the jockey’s in the race to a tasty table. Good food comes with training, and care. Great cooking requires a passion and quality in both ingredients and chef. Great food comes with joy. When the ingredients are of the highest quality, and are treated with respect and care, the results can be amazing. It is the cook’s job to judge the ingredients flavor, aroma, texture and temperament so that the dish or menu does not fight itself. Together they form a creative team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooking, like most endeavors, has lazy or clueless people who participate and sometimes create a bad taste in your mouth. Even the best chef’s, the ones who are willing to take risks and try new things, sometimes have a failed product. These things happen, but when it all comes together, then we find ourselves inspired to say, “I’ll have another.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caryl will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp&amp;amp;v=ly7PONiKGUs"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp&amp;amp;v=ly7PONiKGUs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Address will be sent via email the Wednesday before the dinner</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340472346000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336489478000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>I'll have another</name><id>qxhmlcyqjblb</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339196400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/63920222/</event_url></item>