<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Hemlock Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.494524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Breakheart Reservation/Northeast Metro Tech</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>1061590</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.047448</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I apologize for not posting this information sooner!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll enter the Breakheart Reservation at the Hemlock Road entrance.  It's directly next to the Wakefield vocational high school.  Per Lisbeth, who suggested this location:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn onto Hemlock road (school will now be on your left and the fields on right); continue straight past landrigan field; stay to right of entryway and continue straight to end of parking lot as you enter another high school building parking lot; there is an entrance to the reservation on the right; since it will be Saturday you can park anywhere with no problem. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you get to the reservation and can't find anyone, please call my cell phone: 781-799-9935.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************WEATHER NOTICE********************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case of thunderstorms, please feel free to call me to in the morning.  If it's pouring and/or a thunderstorm, I will post a cancellation on the Meetup website and email everyone NLT 9:00.  But if it's drizzling, etc., I'd like people to call me (or email) and let me know their thoughts.  If we have to cancel, I will try to reschedule for next weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;Laura &amp;amp; Molly&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>790021</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276433323000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275232074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Shore Cavalier King Charles Spaniel June Meetup</name><id>13638695</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275744600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/13638695/</event_url></item>