<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Jen, the organizer of the Central CT comdedy, game night, and trivia group, is also an NHC member and would like to invite you to her group's first ever comedy jam! To the best of my knowledge, not only has the NHC never had one of these, but this will also be the first event of 2009.  You wanted &amp;quot;new&amp;quot;, there ya go! :-) Thanks Jen!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Jen is the contact for this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details below pasted from her website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/CT-Comedy-Game-Night-Trivia/calendar/9409809/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, January 3rd at 2PM-7PM at my clubhouse in Meriden 06450. Address will be e-mailed to Yes RSVPs day before/day of -- up until 10AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU'RE NOT A MEMBER OF COMEDY**GAME NIGHT** TRIVIA go here to register: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though the Central CT **Comedy**Game Night** Trivia** group is comprised&lt;br /&gt;mostly of comedy fans (versus comedians) a few of you have expressed&lt;br /&gt;interest in trying your hand at stand-up and/or improv comedy. I'm&lt;br /&gt;proposing we get together this coming weekend for the 1st ever Central&lt;br /&gt;CT Comedy Jam session. The purpose is to meet new people, come up with a&lt;br /&gt;little bit of comedy material and have some laughs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's how it works:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Introductions&lt;br /&gt;* I'll lead us through some exercises designed to 'extract the&lt;br /&gt;funny' from your observations/life experiences&lt;br /&gt;* We'll provide *constructive* feedback/jot down some ideas for&lt;br /&gt;fresh material--- could be used for an open mic night in the future or&lt;br /&gt;just to see what comes out&lt;br /&gt;* Time permitting we can go through a couple of Improv exercises&lt;br /&gt;or board games - I'll have a few on hand. If you'd like to bring any,&lt;br /&gt;feel free!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* A notebook, pen and your sense of humor!&lt;br /&gt;* There is a coffee machine at the venue and I'll provide some chips and salsa, otherwise if you'd like&lt;br /&gt;soda or another beverage/snack feel free to bring one.&lt;br /&gt;(As long as the beverages aren't in a glass bottle, they have a&lt;br /&gt;strange rule about glass on premises).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Just so you know, I am not an official comedy instructor but I&lt;br /&gt;have led improv groups, graduated from SAK Comedy University - Wayne&lt;br /&gt;Brady's Alma Mater (&lt;a href="http://www.sak.com...)"&gt;http://www.sak.com......&lt;/a&gt;, taken a couple of stand-up&lt;br /&gt;classes and performed at open mics. Plus my 'Supreme Goofball' status&lt;br /&gt;makes me extra qualified. Riiigghhhtt !? &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231198575000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230753460000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comdey Jam with the Central CT comedy, game night, and trivia group</name><id>9415123</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231009200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/9415123/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>