<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wainwright Bank Community Room</name><city>Somerville</city><id>505122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121956</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come to the&lt;br /&gt;Wainwright Community Room &lt;br /&gt;Elm St., Davis Square &lt;br /&gt;Somerville, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JOIN THE BOSTON DYKE MARCH COMMITTEE! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Dyke March committee is starting to plan the 2011 Dyke March!! &lt;br /&gt;...&lt;br /&gt;Help plan one of the country's largest and most progressive Dyke Marches and have a great time doing it. Meet new cuties and hotties and make new friends. The Boston Dyke March is a non-commercial, community-centered, grassroots, inclusive pride event. Come be a part of the action: plan fun events, network with cool people, build your resume, and help make the March what you want it to be. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being on the Boston Dyke March Committee means you are involved directly with the planning and organizing of the March through the year. The Boston Dyke March Committee is made up entirely of volunteers and new people are always welcome. No previous event planning experience is necessary, just willingness to work hard and have fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dyke March is for everyone: Dykes, Lesbians, Queers, Bi-Folks, Transwomen, Transmen, Genderqueers, and Allies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dyke March needs artists, writers, organizers, political activists, fun social people, quiet detail-oriented people, techies, photographers, handi-queers, inexperienced people who want to learn exciting new stuff, experienced people who like the freedom of grassroots organizing, fundraisers, shy people who like working in groups, rowdy people that make everyone laugh, single people just looking for new hotties, partnered people who love socializing, business types, academics, jack-of-all-trades. The Dyke March needs YOU!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jo</member_name><member_id>3137718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathleen</member_name><member_id>7438024</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caitlin Shea</member_name><member_id>9186981</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297905191000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends of the Boston Dyke March</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostondykemarch</urlname><id>997856</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Dyke March</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296045329000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekly Dyke March Planning Meeting</name><id>zrhjqypdbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297900800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostondykemarch/events/16534568/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/d/global_14537517.jpeg</photo_url></item>