<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mallinckrodt Building, Harvard University, 12 Oxford St, Cambridge 02138</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pfizer Auditorium</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1630603</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.138908</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/4/0/event_55466432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Join us for the next installment of the Science in the News spring lecture series, as our grad student friends from Harvard explore the thorny question of when scientists should keep their trap shut and avoid a media circus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science in the News is an organization of Harvard graduate students dedicated to bringing cutting edge research to the public in a fun and informative format.  Their lectures are clear and well presented, and allow for lots of questions and interaction from the audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lecture is from 7:00 to 9:00 (or thereabouts).  We'll begin gathering in the hallway at the entrance to the lecture hall about a half hour beforehand, then go in and get seats about 10-15 minutes before it starts.  There are snacks and refreshments, and afterwards we'll head to one of many Harvard Square watering holes for food, drinks, and discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group beforehand, just look for us outside the auditorium afterwards - we won't be too hard to find.  Just look for the two nerd herders wearing Meetup pins :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the SITN Website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next lecture (May 2nd) features three graduate students who will discuss censorship of science, using the recent avian flu study as an example. When a team of scientists discovered in 2011 how to make the deadly H5N1 “Avian flu” virus transmissible through air, it stirred a debate about scientific ethics and national security that has raged for months everywhere from the top levels of the National Institutes of Health to the front page of the New York Times. this lecture we address the questions swirling around this controversy: What was so dangerous about this discovery that led the US government to ask that a prestigious scientific journal censor the scientists’ reports,why are scientists pursuing such controversial research in the first place, and what role should the government take in controlling the dissemination of scientific advancements?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the entrance to the auditorium...we'll be wearing our Meetup pins</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1336079663000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334461626000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Avian Flu &amp; Scientific Censorship:When should scientists keep their mouths shut?</name><id>60621592</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335997800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/60621592/</event_url></item>