<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Fitchburg Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.375713</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brickbottom Artists Association Inc</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1530834</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084373</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's take a tour together of this wonderful open studios to see over 60 artists at the Brickbottom Studios in Somerville, where artists live and work in one of the nicest artist communities in Greater Boston. Many established and emerging artists. Afterwards we'll adjourn to a cafe' or restaurant.  Hope you can make it. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We'll meet in the first floor gallery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brickbottom is two large buildings right beside the McGrath/O'Brien Highway in Somerville across from Twin Cities Plaza. Visitor Parking is along Joy and Chestnut Street. Take note of the various signs for street cleaning Do not park in the resident's lot or alongside the building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here's what they say:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our 25th Annual Open Studios Event will take place the weekend before Thanksgiving, Saturday and Sunday, November 17th and 18th, 2012 from noon to 6pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Over 60 artists will be showing at Brickbottom and, just two blocks away, more than 50 artists will be showing at &lt;a href="http://www.joystreetartists.org/JoyStreetArtists.html" target="_blank"&gt;Joy Street Studios&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don't miss it.&lt;/strong&gt; See both up-and-coming and established artists' artwork in the studios where they were created. All media are represented from painting and sculpture to photography, digital art and environmental and performance art. Genres range from abstract to realistic and everything in between. Glass blowing, ceramics, printmaking, animation, sound, theatre and music will round out the multi-media event. Bring a photo to Brickbottom to add to &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/119737528176199/" target="_blank"&gt;Reciprocity Stream, our open photo show&lt;/a&gt; -- a new event in honor of our 25th anniversary!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the first floor gallery and I'll have something orange on (just in case you don't recognize me).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Q.</member_name><member_id>2269958</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353191485000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352718892000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brickbottom Open Studios</name><id>91029802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353180600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/91029802/</event_url></item>