<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.485957</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Minuteman Bikeway Bedford Terminus</name><city>Bedford</city><id>923527</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.277222</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey guys - a little stingy on the details right now but I wanted to at least get this on the calendar and will plan to update shortly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know it's getting cold out there but pull on those sweats and head out on the &lt;a href="http://www.minutemanbikeway.org/Media/MinutemanBikewayBrochure2.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Minuteman Bikeway&lt;/a&gt; for a ride through history:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Minuteman Bikeway passes through the historic area where the American Revolution began in April 1775.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, the Minuteman Bikeway is one of the most popular and successful rail-trails in the United States, enjoyed for both healthy recreation and transportation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bikeway has become a new type of “Main Street” where neighbors and strangers alike come together while riding, walking, or skating on the path.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2008, Rails-to-Trails Conservancy inducted the Minuteman Bikeway into the national Rail-Trail Hall of Fame.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Built by the Commonwealth of Massachusetts on an inactive railroad, the Minuteman Bikeway has become a treasured regional resource, used by local residents and visitors from near and far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connecting to the Alewife “T” Station in Cambridge, the bikeway provides an easy way for bicyclists and pedestrians to travel to subway and bus lines, serving to reduce automobile traffic in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bikeway is collectively managed and maintained by the four communities it passes through: Bedford, Lexington, Arlington, and Cambridge.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;End points: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alewife Station, Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Depot Park/South Street, Bedford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Length: 11 miles from Alewife Station to Bedford, with mile-marker posts.&lt;br /&gt;Surface: Asphalt pavement, 12 feet wide.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bethany</member_name><member_id>10111481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258827323000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Grinders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group</urlname><id>1500421</id><group_lat>42.0600013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Foxboro Grind &amp; Grub Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256580795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Minuteman Bikeway</name><id>11715492</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257620400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group/events/11715492/</event_url></item>