<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Return&lt;/b&gt; Russia 2003 105 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: This is part of an ongoing series of Russian films at Coolidge. After the film there will be a brief Q&amp;amp;A session with the organizer of the series. We will get together after this discussion before going to a local restaurant for our own group talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the Golden Lion at the Venice Film Festival, this debut film by Andrei Zvyagintsev is breathtaking, haunting and beautiful. The story of two boys, Andrei and Vanya whose father returns after a twelve year absence to take them on a fishing trip. Punctuated by the passage of seven days the film unfolds to show the torrid relationship between father and sons. The journey, punctuated by mystery and despair, leads the young boys to discover each other and their father, whomever he may truly be.  Coolidge Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Andrey Zvyagintsev's debut feature is a throwback to the days of the 60s, when Russian cinema mesmerised arthouse audiences with simple but evocative tales full of hidden depths. Ostensibly the simple tale of a fishing trip, it's so much more than it pretends to be - as the possible autobiographical elements (the main character shares a Christian name with the director) and thinly veiled allusions to the biblical story of Abraham and Isaac suggest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking place over seven days, it's set in an otherworldly part of Russia where the weather switches from torrential downpours to brilliant sunshine in the space of a few minutes. Even time itself seems to be ticking past at a different pace. As the boys follow their father to a desert island while he searches for buried treasure, it slowly becomes apparent that Zvyagintsev is making a mythical film about the mysteries of fatherhood as seen from a child's perspective. Building towards its finale with portentous certainty, it's a beautifully realized debut from an assured filmmaker.  BBC Films&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Rotten Tomatoes &lt;b&gt;The Return&lt;/b&gt; posted a 96% rating. Here's a link to local scribe Ty Burr's review: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;amp;id=5751" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it-&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will hold a meetup sign in the theater after the film and Q&amp;A session.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224180930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Russia's The Return</name><id>8974152</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226858400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8974152/</event_url></item>