<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;read the entire event description&lt;/span&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;answer all of the questions&lt;/span&gt; that are part of the RSVP process. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - in that case update your RSVP from a computer to generate them again so you can answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your safety and the safety of the group is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;UPDATE 12/19: The good news is that I can still run this hike on Friday, the bad news is that I have to work in the afternoon so I have to change the start time to 10:00 AM. I hope everyone that has signed up can still make it because I was looking forward to meeting so many new people (and seeing the familiar ones too).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does the commercialization of the Christmas season make you want go into hibernation until December 26th? Are you sick of all of the holiday parties? Then why not join us on December 23rd for a hike to celebrate Festivus, a holiday for the rest of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No trees. No lights. No gifts. There will be&amp;nbsp;unadorned&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aluminum"&gt;aluminum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;"Festivus pole" (OK, we will use the summit fire tower for this). There will be an "Airing of Grievances" (each person will get to tell others all the ways that they've disappointed them over the past year) and we will use our hike to the summit, instead of a wresting match, as our "Feats of Strength".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Festivus"&gt;here for more information about festivus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&amp;nbsp;This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if&amp;nbsp;you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are NOT allowed on this trip&lt;/strong&gt;. All participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are allowed on this trip&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;provided they are well-behaved, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, you clean up after them, and you have a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;T&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;round-trip we will use Stage Coach and Harrington Trail to reach the summit - we then follow the same route in reverse to get back to our cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about 3.2 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb about 800 feet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Without including time for breaks it should take an average hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;about 2 hours to complete&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;this trip. It is considered to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;EASY&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/wach.htm"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more information about Wachusett and the surrounding area&amp;nbsp;from the Massachusetts Department of Conservation &amp;amp; Recreation &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trip is considered to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;EASY&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&amp;nbsp;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will comple&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;te the entire&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time.&amp;nbsp;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?CityName=Princeton&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;site=BOX&amp;amp;textField1=42.45&amp;amp;textField2=-71.8667&amp;amp;e=1"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Kahtoola Microspikes or Hillsound Crampons are acceptable for this hike. Since we won't be using these items all of the time either have space in your pack or a way to secure them to the outside of it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clot&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;hing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly draws heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket. Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants. Fleece or wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead of a hydration bladder since the mouthpiece/tube can freeze.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries - lithium work best in colder temperatures. Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket. Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be meeting at the parking area on the north side of Westminster Road in Princeton, MA.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Google Maps this spot is about 65 miles from Boston and it should take about 1 hours 24 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=Westminster+Rd&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=42.476592,-71.892278&amp;amp;sspn=0.009543,0.013797&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFWQbiAIdJvq2-w&amp;amp;vpsrc=0&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=10"&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;here&amp;nbsp;for customizable driving directions to the meeting spot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate&amp;nbsp;in this activity; you know and will follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in either my white or Monica's green Toyota Highlander - both have MA license plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324927436000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323919821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Festivus Trek 2011 (EASY)</name><id>44516192</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324652400000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/44516192/</event_url></item>