<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hough Ave. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.605877</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stage Fort Park</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>925525</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.678803</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Stage Fort Park in historic Gloucester, MA will host Pastimes' annual piratical production.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE:&lt;br /&gt;We have found out that the parking at Stage Fort park is $15.00 per car or maybe you can find a spot on the street?  Not sure where we will meet, so when you get there give the meetup cell a call and I will tell you where we are the phone # is 978-304-2811.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MISSION STATEMENT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our mission statement is first and foremost, to entertain. We believe in the &amp;quot;power of play&amp;quot; and we seek to use comedy and fun to bring joy to people young and old. From the children at one of our festivals to the most dignified executive at our corporate events, we feel we have accomplished our primary goal if people are smiling, laughing, and forgetting their worries even if only for a short time. The way we do this is by spreading and fostering the exciting and relatively new theatrical discipline of Interactive Theater. Our shows and events strive to involve and immerse the audience in the environment we are seeking to portray, to make the audience or guests part of the show and in doing this, involve them in a more rich and memorable experience. We also strive to encourage education and literacy by bringing to life cherished literature and historical periods. We feel that &amp;quot;planting the seed&amp;quot; is the most important thing, and hope that people leave our events having learned something new. Ideally, they will also leave with a newfound sense of curiosity, adventure, and the joy of learning. For this reason, we try to highlight many of the lesser known and fun bits of historical fact. Lastly, we hope to showcase talented performers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston area is home to many talented local actors, amazing variety performers, musicians, artists, and local craftspeople. We have built up an intimate and ever expanding roster, so our clients have access to the most talented performers in the area, just by calling us. We work closely with artisans who construct costumes and props to order as well as all manner of performers. We personally train all of our actors in the unique demands of interactive theater. Pastimes' theatrical division produces family-friendly stage plays and renaissance faire-style shows based on historical and literary sources. Each year, Pastimes produces several interactive events that combine environmental theater with a renaissance faire-type setting to create the ultimate family-friendly adventure. A typical Pastimes show features up to ten scripted scenes that tell one large story over the course of a seven-hour day. In-between the scenes, patrons may tour our host venues (which are often as interesting as the shows), enjoy a number of variety acts, partake of delicious food and refreshments, and shop at our vendor booths, which offer unique items you won't find anywhere else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children are welcome at this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be updating this event on a good place to meet, where you can park and any other information that will be needed PLEASE remember to check back for more updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna will have the Meetup phone: 978-304-2811. Note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/laughing.gif' border='0' alt='laughing' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will update this as the date gets closer...please check back!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277682946000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272231785000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pastimes' annual piratical production.</name><id>13287090</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277568000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/13287090/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/e/global_14623486.jpeg</photo_url></item>