<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1145 Washington Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.343712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Project Place</name><city>Boston</city><id>1154503</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066169</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Amid the talks of economic recession and changing fundraising landscape, the question remains of how social media will affect nonprofit organizations.  &lt;br /&gt;In this meetup Richard Wang, meetup member and social media expert, will demonstrate social media’s return on investment and how to use user centered design to catalyse nonprofit organizations' missions in any competitive business environment. &lt;br /&gt;He will discuss risks and opportunities associated with social media and provide an inside look at several high profile social media examples.  &lt;br /&gt;AND he will offer some best practices or industry standards organizations can adopt to optimize their online efforts, especially regarding user engagement, conversion, and retention. &lt;br /&gt;Finally we'll get to engage in a group brainstorm regarding how to use social media to measure social awareness, improve cause driving fundraising, and re-enforce long term community identity.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So- Please join us for this great evening of ideas, education and brainstorming on a topic we can use wehter part of an organization or not!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;Monique&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monique Morimoto Flaherty</member_name><member_id>8025083</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266537975000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265427216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Inside Look at Social Media and its Impact on the Nonprofit Landscape</name><id>12533443</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266364800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/12533443/</event_url></item>