<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02133</zip><lat>42.335347</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Massachusetts State House</name><city>Boston</city><id>900281</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.153409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;[Justice Duffly has responded to our questionnaire (&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/1412531/Duffly%20Response%20to%20Questionnaire.pdf"&gt;View it here in PDF file&lt;/a&gt;) or &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/1412531/Duffly%20Response%20to%20Questionnaire.txt"&gt;here in text&lt;/a&gt; on restraining orders and child custody. This is an important milestone in our efforts to move the judges and the courts away from heavy handed issuance of restraining and other court orders. She is the first nominee in over a year to respond and so it is very important that everyone who can do so to attend her hearing and make their opinions clear that the courts need to stop micro-managing families in Massachusetts.]&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The public nomination hearing for Fernandes Duffly to the Massachusetts Supreme Judicial Court will be held by the Governor’s Council on January 19, 10 AM, in the State House (Hearing Room B).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Massachusetts Governor’s Council nomination hearings are open to the pubic which   is invited to present testimony in support or in opposition to the nominee. Based on Justice Duffly’s past rulings on the Massachusetts Appeals Court regarding child custody and restraining orders The Fatherhood Coalition will speak in opposition to her nomination at the January 19 hearing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Governor’s Council is composed of eight councilors from across the state with the Lt. Governor presiding over some hearings. Three new councilors have just been sworn in. A majority of council votes is required for confirmation of a judicial nominee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The public hearing for a judicial nominee is the only opportunity for the average citizen to have a say before an individual is placed on the bench for a lifetime appointment. Once confirmed it is virtually impossible to remove a judge in Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joseph Ureneck</member_name><member_id>8050884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295454333000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fathers' Rights Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Greater-Boston-Chapter-of-The-Fatherhood-Coalition</urlname><id>1412531</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Chapter of The Fatherhood Coalition</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294687511000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Duffly Judicial Nomination Hearing on January 19 </name><id>15996033</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295449200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Greater-Boston-Chapter-of-The-Fatherhood-Coalition/events/15996033/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/9/b/global_7743227.jpeg</photo_url></item>