<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Merrimack College</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.667705</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rogers Center</name><city>North Andover</city><id>1255819</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122571</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The &lt;b&gt;BEST BARGAIN in BOSTON!&lt;/b&gt; Great speakers, interactive table top exhibits, lunch plus a free beverage  for only $35. &lt;b&gt;Open to ALL&lt;/b&gt;. Free for Students! $15 for the unemployed or the underemployed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT&lt;/b&gt; - &lt;b&gt;Please Register &lt;a href="http://www.merrimack.edu/rfid" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;at this LINK&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(this MeetUp site should NOT be used for event registration). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JOIN US!&lt;/b&gt; A wonderful day of networking with top players in the Auto-ID and Sensor world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;&lt;b&gt;EXHIBITORS&lt;/b&gt;: 2DU, A2B Tracking Solutions, AuthenTec, Avnet Inc, Bilcare Technologies, ChainLink Research, Cognex Corp, Conair - US AID, Confidex, Emerson &amp;amp; Cuming, Diamond Technologies, Inc, George Schmitt &amp;amp; Co, Laird Cushcraft, Martindale Associates, Merrimack College, Microscan, Nokia, NXP, Pramari, Queralt, Tego, ThingMagic, UMass Lowell and Xerafy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;~   ~ &lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  ~   ~   ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;MIT Enterprise Forum Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing Solutions - &lt;br /&gt;UMass Lowell Nanotechnology Center - &lt;br /&gt;Merrimack College RFID Training Center&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;- PRESENT -&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt;The 2nd Annual&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing Solutions Seminar &amp;amp; Expo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wed. October 13, 2010&lt;/b&gt;, 8:45 am to 7:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Venue:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Rogers Center at Merrimack College &lt;br /&gt;315 Turnpike St.   No. Andover, MA.   01845 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;To REGISTER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://merrimack-friends.informz.net/merrimack-friends/event.asp?eid=1419" target="_blank"&gt;http://merrimack-frie...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year we had a great event at MIT with 44 exhibitors of Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing solutions. This year's event has an expanded program with noteworthy keynote speakers, interesting panels plus interactive table top exhibits. This is a VERY low cost way to network with others and keep up with new developments. It will be &lt;b&gt;FUN, INFORMATIVE and INTERACTIVE&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why You Should Join Us?&lt;/b&gt; Adoption of Auto-ID and sensing solutions is already widespread and is accelerating. Recent announcements spotlight major RFID deployments at the item level for apparel with 100's of millions of tags. Major deployments are underway in industrial settings including: aerospace, petro-chemical, automotive and defense. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who should attend?&lt;/b&gt;  This event attracts a diverse crowd -- people interested in the business benefits of Auto-ID, implementers, developers, investors, research analysts, end users, consultants, educators, integrators, students, hardware and software providers plus many others. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;8:00 am Registration &amp;amp; Coffee&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;8:45 am WELCOME ADDRESS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Professor Jack Adams, Merrimack College&lt;br /&gt;• Dr. Chris Hopey, President, Merrimack College&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;9:00 am VIEWPOINT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Mark Russell, Vice President of Engineering, Technology &amp;amp; Mission Assurance Raytheon Corp. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;9:15 am IUID - Peter Collins, President, A2B Tracking Solutions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IUID – Where it stands and where it’s heading - Item Unique Identification. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;9:45 am INDUSTRY KEYNOTE, Craig Casto, Global Leader RFID, GPS, AutoID Expertise Center&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leveraging Auto ID Technologies to Enable Work Processes Across the Corporation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;10:30 am NETWORKING COFFEE BREAK&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;11:00 am PANEL: RFID Marketing Successes and Pitfalls&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Tom Coyle, Moderator&lt;br /&gt;• Roger Bridgeman, President of Bridgeman Communications&lt;br /&gt;• Mike Liard, ABI Research&lt;br /&gt;• Liz Churchill, Director, Marketing &amp;amp; BusDev, Bilcare Technologies&lt;br /&gt;• Alan Sherman, Director of Marketing,  OATSystems&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;12:00pm Chris Hook, Vice President, RF Controls&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Accurate Real-Time Location of Passive UHF RFID Tags&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;12:30pm LUNCHEON - Merrimack College, Cascia Hall&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exhibit Tables open during lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;1:30pm &lt;b&gt;KEYNOTE&lt;/b&gt; - Martin Meehan, Chancellor, UMass Lowell&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leveraging Nanotechnology for the Next Generation of Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing Solutions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;2:00pm - PANEL: Implementations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Prof. Ram Nagarajan, Univ. of MA, Lowell  &lt;br /&gt;• Prof. Charles Kochakian, Merrimack College &lt;br /&gt;• Steve Miles, MIT Enterprise Forum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;3:00 pm - PANEL: Investing in Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• John Greaves, Moderator&lt;br /&gt;• Ron Wagner, Sivix&lt;br /&gt;• John Chalus, Vice President, Kinetic Advisors, LLC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;4:00-7:00pm - Vendor Showcase – Table top technology demonstrations.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• Libations, hors d’oeuvres and networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;EXHIBITOR HOURS&lt;/b&gt; - 12:30p - 1:30p and 4 - 7 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: before Oct. 1st - $35 (includes lunch)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Special rate&lt;/span&gt;: unemployed&lt;/b&gt; (or under employed),&lt;b&gt; $15&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPEAKER DETAILS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;KEYNOTE ADDRESS &lt;br /&gt;Martin Meehan&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Chancellor of UMass Lowell &lt;br /&gt;University–Industry Collaboration:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Enabling a Multidisciplinary Approach to Nanotechnology and Sensing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chancellor Martin Meehan will discuss the importance of University-industry collaboration for the development of emerging technologies in the Merrimack Valley. The Chancellor will also provide an overview of recent efforts in the state-of-the-art centers of nanomanufacturing pertaining to sensing and the recent infrastructure investments that facilitate innovation in these areas.  Development of partnerships with local industries and academia, as well as strategic investments in research infrastructure and workforce development, are the key factors for keeping Massachusetts and the U.S. competitive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;J. Craig Casto, The Dow Chemical Company&lt;br /&gt;Global Leader, RFID • GPS • AutoID Expertise Center&lt;br /&gt;Leveraging Auto ID Technologies to Enable Work Processes Across the Corporation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn how Dow Chemical is utilizing the various tools in their Auto ID Toolbox, such as RFID, GPS and Bar Codes,  to improve Global work processes throughout the company.  Areas of focus include Supply Chain visibility and safety of shipments, remote worker safety, maintenance, anti-counterfeiting, marketing, and improvements in asset utilization. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chris Hook, RF Controls, LLC&lt;br /&gt;Vice President of Business Development&lt;br /&gt;Accurate Real-Time Location of Passive UHF RFID Tags&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation introduces an Auto-ID technology and system which achieves accurate, automated, real-time location and tracking of standards compliant, passive UHF RFID tags in 3D. As a result of significant innovations in “smart antenna” technology and associated signal processing algorithms, this disruptive innovation achieves unprecedented performance for a passive UHF RFID system, and offers capabilities that have heretofore been associated with active tag RTLS products. RF Controls’ Intelligent Tracking and Control System (ITCS®) has demonstrably changed the market’s perception concerning the utility of passive UHF RFID systems, and solves latent issues which have impeded the wider adoption and large scale deployments of passive UHF RFID systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;VIEWPOINT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark E. Russell&lt;br /&gt;Raytheon Company&lt;br /&gt;Vice President of Engineering, Technology and Mission Assurance&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mark E. Russell assumed the position in July 2008, and was elected a company officer in June 2008. Raytheon Company (NYSE: RTN), with 2009 sales of $25 billion, is a technology and innovation leader specializing in defense, homeland security and other government markets throughout the world. With headquarters in Waltham, Mass., Raytheon employs 75,000 people worldwide. Russell is responsible for 45,000 world-class people working on more than 8,000 programs. Prior to leading Raytheon’s engineering organization, Russell was vice president of engineering for Raytheon’s Integrated Defense Systems (IDS) business. In this role, he was responsible for leading IDS’ engineering activities, including the capture and management of technology and advanced programs; coordination of strategic architecture initiatives; development and production of advanced semiconductor products at Raytheon RF Components; continuous improvement of processes and tools; and product development.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PANEL: INVESTING IN AUTO-ID &amp;amp; SENSING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;John Greaves - Moderator&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Greaves has been actively involved in RFID for many years. His pioneering work in the area of Global Logistics, Inventory Management and the Returnable Transport Items sector with both active and passive RFID has led to the significant adoptions occurring in Supply Chains globally today. He was the founding chair of the US RFID standards group, led the European Spectrum Initiative, was the leader of the GTAG program for EAN.UCC and developed, amongst many significant RFID implementations worldwide, the one tag per pallet UHF solution with CHEP. John has served with distinction in the standards and equipment regulation bodies, ETSI, CEPT, CEN, ISO as well as addressing, and being a member of, many of the leading industry bodies, Institute of Logistics, CIES, ICSC, and as a representative to Auto ID Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;John J. Chalus is a Vice President at Kinetic Advisors&lt;/b&gt; providing financial advisory and capital raising services to middle market companies.  Prior to joining Kinetic Advisors, he was an Associate with Cerberus Capital Management providing leveraged loans to private equity backed companies. He has assisted companies with capital needs and strategic advice for over 10 years acting both as a principal and advisor in private equity and investment banking capacities.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ron Wagner, Research Director for the 2C Lab at George Mason University&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ron Wagner created the concept of Condition Based Logistics. He has been an entrepreneur, an executive with a large defense company, an inventor and a pioneer in the RFID arena.  Co-founder of the Logistics and Maintenance Applied Research center at Georgia Tech, Ron has a patent in low power sensor networking, two International Design Awards for Performance Centered Design, and 14 patents pending in telematics, diagnostics and prognostics.  Currently Research Director for the 2C Lab at George Mason University, Ron is consulting with several small businesses that are working on solutions in the Auto-ID world.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287525443000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272287075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Seminar &amp; Expo</name><id>13292510</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286973900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/13292510/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/8/global_12538664.jpeg</photo_url></item>