<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Are you tired of always nagging your significant other to take that cooking class at the local community center? Are you frustrated with recipes that serve 3-5 when you're only cooking for yourself? Do you find yourself forgetting to eat dinner or hitting the drive-in for another meal-on-the-run that you hardly notice eating because of your hectic schedule? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe you should stop trying to please everyone else but yourself and join us for a night of Brazilian cuisine! We'll wisk you away to the endless beaches of Rio De Janeiro, where you'll be treated to some of the finest culinary delights that South America has to offer - almost! Don't make excuses - Select &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; on the RSVP and start treating yourself with more compassion today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michelle has graciously offered to entertain us with her own interpretation of the famous Bossa Nova song, &amp;quot;The Girl From Ipanema&amp;quot; if at least 15 members join us for what I'm sure will be a night you'll not soon forget!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What more can Michelle do to convince you that it's time to broaden your dining horizons and &amp;quot;spice&amp;quot; up your life? Don't let another fabulous dining event go by without you! Take your body to Chale Ipanema and let the friendly staff take your mind hundreds of miles south to a place where dining is a significant part of the culture, not a necessity to squeeze in between responding to e-mails and family obligations!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chale Ipanema&lt;br /&gt;342 Franklin Ave. (Bliss St.) &lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT 06114&lt;br /&gt;860-296-2120&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although the exterior leaves a bit to be desired, inside you will find the decor pleasantly surprising and the service as friendly as you'll find. Chef-owner Nelson Diorio is a native of Rio de Janeiro and serves up excellent Old World cuisine with a New World touch. Just so you know, sides that were once served dried are now replaced with fresh fruits and vegetables. Try the duck, which is roasted and topped with fresh orange slices, dusted with chopped Brazil nuts, and served with green beans, carrots, and pan-roasted potatoes. A variety of desserts are available if you have room!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1160158425000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1157063363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brazilian Carnivale Cuisine - Chale Ipanema!!!!</name><id>5106710</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1159484400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/5106710/</event_url></item>