<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>165 Brainard Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.734776</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-244-3311</phone><name>Chowder Pot IV</name><city>Hartford</city><id>219703</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.659450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>If you missed it last time, you have another chance to eat/drink/dance at this Singles Party! Here you can mingle in the crowd, but yet feel safe with familiar faces (I will do what i can to get a table and put a MEETUP sign and say its ok for anyone else to sit there too on it but i dont think i can specifically &amp;quot;reserve&amp;quot; one unless someone FESSes UP that its their BIRTHDAY +/- a few days or so). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Going to a singles dance with your friends is a bonus and much appreciated by our last group event there. Its Not so threatening for those of you who are on the shy side! Our group is very friendly and loves to dance! The DJ is great!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Real silverware and dishes! Drinks are full size in glass not plastic!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;U.S.S. Chowder Pot IV &lt;br /&gt;165 Brainard Rd &lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday Nite, June 22, 2007 &lt;br /&gt;Time: 8 pm - 12:30 am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner Buffet 8 - 9:30 pm, coffee/dessert at 11:30 pm, dancing to DJ's Top 40/Soft Rock, dress to impress/no jeans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$17, pay at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for our table with the Meetup sign. ( im printing it in black and white with and putting it in a place where its easy to find)..also if i can, the table will be in a place not so in the line of sound from the speakes...I will do what i can...please walk around and check out the seating area to find us..i know if you are new, its not easy..but be patient..i dont have a cell phone, but ask me personally and i will let you call someone that is going...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP no later than thursday. You can bring guests. &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This dance is sponsored by CT Contacts, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Springfield and Hartford: &lt;br /&gt;I 91 S to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd). Left off exit onto Airport Rd. Go to end of road and turn right at lite onto Brainard Rd. Go thru one traffic lite. Chowder Pot is on right. Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Manchester/Vernon/Sturbridge, MA: &lt;br /&gt;I 84 W to Charter Oak Bridge exit. Go over bridge and take second exit (exit 87, Brainard Rd). Go right off exit. Chowder Pot is on right. Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Danbury and Points West: &lt;br /&gt;I 84 E to I 91 S to exit 27 (Brainard Rd). Turn left off exit onto Airport Rd. Go to end of road and turn right at lite onto Brainard Rd. Go through one taffic lite. Chowder Pot in on right. Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from New Haven: I 91 N to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd) Turn right off exit. Chowder Pot is on right. Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For mapquest, gps and others use 165 Brainard Road, Hartford, Ct to get you close enough..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182772445000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182095887000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dance Like you have Red Ants in the Pants at the Chowda Pot In Hartford.</name><id>5901429</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182556800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5901429/</event_url></item>