<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Hunt Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.836670</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Amesbury Sports Park</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1486796</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.945374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/1/0/event_153301552.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;When was the last time you saw a pumpkin flying through the air???&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;10.13 update:  If you plan on purchasing tickets to the raffle items (see the HUGE list of items they are raffling off by this link: &lt;a href="http://pumpkinchuckingfest.com/raffleitems.html"&gt;http://pumpkinchuckingfest.com/raffleitems.html&lt;/a&gt; ) then you may want to bring name and phone # stickers, I am not sure if we will need them, but to save time and finger pressure you may want to bring them with you.  They have a LOT of fabulous items, if you think you can't win???  Well I did last year, actually I won 2 items.  So you can't win if you don't try/buy, plus it does go to a great cause!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well you will at this event, teams will compete and see how far their catapult can chuck a pumpkin.  Not only that we will be helping out a great cause for Coastal Connections (and a few other great organizations) these &lt;span&gt;organizations embraces the mentally and physically handicapped community and creates a unique guidance path for them based on the individuals strengths and goals. Each program helps provide day to day skills, vocational skills and educational lessons for each student.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides the pumpkin chucking there will also be: &lt;br /&gt;

 Music by Don't Call Me Shirley, bouncy houses, pumpkin decorating, bean bag toss, food and beverages, pie eating contest, a HUGE raffle to help raise money and of course Pumpkin Chucking etc............!  So come on down to Amesbury Sports Park and have some fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;This event is open to children of all ages.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost for this event: FREE to get in you pay for what you buy, eat, raffle coupons etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this event we may stay together, or we can split up and check out what is going on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811, please note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues?  Please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer” You can pay your dues at this event.  Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in front of the band.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350604238000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346089497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pumpkin Chucking!!!</name><id>79586332</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350234000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/79586332/</event_url></item>