<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route One</address_2><address_1>517 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01906</zip><lat>42.482793</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-233-9950</phone><name>Giggles Comedy Club</name><city>Saugus</city><id>929183</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.020456</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>GIGGLES COMEDY CLUB&lt;br /&gt;517 Broadway, Saugus  01906&lt;br /&gt;781-233-9950&lt;br /&gt;November 20 7:15 show&lt;br /&gt;Kelly Macfarland   Cost of the tickets are $20 (plus the $2 meet up fee)&lt;br /&gt;As an experienced stand up comedian, Kelly has an extensive and well-rounded resume including comedy clubs, theaters, colleges and several television appearances. She has been the opening act for the international craze, Puppetry of the Penis. She has opened for Melissa Etheridge and LeAnn Rimes at both the Cape Cod Melody Tent and South Shore Music Circus. Kelly has appeared on Comedy Central’s Premium Blend. You may recognize her from season one of NBC's hit reality series, The Biggest Loser. Kelly worked along side Fred Willard as part of the rambunctious news team of “TV Network” on Turner Entertainment’s broadband site, SuperDeluxe.com.  Kelly is currently traveling the country with the Loretta LaRoche Women in Comedy Tour.  Aside from being an accomplished stand up comedian; Kelly is working her way to being a successful humor-wellness speaker. Speaking to diverse groups of individuals about fitness and health, she shares her life long journey to becoming an athlete through weight loss and acceptance of herself.  Sharing her life experiences in the unique way that only she can, Kelly leaves audiences pleasantly surprised by her candor.  She captivates the crowd with her charm, and her refreshing yet playful point of view makes her irresistible. Her alluring smile and intense energy keeps the audience wanting more.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our table will be reserved under Baby Boomers</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258943713000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Baby Boomers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun</urlname><id>1347228</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Baby Boomers Meetup Group-Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257693519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's have fun and laugh at Giggles!</name><id>11824393</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258761600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun/events/11824393/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/1/7/global_11698887.jpeg</photo_url></item>