<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Tamarac Lane</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.839682</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Belding Wildlife Management Area</name><city>Vernon</city><id>303287</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.446717</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Gloria is leading a hike for her tall friends from the &lt;a href="http://www.hhtallclub.org" target="_blank"&gt;Hartford Heights Tall Club &lt;/a&gt;and welcomes other tall people or those who are not afraid of tall people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With spring having sprung, it's time to get back outside for some hikes. We’ll head to one of Gloria’s favorite haunts, the Belding Wildlife Management Area in Vernon. This is an easy 2-3 mile walk over rolling terrain. Dogs and kids are welcome. The trailhead can be tricky to find for first-timers, so we will meet at the 7-11 on Route 30 in Vernon (corner of South Street and Hartford Turnpike). At 3:15, we will travel as a group to the trailhead. Optional pizza to follow at New England Pizza, back in the same plaza as 7-11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the 7-11 on Route 30 in Vernon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240409514000</updated><rating><average>3.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239457760000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Belding Wildlife Management Area</name><id>10163512</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240167600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10163512/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/e/global_2859934.jpeg</photo_url></item>