<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>43.948500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Piper Trailhead</name><city>Albany</city><id>722609</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.217467</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us for a hike to Mt Chocorua. An energetic hike to a summit with 360 degree views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Piper Trail is an attractive trail that offers maximum walking on open ledges to the summit of Mt. Chocorua.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/6/event_4982614.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It starts at an easy grade on private land following an old logging road. The White Mountain National Forest boundary comes at approximately .6 miles. The Weetamoo Trail turns off to the left at .8 miles and the Nickerson Ledge Trail turns off to the right at 1.4 miles. The Piper Trail ascends moderately past a cleared outlook to Carter Ledge. It then becomes steeper and changes into a series of switchbacks, stone steps, and paving. The Camp Penacook Spur Trail at 3.1 miles branches off to the left and ascends .2 miles to the shelter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/4/event_4982548.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open Ledges soon appear, giving great views to the north, east and south. The Champney Brook Trail comes in on your right at 3.9 miles and .2 miles further, the West Side Trail comes in on your right. The Piper Trail continues following yellow paint marks over open ledges to the summit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: It may be safer during bad weather to follow the West Side and Brook trails to the summit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The trail climbs a rock gully to the summit of Mt Chocorua &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will divide a  large group if necessary into 2 teams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 8.60 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 7 hr 12 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3060 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -3060 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change 0 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Take route 16 north from Chocorua until you see the While Mountain National Forest hiking sign next to a variety store on your left. Follow the dirt road back to the parking lot. This is the Piper trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;There is a $3.00 fee and change is not available but there is a store on route 16 just 300 yards from the trailhead. (Lat:43.56 Lon:-71.13)&lt;/b&gt; Let's Carpool!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Location: Rte. 16, 6 mi. south of Conway behind the Piper Trail Cabins &amp;  Rest.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242739417000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238022102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Chocorua  via Piper Trail</name><id>10036123</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241960400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10036123/</event_url></item>