<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 West St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.316262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 587-1011</phone><name>NORTHAMPTON MA_ FORBES LIBRARY </name><city>Northampton </city><id>832342</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.636533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's 1936 and the Great Depression has taken its toll.  Eighty-six-year-old Hennie Comfort has lived in Middle Swan, Colorado -  up in the high country of the snow-covered Rocky Mountains - since  before it was Colorado. When she first meets seventeen-year-old Nit  Spindle, Hennie is drawn to the young grieving girl. Nit and her husband  have come to this small mining town in search of work, but the  loneliness and loss Nit feels are almost too much to bear. One day she  notices an old sign that reads "Prayers for Sale" in front of Hennie's  house and takes out her last nickel. Hennie doesn't actually take money  for her prayers, never has, but she invites the skinny girl in anyway.  The harsh conditions of life that each has endured help them to create  an instant bond, and a friendship is born, one in which the deepest of  hardships are shared and the darkest of secrets are confessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This  novel tells the tale of a friendship between two women, one with  surprising twists and turns, and one that is ultimately a revelation of  the finest parts of the human spirit.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Community Room, downstairs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Annie</member_name><member_id>1543974</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317750540000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paradisecityreaders</urlname><id>1404829</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Paradise City Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302626218000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October: Prayers for Sale, Sandra Dallas</name><id>17277719</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317682800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paradisecityreaders/events/17277719/</event_url></item>