<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is closed to new RSVP's. Please call or email me if you are interested in joining us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizers -- Monica Trust 9788771119 and Emily Singer&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you are interested in participating in this event be sure to answer all of the required questions during the RSVP process. Unless you are someone that I hike with regularly please take the time to answer them with as much information as possible - even if you have answered them before.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the objective of this trip is to enjoy ourselves as we climb, your safety, and the safety of the others in our group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this trip, or overestimate your skills and abilities, you may put yourself and/or others at risk - consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Moosilauke is a mountain, 4,802 feet high, in the southwest White Mountains Region of New Hampshire, United States. It is located within the town of Benton. The Appalachian National Scenic Trail passes over the mountain. Moosilauke is the tenth highest, as well as the southwesternmost, of the 4,000 foot summits in the White Mountains.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The summit of Moosilauke is treeless and offers panoramic views of Franconia Ridge and the Kinsmans to the north, great views into Jobildunc Ravine to the southeast, and the Green Mountains to the west. The first winter high country weather observatory was set up at the top of Mt. Moosilauke in the winter of 1869-1870. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Trip is 6.5 miles and should take 6 1/2 hours not including breaks or lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summit via Glencliff Trail &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MODERATE 7 mile winter hike (7 hours) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Weather&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is winter in the mountains. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel this hike - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?CityName=Benton&amp;amp;state=NH&amp;amp;site=GYX&amp;amp;textField1=44.1031&amp;amp;textField2=-71.9022&amp;amp;e=0" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Footwear: Hiking boots or trail shoes. Snowshoes and some form of traction (e.g. crampons and microspikes) is mandatory.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater - ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain jacket with hood.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and enough water to stay hydrated during the trip. Hydration bladders may freeze during winter - bottles with insulating sleeves work best.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in cold temperatures). Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Optional Items: Waterproof/windproof pants. Waterproof gaiters. Trekking poles. Camera.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am not certified or trained in wilderness first aid. You will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Information&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is encouraged - indicate in your RSVP if you need a ride or can give one. You are responsible for making your own arrangements so you should check back often and contact others who might want/need to carpool.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All MAYBE RSVPs will be changed to NO three days before the event so people who might be on the WAITING LIST have an opportunity to make the necessary arrangements in order to participate.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will begin this hike at 7:45 AM. According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 137 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 28 minutes to drive there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=43.998009,-71.882161(Glencliff+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFTlbnwIdTyq3-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=43.998009,-71.882161&amp;amp;sspn=0.003242,0.009742&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.593533,-68.57666&amp;amp;spn=2.86305,10.777588&amp;amp;z=7" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for driving directions to the meeting spot.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to Get There: From Hanover, drive north on Route 10 to Orford and turn right on Route 25A (alternatively, take I-91 North to Exit 15, then cross back into New Hampshire to pick up 25A). When 25A ends in Wentworth, turn left on Route 25/Route 118. Drive through Warren, then continue straight when Route 118 splits off to the right. In Glencliff, turn right onto Sanitarium Road (look for a sign for the New Hampshire Home for the Elderly). Pass the left turn for the North &amp;amp; South Road, then park on the right in the parking area (&lt;b&gt;WMNF parking fee required&lt;/b&gt;). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be driving a Off White Lexus SUV with MA license plate</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emily Singer</member_name><member_id>7452900</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292887326000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291683474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Get the Moose! via Glencliff Trail</name><id>15662147</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292676300000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15662147/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/a/global_7169402.jpeg</photo_url></item>