<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Route 2A)</address_2><address_1>247 Littleton County Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01464</zip><lat>42.514290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 456-9386</phone><name>Friendly Crossways</name><city>Harvard</city><id>1266363</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.534294</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello Cyclists, I just wanted to let you know you can still do the ride tomorrow for $5.  However, we're sorry, but the Barbecue &amp;amp; rally are full and registration for the full day is closed. You can still come for the rides by paying $5 when your register just show up.  If you are interested in staying for the barbecue you may be able to substitute for any registered participants who are unable to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for any inconvenience this may cause, or perhaps its good news for some of you who weren't doing it because of the costs...  Happy Peddaling!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cyndi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey Everyone I have signed up for the AMC Bike Rally along with a few friends and I thought their might be some others in this group interested in doing it too!  So I decided to post it here:  I'll bring a balloon with me so you can find me before and after ride.  &lt;b&gt;I believe I am doing the 27 mile ride, may add a few on to that!  50 is a little to far for me right now!  That way even if we don't ride together perhaps we can do some socializing together afterwards as a group.  Should be a blast.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amcboston.org/bicycle/bikerally.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amcboston....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The 32nd annual AMC Boston Chapter Bicycle Rally will be held at the &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friendly Crossways Hostel&lt;br /&gt;247 Littleton County Road&lt;br /&gt;Harvard, MA 01451 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;on Saturday, June 12, 2010. It is a wonderful opportunity for cyclists of all levels to get together to begin the summer bike season. Come help us celebrate.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year there will be arrowed rides of 27, 50 and 67 miles on beautiful rolling terrain, and a 15 mile follow the leader ride. Helmets are required. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The schedule and ride departure times&lt;br /&gt;are below. Please try to arrive one half hour prior to your ride's scheduled departure time so you can check in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:00 am 67 mile ride &lt;br /&gt;10:30 am 50 mile ride &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am 27 mile ride &lt;br /&gt;12:30 am 15 mile ride &lt;br /&gt;4:00 pm Happy hour and socializing. (Showers are available) &lt;br /&gt;5:30 pm Dinner (chicken barbecue or vegetarian) &lt;br /&gt;7:00 pm &amp;quot;La Premiere Feminine&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Melinda Lyon talks about her experiences of twice being the first woman to finish the grueling 1200km Paris-Brest-Paris ride. Melinda has done this classic ride, held every four years, four times. She has also done the 1200km Boston-Montreal Boston ride six times and is the women's record holder.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$30 includes rides, showers, happy hour, dinner and speaker.&lt;br /&gt;Rides only— $5 (no registration, pay at the rally)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For information Contact Jack Donohue (781-275-3991 before 9PM). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To register Press this button to go to the registration page &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;REGISTER&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amcboston.org/bicycle/bikerally.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amcboston....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at the rally!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Bad weather may cancel the rides, but the dinner and the speaker will occur, rain or shine. Since we have to make commitments to the caterer for the number of people who are going to attend, no refunds can be made. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;What to bring on the day of the ride:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helmet Required &lt;br /&gt;Food for lunch &lt;br /&gt;Water bottle(s) &lt;br /&gt;Bicycle (in good working condition) &lt;br /&gt;Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;Bug repellent, spare tube, patch kit, pump, tire irons, sun glasses &lt;br /&gt;Personal items, including towels and soap &lt;br /&gt;BYOB for happy hour, soft drinks are provided, alcoholic beverages are not &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;Friendly Crossways Youth Hostel and Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;247 Littleton County Road&lt;br /&gt;Harvard, MA 01451&lt;br /&gt;(978) 456-9386 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Commuter Rail:&lt;br /&gt;Take the Fitchburg line to Littleton. Check the schedule. According to this Google map, it is 3.2 miles from the train station to the hostel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston area:&lt;br /&gt;Route 2 west to first exit past Route 495, Exit 39 (Taylor St.)&lt;br /&gt;Left at end of ramp onto Taylor St.&lt;br /&gt;After 0.8 mile, left onto Whitcomb Ave. (&amp;quot;Peace of Mind&amp;quot; child day care center on corner of Taylor and Whitcomb)&lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles to the Hostel, a big white house on right (247 Littleton County Rd).&lt;br /&gt;Parking is about 50 yards further down road on left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-495:&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 29B to Route 2 west.&lt;br /&gt;Stay in the right lane and almost immediately take Exit 39 onto Taylor St.&lt;br /&gt;Follow directions above.&lt;br /&gt;See their web site &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Travel Directions&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ride Cue Sheets&lt;br /&gt;Cue sheets for All Rides Right click on the link to download.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cyndi</member_name><member_id>3604417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276826862000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275326783000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC 32nd Annual Spring Bike Rally</name><id>13647381</id><headcount>120</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276351200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/13647381/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/8/0/global_15412224.jpeg</photo_url></item>