<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>356 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.433056</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Slater's</name><city>Bolton</city><id>10805442</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.575493</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://i663.photobucket.com/albums/uu352/northernmusic/Marty2-15-13SlatersPoster11x17.jpg" width="400" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/471465949582276" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i663.photobucket.com/albums/uu352/northernmusic/dougbell/button_facebook_event_page.jpg" width="125" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Friday ~ February 15, 2013 ~ 7:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FREE Marty Beecy Open Mic Showcase &lt;br /&gt;

Featuring Bob Martin - Americana and Folk &lt;br /&gt;

Singer-Songwriter and Acoustic Guitarist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slater's &lt;br /&gt;

356 Main St, (Route 117), Bolton, MA 01740 &lt;br /&gt;

TEL: 978-779-6680 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.slaters.biz" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.slaters.biz&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/SlatersBolton" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/SlatersBolton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All musicians are invited to share their talent in this music venue with great acoustics and a very lively appreciative audience. Join in the live entertainment and enjoy delicious barbeque, homemade wood-fired brick oven pizza, along with beer and wine!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emerging from the same New England city as Jack Kerouac - Lowell, Massachusetts native Bob Martin was greatly influenced by the beat poet's writing and career. While attending law school in Boston during the 60’s, Martin became immersed in the local folk scene and played the Nameless Coffeehouse, Club 47 (now Club Passim) and eventually found himself sharing the bill at Gerde's Folk City in New York with some of folk's greatest songwriters. It was at Gerde's that he was "discovered” and the focus of a label bidding war that RCA Nashville eventually won.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1972, Bob Martin recorded his first album Midwest Farm Disaster for RCA at Nashville Studios. He worked closely with Chet Atkins, (an executive at RCA at the time) and many exceptional studio musicians including drummer Kenneth Buttrey, (a key player on Bob Dylan's Blonde On Blonde album). Although critically heralded, Martin's career was not given priority and in turn, he left the professional music business and dropped out of the mainstream, moving “back-to-the-land” on a remote mountaintop farm in West Virginia. Midwest Farm Disaster remains a cult classic and continues to find new fans across generations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Martin continued to write songs, poetry, novels and pursue his muse through various artistic endeavors. In 1982, he connected with some friends at June Appal Records of Whitesburg,KY, and got back in the studio to make a second album, Last Chance Rider. The record was recognized as one of the top three folk albums in the country by the NAIRD and features the talents of Jerry Douglas and Jack Wright. Martin however chose to play music on his own terms and kept his live shows to a hobby schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was another ten years, until the release of The River Turns the Wheel on his own imprint Riversong Records. The album hosts vocal appearances by friends Bill Morrissey and Cormac McCarthy and is considered Bob Martin's most commercially successful album. Despite his reluctance to engage the music business, The River Turns The Wheel grabbed the attention of music critics around the country. The release reached number sixteen on the Gavin Americana Chart and was chosen as one of the top ten albums in 1997 by Brad Kava of The San Jose Mercury News. Dave Perry of The Lowell Sun chose it as the best folk album of 1997 and Tom Flannery of The Electric City News also picked it as the best CD of that year. He toured nationally and supported Merle Haggard in 1999.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Martin didn't wait as long to release his fourth album Next To Nothin’ (Riversong Records 2000), and received more rave reviews and extensive airplay on Americana radio programs around the country. In 2010 Martin issued his first live record Live at The Bull Run and he continues to perform nationally and internationally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I was first struck by the power of Bob Martin’s songwriting on Midwest Farm Disaster in the 1970s. His lyrics are powerful, direct and moving. This is a writer that has style, economy of lyric and the ability to tell a good story. Listen to the story in "My Father Painted Houses" from the CD "Next To Nothin". SI Kahn singled him out as one of the best Songwriters in the country." &lt;br /&gt;

Dick Pleasants - WUMB-FM Boston (Oct 2007)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If he had been given the right opportunities, and received the right breaks, he could have been bigger than Dylan." &lt;br /&gt;

Charles Laquidara - Legendary WBCN-FM Boston DJ (Sep 1, 2006)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bob Martin Web Sites &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.riversong.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.riversong.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/bobmartinriversong" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.myspace.com/bobmartinriversong&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bob_Martin_(folk_musician" class="linkified"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bob_Martin_(folk_musician&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marty Beecy ~ Singer, Songwriter, Guitarist &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/martybeecymusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.myspace.com/martybeecymusic&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.reverbnation.com/martybeecymusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.reverbnation.com/martybeecymusic&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Marty-Beecy-and-The-Rogue-Loons/348766855216547" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/pages/Marty-Beecy-and-The-Rogue-Loons/348766855216547&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Promotion by Richard Axtman ~ Northern Music &lt;br /&gt;

northernmusic@yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/richard.axtmanii" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/richard.axtmanii&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/northernmusicagency" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.myspace.com/northernmusicagency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360985861000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358492559000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Marty Beecy Open Mic Showcase Featuring Bob Martin</name><id>100196982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360974600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/100196982/</event_url></item>