<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1066 Front Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03102</zip><lat>43.019249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Manchester Community College</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1566655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.480988</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Save this date! Straight back from St. Lucia (poor guy), Bill Rogers will be presenting on many tips and tricks on the art of retouching photographs. Layers, channel mixing and many more things will be covered. This should be a don't miss! Bill has spent over two decades working as a photographer, producer and creative director. Also, I would like to take this opportunity to please consider giving a donation to the &amp;quot;MCC Presidential Opportunities Scholarship Fund.&amp;quot; Our group has always been free to the members. Manchester Community College is a generous supporter of our group and has been kind enough to give us use of the facilities there. Penny pays for the meetup.com fees (over $140/yr) and only asks that we consider giving something back to the school. You may make checks out to &amp;quot;Manchester Community College&amp;quot; with President's Scholarship in the memo and send it to the school or bring it to the meeting or send it to Penny (email for more info). It would be great to give the scholarship fund a more than needed boost. How much? Whatever you think is fair. I suggest even the price of two of your favorite restaurant meals or bottle of wine (unless you have incredibly high taste, then one would suffice, lol). We look forward to seeing as many of you as can make it.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Penny Savage</member_name><member_id>10532962</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321720245000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ManchesterAUG</urlname><id>1532602</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Manchester Adobe User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320982399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November Manchester Adobe User Group Meeting</name><id>40769692</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321570800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ManchesterAUG/events/40769692/</event_url></item>