<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Pocahontas Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>03905</zip><lat>43.071270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fort Foster </name><city>Kittery Point</city><id>845838</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.686638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Have not been to the beach in a while......thought it would be nice to head over to Fort Foster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So pack up your pooch,  some doggie treats,  dress in layers and let's meet at Fort Foster for a nice walk along the water and exploring at the Fort.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget your pooper bags !!    &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Game plan is to meet at Fort Foster at 11:30 am and walk along the shore for a couple of hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/f/highres_11041039.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you that have never been to Fort Foster,   it is an historic site,  grounds of an old Fort that protected the coastline.   There is a lovely walkway along the shore that has beautiful views.  You can do an easy walk on this path or you can go down on the rocks and let the dogs swim.  Plenty to do at this really nice area.   There is also a nice large grassy area overlooking the ocean if you just want to sit and read a book or have a snack with your dog.   Something for everyone here !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plunk is  looking forward to a nice walk with her regular buddies as well as meeting some new ones.  &lt;br /&gt;Holly will likely be bombing around,  chasing thrown tennis balls and jumping in the water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll try to do a nice walk and also allow time for the dogs to play in the water.   So please join us for an afternoon at the shore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions,  please email either Scott and Holly or Judi and Plunk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Woof woof&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And don't forget to dress in layers.  It may be a tad chilly along the water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS -  High tide is right around High Noon (sounds like an old Western Movie).   But we still should have enough beach area for walking under the pier and allowing the dogs to go swimming.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Plunk will be the cute beagle screaming "Over Here.....over here.......over here !!!  "</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judi-Judi-Judi</member_name><member_id>7477606</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott </member_name><member_id>8373739</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289499582000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286896838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fort Foster</name><id>15083890</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287847800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/15083890/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/b/global_11260107.jpeg</photo_url></item>