<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Nichole is hosting our &amp;quot;Girl's Just Wanna Have Fun!&amp;quot; Book Club!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Book to Get:  &lt;u&gt;&amp;quot;Sweet By and By&amp;quot;&lt;/u&gt; by Todd Johnson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Johnson's bittersweet and often humorous hen-lit debut portrays the lives of five very different Southern women: compassionate Lorraine, bossy Margaret, grief-stricken Bernice, ambitious April and brusque Rhonda. At the center of this character-driven novel is Lorraine, a nurse at the nursing home where Margaret and Bernice live. As the three women drift into friendship, hairdresser Rhonda arrives to take a part-time job, and the older women begin to change her life. Lorraine's daughter, April, meanwhile, is also gradually drawn into the circle. The story unfolds slowly over decades and life milestones, giving the characters plenty of time to reveal themselves. Johnson has a sure ear for Southern speech, though the dialect can become tiresome, and the narrative's lack of plot makes the novel feel overlong. Nevertheless, the underlying message of the power of love and friendship resonates, as does its depiction of the way in which people leading unremarkable lives can have a tremendous impact on those around them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;  BYOB&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Snack and appetizers will be provided by Nancy!  Thanks Nancy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt;  Take the driveway on the right side of the house to park in back.  Do not park in driveway in front of house  Nancy, is on the second floor.  Take stairs on the right side of the house.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharon</member_name><member_id>8235187</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276768780000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272822159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club Hosted by Nichole</name><id>13357792</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276209000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/13357792/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/4/global_5975620.jpeg</photo_url></item>