<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Oxford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375286</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard University Science Center - Hall A</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>776344</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117034</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;A new free lecture series called &amp;quot;Science and Cooking&amp;quot; is being held this Fall at Harvard University on almost every Monday night at 7:00 pm usually in the Science Center D lecture hall. Go to &lt;a href="https://www.seas.harvard.edu/cooking" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.seas.harv...&lt;/a&gt; to view the scheduled lectures.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&lt;/b&gt;: Sous-vide Cooking: a State of Matter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When:&lt;/b&gt; Sept 13, 2010, 7 pm - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speaker:&lt;/b&gt; Joan Roca (El Celler de Can Roca)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seas.harvard.edu/news-events/calendars/science-cooking/sous-vide-cooking-a-state-of-matter" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.seas.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Together with his brothers Jordi, the pastry chef, and Josep, the sommelier, Juan Roca operates the celebrated restaurant El Celler de Can Roca. Chef Roca has become most well known for his work with aroma and flavor, and avant garde experiments to fuse the two&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... The speaker literally wrote the book on this cooking technique based on cooking items stored in airtight plastic bags in water baths at low heat. A few of them, in fact. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be in &lt;b&gt;The Garage&lt;/b&gt; at 36 J.F.K. Street in Harvard Square inside Felipe's Taqueria &lt;a href="http://www.felipestaqueria.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.felipestaq...&lt;/a&gt; grabbing a bite to eat starting at 5:45 pm. Felipe's is on the lower level of the food court. He'll have a red MEETUP sign on the table. &lt;br /&gt;Since this lecture series is first-come first-serve, we probably should grab seats as a group by 6:40 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can start heading to Science Center D at 6:30 pm. It should be maybe an eight minute walk: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=JF+Kennedy+St&amp;amp;daddr=Unknown+road&amp;amp;geocode=FcuOhgIducvC-w%3BFW-bhgIdidXC-w&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=dme&amp;amp;mrcr=0&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=17&amp;amp;dirflg=w&amp;amp;sll=42.374715,-71.117828&amp;amp;sspn=0.006008,0.009624&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=17" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not joining us for dinner? Feel free to meet us outside the lecture hall. The doors, if I remember correctly, should have the letter &amp;quot;D&amp;quot; painted on them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sous Vide Cuisine, according to Amazon:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Sous-Vide-Cuisine-Joan-Roca/dp/8472121127" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Science &amp;amp; Cooking Lecture Series:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.seas.harvard.edu/cooking" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.seas.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These lectures compliment a new General Education science course &amp;quot;Science and Cooking: From Haute Cuisine to the Science of Soft Matter&amp;quot;. Lectures are free, open to the public, and &amp;quot;consist of a brief introduction by Harvard professors followed by a broad-based talk by the chef that may or may not contain material relevant&amp;quot; to the class. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;The Slowest Food: Why American chefs have taken up sous-vide cooking&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.slate.com/id/2123101/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.slate.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sous vide is the practice of cooking food at low temperatures in vacuum-packed plastic bags. (The term is essentially French for &amp;quot;vacuum-packed.&amp;quot;) Once you get beyond the cosmic ick of cooking in plastic, the sous-vide effect—something I have experienced in a few European restaurants and some ragtag home experiments—is uncannily tender. Food looks firm and neat but collapses quite willingly in your mouth. And since no juices or vapors escape from those little plastic parcels, food cooked sous vide is full of flavor—a little garlic goes a long way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Cooking in sealed packets is nothing new. For centuries, people encased food in something more or less waterproof, like a pig's bladder, and heated it in a water bath. Food cooked this way was steamy, moist, and perfumed with any herbs or spices sealed inside the bundle. Then, in 1974, a French chef named Georges Pralus learned that he could prevent the shrinkage of foie gras during cooking if he sealed it in plastic and poached it slowly. Pralus went on to teach the great chefs of the era, including Paul Bocuse, Alain Ducasse, and Michel Bras, about his method, and the technique became fairly common in Europe [...]&amp;quot; [ &lt;b&gt;MORE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.slate.com/id/2123101/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.slate.com/...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More about Joan Roca, on StarChefs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.starchefs.com/cooking/?q=node/57" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.starchefs....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Born to culinary parents, Spanish Chef Joan Roca’s earliest memories of cooking are with his mother in the kitchen of their family owned Restaurant de Can Roca, which served traditional Catalan cuisine. It is no surprise, then, that all three Roca brothers – Joan, Josep, and Jordi – ended up in the restaurant business. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;After going to culinary school in Girona, Roca and his brothers opened their own restaurant, El Celler de Can Roca, next door to their parents’place. In the beginning the restaurant was housed in a tight, ill-suited space. Roca could barely turn around in the kitchen, and the decor was modest and simple. Eventually the kitchen was remodeled to suit the evolving cuisine, which had outgrown its simple country roots. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Each of the Roca brothers has his own area of expertise – with Joan overseeing the cuisine, Josep selecting the wines, and Jordi handling the pastry. Today El Cellar de Can Roca has 2 Michelin stars, and Joan Roca is widely regarded as a leader in modern Spanish cuisine. Like many of his renowned Spanish counterparts, Roca dexterously combines tradition with modernity – he is known for his creative renditions of classic Catalan dishes, from suckling pig to sea cucumber&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions and Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://samsara.bebear.net/~alcrockett/sciencecenter/about/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://samsara.bebear...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our address is 1 Oxford Street, Cambridge MA. This is useful if you know where Oxford Street is, but since it is only about 1/3 of a mile long and inaccessible from Massachusetts Avenue, this is not much of a help for most people. We are very close to the intersection of Kirkland Street, which is also very short and again may be obscure to many who are unfamiliar with North Cambridge [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This interactive official university map &lt;a href="http://map.harvard.edu/level2.cfm?mapname=camb_allston&amp;amp;tile=F7&amp;amp;series=N" target="_blank"&gt;http://map.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt; shows the Science Center in the middle of the image. This is a very good map, with links &lt;a href="http://www.hpai.harvard.edu/pr/maps/maps.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hpai.harva...&lt;/a&gt; to other various map resources at Harvard, MIT, and the MBTA. As you can tell from these maps, we are very close to the middle of Harvard Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Science Center has no parking garage. One can usually find a space on Massachusetts Avenue, but it may take a bit of searching. We recommend parking at the Alewife or Braintree MBTA stations and riding the Red Line to the Harvard stop&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Website of El Celler De Can Roca:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cellercanroca.com/PORTADA/intro_2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cellercanr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The brochure for this lecture appears as the restaurant's splash page. On the &amp;quot;Who is Who&amp;quot; page, Joan is the savory mind, Josep is the liquid mind, with Jordi having the sweet mind, describing these three brothers as a triad as a creative arguement. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284487053000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284065259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joan Roca, Sous-vide Cooking @ Science &amp; Cooking lectures, Harvard lecture</name><id>14715185</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284418800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14715185/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/4/global_17829636.jpeg</photo_url></item>