<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Whitney Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.310850</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 773-1776</phone><name>Anna Liffey's</name><city>New Haven</city><id>207380</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922460</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join NHCer Larry for a fun Friday Night at Anna Liffey's featuring cover band "Shiver".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Shiver"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; will be playing downstairs at 10pm.&amp;nbsp; The band plays a HUGE variety of music from famous groups you might know like: AC/DC, Aerosmith, Alice In Chains, All-American Rejects, Ataris, Beastie Boys, Billy Idol, Billy Joel, Bon Jovi, Bowling for Soup, Buckcherry, Cheap Trick, Def Leppard, Fall Out Boy, Foo Fighters, Free, Fuel, Gavin DeGraw, Godsmack, Goo Goo Dolls, Good Charlotte, Green Day, Guns-N-Roses, Heart, Jet, Journey, Kiss, Led Zeppelin, Lenny Kravitz, Lit, Maroon 5, Metallica, Michael Jackson, Motley Crue, Nickelback, The Outfield, Poison, Puddle of Mudd, Queen, Rage Against the Machine, Saliva, Shinedown, Sponge, Stone Temple Pilots, Sublime, The Toadies, Tommy Tutone, Tool, Trapt, U2, Van Halen, Wild Cherry and many more!&amp;nbsp; (Ok I know that list is a mouth full.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You May want to checkout their &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/shiverrocks?ref=ts" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/shiverrocks?ref=ts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a cover charge to get in the door, expected to be in the $3-$5 range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;ALSO&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Playing upstairs, you can see &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;"SELL THE KIDS"&lt;/span&gt;, a Nirvana cover band featuring &lt;em&gt;NHC's very own Meredith&lt;/em&gt; filing in on Bass!&amp;nbsp; So if you're in the mood for some good 90's music stop upstairs!&amp;nbsp;(Currently scheduled for 11, but in a&amp;nbsp;collection that starts at 9, so check it out.)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Larry&lt;/span&gt; is hosting this meetup, and will&amp;nbsp; be getting there to stake out a spot around 9:30.&amp;nbsp; He can be reached at 203-466-2226 if you have trouble finding him or have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Party Express Group is also being invited to this meetup, so you may run into them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm sure most of you are familiar with the location:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Anna Liffey's&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a charming old Irish Pub in Downtown New Haven.&amp;nbsp; You can find some good pub food and friends here just about any day. Located on&amp;nbsp;Whitney Avenue, just after it changes over from Church Street, with a big old Irish Flag out front.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Larry whom will host this meetup, he can be reached at 203-466-2226</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry T </member_name><member_id>13177409</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306689152000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305738574000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>See "Shiver" at Anna Liffey's!</name><id>18849151</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306548000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/18849151/</event_url></item>