<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come join us this Friday night at one of Boston's great venues, 33 Lounge!  Expect DJs to spin a combination of hip-hop and international house all night in a great atmosphere.  A fun place to meet new people and to get your groove on!  All members welcome, and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 9pm in the LOUNGE bar at STIX Restaurant.  STIX is right next to 33, and you should proceed to the STIX Lounge to meet the group.  We will head over to 33 around 10:15pm to beat the lines.  Please meet us at STIX lounge as you may not find us later.  Cover:  I do not expect a cover, but be prepared for one in any case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as this is an upscale venue.  If traveling by T, Copley Square is the closest T stop on the green line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**On a side note, please look on the message board for Meetup Etiquette and other thoughts about the group**&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the site.  Call my cell if you have questions or trouble finding the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204639545000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Our meetup group is one of the largest in Boston because people have a great time meeting new people and enjoying the Boston Nightlife!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204002491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Get Your Groove On @ 33! This Friday, Feb 29th!!</name><id>7409529</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204336800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/7409529/</event_url></item>