<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hungry?  I mean REALLY hungry?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those south of the Hub, up for a great meal out, we'll be heading to Fire and Ice in Providence Place Mall. Friday night the 16th.  For those who haven't experienced this gastronomical wonder of the world, this is the time.  Explore their website at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fire-ice.com/menu/menu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fire-ice.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to get a feel for what you're in for.  This all you can eat dining experience is not for the slight of stomach. $16.95 covers as many trips to their magical grill as you desire.  Drinks, desserts and appetizers (if you can fit them in:-)  are priced separately, so come prepared to spend $25-30-ish at least per person depending on what else you wish to explore.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Providence Place are provided on the website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fire-ice.com/locations/providence.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fire-ice.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 22C exit off 95 basically dumps you straight into the mall parking lot.  Once you enter the mall, head down the escalators to the restaurants on street level.  Fire and Ice is to the right facing the street from the inside of the mall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet between 7 and 7:15 pm inside the restaurant.  Reservations have been made for 8 people.  Please be respectful of the restaurant and your peers and keep your RSVP accurate.  Sorry, no maybes for this one.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, feel free to contact Lisa.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beantown and Beyond</member_name><member_id>4494456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195616658000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194663980000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at Fire and Ice, Providence, RI</name><id>6713019</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195257600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/6713019/</event_url></item>