<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 may street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.257946</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Photo Studios</name><city>Worcester</city><id>2095731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.825211</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;DETAILS: Calling all photographers, models, makeup artists, hair stylists, designers, and those aspiring: The Great Model Shoot is an exciting networking event at what is becoming the largest co-op style photo studio in New England. Every shoot is unique, so don't miss it&lt;span&gt;! All are welcome, from first-timers to seasoned professionals. THE BIG IDEA: Network with others in the field! Build an amazing portfolio! Get experience! Learn and share ideas in a fun group setting... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 COST: Models $20 / Photographers $40 / for the ENTIRE day! / MUA, Hair, Designers: no cost! in return for donating time, skills and supplies for styling models. Price basically covers our cost to run the studio and includes lunch. (Ask us how to become a WPS member to get a discount on events!) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 WHAT TO BRING: Models should bring a variety of outfits and accessories that they would like to be photographed in. Feel free to go all out and be as unique as you want. Come early to get the most out of the day. This month is the "Valentine Edition." All attendees are encouraged to bring business cards. WPS also invites you to bring equipment/lighting, props, themed costumes, or just show up with your awesome personality. ;) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 CODE OF CONDUCT: &lt;br /&gt;

 There is NO NUDITY at The Great Model Shoot. Don't despair, there will be nude shoots scheduled in the near future. Our plan is to hold events to suit all types of photography. This event will be PG-13. Scantily-clad models MUST wear a robe between sets and during breaks. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Alcohol and drugs are strictly prohibited at all times. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Inappropriate behavior will result in a verbal warning by a WPS staff member. If such behavior continues, you will be asked to leave. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; This rules are put in place for everyone's safety and comfort. Any questions can be directed to Patrick (patrick@worcesterphotostu&lt;span&gt;dios.com) or the studio manager, Jenn (jenn@worcesterphotostudio&lt;/span&gt;s.com).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329790029000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327696134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Model Shoot v14 - Valentine's Edition</name><id>49898212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329656400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/49898212/</event_url></item>