<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>355 Congress St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.350210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bocoup Loft</name><city>Boston</city><id>1236793</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.048282</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Snow Alert:&lt;/b&gt; If there is severe snowfall on Wednesday or a snow emergency is declared in Boston, we will likely reschedule the meeting. Please check your e-mail or this page before you head out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feature Presentations:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Introduction to Sonar:&lt;/b&gt; In its unyielding ambition, Sonar seeks to satisfy any workflow. From non-linear Ableton-esque loop/sample triggering, to recording, software synthesis, step sequencing, mixing, and mastering, Sonar has features to make just about anyone drool. Composer, producer, and engineer Eric Hodge will lead a guided tour of this recently-updated powerhouse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Introduction to Orchestration, Part 1:&lt;/b&gt; For those with a secret hunger (or a mild interest) to produce symphonies, film scores, and showtunes on the computer. Topics will include the basics of voice leading; instrument families, ranges, articulations, and expressions; scoring practices; demos of some relatively inexpensive sample libraries; and who knows what else? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, we invite you to share your music with the group. Please shoot me an e-mail (yevster ~ gmail ~ dot ~com) or comment on this meetup's page if you would like us to play your song at the meetup. And, of course, we will have our customary book raffle and plenty of opportunities to mix and mingle with your fellow musicians.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The doors will open at 6:30. The presentations will start at 7. Please remember to RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yev</member_name><member_id>3234171</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296506672000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Music Makers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>musical</urlname><id>413373</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Music Makers With Relaxed Expectations</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294023178000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January 2011 Meetup</name><id>15891778</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296084600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/musical/events/15891778/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/2/2/global_20645922.jpeg</photo_url></item>