<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Emerson Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.615200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Open Door</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1528276</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.675987</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Do you like to paint?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Do you like to help out a great cause?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s go paint a bowl for the Empty Bowl&amp;hellip;. See the actual event in May which we will be scheduling soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information about the Bowl painting event:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have painting skills?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; No matter what your answer is come on down to this event and paint a bowl anyways, maybe they will even let us paint 2 bowl&amp;rsquo;s.... each? How gratifying would it be to see your bowl on the table amongst all the bowls that people are picking from, to take home on the day of the Empty bowl event in May (see below)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will have to make a reservation for this event so PLEASE only serious RSVP&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; If your plans change please come back and change your RSVP as soon as possible, so we can tell them that the # of people is different.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Be prepared I am NOT sure we will all be able to sit together, if this is a problem then this event may not be for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information about the Empty Bowl Event:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mission of The Open Door is to alleviate the impact of hunger in their community.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; They use practical strategies to connect people to good food, to advocate on behalf of those in need, and to engage others in the work of building food security.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that the painting time is only from 10:00-noon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At the Empty Bowl event:&lt;/strong&gt; The meal is simple&amp;mdash;soup, bread and a cookie. Guests can choose and keep a soup&amp;nbsp;bowl&amp;nbsp;handcrafted for this community event this could end up being one of the bowls that you had painted. The&amp;nbsp;bowl&amp;nbsp;goes home as an unspoken reminder that somewhere someone&amp;rsquo;s&amp;nbsp;bowl&amp;nbsp;is&amp;nbsp;empty. This is an event that is held in May that we have attended the last 2 years and will be putting on the calendar this year.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We will be scheduling this event soon.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--It can be a little tight, please make sure you are not blocking anyone&amp;rsquo;s driveway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--Is it time for you to pay your dues?&amp;nbsp; Please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo; You can give your dues to either Donna or Janet at any event.&amp;nbsp; Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be outside waiting for everyone, the painting starts at 10am, if you come in later than that come look for us at the tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vicki</member_name><member_id>4058114</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331557505000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329449027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paint a bowl (for the empty bowl to be posted soon)</name><id>52683002</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331390700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/52683002/</event_url></item>