<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>464 Abbott Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01453</zip><lat>42.548771</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doyle Center</name><city>Leominster</city><id>5561482</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.773987</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's raise some money for NEADS! One of our esteemed members, Heather Mills, is the co-chair for the WXY Young Professionals group for the Wachusett Chamber of Commerce. Every year they try to achieve the goal of giving back... This year they are helping NEADS raise money with their Walk-A-Thon! This event is happening June 2nd, 2012 and they are building two teams. Each chair will lead a team. Heather's goal is to get at least 10 people on her team to collectively raise at least $1,000! This is a dog friendly walk!! Bring your pooches!! Heather's fantastic boy, Champ, CGC will be there having a blast! ~~~ Come show your support for a great cause! This walk will be in Leominster at the Doyle Center (464 Abbott Ave). ~~~ Stroll along with Champ and Heather to raise money for a great service! If you love dogs and/or know anyone who has benefited or could benefit from an assistance dog, you know this is a walk for you! ~~~ Registration is from 9-10 and the walk is at 10. There is a 1 mile handicapped accessible route or a 3.5 mile route. ~~~ RSVP here and contact Heather for more information and to register at the following: Heather R. Mills, (978) 368-0173/hmills@wcu.com ~~~ Heather &amp;amp; Champ would love to have you on their team! Here is the link for more info! &lt;a href="http://www.neads.org/page.aspx?pid=598" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neads.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338657934000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328571144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk for NEADS! (National Education for Assistance Dog Services)</name><id>51310352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338645600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/51310352/</event_url></item>