<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>63 Washington St</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>01867</zip><lat>42.520500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>63 Washington St</name><city>Reading</city><id>6437772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.108932</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/1/4/event_18375892.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hi everyone! I invite you to see a wonderful movie &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;The Shadow Effect&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's more than a movie, it's a chance to go deeper into understanding yourself, and others around you. It's inspirational and extraordinary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is it, your shadow?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How it affects you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deepak Chopra, Marianne Williamson, Dr.David Simon&lt;/strong&gt;, and other world-renowned thinkers join &lt;strong&gt;Debbie Ford&lt;/strong&gt; (the acclaimed expert on the human shadow) in this stunning documentary to reveal the transformative power of your shadow - the parts of yourself that you dislike and disown, the past that you regret and repress, and the future that is waiting to be birthed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Shadow Effect&lt;/em&gt; will leave you breathing deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please, come to join me on the journey of healing and transformation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's look and discover our own shadows, take back our power and step into the possibility of the next greatest evolution of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reclaim your right to be who you always wanted to be in the world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is so terrifying? To be present to someone who is willing to speak the truth, someone who is willing to acknowledge that we all have the tendency to lie, betray, cheat and inflate ourselves. We also have the ability to have impeccable integrity, to be faithful, to be courageous and to be an expression of the divine.  Debbie Ford, the creator of the movie, is a #1 New York Times best-selling author and an internationally recognized expert in the field of personal transformation and human potential. Debbie’s laser eye and her courageous voice have popped millions out of denial and terrified the weak of heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This movie night can be a good chance to meet and talk with new members and make our group bigger. It's also a possibility for a follow-up interactive class-discussion as the next group meetup. I hope to see you here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love and Peace, Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested donations: $5 +&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There is a white, two-family house on the corner of the one-way part of Washington street</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>9452646</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347722010000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>members with unlimited potential</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club</urlname><id>1467921</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Holistic Lifestyle  Women's Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344030873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie night + discussion!</name><id>76230972</id><headcount>2</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347663600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club/events/76230972/</event_url></item>