<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Storrow Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.361210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Community Boating</name><city>Boston</city><id>628570</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072360</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thought I'd schedule a skate to coincide with a Free Friday Flick.  You know you've heard of them before, but have you ever been to one?  It's a fun thing to do on a nice night in the summer.  Also, unlike other Hatch Shell events, it's never crowded.  The movie this night is Iron Man with Robert Downey Jr.  I haven't seen it yet and this is the last free flick of the season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet at 7:00 p.m.  That gives you plenty of time to go home after work and change or come straight from work for those of you who work late.  We'll skate for about an hour.  The movie starts at &amp;quot;dusk&amp;quot; which usually is about 8:15 p.m.  There's also a snack bar where you can get refreshments while enjoying the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instead of meeting at the oval where everyone else meets we'll meet across from the Community Boating Center. If you take the Redline to Charles/MGH and walk over the footbridge it's right at the bottom of the stairs. If you are coming a different way, it's behind the Hatch Shell and before the bridge the Redline crosses to Cambridge. You can see the Center in the picture above. There's one covered bench across from the Center and it's next to a stone water bubbler.  We'll meet there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can RSVP &amp;quot;No&amp;quot;, Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot;.  Whatever you choose, please update your RSVP if your plans change.  Let me know if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In front of Community Boating, sitting on covered bench next to water bubbler.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268061301000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246226789000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Skate &amp; Iron Man Flick</name><id>10754963</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251500400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/10754963/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/1/b/global_4311867.jpeg</photo_url></item>