<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;NEWEST STUFF:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Movie Lovers,
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, there's been a death in my family and I'm not going to be able to make The Help. Instead of cancelling the whole thing for 50 people, I've asked my wonderful husband, Paul, to help out. He'll be handing out vouchers to the people on the Yes list at 6:00 on Wednesday evening right outside the theater, under the marquis. If you are on the Yes list and you aren't there by 6:15, your ticket will be given away to someone else. With 15 people on the Waiting List, I'm sure it will have a taker.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Yes Listers: Please keep your RSVP up to date. This enables Waiting Listers to make plans. If you're running late, catch traffic, get lost, whatever, sorry, but this time you're out of luck. I usually wait or even come out of the movie after it starts to hand out vouchers to people who have come late and let me know they're late, but this time that courtesy will be impossible.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Waiting Listers: If you're feeling lucky, show up at the theater by 6:15 and catch any low-hanging fruit (i.e., vouchers that no-shows won't get) and see the movie for free!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Paul is a tall (6'3") blond guy, early 50s, and very handsome. :-) He's hard to miss. Just tell him you're there for the meetup. Also tell him your name and if you're on the yes list or the waiting list, so he can dole the vouchers out appropriately.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Please, please, please, DON'T call me if you're going to be late. I'll be in North Carolina by Wednesday night and honestly, will have bigger fish to fry than the movie (hard to believe, I know!). :-) Normally, I love people to call me for a movie, but this time is an exception.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the show, everyone! It's supposed to be a great movie!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;-Dana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, we've reached 50 people, and I just found out that's the limit, so I've closed this to new RSVPs. Please keep your RSVP up to date (that is, if you can't make it or would like to decrease the number of guests you'll be bringing), as there may be people waiting to get in if there are cancellations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance for making this our BIGGEST meetup ever!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie itself is free, but the concessions aren't. I do, however, as usual, have vouchers for small popcorns and small fountain sodas ($3 each). So bring cash if you'd like to partake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll be meeting at 6:00 p.m. in the theater lobby so that we can be assured of getting seats (they give away more vouchers than there are seats in the theater). With a group this large, I'm sure we'll all find someone to talk to in order to pass the time! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Dana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bestselling book 
&lt;em&gt;The Help&lt;/em&gt; is now a movie! Join other movie fans for a free screening on July 13!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just got this email from a rep for Disney movies:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;-----------------
 &lt;br /&gt;



Hey There,

My name is Omri and I am reaching out to you on behalf of
 &lt;br /&gt;




 Walt Disney Motion Pictures and I would like to invite you
 &lt;br /&gt;




 and your members to an upcoming FREE advanced screening of
 &lt;br /&gt;




 THE HELP on July 13 at the Framingham theater.

The film is based off the Best Selling author Kathryn
 &lt;br /&gt;




 Stockett&amp;rsquo;s, &amp;ldquo;The Help&amp;rdquo;.
 &lt;br /&gt;




If you are unfamiliar with the novel, the story 
takes place in Jackson, Mississippi in 1962 and it is
 &lt;br /&gt;




 about a girl who returns home after college and forms
 &lt;br /&gt;




 and unexpected friendship with African-American Maids
 &lt;br /&gt;




 and she writes a book about the previously unheard
 &lt;br /&gt;




 voice of a racially divided struggling community.

 Below is the movie trailer:
&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/video/imdb/vi809278745/"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/video/imdb/vi809278745/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
----------------------
 &lt;br /&gt;




So, if you'd like to go, please RSVP by June 24 (next Friday) at 11:45 p.m.
and let me know if you're planning on bringing any guests.

Remember: The movie is free!
 &lt;br /&gt;





--Dana
&lt;/pre&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Paul under the marquis outside the theater: tall, blonde, handsome!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1311122400000</updated><rating><average>4.26999998093</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308174501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Screening -- The Help</name><id>22354121</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310594400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/22354121/</event_url></item>