<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Experience the positive shifts that occur in life and relationships as you learn how to be more centered and focused on your passions, but balanced with compassion and connection to others. At guided meditation on Monday evenings with Sally Fiore, you will release tension and stress, experience deep peace and love in your core, connect with your own authentic purpose and vision, pour beauty and grace into your energy field outside of your physical body, all of which boosts your immune system and can actually aid in healing dis-ease. Receive encouragement and support from this wonderful group of women whose energy and intention is so pure. Feel the healing energy of the sacred gardens and grounds at The Larches Inn, and by Sweet Mother Earth and the natural elememts that we honor as contributors to our journey. We work together on healing emotional scars, on releasing old patterns and behavior that no longer serves us, weight loss and self esteem, and deepening spirituality. Understand that you are making an invaluable contribution to the sea of human consciousness when you let go, meditate and chant your way to making your dreams reality, and take a pro active role in creating a life of health, joy and abundance. When we walk in "Right Relationship" with the Earth and all of its living creatures, many wonderful blessings fall into place for us! Please join us, and journey with us for a reason, a season,or a lifetime! Sign up for six weeks for $55.00, or drop in any Monday for an offering of $10.00 per class&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sally Fiore</member_name><member_id>8203589</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301408987000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299245961000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Right Relationship" Meditation Every Monday Night at 7:00</name><id>rmqpqypfblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301353200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/16999820/</event_url></item>