<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Madison starting with July 26, 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa  26     High   5:27 AM     4.7   5:40 AM     Set  2:47 PM      48&lt;br /&gt;    26      Low  11:25 AM     0.5   8:13 PM&lt;br /&gt;    26     High   5:50 PM     5.5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; SAT&lt;br /&gt; SW WINDS AROUND 5 KT...BECOMING S IN THE AFTERNOON. SEAS 1 FT&lt;br /&gt; OR LESS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; SAT NIGHT&lt;br /&gt; SW WINDS 5 TO 10 KT. SEAS 1 FT OR LESS...THEN 1 TO 2 FT&lt;br /&gt; AFTER MIDNIGHT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday: Sunny, with a high near 77. Calm wind becoming south between 6 and 9 mph.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Night: Partly cloudy, with a low around 71. South wind between 5 and 7 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As most of you know, there are other spots to paddle in this area yet i will only choose a location of ample parking for a larger group with as good of directions i can find and or improve upon, I prefer and i assume you want events that start at the noon hour which can go on all day till sunset or later..although i understand early events may have advantages etc...But not if you dont have to and have to drive a ways...&lt;br /&gt;Nor do i want to be some Bloaking Loud mouth asshole in the lead setting the total pace etc..&lt;br /&gt;This is a discovery event for you, (I have been here a long time ago)...we take our time, look in interesting places and let the group set the dynamics...or you can go off on your own..its to be a enjoyable time...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I usually dont care to go with other groups (too many bad experiences and clash of methods, ideals, directions...waiting times, and in general ..more boring or something people i just dont have time for unless they are exciting then its a great time... etc..although if you like them, i will say thats ok.) yet i invite them to my events because then its my world and reality they enter....and they too can enjoy the after events of barbie-q's and conversation in a easy dynamic outside settinng...no restaurant odd seating..etc... or they can JUST GO AWAY as Deputy Dog used to say..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING SOME FOOD, ADULT BUGG JUICE..WATER, SUNSCREAM ..WELL YOU KNOW WHAT TO BRING..&lt;br /&gt;AND YUR PADDLING SAFETY STUFF... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF THE WATER LOOKS GOOD YOU CAN ACTUALLY TRY A DEEP WATER RE-ENTRY IN SOME REAL WAVES.. AS WE JUST WATCH YOU STRUGGLE AND HAVE A SANDWITCH MAYBE OFFERING YOU A BITE IF YOU SURVIVE...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This over the years has been a good location because there are 2 rivers to explore if the seas are not great..but also if you want to there are a few places along the shore to explore also..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its not a great place for a Barbie-q but there is a good spot for a grinder, fruit salad..(portable stuff)..The Red House on the beach...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will choose a better place for the after event in the area...&lt;br /&gt;or around on the circle beach in a secluded area..etc..&lt;br /&gt;TBD..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;91 south to rte 9 south&lt;br /&gt;exit #9 for rte 81 south all the way to the Clinton PremiumOutlet stores, then get onto 95 SOUTH there for a few exits..&lt;br /&gt;Take exit # 60 for Mungertown Road, take left, head to rte 1&lt;br /&gt;At end of Mungertown Rd take left onto rte 1 then first right road turn onto NECK RD..follow rest of directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East: (from Clinton)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 South to exit 60. Turn left off the exit onto Mungertown Road. Travel south on Mungertown Road for approximately 0.6 miles. Turn a slight left onto Boston Post Road (rte 1) . Travel on Boston Post Road for approximately 0.2 miles. Turn right onto Neck Road. Travel approximately 100 yards to an intersection and turn right again (it looks like a little triangle green thing), continuing on Neck Road. Follow the Boat Launch signs. Travel on Neck Road for approximately 1.3 miles. At the end of Neck Road, turn left onto Ridgewood Avenue. Travel on Ridgewood Avenue for approximately 0.3 miles. At the end of Ridgewood Avenue, turn right onto Circle Beach Road (dirt road). Travel on Circle Beach Road for approximately 0.3 miles. The boat launch entrance is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOOK FOR THE ORANGE Traffic CONE ON MY CAR ROOF...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West: Take I-95 North to exit 59. Turn right off the exit onto Soundview Road. Travel south on Soundview Road for approximately 50 yards. Turn left onto Boston Post Road. Travel on Boston Post Road for approximately 2.2 miles. Turn right onto Neck Road. Same as above...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Homless Persons Bathtub= Pungo 12' with floataion bags 1nstalled= KATHY`G&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= AL-R&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = ALEX&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= BILL&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenland= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= HOLLY ?????????????????????????????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 10 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Toyota Avalon with a Kayak Trailer and a few Orange Traffic Cones on ROOF</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217354227000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216735796000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sea &amp; Recreational Kayaks, CIRCLE BEACH, West River &amp; Ocean Paddle event, .</name><id>8388462</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217088000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8388462/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/global_474104.jpeg</photo_url></item>