<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Dues (unless prepaid)</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Venez &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... boire un martini, une bière, un cafe, ou un thé.&lt;br /&gt;... faire la connaissance d'autres francophones.&lt;br /&gt;... profiter d'une discussion en français avec des amis.&lt;br /&gt;... ecouter un peu de musique.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venez nous rejoindre!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*NEWS FLASH #1* On 108/Central Avenue southbound, just above Dover Soul, THE BRIDGE IS CLOSED, so you can't reach Dover Soul like usual. The Orchard Street lot (behind Dover Soul) is open, but you must enter it from the rear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling NORTH on 108/Central Ave, turn left on Washington St (NB: Crescent City Bistro on far left), then take first right onto Chestnut St. Look for what looks like an apartment parking lot (first right?), and turn in. Zig-zag toward back right, then turn left into the metered parking area behind Brick House. Park, then walk around to the street side of the buildings to Dover Soul. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling SOUTH on 108/Central Avenue, follow detour signs to Chestnut St. After the traffic light at Curves (L) and Goodwill (R), look for apartments on your left, and turn in. Zig-zag toward back right, then turn left into the metered parking area behind Brick House. Park, then walk around to the street side of the buildings to Dover Soul. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: You can exit Orchard St onto Central Ave as usual, for destinations north as well as south. (Toujours des questions? Call Dover Soul at 603-834-6965.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*NEWS FLASH #2* Dover Soul is in transition.  Little Louie's has been closed, and &amp;quot;OUR&amp;quot; SOFAS HAVE BEEN REMOVED from the back of the café. Meet in the Martini Bar instead (walk to the back of the café and turn right).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*NEWS FLASH #3* SOYEZ SAGE!  Don't try to drive if the roads are bad. Look at a map to get an idea of possible detours, and check road closings before traveling: &lt;a href="http://www.wmur.com/news/9214227/detail.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wmur.com/n...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.doversoul.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.doversoul.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.doversoul....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam Angulo</member_name><member_id>789593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastNHFrench</urlname><id>63967</id><group_lat>43.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>Seacoast NH French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1145491355000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May French Meetup #2: mercredi réunion</name><id>4905770</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1147906800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastNHFrench/events/4905770/</event_url></item>