<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Kearney Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01852</zip><lat>42.645347</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Middlesex Community College</name><city>Lowell</city><id>826825</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.307161</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>On Saturday, December 6th (this coming Saturday!) join us for One-Shot Game Day/ JiffyCon at Middlesex Community College in Lowell (no affiliation with the college, just using the space).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The focus is on trying out new role playing games- some popular and some independently published games, some run by the authors!  Games planned include D&amp;amp;D 4e, Misspent Youth, Zombie Cinema, and Factions at War.  Haven't played 4e yet?  Now's your chance?  Need something besides just D&amp;amp;D?  Come on in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be a &amp;quot;Board Game Corner&amp;quot; with all of the favorites and unsung cool games.  Heard about a certain game but never got the opportunity to try it out?  That is the whole focus of this con!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is an admission, but it's just to cover cost of food (lunch is included!).  We'd consider bringing food as an equitable pay (talk to us first though).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids 8 and up are welcome!  Planning on bringing some kid friendly games!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration starts at 9:00 and games start at 10:00 and go until 5-6.&lt;br /&gt;All of the information can be found here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://brilliantgameologists.com/blog/64" target="_blank"&gt;http://brilliantgameo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Myriad Games in Salem, NH is helping support this by providing fabulous door prizes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's sure to be a ton of fun.  A great chance to de-stress between the holidays!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;EDIT: Details for finding this!&lt;/b&gt;  (There are still openings, come on in, you'll have fun!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration begins at 9:00 and games start at 10:00.  We'll have some munchies and coffee at 9:00 for the people who are right on time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: Don't park in the little lot in front of Middlesex Community College (Lowell Campus).  On the street right there are meters- all free on the weekend.  Or there is a parking lot across the canal, behind the college, but it's a pain to get to unless you've been there before.  Across the street from the college is a grey brick federal building that has a lot in the back- you can park there too.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to find us: Classes are held at the college on Saturday so we're not going to be alone!  We'll hang up signs though pointing the way- we're in the lower cafeteria if you are the &amp;quot;asking directions type&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to see everyone!  Bring games to share- it'll be a blast!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park across the street behind the post office looking building.  Follow signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>1260251</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228864332000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228365467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One-Shot Game Day/ JiffyCon</name><id>9278021</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228572000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/9278021/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/f/global_3081279.jpeg</photo_url></item>