<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West Hartford Center</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06110-1506</zip><lat>41.734531</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Viadel Gusto and Bella Gusta both in town center West Hartford then end at Bricco</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1584862</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.718773</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gusto-italia.us/page-3#!__via-del-gusto"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/7/f/event_22421599.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Via del Gusto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;is an Italian Market run by a retired Exectutive Chef. They feature all things Italian and yummy to eat. Our host for the evening will talk about her favorite recipes, and the special items you can find in the shop. We will start at this site at &lt;strong&gt;6:30PM 16 La Salle Rd, West hartford, CT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we will walk around the corner to &lt;a href="http://bellagustaoils.myshopify.com/"&gt;Bella Gusta Oils&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;where owner Lydnia Przybylski will hold a tasting of her oils and vinegars, teach us how to make a little sumtinsumthin and share a few of her favorite recipes, with samples. &lt;strong&gt;Bella Gusta Oils is at 981 FArmington, West Hartford and we will meet there at 7:30.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can only attend one of these two, please let me know which so I can balance the group. Due to the size of the shops I need to strictly limit attendance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cost to this event but please be prepared to buy yummy things from these vendors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you would like to go out to dinner afterwards at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.billygrant.com/bricco.html"&gt;Bricco&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;just to stay with the Italian theme. I will need to make a reservation. If you want to join the group for dinner but not attend the first part of the evening let me know that as well. &lt;strong&gt;We'll meet at Bricco 78 La Salle Rd, West hartford at 9:00PM, but I will have them be able to seat us at 8:30PM. &lt;/strong&gt;I am sure you know you will need to pay for whatever you order at Bricco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Now this is a three in one deal that you can do 1 to 3 parts of so when you RSVP you must be very very clear which parts you'll be doing. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;When you&amp;nbsp;RSVP please put clearly answer the questions so i can coordiante everything and accomodate as many folk as possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Read the write up in total please - this is a three in one deal.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306191762000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Viadel Gusto and Bella Gusta have both invited us to come for a special visit.</why><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301438944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gusta, Gusto!</name><id>17107412</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305844200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/17107412/</event_url></item>