<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>405 Capitol Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.763733</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>La Paloma SAbenera</name><city>Hartford</city><id>966778</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689034</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Film 101 is a new monthly program that La Paloma Sabanera and Capitol Cinema Collective &lt;/strong&gt;(avec Rabbit Ears Media) will be presenting to promote an appreciation of classic cinema and discussions of film. To that end, the films selected will be connected by theme or influenced from one film to the next. Curators cinephilette &lt;em&gt;Meghan Maguire Dahn &lt;/em&gt;and cinemagician's apprentice &lt;em&gt;Helder Mira &lt;/em&gt;will be selecting films and film makers who influenced one another, discussing their impact on cinema and film culture. &lt;br /&gt;First up:&amp;nbsp; FREE ADMISSION &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BAND OF OUTSIDERS (Bande &amp;agrave; part, 1964, directed by Jean-Luc Godard) Based on the novel &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Storyline A triangle: Franz, Arthur, and Odile. Franz, a young man with Alain Delon good looks, has met Odile in an English class. She lives in Joinville with wealthy benefactors and has mentioned to Franz that Mr. Stolz keeps a pile of 10,000 franc notes unlocked in his room. Franz tells his friend Arthur, a swarthy guy whose shady uncle is pressing him for money. Arthur and Franz, who mimic American movie tough guys, case Odile's house, pressure her to assist them with a burglary, and make passes at her as well. She's alternately compliant and distressed. Will they pull off the heist? &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt; The discussion will focus on the influence of Orson Welles' film noir masterpiece Touch of Evil on Godard and the French New Wave. &lt;br /&gt;Join us for an evening of film appreciation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s3HME4oDPNk"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s3HME4oDPNk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a small venue. Ask the owner if you can't see me..</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306377209000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305665566000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film 101 presents : BAND OF OUTSIDERS @ La Paloma Saberna Coffee Shop</name><id>18740181</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306363500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/18740181/</event_url></item>