<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>335 Somerville Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02145</zip><lat>42.380650</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>617-666-3589</phone><name>Sally Obrien's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>502279</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098145</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come on out and see the band STRETCH play a FREE SHOW at Sally Obriens Bar and Grill!&lt;br /&gt;Located in Union Square at 335 Somerville Ave in Somerville, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sallyobriensbar.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Sally Obrien's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sally Obrien's has food available to those that might want to come early and get a bite to eat.&lt;br /&gt;If there is enough interest we could meet before the show and get a bite to eat somewhere close and have some drinks. I can update the information as we get closer to the night of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/stretchinboston" target="_blank"&gt;Listen to STRETCH!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stretch is typically a 5 piece Jazz band playing a unique Jazz, Fusion and even Reggae mix. &lt;br /&gt;Dave Hess is playing woodwinds, Paul Erlick and Mike Herman's on Guitars. &lt;br /&gt;George Chinaglia plays Bass and their Drummer Randy Wooten.&lt;br /&gt;Stretch does not play very often so catch them when you can, you won't regret it.&lt;br /&gt;Many people who have seen them insist they are better to hear and see Live than recorded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to Meetup with some of you there. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of time to sign up and schedule to see this group.&lt;br /&gt;E-mail me if you have any questions...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Sally Obrien's is a relatively small place. It would be pretty hard to miss me. I can provide my cell phone number on request to any meetup member who are planning to attend.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg D</member_name><member_id>4879355</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206943391000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Please come see this Free Show and enjoy the Unique blend of talented musicians and varied music styles that make up the great Music of Stretch. You won't regret it!</why><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202160373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stretch (Jazz) @ Sally Obrien's Bar and Grill</name><id>7262665</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206671400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/7262665/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/global_3144156.jpeg</photo_url></item>