<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 1A</address_2><address_1>675 Ocean Blvd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03870</zip><lat>43.041522</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-7406</phone><name>Odiorne Point State Park</name><city>Rye</city><id>1004721</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.715843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Odiorne Point State Park offers one of the most beautiful natural settings along New Hampshire's 18-mile coastline.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come with us to hike the beautiful Odiorne Point trails and visit The Seacoast Center at Odiorne Point State Park. The state park is a great place to explore with its 350-acres of hiking trails through multiple habitats. The Seacoast Science Center will take us deeper into those habitats with a tide pool touch-tank. There are also interpretive exhibits, a 32-foot skeleton of a humpback whale, amazing views of the seashore, a rare blue lobster in their "Gulf of Maine" exhibit hall and much more. This will be an opportunity to enjoy learning things you never knew about the coastline and all of its creatures. &lt;br /&gt;

 We will start by hiking parts of the extensive network of trails that wind through the dense vegetation as they traverse the park. There are spectacular views of the ocean and the rocky shore, with evidence of past military occupation. We'll stop for lunch (please pack your own) then continue to the Science Center where we can spend as much time as we want to end our great day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meetup location and additional details will be announced soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350937053000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350284288000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Odiorne Point State Park - Hike, explore, and Discover the Seacoast</name><id>87019622</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350829800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/87019622/</event_url></item>