<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What Pat wrote:&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, 5.17.09 I'm planning to hike Scar Ridge via the ski &lt;br /&gt;trails on Loon Mountain.  In terms of mileage and vertical gain &lt;br /&gt;this hike is much tougher than the numbers indicate.  It should &lt;br /&gt;be smooth sailing up the Loon ski trails to the North Peak &lt;br /&gt;(elevation 2900 feet).  We'll proceed roughly 0.3 miles along a &lt;br /&gt;backcountry ski trail and turn off as the trail continues &lt;br /&gt;towards Black Mountain.  From here it will be a tough 1.0 mile &lt;br /&gt;bushwhack with a vertical gain of ~900 feet.  This bushwhack is &lt;br /&gt;notorious for the dense trees along the ridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In total the hike will encompass 6.0 miles with a vertical gain &lt;br /&gt;of 2600 feet.  I'd estimate the trip time to be roughly 6 &lt;br /&gt;hours.  There are no views from the summit but there are nice &lt;br /&gt;views north towards Franconia Ridge along the ski trail.  It &lt;br /&gt;won't be pretty, but peak #97 on the New England 100 highest is &lt;br /&gt;not known for her beauty.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's start early in hopes the cooler night air will harden any &lt;br /&gt;remaining snow, making our ascent as easy as possible.  Meetup &lt;br /&gt;time 8 am in the  eastern end of the Loon parking lot.  &lt;br /&gt;Questions?  Email me at pcushing21 at yahoo_dot_com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you're game!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pat&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Email Pat at pcushing21a@ yahoo_dot_com</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242735100000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241999434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scar Ridge via the ski  trails on Loon Mountain</name><id>10381608</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242561600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10381608/</event_url></item>