<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mulberry St</address_1><state>NY</state><lat>40.719328</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Little Italy</name><city>New York City</city><id>1054044</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.997314</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;The 82nd Annual Feast of San Gennaro, New York City’s longest-running, biggest and most revered religious outdoor festival in the United States, will be held Thursday, September 10, through Sunday, September 20, 2009, on the streets of historic Little Italy, the lower Manhattan neighborhood which served as the first home in America for hundreds of thousands of Italian immigrants who came here seeking to improve their lives beginning in the early part of the 20th century.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Indoor and outdoor dining at 35 of Little Italy's most famous Italian restaurants. More than 300 licensed street vendors selling international foods, official Feast of San Gennaro, New York City and Little Italy souvenirs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&amp;quot;One of New York City's major cultural attractions!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fun for the entire family!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;New York City's biggest and most famous street party!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A celebration of the Patron Saint of Naples!&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;For those who want to get there early:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;(The Official Feast Day)&lt;br /&gt;3 PM -- A Celebratory Mass in honor of San Gennaro led by Father Fabian Grifone, Pastor of the Most Precious Blood Church.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;4 PM -- A Religious Procession in which the Statue of San Gennaro is carried through the streets of the Feast.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting to Little Italy&lt;br /&gt;Little Italy is located in lower Manhattan and is easily accessible by subway, bus or car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Grand Central Station.&lt;br /&gt;From the East Side: Take the 6 subway downtown to the Spring Street station. Walk East 2 blocks to Mulberry Street. OR Take the M103 bus on Lexington Avenue down to Grand Street and walk West 3 blocks to Mulberry Street&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We can meet in front of the Church.  109 Mulberry St.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253563738000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251898172000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 82nd Annual Feast of San Gennaro Little Italy NY</name><id>11267733</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253390400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/11267733/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/8/global_10515128.jpeg</photo_url></item>