<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1585 Hancock St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.246960</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-773-5888</phone><name>Little Q Hotpot</name><city>Quincy</city><id>421408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.000916</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us at the Little Q Hotpot to share some food together.  Cook at your table and enjoy some great conversations with other South Shore Dining Members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many shout outs on Yelp.com for The Little Q.  All agree they enjoyed the food and fun cooking their own food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will also be a good opportunity for members to pay their 2010 Annual Membership Fee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come and join in this fun festive time with the South Shore Dining Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, December 18th @ 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Little Q Hotpot&lt;br /&gt;Quincy, MA&lt;br /&gt;P:&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.littlequsa.com/Web/Home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;littlequsa.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer: Jeanne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Up to 2 per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price Range: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cash Only Policy: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: Annual Members - None. Group Members and Guests - $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Thursday, December 17th at 7:00 PM. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer. Changes to No after this point will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: Please refer to this aptly named page on the About page for full details.  If weather could potentially be a problem we will post an update here the week of the event with a final update/guideline around the RSVP Deadline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: To be posted the week before the event.  (Credit to Little Q's wesbite.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview: Located in the Quincy Fair Mall in Quincy Center, they are the last remaining restaurant so once inisde the building it shouldn't be too hard to miss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Resveration in Jeanne White's Name and South Shore Dining Group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>714439</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262910926000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260105074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Q" Join us at Little Q Hotpot on December 18, 2009</name><id>12028405</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261179000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/12028405/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/d/global_12111101.jpeg</photo_url></item>