<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>160 Shield St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06110</zip><lat>41.728271</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>A Dong Supermarket</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1562930</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.722130</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/4/c/event_22421548.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We have done this previously and it was a lot of fun. This time we are combining it with a vietnamese lunch. I will bring a large cooler so if anyone buys any products that require cooling we can keep stuff in the cooler during lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I shop there frequently and can recommend some products but you should expect many products that do not carry english labels so you may need to brush up on your chinese and japanese.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After shopping we will be having lunch at Pho Boston, which is my favorite place for a wonderful vietnamese soup called &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pho"&gt;Pho&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RSVP list closes 3 days before the event so I can have a final head count because I am going to make a reservation at Pho Boston. If you only plan on coming to A Dong but not to Pho Boston please note it when you are RSVPing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside next to the entrance and I will be wearing a brown T-shirt that has a schematic of the various beef cuts on it</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gady</member_name><member_id>8983958</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304946094000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><why>This is the largest Asian market in the area and it is an opportunity to shop for unusual and exotic ingredients. After we are done we will have lunch at Pho Boston.</why><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300161882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shopping at A. Dong and Lunch at Pho Boston</name><id>16925269</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304780400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/16925269/</event_url></item>