<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>63 Chatham St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359682</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-367-6172</phone><name>Trinity Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>723067</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054460</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We have just finalized our fundraising event for the Boston Angels team Autumn Bike Trek for the American Lung Association.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Help the Boston Angels raise money for the American Lung Association Bike Trek!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us at our Summer Fundraiser Thursday, August 7th to raise money for our 160 mile Bike Trek for the American Lung Association!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Angels will be hosting a party at Trinity Bar in Faneuil Hall in Boston. The Boston Angels is a local Boston team participating in Autumn Escape Bike Trek to raise money for The ALA. We need your help!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join the fun and your chance to win dozens of prizes or participate in our Silent Auctions. 100% of proceeds will go directly to our team fundraising initiative. Sip our complimentary tasty Angel Martini special, munch on some scrumptious treats (sushi form Duozo and so much more), meet the members of our team, and dance the night away. It’s an incredible way to contribute to a worthy cause, support the team, and end your work day. The giveaways are huge and we can't reveal-you'll have to come to find out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Trinity Bar (3rd floor) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;63 Chatham St, Faneuil Hall Marketplace &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02109 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;617-367-6172 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donation: $10 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trinity will validate parking at 35 State Street for a total of $10 fee.. This is centrally located to the Green, Blue and Red line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are unable to join us please donate to the Boston Angel’s team on my page securely at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mrsnv.com/evt/e01/part.jsp?rid=849493&amp;amp;id=1679&amp;amp;acct=8013393647" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mrsnv.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I appreciate your support and hope you will join us! Spread the word--this is an important cause and means a lot to me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terri&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My team and I will be in White</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218319582000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217300316000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Angels fundraiser for the American Lung Association</name><id>8431967</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218146400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/8431967/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/1/global_4965521.jpeg</photo_url></item>