<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Springfield Uprising Men's Group is holding an Open Men's Group from 6:30 until 9:00 pm at 380 Union Street, West Springfield, MA. You are invited to attend this meeting - get support with whatever is going on in your life, celebrate your success with a group of peers, connect with other men who are dedicated to personal growth and the betterment of the planet. Overcome the isolation that so many men experience every day ... feeling unseen even when surrounded by co-workers, friends and family. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Men need a place to tell the truth about themselves - the beautiful truth and the ugly truth of being a man. &lt;br /&gt;Hearing men speak the truth about themselves makes it easier to let down the mask that we each wear for the world. Getting honest about who we are in a safe space is the ONLY way we will learn new habits, new skills and new ways of being. This honesty creates new possibilities. Taking this risk makes it easier to take other risks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have had several men ask me - what is this is all about ? what do you do?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We sit in a circle on chairs. We talk to each other about what's going on in our lives. We listen to one another. We do not shame or criticize. We do not spend time giving advice. We resolve conflicts, both internal and external, by taking responsibility for ourselves. We use exercises that you can learn to use in your life to help you be more connected, more awake, better able to navigate the difficulties in your life. We form a community of men that are here for one another in a way that few men get to experience these days. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A men's group is a place to figure out what you want in your life, take steps to make it happen and continually look at what is getting in the way of being fully alive and empowered. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you want better relationships with family, friends, co-workers?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you want to learn how to better handle situations that stump you over and over?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you want to break out of a rut that you have been living in for years?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you want to sit with men actively working to make the world a better place?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you want to discover what being a man is all about ... FOR YOU?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you instinctively NOT trust men (or women or yourself)?  You learned this somewhere. Not only is it bad for your physical health, but it is probably preventing you from living fully.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us! Support yourself!&lt;br /&gt;The ManKind Project is a world-wide community of men. We are not for profit and non-religious.&lt;br /&gt;Learn more about men's work, &lt;a href="http://www.mkp.org" target="_blank"&gt;the ManKind Project &lt;/a&gt;and the New Warrior Training Adventure.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>park between Charlie's Diner and A to Z Movers. (the 3 story warehouse) - Look for AtoZ Moving Trucks and Sign. Entrance is on the ground floor, front corner of the building. Look for the Elephant in the entryway.  (seriously!)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boysen </member_name><member_id>7527796</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert</member_name><member_id>9199047</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279844600000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Men</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>openmen</urlname><id>1200732</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5500030518</group_lon><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272327176000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Men's Group - for self-awareness &amp; empowerment Monthly Meetup</name><id>ptldnynkbcc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279751400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/events/13300265/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/d/global_4591725.jpeg</photo_url></item>