<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>149 Alewife Parkway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.393603</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Summer Shack Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>689448</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.140997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Looks like these are the two possibilities for Saturday Night's Drive In:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Other Guys Screen 1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLAYING:    Aug 13-19&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SHOWING:    8:15PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RATING:    PG13&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RUNNING TIME:    1 Hr 47 Min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg star as cops in this comedy directed by Adam McKay and co-written by McKay and Land of the Lost scribe Chris Henchy. Dwayne Johnson, Samuel L. Jackson, and Steve Coogan co-star.&lt;br /&gt;When a forensic accountant and a trigger-happy detective, both of whom idolize the city's top cops, get a chance to step up and improve upon their &amp;quot;B team&amp;quot; status, things don't quite go as planned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Despicable Me Screen 2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Playing:   Aug 13-19&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Showtime:    8:15PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rating:   PG&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Running Time:    1Hr 35Min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a happy suburban neighborhood surrounded by white picket fences with flowering rose bushes, sits a black house with a dead lawn. Unbeknownst to the neighbors, hidden beneath this home is a vast secret hideout. Surrounded by a small army of minions, we discover Gru, planning the biggest heist in the history of the world. He is going to steal the moon (Yes, the moon!). Gru delights in all things wicked. Armed with his arsenal of shrink rays, freeze rays, and battle-ready vehicles for land and air, he vanquishes all who stand in his way. Until the day he encounters the immense will of three little orphaned girls who look at him and see something that no one else has ever seen: a potential Dad. The world's greatest villain has just met his greatest challenge: three little girls named Margo, Edith and Agnes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Picture yourself sitting on your lounge chair or blanket, outside, on a glorious summer evening with stars twinkling overhead and a gentle breeze wafting through your hair. Well here we go again!! The group is having another road trip to the Mendon Drive-In and here's to having some fun!! Should prove to be a nostalgic re-visit for some and a first -time experience for others. We'll meet at the large letter T at the Alewife Station outside the Bertucci's Restaurant where Susan and John will coordinate the drivers and passengers. People who are willing to drive for this event, can park in the Summer Shack Restaurant parking lot across the street from the T Station. Those who need a ride, should arrive on the Red Line and wait at the large T.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Since the drive-in charges $20 a carload, both drivers and passengers will be depending on each other to be there and share the cost. The total number of people that can go will depend on the number of people who will be driving. Cars should probably seat 4 people and passengers will of course have to chip in for gas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll plan to get there well before sunset and do some tailgating. There's a tasty concession stand there (word is that locals go just for the food sometimes) and you can bring in food and non-alcoholic drinks. Bring Frisbees and other such stuff for a little relaxation before showtime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP, PLEASE write in the comments if you can volunteer to drive or if you are going to be a passenger. Also, if you're a driver, please indicate how many passengers, not counting yourself, can go with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alas, we won't know the movie that is showing until the Monday before. Since we are all in this one together, for better or worse, dropping out at the last minute would be grounds for being removed from the group and would not at all be appreciated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll keep updating this posting with more info and ideas as we get nearer to the big night. The movie will start around 8:30 so we'll plan to meet at Alewife at 5:30. Rain or shine event. Also, for liability purposes, we can only include people over the age of 18.&lt;br /&gt;Here's the link to the &lt;a href="http://www.mendondrivein.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Mendon Drive-In&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you decide to join us for what should be a fun evening,&lt;br /&gt;Susan and John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John and Susan will be holding MEETUP Signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276455162000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fourth  Annual Drive-In Movie Event at the Mendon!</name><id>13787880</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281821400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13787880/</event_url></item>