<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 South Main St., Suite 100, West Hartford, CT 06107</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.758820</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wu Healing Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1626501</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.743515</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;History of Tong Ren Tong in Chinese means bronze; Ren means man or human. Tong Ren can be translated as 'bronze man'. In the Sung Dynasty (1023 AD), Emperor Ren Zhong Sung summoned the highest medical faculty of the Empire to write up the "New Bronze Man's Points of Acupuncture Diagram and Note". Dr. Wang Wei-yi was responsible for designing the acupuncture bronze man (human figure made by bronze). In 1027 AD, two identical bronze men were made, which were named Tong Ren (meaning "bronze man" in Chinese). Tong Ren Healing is an important component of the Tom Tam healing system. To commemorate the Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM) pioneers for their invaluable contribution to the world on the medical front, "Tong Ren Healing", an energy healing system developed by Tam was named after the acupuncture figure created by the TCM forerunners. Tong Ren Technique Tong Ren healing is becoming increasingly popular and widespread. Worldwide, and on a daily basis, people with serious illnesses are treated by Tong Ren therapists. Countless patients benefit from and are healed by Tong Ren Therapy. Each Tong Ren therapist has his/her own way of healing people. The effectiveness of the healing is high, and the cost is low. Tong Ren Therapy is extremely easy to learn. Basically there are three major techniques &amp;ndash; with (1) the hammer, (2) laser beam, and (3) pins. Discing technique is the latest technique developed and applied in Tong Ren practices. Tong Ren Therapy is based on the power of our mind creating energy for healing. The source of this energy is from the collective unconscious, which is connected to the super conscious. When we practice Tong Ren, the focusing of our mind comes from our subconscious and unconscious - which means, &amp;ldquo;Just do it&amp;rdquo;. If we make a conscious effort to focus, the focusing comes from our conscious mind, not from the unconscious mind. No one can consciously access one&amp;rsquo;s unconscious mind. The unconscious mind is instinctive and cannot be controlled. Functions of the unconscious mind are automatic reactions. This use of the mind with the hammer technique facilitates the breaking down of blockages, which can then let energy pass within the body freely. With Tong Ren healing, we do not need to think or focus on the breaking down of the blockages, because the thought has already been stored as memory in our subconscious mind. Using the hammer technique, we hit points on the doll for about 10 to 15 minutes. As a rule this is enough. Patients can hit the doll for self-healing, but the best way is to ask someone else to do it because in this way the patient can be totally relaxed in order to receive the healing energy. A child&amp;rsquo;s mind is purer than an adult&amp;rsquo;s and without resistance. That is why children are more effective when using the hammer technique than most adults. With late stage cancer, daily use of Tong Ren healing is required. With cancer at an early stage, we can use Tong Ren two or three times a week. If the patient wants to do it or have it done on him/her more often, it is all right to do so because there are no side effects with Tong Ren healing. The more you do it, the more you benefit from it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ming Wu</member_name><member_id>10379237</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305590866000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304016434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tong Ren Healing</name><id>ncvxqyphbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305586800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/18238441/</event_url></item>