<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the Museum of Science Website&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/events_activities/lectures&amp;amp;d=4232" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/ev...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lecturer&lt;/u&gt;: Neil Gershenfeld, director, MIT's Center for Bits and Atoms. This presentation is part of the ongoing series DIY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, March 10, 2010 | 7:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Museum of Science, Cahners Theater, 2nd floor, Blue Wing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Give ordinary people the right tools, and they will design and build the most extraordinary things. That's the idea behind Fab Labs, an idea hatched by star physicist and DIY enthusiast Neil Gershenfeld, who teaches a wildly popular course at MIT called How To Make (almost) Anything. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fab Labs provide access to prototype tools for personal fabrication, like a PC that can output functional objects instead of images on a screen. The labs have spread from their start in inner-city Boston to the bottom of Africa and the top of Norway, with projects tackling applications in areas including healthcare, agriculture, housing, and communications. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Join Dr. Gershenfeld for a peek at the science behind Fab Labs, an introduction to machines that make machines, and a tour around the world to see how these tools are transforming how people live, work, and play. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Seating is limited. Passes are available in the Museum lobby beginning at 5:45 p.m. on the day of the program. First come, first served. Museum members may reserve a limited number of seating passes in advance&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nerd Fun has been to so many lectures at the Museum of Science, The Museum of Science just puts aside twenty tickets for the Nerd Fun group. T.J. should be showing up at 5:45 pm to pick up tickets and distribute them to people who need them. Drop by at anytime! T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag, and will be waiting in the front lobby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it isn't too busy, they allow him to go up to the lecture hall and reserve seats with little MEETUP signs near the center front. We can head upstairs at 6:40 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Care to hang out at ArtBar after&lt;/b&gt;? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.artbarcambridge.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artbarcamb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;ArtBar is a warm, intimate retreat for food and art lovers located at the Royal Sonesta Hotel in Cambridge, MA. The ArtBar boasts stellar selections from the hotel’s world-class art collection while the restaurant features innovative cuisine, a well curated wine list and art themed specialty cocktails. Patio seating along the Charles River offer unparalleled riverside dining with views of the Boston Skyline make the ArtBar a neighborhood destination for Cambridge&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lecture should be over around 8:00 pm, 8:15 pm. Coupons for a free appetizer or dessert for the Royal Sonesta's ArtBar. Anybody want to hang out there after? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dinner Menu&lt;/u&gt;: The four dollar items from the Happy Hour menu are free with the coupon: &lt;a href="http://www.artbarcambridge.com/menus/dessert/50-bar2.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artbarcamb...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dessert Menu&lt;/u&gt;: The three or four dollar &amp;quot;small bites&amp;quot; listed are free with the coupon: &lt;a href="http://www.artbarcambridge.com/menus/dessert.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artbarcamb...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Neil Gershenfeld, from his MIT faculty Page&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ng.cba.mit.edu/neil/bio.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://ng.cba.mit.edu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Prof. Neil Gershenfeld is the Director of MIT's Center for Bits and Atoms. His unique laboratory is breaking down boundaries between the digital and physical worlds, from creating molecular quantum computers to virtuosic musical instruments. Technology from his lab has been seen and used in settings including New York's Museum of Modern Art and rural Indian villages, the White House and the World Economic Forum, inner-city community centers and automobile safety systems, Las Vegas shows and Sami herds. He is the author of numerous technical publications, patents, and books including Fab, When Things Start To Think, The Nature of Mathematical Modeling, and The Physics of Information Technology, and has been featured in media such as The New York Times, The Economist, and the McNeil/Lehrer News Hour. He is a Fellow of the American Physical Society, has been named one of Scientific American's 50 leaders in science and technology, has been selected as a CNN/Time/Fortune Principal Voice, and by Prospect/FP as one of the top 100 public intellectuals. Dr. Gershenfeld has a BA in Physics with High Honors and an honorary Doctor of Science from Swarthmore College, a Ph.D. from Cornell University, was a Junior Fellow of the Harvard University Society of Fellows, and a member of the research staff at Bell Labs&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About MIT's Center for Bits and Atoms (CBA):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://cba.mit.edu/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://cba.mit.edu/ab...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;CBA was founded by Profs. Isaac Chuang, Neil Gershenfeld, Joseph Jacobson, and Scott Manalis, with Marvin Minsky. It was launched by a National Science Foundation award in 2001  that is supporting the creation of a unique shared experimental resource that enables the creation of form and function across nine orders of magnitude in length scales, as well as an associated intellectual community drawn from across MIT's campus spanning the historical divisions that have emerged between the study of computer science and physical science, and between the development of software and hardware. CBA's government funding is complemented by corporate sponsorship for technology development and transfer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] One of CBA's grand challenge goals is quite literally to create &amp;quot;it from bit,&amp;quot; seeking to realize von Neumann's vision of a universal assembler. Analogous to the earlier results in communications and computation, if logic can be introduced into the process of physical assembly then perfect macroscopic structures could be built out of imperfect microscopic parts. Biological proteins are in fact produced in exactly this way, by programs run by cellular molecular machinery&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Fab Labs FAQ&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://fab.cba.mit.edu/about/faq/" target="_blank"&gt;http://fab.cba.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fab labs provide widespread access to modern means for invention. They began as an outreach project from MIT's Center for Bits and Atoms (CBA). CBA assembled millions of dollars in machines for research in digital fabrication, ultimately aiming at developing programmable molecular assemblers that will be able to make almost anything. Fab labs fall between these extremes, comprising roughly fifty thousand dollars in equipment and materials that can be used today to do what will be possible with tomorrow's personal fabricators. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fab labs have spread from inner-city Boston to rural India, from South Africa to the North of Norway. Activities in fab labs range from technological empowerment to peer-to-peer project-based technical training to local problem-solving to small-scale high-tech business incubation to grass-roots research. Projects being developed and produced in fab labs include solar and wind-powered turbines, thin-client computers and wireless data networks, analytical instrumentation for agriculture and healthcare, custom housing, and rapid-prototyping of rapid-prototyping machines&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/visitor_info/maps_and_directions" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/vi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Take the M.B.T.A.'s Green Line subway to Science Park station. This will be the Green Line's Lechmere-bound 'E' train. The Museum is diagonally across the street (O'Brien Highway), just over the Charles River Dam draw bridge&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268438990000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266520235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Neil Gershenfeld, FabLabs, "How to Make (Almost) Anything" @ Museum of Science</name><id>12639675</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268265600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12639675/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/1/9/global_13181657.jpeg</photo_url></item>