<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>154 Shrewsbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.250000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-754-3761</phone><name>Cafe Dolce</name><city>Worcester</city><id>117996</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.769997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello All! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going to do a real casual get together at Cafe Dolce on Sunday Oct 15th to hang out - check out our work hanging on the walls...anyone and everyone is welcome...We'll be there at 5pm. Here is the info about the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna and Scott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COFFEE HOUSE FOCUSES ON EXHIBITING LOCAL PHOTOGRAPHER?S WORK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It seemed like things just came together at the right time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Erb was initially just looking for a place where the Worcester Photography MeetUp Group could assemble and share their ideas about photography on a consistent basis. Michael Carrigan, the owner of Caffé Dolce, agreed to this arrangement, not entirely sure where things would lead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once Carrigan saw some of the work of the people in the group, he approached Erb with a question: would the members of the group be interested in displaying their work on the walls of his establishment?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ?Once I started talking with them, they were nice!? said Carrigan. ?It seemed sort of random, but I?ve been wanting to do something like this for a long time.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?Something like this? meaning having local artists showcasing their work inside the café itself. After a detailed discussion, Erb realized immediately what was at hand: ?Of course we would love that opportunity!?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Caffé Dolce will be featuring different photographers? work on a revolving monthly basis: ?People in the general public will be able to buy the photos as well!? said Carrigan, adding that some pieces that he particularly likes will have a more ?permanent? home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In October, the featured artists at Caffé Dolce will be the founders of the Worcester Photography MeetUp Group, Scott Erb and his wife Donna Dufault. In a series entitled ?Worcester and Beyond,? the exhibit will feature images from around Worcester, Mount Manadnock, Hope Cemetery, and surrounding areas. Scott Erb, Mark Doyle and Donna Dufault?s now infamous ?Chairs of Worcester? will hang amongst their other images.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you?d like to see the work and partake of some of the best coffee and desserts Worcester can offer, swing by Caffé Dolce (open M?Th 4pm-midnight, F &amp;amp; Sat, 4pm-1am, and Sundays 3pm-11pm) and check it out! In addition, if you?d like to join the Worcester Photography MeetUp Group, they meet on the second Thursday of every month, from 7:30pm-10pm. Check the web site for details: &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/22/"&gt;http://photo.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact person: Scott Erb can be reached at 774-239-0214 or 508-421-3912 or scott@erbphoto.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1161118853000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1159834591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Oct 15th - Drink, eat, be merry... or susan...or whoever.</name><id>5168806</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1160946000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/5168806/</event_url></item>