<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>163404</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Valley 9/11 Truth meeting begins at 6pm, which will cover an overview for the 9/11 truth movement in 2008. The film, &amp;quot;Loose Change Final Cut&amp;quot; is the third installment of the documentary that asks the tough questions about the 9/11 attacks.This film program begins at 7:00 pm. Expected for this evening will be one or more of its following filmmakers: Dylan Avery * Korey Rowe * Jason Burmas. Film running time is 2-hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/270/files/"&gt;files&lt;/a&gt; to download handouts for this event and meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loose Change, a documentary ..which just might be the first Internet blockbuster.&lt;br /&gt;-Vanity Fair&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loose Change is a... blizzard of statistics, photographs, documents, eyewitness accounts&lt;br /&gt;and expert testimony set to a trippy hip-hop backbeat.&lt;br /&gt;- TIME MAGAZINE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;millions of people have heard its message.&lt;br /&gt;Like it or loathe it, you can't ignore Loose Change.&lt;br /&gt;-The Guardian-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://loosechange911.com/"&gt;Visit the Loose Change website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.loosechangethefinalcut.com/"&gt;Loose Change The Final Cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Infowars.net | November 9 , 2007&lt;br /&gt;Loose Change: Final Cut Is Here&lt;br /&gt;BY Steve Watson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loose Change: Final Cut has arrived. Two days ahead of the original schedule, the long awaited final version of the film that took the 9/11 truth movement mainstream is now available to buy on DVD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original Loose Change and Loose Change 2nd Edition have been viewed at least 50 million times over the Internet, making it one of the most watched movies in history, but the Final Cut goes above and beyond, making it not simply the third in a trilogy but a completely new film with oodles of unseen footage, commentary, interviews and eyewitness testimony.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In an effort to be the catalyst for a new independent investigation of 9/11, the film features new and exclusive interviews with firefighters, EMT's, first responders and other officials who were all eyewitnesses to multiple secondary explosions in the twin towers and around the ground zero area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View the official trailer below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://feareffect.wordpress.com/2007/11/11/loose-change-final-cut-is-here/"&gt;&lt;a href="http://feareffect.wordpress.com/2007/11/11/loose-change-final-cut-is-here/" target="_blank"&gt;http://feareffect.wor...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part of the revenue from the sales will be donated to 9/11 victim's charities such as The &lt;a href="http://www.fealgoodfoundation.com/"&gt;Feal Good Foundation&lt;/a&gt; and WTC Families for Proper Burial.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film will be subject to selected cinematic release in 2008, but many grassroots and selected theatres have already agreed to pick up the movie from December onwards across the U.S and Europe and the Loose Change team are encouraging activists to ask that their local theatre to screen the documentary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Throughout the year Dylan Avery Jason Bermas and Corey Rowe, have been negotiating with various different producers in Hollywood in hope of securing a mainstream release. However, the team recently decided to forgo such a deal in order to retain full editorial control of the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This just wasn?t an option for us, as the integrity of our message is ultimately all that we have, and we feared that 'the machine' would corrupt or squash our film and its movement.? an official statement read.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trio are also extremely proud of the manner in which their initial release of the internet phenomenon documentary has spawned a move that has seen the release of scores of successful independent grassroots films. The team wish to continue to challenge the traditional marketing channels and reinvent the way that films are distributed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alex Jones worked with the trio in an executive producer role on the film and has partly financed it's production and distribution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other consultants on The Final Cut include Professor David Ray Griffin, author of three widely read studies of the 2001 attacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the coming weeks and months we expect to witness the launch of a fresh wave of attacks against the 9/11 truth movement by neocon hacks such as Bill O'Reilly, who has regularly equated the movement with terrorists , a tactic that has since been echoed by other mainstream gatekeepers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;O'Reilly admits right off the bat that he has not even seen Loose Change, following in the trend of his fellow debunkers who have already arrived at a judgment without even checking the evidence. O'Reilly has made the argument that  Loose Change should be banned just as some books should be banned.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201224334000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196373671000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LOOSE CHANGE FINAL CUT - film and discussion</name><id>6827000</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201042800000</time><rsvp_limit>80</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/6827000/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/global_576113.jpeg</photo_url></item>