<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Lewis Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.363681</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.227.4198</phone><name>Boston Sailing Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>706695</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051065</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;I'm racing in the Beringer Bowl, and will more than likely be still on the way back from the Cape this day. It is an open event though, so feel free to show up, get on the water, and meet with some sailors. In your RSVP put what you'll be wearing so other meetup.com members can find you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open House July 19th&lt;br /&gt;With the summer in full swing in New England, the idea of sailing is high on many people?s lists of things to do outdoors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's why the Boston Sailing Center will give novice sailors a feel for what it?s like to take the helm, and introduce them to the school?s beginner course for adults during a special open house featuring free sailing on Boston Harbor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will be held on Saturday, July 19 from 1pm to 5pm at the Center?s sailing docks on Lewis Wharf in downtown Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Olson 25 sailing on Boston Harbor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First-time sailors and those with limited sailing experience are invited to give it a try.  Complimentary ?round-the-harbor sailboat trips will be supervised by experienced skippers aboard boats ranging in length from 23 to 40 feet.  Free refreshments will also be served. &lt;br /&gt;The Center's teaching staff will be on hand to answer questions about sailing basics, and about the five-week, weekend and ?vacation week? formats of the school?s 26-hour Learn to Sail course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who sign up during the event will receive a $100 discount off the regular course fee of $795.  Discounts on advanced courses and one-year sailing memberships will also be available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now in its 32nd season, the Boston Sailing Center is headquartered in a converted Louisiana riverboat that is permanently docked at Lewis Wharf.  The Center?s classrooms and boat moorings are a five-minute walk north of Faneuil Hall Marketplace along Atlantic Avenue.  Public parking is available nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;QUICK FACTS:&lt;br /&gt;Who:  Boston Sailing Center&lt;br /&gt;What:  Open House reception featuring free sailing on Boston Harbor&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Sailboat docks located at Lewis Wharf, off Atlantic Ave., Boston         &lt;br /&gt;When:  Saturday, July 19, 1-5pm&lt;br /&gt;Dress: Seasonal ? bring a light jacket or windbreaker for added comfort.&lt;br /&gt;Cost:  FREE&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments:  Provided on site at no cost.&lt;br /&gt;Reservations:  First come, first served&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicholas</member_name><member_id>1525004</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216695786000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215620541000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Sailing Center Open House</name><id>8307173</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216486800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/8307173/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/9/global_103977.jpeg</photo_url></item>