<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Who should come&lt;br /&gt;    Those that want to eat DEVILISH and have DEVILISH Laughs..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to find the organizer(s)&lt;br /&gt;    &amp;quot;I will try to park in a visible area, however, as our groups will pick a spot big enough for all of us, LOOK FOR THE ORANGE TRAFFIC CONES at our party spot&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;    --AL-r &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;This event is Steve T's Walkers Event that seems like a good event and location for a few of our groups to get together..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am listing it on all my groups, and as a RSVP because i will be there....but its good to go to Steve's Group for any updates..etc..&lt;br /&gt;We both will do what we can to coordinate the event between our groups..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some food..LOL&lt;br /&gt;Hide the BOOZE...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok info from Steve's listing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When&lt;br /&gt;Monday, May 26, 2008 at 10:30 AM 20080526T143000Z&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where&lt;br /&gt;Devil's Hopyard State Park&lt;br /&gt;366 Hopyard Rd.&lt;br /&gt;East Haddam , CT 06423&lt;br /&gt;860-526-2336&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to find the organizer(s)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I'll be wearing my bright orange Cabela's Hat.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;--Steve Theriault&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have the customary ORange TRAFFIC CONES NEAR OUR SITE...AND CAR IF I CAN PARK CLOSE TO OUR SPOT.. AL-R&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEMORIAL DAY PICNIC AT DEVIL'S HOPYARD STATE PARK IN EAST HADDAM (&amp;amp; VOLLEYBALL)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will celebrate the holiday on Monday, May 26th at 10:30 a.m. to approx. 7 p.m. at Devil's Hopyard State Park in East Haddam, CT. The event is BYOB (as long as everyone is over 21 years old), and it is unclear whether the state park officially allows alcohol but if you bring it, be discreet and be aware that alcohol is definitely not allowed on the beach/boardwalk area. I will provide some hot dogs and hamburgers and I would ask that as you RSVP, you let me know if you can bring some burgers and dogs or a salad or side dish to go with them. We will attempt to have a volleyball net put up to play. The weather looks good and we should have a great time!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;STEADY RAIN CANCELS. CALL OR CHECK MEETUP WEBSITE IF IN DOUBT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: Steve Theriault, Cell: 860-919-6735. stevetheriault@snet.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUT GO TO STEVE'S SITE FIRST....i dont think he wants too many calls&lt;br /&gt;Steve's site: &lt;a href="http://walkers.meetup.com/266/"&gt;http://walkers.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Devil's Hopyard's principle feature, Chapman Falls, drops more than sixty feet over a series of steps in a Scotland Schist stone formation. The water from the splash pool at the base of the falls, continuing as the Eight Mile River, flows through the park's hemlock-canopied picnic area, providing a tranquil setting for a family outing. Many myths surround the name of the park, including one about a man named Dibble, who grew hops for beer-brewing. Through usage, Dibble's Hopyard supposedly became Devil's Hopyard. Another tale says that the Devil passed by the falls and accidentally wet his tail. Furious, he burned holes in the stones with his hooves as he bounded away. Now, we know that the potholes near the falls, which are some of the finest examples of pothole stone formations in this section of the country, were formed by stones moved downstream by the current, trapped in an eddy where the stone was spun around, wearing a depression in the rock. When the rock wore itself down, another would catch in the same hole and enlarge it. Perfectly cylindrical, the potholes range from inches to several feet in diameter and depth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;Devil's Hopyard&lt;br /&gt;366 HOPYARD ROAD&lt;br /&gt;East Haddam CT 06423&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; WE WILL BE PARKING AND PICNICKING IN THE vicinity OF THE LOWER LOT, BELOW THE FALLS. (WHEN ENTERING, DON'T TAKE LEFT BUT KEEP RIGHT AND GO DOWN THE HILL.) &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From CT Route 9: take Exit 7, then a left at the end of the exit ramp onto CT Route 154 north. Take a right at the first traffic light and follow the signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 395: take Exit 80 west. Take a right onto CT Route 82 west. Take a right onto Hopyard Road and follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91-S: take Exit 22 for Route 9-S toward Middletown (its the left one on 91 south), Follow 9-2 to Exit 10.&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9A-S to Tylerville. Take Route 82-E over CT River and continue for about 3 miles.&lt;br /&gt;At the stop sign take a right, and then take immediate left. Follow that road for approximately 8 miles, then follow the signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When on Hopyard Road at apx # 366-373 you will find the intersection of Foxtown Road to the left,&lt;br /&gt;stay on Hopyard Road for a short distance more, go down the hill, slow down....the park entrance is on the left...&lt;br /&gt;You have to look for us in this area..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will give some other directions as i take another look at the map..&lt;br /&gt;but these look ok so far..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I personally will take Rt 2 from Glastonbury and then at exit 19 will take rte 11 down to exit 5..&lt;br /&gt;take a right on to Witch Meadow Rd, changes to Alexander then to Old Salem, (part of this is a dirt road)&lt;br /&gt;then at the end of this road take a left on to Haywardville Rd, then a left on Hpoyard Rd..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUT INSTEAD OF THIS DIRECTION STUFF................GET A GPS...&lt;br /&gt;Fees&lt;br /&gt;There are no parking fees, but there is a nightly camping fee at Devil's Hopyard State Park.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211985448000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211220173000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>There is more to life than just Kayaking, WEEKEND PARTY at THE HOPYARD 4+ Groups</name><id>7968733</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211812200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/7968733/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/global_474104.jpeg</photo_url></item>