<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>40 Talbot Ave.</address_2><address_1>Aidekman Arts Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02153</zip><lat>42.403881</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-627-3493 (box office)</phone><name>Balch Arena</name><city>Medford</city><id>1047983</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120342</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jumbos,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have gobbled up 20 tickets for the play and I am inviting you, and 18 of your&amp;nbsp;colleagues and friends to enjoy a night of comedy as we watch our students perform the Oscar Wilde farce The Importance of Being Earnest.&amp;nbsp; TuftsLife website describes the play this way:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Originally dubbed 'a trivial comedy for serious people,' The Importance of Being Earnest is a masterpiece of confusion. Names are confused. Places are confused. Identities are confused. Lineages are confused. Hearts are confused. Indeed, confusion nearly seizes the day! But confusion, no matter how trivial, is a serious, if funny problem. The wisdom in this classic romp is, perhaps, that when one is in love, being earnest is of the utmost importance&lt;/em&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's get together to unwind, share a few laughs, and support our talented students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Note: a separate dinner Meet-up is scheduled prior to this play at Taipei Tokyo in Davis Square&amp;nbsp;where many of us will gather to&amp;nbsp;enjoy a combination of&amp;nbsp;fine Chinese &amp;amp; Japanese cuisine as well as&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;wide&amp;nbsp;variety of sushi.&amp;nbsp; Please check out that Meet-up too and RSVP separately for each event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll gather in the hallway heading towards the Art Gallery prior to seating.  I will try to remember to wear a Meet-up name tag, but failing that you can just look for the bald dude.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich K</member_name><member_id>9340572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298654322000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Tufts University's Department of Drama &amp; Dance presents The Importance of Being Earnest by Oscar Wilde, directed by Sheriden Thomas at the Balch Arena Theater.</why><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296972808000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Farcical Fun: The Importance of Being Earnest</name><id>16460591</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298595600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/16460591/</event_url></item>