<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Vassar Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139 </zip><lat>42.359452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zesiger Sports &amp; Fitness Center at MIT</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>847916</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096264</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Kick-off the new season at the east coast's LARGEST multisport conference and expo!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Multisport World Boston returns to the Zesiger Sports &amp;amp; Fitness Center at MIT on Saturday, March 19, 2011. Going on it's 9th year, Multisport World Boston is the definitive to kick-off to a new multisport season in the northeast featuring informative SEMINARS, hands-on CLINICS, classroom-style WORKSHOPS, the Champion System Team Challenge and other COMPETITIVE EVENTS, activities for the kids and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Multisport World Boston is also home to a large and diverse vendor expo featuring 80+ exhibiting sponsors including retailers and manufacturers of swim, bike and run gear and apparel, training aids, nutritional products... race directors for some of the most popular events in the region... certified coaches... health &amp;amp; wellness providers... multisport clubs and more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Headlining a terrific list of speakers is 6x Ironman World Champion, DAVE SCOTT!  Dave is one of the most recognized names in the sport of triathlon.  A 6x Ironman World Champion and the only inductee to both the Ironman and USAT Triathlon Hall of Fame, Dave brings his years of wisdom, wit and passion for helping others to Multisport World where he will deliver the keynote seminar, lead a workshop and, as an extra bonus, he will give a 3.5 hour active workshop on Sunday, March 20th (the day after Multisport World Boston).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission to the seminars and vendor expo is FREE and the first 1,000 registered attendees will receive a valuable swag bag with a new water bottle, product samples, money-saving coupons and more. Plus, all registered attendees are eligible to win valuable giveaways and receive discounts on selected clinics. &lt;a href="http://triathlontraining.net/expo/reg/boston/" target="_blank"&gt;CLICK HERE &lt;/a&gt;for more details and to register now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Still not sure whether or not you want to attend this year's event? Here are 11 reasons why you don't want to miss the 2011 Multisport World Conference and Expo in Cambridge, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Start the day running with the Newton Running Campus Dash. A 3-mile run around the MIT campus. Great swag and prizes from Newton Running. &lt;a href="http://www.multisportworld.com/Boston/Competitive_Events.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Details here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Get faster on the swim. Register for one of the &lt;a href="http://www.multisportworld.com/Boston/Clinics_and_Workshops.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Total Immersion swim clinics&lt;/a&gt; to improve your technique and go faster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Gear up for the season. Exhibiting sponsors on the expo will include retailers and manufacturers of bikes, apparel, running shoes, wetsuits, nurtritional products and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Meet professional triathlete Dave Scott. A 6x Ironman World Champion, Dave will deliver a keynote seminar and much more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Find a new race for the season. Multiple race directors will be exhibiting on the expo floor to give you details on their races and answer your questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Improve your running technique. Sign up for one of the &lt;a href="http://www.multisportworld.com/Boston/Clinics_and_Workshops.htm" target="_blank"&gt;ChiRunning clinics&lt;/a&gt; and discover how ChiRunning takes the pounding, pain and potential damage out of the sport of running.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. See inside the &amp;quot;coaching files&amp;quot;. Attend the &lt;a href="http://www.multisportworld.com/Boston/Seminars.htm" target="_blank"&gt;seminar &lt;/a&gt;from the coaches at Tri-Hard Endurance Sports Coaching on the key triathlon questions they answer every day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8. Compete in the Fast Splits Indoor Bike Time Trial. Race a 10k course... Spinervals DVD for the first 50 registrants, great prizes and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9. Get your first triathlon experience off on the right foot. Attend the &lt;a href="http://www.multisportworld.com/Boston/Clinics_and_Workshops.htm" target="_blank"&gt;workshop&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;quot;The First Time Triathlete&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10. Get stronger and get faster. Attend the &lt;a href="http://www.multisportworld.com/Boston/Clinics_and_Workshops.htm" target="_blank"&gt;workshop,&lt;/a&gt; Strength Training for the Multisport Athlete&amp;quot; presented by Boston Performance Coaching.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11. Win valuable giveaways. All registered attendees can win some great giveaways and the first 1,000 registered attendees get a free swag bag! &lt;a href="http://triathlontraining.net/expo/reg/boston/" target="_blank"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to register.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Rice</member_name><member_id>2673515</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301173217000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Triathletes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Tri</urlname><id>584357</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8399963379</group_lon><name>Mass Tri</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296100266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Multisport World Conference and Expo</name><id>16203519</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300543200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Tri/events/16203519/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/global_21084023.jpeg</photo_url></item>