<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather for Saturday    UPDATE  Its not the best but looks OK, Cloudy and a possible sprink in the afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If conditions change on the water we can easily modify our trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am proposing just head to Columbia and do the Barbie-q under the Pavillion, its on the way home for the majority of us anyway, but lets see ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update if necessary by apx 9 to 10 am the day of the event. so far this morning ..its still ON..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; For more specific weather at our paddling area:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KIJD&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usairnet.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;The grill and fire pit is already loaded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I see a Bass fishing tournament of 12 boats scheduled for Saturday ?, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/fishing/general_information/fishingtourbydate.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The river near the airport is the one that comes from Diana's Pool that we found to be a great place in the fall season picknicks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the paddling event is also the Pot Luck Picknick nearby so remember to be prepared to join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;___&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow Boat Launch:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For GPS use 300 Bassetts Bridge Road Mansfield Center CT, (its close enough)..&lt;br /&gt;mapquest or other...just compare the directions below to what you get..they better be similar..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup map link above looks ok.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Option 1--From Hartford take I-84 heading EAST, take Exit 68 = south on rte 195 through Storrs to Mansfield ctr (about 11 miles from 84)&lt;br /&gt;Go 0.5 mile past rte 89 junction and turn left onto Bassset Bridge Rd at the stoplight, should see Mansfield Hollow Park sign. &lt;br /&gt;Go apx 1 mile Will see a picknick area on left but go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford option 2--- take I-384 East toward Bolton, bear right onto rte 6 and follow rte 6  toward Willimantic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; rte 6 and rte 66 will intersect at a light. Take a left on to 6.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow this highway to the second exit, go straight (=rte 633 or S. Frontage Rd.) it is actually a parallel to rte 6 connector to rte 195, (and heads towards the Mall &amp;amp; food store..etc)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Signs for UCONN should be there somewhere too,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go North on rte 195 toward UCONN for about 2 miles then turn right at the onto Basset Bridge Rd, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You Will see a picknick area on left but go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The picknick area you passed will be where we go after the paddling is done if we choose this location ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember and PRINT the directions.LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the boat launch, i will park as close to the bridge tunnels as i can, so look for me in that area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok bring some food, chaire, bugg juice and other stuff for several hours on the water and the picknick after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday May 29, start paddling by 12 noon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(if you arrive late, we will be heading North to the UP stream towards the Fenton River.&lt;br /&gt;then we return to go through the tunnels to the dam side)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be wearing the orange hat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why earlier ? to get ya all used to it, remember last years traffic to the beach ? &lt;br /&gt;The parking , and of course a longer time to enjoy the locations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring sun protection , water, and some paddling gloves, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh yes, almost forgot, Bring a snack for the Half Point of our trip while stopping at a bridge where that Dilliverance Movie Banjo Player is waiting (throw him some Pork Skins).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As with all my trips, i don't give specifics,  its for your discovery as i discovered them for my first time,&lt;br /&gt;and i dont offer the paddling time or milage.. when we are done ..we are done--- when we are done paddling then its the barbie-q.. anticipate the entire day and a good part of the evening by a nice fire. Real wood or my special fire pit.&lt;br /&gt;-----------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;xxxxxxx&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddle &amp;amp; Leash,   Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dougnation of 20 bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality dillivered and picked up at the site etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any wide yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will only bring the yaks that are confirmed by a yes and by persons i have some familiarity with..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybee's obviously can't reserve any yaks and if ya reserve one and don't show up ya won't ever get a second chance to again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry i don't like to leave un-attended yaks on the trailer. They get stolen too easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF USING MY YAKS YOU CANT LOOK LIKE A BONEHEADED BEGINNER AND STEP INTO THEM VIA THE FLOOR OR DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. Only Novices in cheap boats do that...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way and you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro and impress the others who don't know how. Or you may laugh at the ones that fall in who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: always get out parallel to shore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes and paddling  style, and tight fit adjusted...if you have your own please bring it..&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths and types of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some cheap ones for that.)-&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourtie Yak Pad optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Riot Tourlite 15, Blue, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For small paddler (apx 150 lbs) with Intermediate Experience.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://wickedwaters.com/riot-tour-lite-15.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://wickedwaters.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;transitional kayak, 15'=   &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;THIS KAYAK IS FOR SALE $550.00&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.....I will have this at the event to try if reserved...  =  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; SOLD &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cobra Expidition, Yellow,  Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For an average sized paddler apx (150 to 220 lbs) with Intermediate experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cobrakayaks.com/expedition.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cobrakayak...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fast Sea kayak,  Sit On Top type, moderate to low initial stability, 18', = &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;THIS KAYAK IS FOR SALE $500.00&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.....I will have this at the event to try if reserved...  =  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RESERVED FOR BETH&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer, Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with Novice and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RESERVED FOR LAURA Z..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro, Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (150-200 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;AVAILABLE   BUT NOT ENOUGH SPACE TO TRANSPORT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RESERVED FOR MAUREEN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Modified), Yellow, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RESERVED FOR NINA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RESERVED FOR MARYBETH ??&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guillemot Night Heron&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenland Paddle available also if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with beginner/intermediate and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (45 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RESERVED FOR AL-R&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;THE AFTER PARTY CAN BE RIGHT AT MANSFIELD HOLLOW PICNIC AREA (NEARBY) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                       OR&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; At  COLUMBIA RECREATIONAL FIELD UNDER THE PAVILION Which IS A BIT MORE SECLUDED AND PRIVATE FOR US..WE MAKE OUR DECISION AFTER THE PADDLING IS DONE AS TO WHICH WE MAY LIKE MORE..&lt;br /&gt;I do not know if its reserved yet.&lt;br /&gt;If we choose the Pavillion,  its on the way home for most of us, continue on &lt;br /&gt;rte 66 EAST,&lt;br /&gt;cross over rte 6, and go apx 3 miles to a flashing yellow light, take THAT right onto HENNIQUIN RD, go apx 1 mile to the park entrance on the left.&lt;br /&gt;Apx GPS is 34 Henniquin Rd, Columbia ct&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there.&lt;br /&gt;AL-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Kayak Trailer - Orange Stryped Cones at boat "CARRY IN" area Orange Hat also.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275450457000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274882267000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*KAYAK EVENT*  Mansfield Hollow Reservoir Areas &amp; Group Pot Luck Barbie-Q Nearby</name><id>13600721</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275147000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/13600721/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/e/9/global_13233817.jpeg</photo_url></item>