<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Boylston Green Line stop)</address_2><address_1>204 Tremont St.,</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351942</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-423-0785</phone><name>Limelight Stage + Studios</name><city>Boston</city><id>837875</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064671</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You’ve always wanted to try karaoke, but not even 3 shots of tequila help. Or maybe that wedding, party, business event, or trip to Asia (or Brazil) is coming up where you want and/or need to get up there and sing one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t have a “Total Eclipse of the Heart”! Are you ready to “Break on Through to the Other Side”? Do you want to achieve “Paradise by the Dashboard Light”? Then “Welcome to the Jungle”!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But you say, “My voice stinks! I can’t sing! I can’t get up in front of a group and do that!” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Nigeria they say, “If you can talk, you can sing.” Karaoke is not about being Sinatra, Streisand, Springsteen, or Stefani. Karaoke is about letting go and enjoying expressing yourself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Karaoke-Do™ (kah-rah-OH-keh-DOH, “‘empty orchestra’-Way”) is a path to enlightenment and growth, without the complicated body positions. Join Founding Grand Master Shihan Scott A. at Limelight, the venerable karaoke dojo, for the practice and insight that will get you to take the mike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have fun as you: &lt;br /&gt;• Learn to use your breath the right way. &lt;br /&gt;• Find, exercise, and use your voice. Yes, even yours. &lt;br /&gt;• Pick a song to sing. &lt;br /&gt;• Become one with the music and the applause! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We meet in a private studio at Limelight, so your first live performances are in front of a small, like-minded group. (Space limited.) No pre-requisites, except a desire to sing. Every session is the “first session”. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Founding Grand Master Shihan Scott A.: &lt;br /&gt;• Master of Education from Harvard (and he has the ring to prove it.) &lt;br /&gt;• Sang 8 years with a prominent Boston chorus. &lt;br /&gt;• Had 2 voice lessons, very long ago. &lt;br /&gt;• Spiritual leader in houses of worship. &lt;br /&gt;• Ordained Minister, Church of Spiritual Humanism. &lt;br /&gt;• Student of karate-do, tai chi chu’an, and Kabbalah. &lt;br /&gt;• Karaoke devotee since 1993. &lt;br /&gt;• Has sung karaoke from California to Kuala Lumpur (traveling east). &lt;br /&gt;• Taught computer consciousness as a software trainer. &lt;br /&gt;• Non-judgmental, supportive, encouraging. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To pre-register, or if you have questions, contact Founding Grand Master Shihan Scott A. here or at Step1Ventures@GMail.com. For directions or other information about Limelight, visit www.limelightboston.com. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sessions can also be arranged for private groups and corporate events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To sum it up: &lt;br /&gt;Karaoke-Do: Personal Growth through Public Exposure™ &lt;br /&gt;Thursdays, 8:00-9:30pm &lt;br /&gt;Limelight, 204 Tremont St. (Near the corner of Tremont and Boylston), Boston &lt;br /&gt;$10.00 ($1.00 off if you pre-register by noon Thursday). No Limelight cover charge for students of the Way! Dojo space is limited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing and hearing you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Karaoke-Do: Personal Growth through Public Exposure™ is a trademark of Step 1 Ventures.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask at the entrance which room Karaoke-Do is meeting in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shihan Scott A.</member_name><member_id>8548447</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232068562000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Karaoke-Do-ka</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Karaoke-Do-Personal-Growth-through-Public-Exposure</urlname><id>1342977</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Karaoke-Do: Personal Growth through Public Exposure™</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230191782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Karaoke-Do: Personal Growth through Public Exposure™ January Meetup</name><id>9386521</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231462800000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Karaoke-Do-Personal-Growth-through-Public-Exposure/events/9386521/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/f/e/global_6739022.jpeg</photo_url></item>