<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374401</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-903-7371</phone><name>Private Location #2</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>832579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121895</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you wish that you could just get out on the dance floor and have fun like everyone else, but you're a little too self-conscious to take the risk?  Would you like to be able to blend in and have fun at parties, weddings, and even dance clubs?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you answered &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to either of these questions, then you're going to love this.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;You see, I know what it's like to fear the dance floor.  All my life I never knew how to freestyle dance with another person, or even by myself.  Whenever I would ask people for advice, they would say, &lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;How do you freestyle dance?  You just get out there and do it!&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Okay, thanks for that, but &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; helpful.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The truth is, there isn't much help out there for total beginners when it comes to freestyle dancing.  Sure, there are dozens of places to learn swing or salsa, but when it comes to &amp;quot;fast dancing&amp;quot; with someone at a party, people just expect you to know how to do it.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Well help is on the way, because that's what this unique event is all about.  For years now, my friend Lisa Medley has been teaching total beginners how to blend in (and even look good) on any dance floor, and she's coming to Boston to teach a special class just for our group.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&lt;br /&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to &amp;quot;find the beat&amp;quot; in any music so you know exactly how to dance to it.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You'll learn exactly what to do with your feet and hands so you look totally natural on the dance floor.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You'll learn the basic framework of freestyle dance and how to use it to discover your own unique style of movement (it's much easier than you think when you use Lisa's system).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;BONUS SECTION - THE SECRET STRUCTURE OF HAVING RHYTHM - (taught by yours truly)&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I am going to admit something to you.  I used to consider myself a hopeless case when it came to having rhythm.  It frustrated me when I'd see other people dancing and making it look so natural.  It seemed like they had some kind of special ability that I didn't.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;And then I discovered their secret!&lt;/b&gt;  It's true!  Someone taught me the big secret to having rhythm, and as soon as I learned how it was done, it was like the curtains were thrown wide open and I could finally see what I had been missing all those years.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Everywhere I went, I noticed good dancers that had perfect rhythm all doing the same thing, and once I knew their secret (which was invisible to most people, even themselves), my fear and awkwardness was gone.  Whenever I went somewhere that had a dance floor, I confidently strode out there as if I had magical powers!&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;After Lisa is finished teaching her portion of the workshop, I will teach you the surprisingly simple secret of having rhythm on the dance floor.  It only takes ten minutes to learn, and once you have it, you've got it for life.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  Please plan on arriving by 3:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members.  We start promptly at 3:30 and go until 5:30 (with a break in the middle).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to 30 people due to the size limitations of the classroom (we'll be moving around, not sitting in our seats).  Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, April 25th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and so you have time to meet some of the other students and make new connections.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272406931000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271577800000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Survive On The Dance Floor</name><id>13214020</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272223800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/13214020/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/1/global_14444977.jpeg</photo_url></item>