<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street and Moody Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.376185</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waltham Common</name><city>Waltham</city><id>835245</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.237073</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great place to relax outside during the summer.  Jay and I go all the time because we live in Waltham and I love the different music each week.  There are a lot of people who go to enjoy the music and just chill in the common.  I like to dance by my tree like no one is watching.  :0)  It's even light enough in the beginning to toss a frisbee around for a while.  The music usually ends around 8:30.  This is going to be their last concert for the summer.  The Reminisants are performing 50's and 60's music.  if you would like to join, feel free to bring a blanket or lawn chairs because there is no seating, but you can see the band stand no problem from almost anywhere, and you can definitely hear the music throughout the common.  You can check it out for yourselves: &lt;a href="http://www.walthamarts.org/concerts.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.walthamart...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no official address for Waltham Common, but it is near Cafe on the Common, which is 677 Main Street if you need it for a GPS.  Otherwise, the commuter rail will get you there or take bus 70 from Central Square in Cambridge.  Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have a great day,&lt;br /&gt;Tammy and Jay&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be set up by the tree near where the police cars are.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tammy </member_name><member_id>7303013</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251414280000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250702520000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Concert at the Waltham Common</name><id>11149018</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251241200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/11149018/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_9634902.jpeg</photo_url></item>