<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I thought it would be fun to combine the next meetup with my birthday which happens to fall on a Saturday this year :)&lt;br /&gt;So... here are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What? Big Salsa Party (aka my birthday celebration). Featuring Maestro DJ Hernan&lt;br /&gt;When? Dec 8, 9pm - ?? am&lt;br /&gt;Where? Corner of Pine Vale rd and Hardy Pond Rd in Waltham. Number on the mailbox is 180. &lt;br /&gt;I will have either the entire house (huge living + dining room space with hardwood floors plus finished, tiled basement) open for dancing, or just one of the floors, depending on how many people come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: There is a small parking lot that can fit about 20-30 cars at the beginning of the street (5 houses down, so only a few yards away from the house) as well as on-street parking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details: I am planning to provide a limited amount of appetizers and non-alcoholic beverages, so please bring your favorite beer or other beverages. If you'd like to help with the appetizers, plates/cups/utensils or anything else, let me know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I am sure there are more salseros/as out there who are not on facebook or meetup, please feel free to bring your favorite salsa friends, but please let me know who you are bringing :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, I can be reached at theonlymasha@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you will join me (and shhhhhh... i might make this into an annual event, but don't tell anybody yet). AND SINCE SOME OF YOU ASKED... OF COURSE THIS IS OPEN TO ALL OF THE MEMBERS OF THIS GROUP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;Masha&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197338736000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194654975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Masha's Birthday/Salsa bash</name><id>6712295</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197165600000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/6712295/</event_url></item>