<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you long to be in a relationship with someone amazing? Someone you're &lt;em&gt;wildly&lt;/em&gt; attracted to? Someone that totally "gets" you and accepts you just the way you are (without trying to fix, change, or turn you into someone you're not)?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you answered "yes" to any of these questions, then you're going to love this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You see, 2012 is just starting, and this is the perfect chance start fresh and go for what you really want. Would you like to get better results than you got last year? If so, then you need to give yourself the gift of learning better tools and strategies for attracting and keeping your ideal partner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this unique event, you'll learn a proven system for attracting incredible new relationship prospects into your life anytime you want. This is the same system I use myself, and it's proven to be highly successful (not to mention easy and fun). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN: &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to develop an "attraction web" that automatically puts you in the way of interesting singles that are looking for a relationship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The best places to go in order to meet interesting and attractive singles who are looking for a relationship. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The single most important ability you must develop in order to be interesting and attractive to other people. Once you master this, you'll have a never ending supply of quality people wanting to spend more time with you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 simple secrets I learned from studying the law of attraction that draws your ideal dating prospects to you like a magnet. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The "secret question" that everyone's subconscious mind is asking when you first meet them, and how this one question determines if they will even consider dating you or not. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to approach someone you're interested in and start a conversation with them. &amp;nbsp;It's easier than you think, once you know this proven conversation starter. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 HOW TO GET INVOLVED &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Where is it? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The seminar is conveniently located at an adult education center in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line. Please plan on arriving by 2:45pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members. We start promptly at 3:00 and go until 5:00 (with a break in the middle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is it free? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Since it's the new year and I want to help as many people as possible, I decided to make this one free. &amp;nbsp;These seminars normally cost $25, but this one is on the house. &amp;nbsp;If you've been on the fence about coming to an event, now is your chance to see what we're all about with no risk on your part. &amp;nbsp;Come join us, and see what we're all about. &amp;nbsp;I'd love to meet you :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; Because we are going to be moving around, and doing some fun exercises, I have to limit this event to 35 people due to the size limitations of the room. &amp;nbsp;Be sure to put in your RSVP now in order to lock in your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot. &amp;nbsp;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warmly,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Jason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go through the front door and follow the signs that say SEMINAR.  It's easy to find.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>22</waitlist_count><updated>1326837020000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>55</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326247105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE DATING SEMINAR:  How To Meet and Attract Your Ideal Mate</name><id>47595112</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326657600000</time><rsvp_limit>55</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/47595112/</event_url></item>