<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red starts at 7:40, so let's meet right inside the ticket lobby at the AMC at 7:10. Then I'll buy us all tickets and we can go get snacks and head into the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow for Red!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810143371/info" target="_blank"&gt;Red&lt;/a&gt; promises to be a smart, funny movie about a bunch of has-been CIA agents who are forced back into action. With a cast that has rivaled any movie in recent memory, it's sure to deliver a memorable evening. Some of the stars:&lt;br /&gt;Bruce Willis, Morgan Freeman, John Malkovich, Helen Mirren, Mary-Louise Parker, Ernest Borgnine, Richard Dreyfuss, Morgan J. Freeman. Holy star-studded cast, right?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frank, Joe, Marvin, and Victoria used to be the CIA's top agents -- but the secrets they know just made them the Agency's top targets. Now framed for assassination, they must use all of their collective cunning, experience and teamwork to stay one step ahead of their deadly pursuers and stay alive. To stop the operation, the team embarks on an impossible, cross-country mission to break into the top-secret CIA headquarters, where they will uncover one of the biggest conspiracies and cover-ups in government history. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Red!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289151923000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287606665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red</name><id>15174736</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288911600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/15174736/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>