<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Webster Avenue</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03755</zip><lat>43.706135</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dartmouth College: Rockefeller Center</name><city>Hanover</city><id>1605493</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.290558</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, April 27th Gene Baur, Co-Founder and President of Farm Sanctuary, will give a talk on the consequences of factory farming (please see below for abstract). Afterwards, there will be a catered vegan dinner and Mr. Baur will sign copies of his national best-selling book "Farm Sanctuary: Changing Hearts and Minds about Animals and Food" (copies of the book will be available for purchase at the event).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The talk will take place on the Dartmouth College campus in Rockefeller 003 at 5:45 PM, with dinner immediately following. Both the lecture and dinner are FREE and OPEN TO THE PUBLIC. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the course of this lecture, Mr. Baur will discuss his reasons for founding Farm Sanctuary and the ways in which animal agriculture has transformed since the organization's beginnings in 1986. He will address the current realities of the industrial food system, including the use of antibiotics and hormones and environmental consequences such as climate change and air and water pollution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through his lecture and the following Q&amp;amp;A session, audience members can engage in discussions about where our food comes from and explore the difference an individual can make on a global scale through his or her food choices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Room 003</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lola</member_name><member_id>915277</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303945094000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pioneers of Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-430</urlname><id>650201</id><group_lat>43.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.2699966431</group_lon><name>NH/VT Vegan Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302657082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner with Gene Baur, Farm Sanctuary President and Co-Founder</name><id>17285015</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303940700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-430/events/17285015/</event_url></item>