<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1403775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105443</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Off the Grid: Inside the Movement for More Space, Less Government, and True Independence in Modern America by Nick Rosen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Written by a leading authority on living off the grid, this is a fascinating and timely look at one of the fastest growing movements in America. In researching the stories that would become Off the Grid, Nick Rosen traveled from one end of the United States to the other, spending time with all kinds of individuals and families striving to live their lives the way they want to-free from dependence on municipal power and amenities, and free from the inherent dependence on the government and its far-reaching arms. While the people profiled may not have a lot in common in terms of their daily lives or their personal background, what they do share is an understanding of how unique their lives are, and how much effort and determination is required to maintain the lifestyle in the face of modern America's push toward connectivity and development.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs with a copy of the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>H H</member_name><member_id>6628358</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340295155000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1481208</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337797879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Off the Grid: Inside the Movt. for More Space, Less Gov't &amp; T ... by Nick Rosen</name><id>66032152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340145000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group/events/66032152/</event_url></item>