<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>288 Lyman Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01532</zip><lat>42.302799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Westborough State Hospital</name><city>Westborough</city><id>2771301</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.605942</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;The Westborough Sprint Triathlon&amp;nbsp;returns to&amp;nbsp;Lake Chauncy&amp;nbsp;August 14, 2011&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;The Westborough Sprint Triathlon will begin with a 0.25 mile swim in Lake Chauncy. Athletes will then transition to a&amp;nbsp;13.9 mile bike course. After completing the bike course, athletes will head out on a 3 mile run that is mostly off road on the scenic and flat trails that surround Lake Chauncy.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Event Date, Location&amp;nbsp;and Start Time:
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The Westborough Sprint Triathlon will be on Sunday,&amp;nbsp;August 14, 2011 in&amp;nbsp;Westborough, MA.&amp;nbsp;The location of the race is on the grounds of the Westborough State Hospital located at 288 Lyman Street. Participants will enter the Hospital grounds from Hospital Avenue which is off of Lyman. Westborough is located&amp;nbsp;about&amp;nbsp;35 miles&amp;nbsp;west of Boston. The race will start&amp;nbsp;at 8:00AM.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Event Distance and Course Maps:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Swim&lt;/span&gt;: The swim will be 0.25 miles in the calm waters of Lake Chauncy. 
&lt;a href="http://www.mapmyrun.com/run/united-states/ma/westborough/671127129311776702" target="_blank"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Click here&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/a&gt; to see the location and layout of the swim course. Upon exiting the water athletes will run to transition to grab their bike and head out onto the bike course. 
&lt;a href="http://www.sunmultisportevents.com/Assets/Sun+Multisports+Digital+Assets/Races/Westborough+Transition.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Download&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/a&gt; the transition map. 
&lt;strong&gt;Are you a little nervous about an open water swim?&lt;/strong&gt; Let the coaches from Vescio Multisport Performance Services help you out! They'll be conducting an open water swim clinic at Lake Chauncy on Friday, August 5th. 
&lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/a/mpstraining.com/services/open-water" target="_blank"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for more information and to register.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Bike&lt;/span&gt;:&amp;nbsp;The bike course&amp;nbsp;will be&amp;nbsp;13.9 miles along the roads of Westborough, Northborough, Marlborough and Southborough. This course will 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; be closed to traffic and features a variety of rolling hills. The exact route can be found with a 
&lt;a href="http://www.sunmultisportevents.com/Assets/Sun+Multisports+Digital+Assets/Westborough+Bike+Course.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;. You can also 
&lt;a href="http://www.sunmultisportevents.com/Assets/Sun+Multisports+Digital+Assets/Races/Westborough+Bike+Cue+Sheet.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;download&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/a&gt; the bike course cue sheet.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Run&lt;/span&gt;: After returning from the bike course and racking your bike in 
&lt;a href="http://www.sunmultisportevents.com/Assets/Sun+Multisports+Digital+Assets/Races/Westborough+Transition.pdf"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;transition&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/a&gt; , athletes will head out onto the&amp;nbsp;run course which is&amp;nbsp;approximately&amp;nbsp;3 miles. The first 1.75 miles of the run (approximately) are on the trails surrounding Lake Chauncy. This is a very scenic stretch that includes some shady tree cover, but understand these are trails which feature sections of grass, loose gravel and some roots -- nothing too adventurous, but enough for you to pay attention so you don't twist an ankle.&amp;nbsp; After exiting the trails athletes will turn left on Chauncy Street, then left on Lyman Street and left onto Hospital Road back to the finish. The last 300 yards&amp;nbsp;of the run will be on grass across playing fields (very spectator friendly!). This is a scenic, flat course with a few rolling hills. Aid stations with water and Hammer Nutrition Heed electrolyte drink will be available at run aid stations near mile 1 and mile 2. &amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.sunmultisportevents.com/Assets/Sun+Multisports+Digital+Assets/Westborough+Sprint+Tri+Run.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to see the&amp;nbsp;run course.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;The race venue is located at 288 Lyman Street in Westborough MA.&amp;nbsp; Lyman Street is accessible from either Route 9 Eastbound or Westbound.&amp;nbsp; Travelling westbound on Route 9, you will make a right on Lyman St.&amp;nbsp; Travelling eastbound on Rte. 9, you will make a left on Lyman Street.&amp;nbsp; The turn for Lyman Street is at a traffic light.&amp;nbsp; See below for directions on where to park.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;There are&amp;nbsp;multiple locations available to you for parking.&amp;nbsp;There will be parking on the side of Hospital Road within the grounds of Westborough State Hospital. There will also be parking at the Hadley Building on Lyman Street which is just across the entrance from Westborough State Hospital. Lastly, parking is available at the parking lot located on Haskell Street. Haskell Street is off Lyman Street right by the entrance to Westborough State Hospital. 
&lt;a href="http://www.sunmultisportevents.com/Assets/Sun+Multisports+Digital+Assets/Westborough+Tri+Parking.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Click here&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/a&gt; to see an area&amp;nbsp;map that identifies each of these parking&amp;nbsp;locations as well as the location of the race start, race finish, transition&amp;nbsp;and race day packet pick-up.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Entry Fee:
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Individuals $80 and&amp;nbsp;Relay Teams $135. NOTE: Online registration closes at 6PM EST on Friday, August 12th. Registrations will be processing in person during race packet pick-up hours which are indicated below.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Awards:
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Awards will be given to the top 3 male and female finishers in each age group as well as for the top 3 Athenas and Clydesdales. All 3 members of the 1st place Mixed, Female and Male relay teams will also receive an award.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;For more info go to the 
&lt;a href="http://www.sunmultisportevents.com/Westborough_Sprint.htm"&gt;Sun Multisport Events&lt;/a&gt; website.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Rice</member_name><member_id>2673515</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313396797000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Triathletes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Tri</urlname><id>584357</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8399963379</group_lon><name>Mass Tri</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311829308000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Westborough Sprint Triathlon</name><id>27328981</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313321400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Tri/events/27328981/</event_url></item>