<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>717784</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703319</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of our members, Dianne, suggested the following event.  She is facilitating an introduction to the film as well as a discussion afterward.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See below:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Real Art Ways on Monday, they will be showing the matinee film &amp;quot;The Four Hundred Blows&amp;quot; by Truffaut.  It is a revered work in the history of film. It costs only $5 and includes a light lunch starting at 1:00.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be other Meetup people there and I'd appreciate it if you'd let other film fans know about this great event.  I don't expect you to organize anything around it- just letting people know would be great.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Hartford Courant: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a boy, François Truffaut went to the movies to forget his troubles. When he grew up, he made a movie about a boy who did the same thing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The 400 Blows&amp;quot; tells the story of Antoine, whose mother and stepfather have little time for him. His teachers dislike and distrust him, only with partial justification, and he has run-ins with police. Whenever he has the chance, he reads his beloved Balzac and goes to the movies, immersing himself in other people's lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Truffaut's classic will be shown Monday, Jan. 4, at Real Art Ways. It is 99 minutes, in French with subtitles and unrated. It will be shown at 1:30 p.m., preceded by a refreshment period and followed by a discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Real Art Ways is at 56 Arbor St., Hartford. Admission is $5.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for each other in the lobby.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262801880000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262543962000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Four Hundred Blows</name><id>12206949</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262628000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/12206949/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/8/global_5165560.jpeg</photo_url></item>