<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>49.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us for a very special event.  &lt;a href="http://www.patternliteracy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Toby Hemenway&lt;/a&gt;, author of Gaia's Garden, will be following his &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/calendar/12428797/"&gt;Friday night talk&lt;/a&gt; with a more &lt;b&gt;in-depth half-day workshop on Saturday morning&lt;/b&gt; (9am to 1pm).  This will be an excellent opportunity for &lt;i&gt;both permaculture novices as well as seasoned practitioners&lt;/i&gt; to take in some fundamentals from a very experienced teacher and designer, a leader in the permaculture &amp;quot;community&amp;quot; with intimate perspective on rural, urban and suburban permaculture applications. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is co-sponsored by &lt;a href="http://www.tnsk.org/index.html"&gt;The New School&lt;/a&gt; in Kennebunk and will be held at their wonderful facility (approx halfway between Portland and Portsmouth). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workshop will be followed by a shared potluck lunch.  Please bring your potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin) and a dish to share.  Morning coffee/tea/snacks will be provided.  Please bring a notebook and digital camera if desired. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;More about Toby Hemenway  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Toby Hemenway is the author of the first major North American book on permaculture, Gaia's Garden: A Guide to Home-Scale Permaculture, and an adjunct professor at Portland State University. He is also Scholar in Residence at Pacific University.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After obtaining a degree in biology from Tufts University, Toby worked for many years as a researcher in genetics and immunology, first in academic laboratories including Harvard and the University of Washington in Seattle, and then at Immunex, a major medical biotech company. At about the time he was growing dissatisfied with the direction biotechnology was taking, he discovered permaculture, a design approach based on ecological principles that creates sustainable landscapes, homes, and workplaces. A career change followed, and Toby and his wife spent ten years creating a rural permaculture site in southern Oregon. He was associate editor of Permaculture Activist, a journal of ecological design and sustainable culture, from 1999 to 2004. His current project is developing urban sustainability resources in Portland, Oregon, where he now lives. He teaches permaculture and consults and lectures on ecological design throughout the country. His writing has appeared in magazines such as Whole Earth Review, Natural Home, and Kitchen Gardener. He is available for workshops, lectures, and consulting on a wide variety of topics related to permaculture, ecological design, Peak Oil, local food systems, and other subjects.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267452486000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265303362000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intro to Permaculture Workshop w/Toby Hemenway, Author of Gaia's Garden</name><id>12518475</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267279200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/12518475/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/b/global_12942939.jpeg</photo_url></item>