<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This event is listed on the Leisure Cycling meetup where 3 people have said Yes and 10 have said Maybe. It is also on the hiking meetup where 13 people have rsvp'd Yes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 3 ways to participate; 1) come for the bike ride Saturday afternoon, 2) stay overnight Saturday either in a hotel or camping, 3) stay Sat-Mon nights camping. Please state in the comments section of your rsvp what your plans are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can rent a bike at the trail head for $16 for 4 hours. If you have your own bike but no rack for the car you can probably get a ride with someone who can take you and your bike. Ask for a ride in your rsvp and I will help you find someone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 12 in the parking lot at the beginning of the rail trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will cycle 10 miles along the trail and stop at Cobie's clamshack. This is adjacent Nickerson State Park, so we can make a stop at the beach, too. We should be back at the starting point by 4 or 5 o'clock. Total cycling time should be about 2 hours at a moderate pace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can come just on Sat for the ride, or spend the weekend on the cape. I will be staying on the cape camping for 3 days at the North of Highland campground, which is out near the end of the cape. Please reserve a site if you would like to join me for camping. I can also have a second tent on my site. Some people have indicated that they would like to stay at a hotel. Either way, we can make plans to spend some time together on Saturday after the ride and on Sunday too.  For those camping, we will organize some group events in the next couple of weeks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cobies.com/menu.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cobies.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rail Trail website and map at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/ccrt.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.capecodcamping.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.capecodcam...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(508)487-1191 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.barbsbikeshop.com/locations.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.barbsbikes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 25-mile Cape Cod Rail Trail starts at Barbara's Bike Shop in South Dennis and extends to Wellfleet. The picturesque paved trail offers safe off-road riding with family and friends. Stop along the way for lunch or a swim in one of the area's crystal clear ponds. 4 hour bike rental for $16.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DENNIS STORE  &lt;br /&gt;430 Route 134&lt;br /&gt;South Dennis MA 02660&lt;br /&gt;(508) 760-4723&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188364378000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186884245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Cod trip</name><id>6165012</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188057600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6165012/</event_url></item>