<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's DANCE!! &amp;nbsp;I don't know about you but I LOVE to dance -- any time, any place, anywhere! &amp;nbsp; I'm very excited to get these dances going again. &amp;nbsp;I am committed to revitalizing these dances so that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) &amp;nbsp;We have a GREAT time together; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) &amp;nbsp;There are plenty of opportunities to meet other singles&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HERE ARE A FEW TIPS THAT WILL MAKE THESE DANCES A SUCCESS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;DISCOVER&lt;/em&gt; someone new and invite them into your conversation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;ASK&lt;/em&gt; five people to dance every time you attend&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;N&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;NEVER&lt;/em&gt; say 'no' the first time someone asks you to dance; take a risk, say YES!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;CHALLENGE&lt;/em&gt; yourself by trying something new&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;ENTER&lt;/em&gt; the dance space with your best self forward&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inspire a spirit of inclusiveness in a community of like-minded folks - be friendly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please invite your friends, especially those of the male persuasion. &amp;nbsp;My personal goal is to have an equal number of men and women on the dance floor together. &amp;nbsp;Please contribute by inviting others to come and dance with us. &amp;nbsp;Thank you!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DETAILS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need a minimum of 50 people for this dance to happen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please RSVP by November 19th and pay ahead so that your spot is reserved!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This dance will end at 11:30 pm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you would like to bring wine or a snack/dessert to share, your entry fee will be $12 (there will be non-alcoholic beverages at the dance.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be light snacks at the dance, too; please eat dinner before arriving (or better yet, meet each other for dinner and then head over to dance together!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm really really looking forward to meeting you! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robyn&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location and Directions- Temple Shalom Emeth, 16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;128 North Exit 32B Middlesex Turnpike (Burlington/Arlington) At the end of the ramp turn right onto Middlesex Turnpike - on the left is Barnes/Noble- After the Burlington Mall turn right on to Burlington Mall Rd. - on left is Longs Jewelers- Take left after you pass Kohl&amp;rsquo;s on your left which is Lexington Street- Temple Shalom Emeth is on your left at 16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two parking lots on the right side of building. Enter through the side entrance at the end of the building. Third parking lot is two houses up at Church - we have permission. Fourth parking lot is across the street - McGinnis Ave., - Mt Hope Church.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will welcome you at the door with a warm smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323569232000</updated><rating><average>3.22000002861</average><count>18</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>147</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315435015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dance, Dance, Dance!</name><id>32670122</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321752600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/32670122/</event_url></item>