<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>520 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-347-4777</phone><name>La Boca</name><city>Middletown</city><id>348749</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.660004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There was such a positive response from the last event here and there were quite a few people who wanted to come but it was full.  I decided to give it another shot!  Join us at La Boca Mexican Restaurant and Cantina for fun and trivia.  Here is what their website says:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We offer casual, upscale dining in our restaurant and a relaxed, fun bar atmosphere in our Mexican style cantina. We serve authentic Mexican food. Our chef's innovative, cultural offerings set us apart and make us the most popular Mexican restaurant around! Our customers range from families (kid's menu available) and couples, to the &amp;quot;wilder&amp;quot; Cantina patrons. No matter what the occasion calls for or your appetite demands, our professional staff at La Boca promises to make your next dinning experience truly unforgettable.&amp;quot;  &lt;a href="http://www.labocaonline.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.labocaonline.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Trivia Challenge begins at 8:30pm so we should have plenty of time to eat and then concentrate on winning the $25 gift certificate that's up for grabs!  There is a second game that is played with a $50 gift certificate up for grabs at a steak house.&lt;br /&gt;Please only RSVP if you know you can make it.  I will be keeping track of who RSVPs but does not show up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NickiJ has offered to help organize this event.  Thanks, Nicki!!!  Her cell phone number is 860-307-1550 if you have any questions.  Reservations are in her name.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542194000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190206492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>More Trivia and Tamales at La Boca in Middletown!!!</name><id>6388328</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191366000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/6388328/</event_url></item>