<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Kayak Reservation/rental</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per al's kayaks rented.</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ok since most of you can now handle a simple 9 mile trip down stream.. Here is another downstream trip..&lt;br /&gt;I checked the tide tables, things look good so far for saturday or sunday as a back up day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The places on the list can be seen in one day but if some are too tired we can stop in a nice area right across from seldon island, (deep river dock) and skip hamburger..&lt;br /&gt;then go to the cars in Essex.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some lunch and water..the usual acessories...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting to the start point:&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford,&lt;br /&gt;Take rte 9 south to exit # 7&lt;br /&gt;Take the connector (rte 82) to the Goodspeed oprah house..(left on 154, Middlesex tpk then the first right back onto 82= Bridge road.&lt;br /&gt;Cross the CT River bridge, pass the Goodspeed and Gelston House, take the just past the Gelston house = Lumber Yard road...go past the Goodspeed parking lot take the first right into the grass  boat ramp are lot just before the fence.&lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest, GPS and others, 14 lumber yard road, east haddam, ct that will get you close enough...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essex drop car off:&lt;br /&gt; from the Gelston House go back to rte 9..&lt;br /&gt;Rte 9 south to exit #3&lt;br /&gt;take a left on to 154 = main st then a left onto west avenue, if you missed this the next left is 153, take a left there= west ave, its a triangle thing,&lt;br /&gt;ok when on west ave go into the town a bit around in  half circle untill you see a 4 way intersection with North Main street,&lt;br /&gt;take north main by going strait till you get to the first right, thats bushnell, take the right onto bushnell, go a short ways look left, (bushnell park boat ramp) for a grassy lot, i think its called Teal Lane&lt;br /&gt;Mapquest, GPS and others, put in #1 Teal Lane, Essex CT or if that dont work just try Bushnell st, essex, ct&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOOK AT YOUR MAPS...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184693676000</updated><rating><average>3.20000004768</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183589706000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT River Coves, Chapman, Waleboane, Seldon, Hamburger..</name><id>5975528</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184520600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5975528/</event_url></item>