<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate...I have to be back to my car by 1pm, so we can go 1.5 hours one-way...3 hours altogether.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quabbin Reservoir: my favorite place!&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/5/4/event_73249492.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin is the most beautiful place in Massachusetts! You can see some pictures at my website: &lt;a href="http://www.custom-pro.com/portfolio/quabbin" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.custom-pro.com/portfolio/quabbin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Park is at the southern end, with paved roads, long dams, and beautiful viewing spots. Goodnough Dike is the view shown in the photo above! Park in the dirt lot before&amp;nbsp; the the Goodnough Dike loop (just under a mile after entering the park via the East Entrance).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll walk the loop over the dam and back through the woods. Then we'll go along the main road about halfway through the park. This probably means we'll go to Hank's Meadow or Enfield Overlook. There are outhouses with sanitizer where we're parking and at both viewing spots. Bring a drink and maybe a snack or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry-in, carry-out. (Take your trash with you...well, the Visitor's Center and tower have trash bins.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to attend even if you didn't RSVP, but please be aware I leave my house about 9am. If you are running late, I won't know to wait for you, but you can probably catch up to me on the dam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. (From the North, use I-290 to get to Route 9.) Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware and some steep hills, there's not much except scattered houses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The East Entrance is on the right, around the curve after a pulloff where fishermen park. (The pulloff has a wood barrier at the start of a trail.) Enter and continue straight almost a mile to the loop road. (There will be a sign that says "Goodnough Dike.") I'll park in the small dirt lot on the right, immediately before this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you pass marsh on both sides of the road, you've gone too far. That's okay, just take the next entrance (the Middle Entrance) on the right. After more than a mile, continue straight through the rotary. (Don't go uphill to the tower.) The Goodnough Dike loop will be a few miles further on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live closer to Route 31 or 122 than to I-290, just take the appropriate route South to Route 9, then follow directions "from Worcester" as above. Or, as an alternative, take 122 North (it heads kind of West), and take Route 37A South to Route 9. See the directions from Worcester...pick it up from downtown Ware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points North and West:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the North, take Route 202 South. (From east or west, use Route 2 to get there.) Turn left and go East on Route 9. The East Entrance is the 3rd entrance on your left, and it will take you at least 5 more minutes to get there. Before you get there, you will pass a marsh on both sides of the road. Also, there's a sign for the wildlife sanctuary on the right, shortly before you see the park entrance on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322370930000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322182322000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Goodnough Dike @ Quabbin Reservoir</name><id>42307772</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322319600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/42307772/</event_url></item>