<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Last week's Skype call was a spirited discussion that raised many challenging questions. In our follow up meeting we continue reading Darwin's Origin of Species as well as looking into some of the ideas often associated or attributed to Darwin. Some of the questions we may try to address include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there a philosophy of Darwin? If so, what is the metaphysics, epistemology and ethics of that philosophy? Or is it a new way of thinking that breaks away from the structure and approach of traditional philosophy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is the meaning and legacy of Darwin? What are the lessons we should learn from Darwin? What does it mean to be Darwinian?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can we hold Darwin responsible for Social Darwinism? Is it an idea Darwin held or would have supported? Is it a logical extension of his ideas? A misreading or misapplication (and if so how)? Or is it an anachronistic misreading into Darwin of ideas that were completely foreign to him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggestions for reading further parts of the work: chapters VI and VII and the Conclusion, Chapter XV&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim</member_name><member_id>840234</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>mike</member_name><member_id>2266223</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilie</member_name><member_id>4710889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336091941000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334869109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skype -- Darwin: On the Origin of Species</name><id>61302682</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336003200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/61302682/</event_url></item>