<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This hike is a 3.0 mile looping hike of low to low-moderate effort on mostly forested land. There is a gradual upward trend for the first half of the hike on the South Boundary Loop and that is where some effort will be expended. A few stream crossings over small rough bridges of half logs and peaceful atmosphere prevail on this conservation land hike. I haven't hiked here in 4 years so it will be good to see what changes have happened.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the dirt parking lot just before 2 PM and start the hike on the hour. We should be done by about 4 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: The McCann Family Farm is a hilly 84 acres of farmland and mixed forest. Located on it are two brooks and two vernal pools. It includes hiking trails and the Whit Davis Bird Sanctuary, and is managed and preserved by the Northern Connecticut Land Trust (NCLT).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location/Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;The McCann Family Farm is Route 190 east of the village of Somers. Parking lot is on the south side of 190, about 0.7 miles east of Route 83. The entrance is a short dirt road with a very dark wooden sign marking the entrance so be alert. Parking is in a dirt lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to parking lot meetup&lt;/b&gt; (around 650 Main St., Somers, CT):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?city=Somers&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=650+Main+St&amp;amp;zipcode=06071-2119&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.985369&amp;amp;longitude=-72.44139&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://classic.mapque...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Northern Connecticut Land Trust (NCLT)&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1295104537000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293304520000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at McCann Family Farm Nature Preserve in Somers CT</name><id>15818072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294599600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15818072/</event_url></item>