<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This time we're going to try a "code review"-style meeting where anyone of any skill level is invited to bring a bug (or it could be another kind of repeatable brick wall you're at related to iOS) in and we'll spend a portion of our time showing, telling, and squishing the issue.  Please just come and participate, or if you want to supply an entomological specimen see if you can:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have a clear, reproducible problem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have the code isolated in a project or version that you are ok w/ other people looking at&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's kind of what happened last meeting for two of us, but now it's an official invitation. &lt;span&gt;Based on the number of people we might rotate every 5 to 25 minutes or so.&lt;/span&gt; To anyone particularly plagued that wants to assure a spot: let me know in advance, otherwise the early bird gets 'em.  If you're bug free, feel free to bring a concocted stumper for us to solve if time allows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Matt Bastide for this concrete suggestion and for his presentation last time on using Core Data with Magical Record, among other goodies he shared.  Those more conceptual discussions are excellent, so I hope others continue to propose them, but it's so very useful to hear others thoughts on actual code problems.  I'll always lend what I can, but as a relatively hackish coder: I must say thanks again to those more experienced among us who've been generous with their time at some of these 25 meetings over the last 3 1/2 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I realize that Friday may not be be so great for everyone, but I'm now going to be working in Boston (at the School of the Museum of Fine Arts) through Thursday nights and I'd like to attend meetings if possible. I did check with those who come regularly, but I believe you can also create an event for whenever you like on this page if you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;happy coding and maybe we'll see you there,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Brian&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Reeves</member_name><member_id>4215226</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350090130000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>interested parties</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portland-iPhone-Developers-Network</urlname><id>1454525</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine iOS Developer Network  (iPhone/iPad)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345746231000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bug Squishing Party</name><id>79049342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350079200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-iPhone-Developers-Network/events/79049342/</event_url></item>