<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Paddlers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOU CHOOSE THE TALK YOU ARE INTERESTED IN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Original Text edited to make it fit on this page)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be there all day, so stop by if you like. al-r&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;On Jan. 29 you have a great opportunity to get out of the house &amp;amp; attend a free paddling workshop at the CT Marine Trades Association (CMTA) Hartford Boat Show  (&lt;a href="http://www.ctmarinetrades.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctmarinetr...&lt;/a&gt; ), at the CT Convention Center  ( &lt;a href="http://www.ctconventions.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctconventi...&lt;/a&gt; ) in downtown Hartford from 10 am to 4 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;Seminar Room 14 on the Ballroom level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt; You do not need to pay admission to the boat show to attend these talks in a seminar room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is brought to you courtesy of the CMTA  &amp;amp; the  CT DEP Boating Division. Please contact Mark Chanski (Mark.Chanski@ct.gov,  860-447-4371)  or myself with questions. Please spread the word!  &lt;br /&gt; I hope to see you there!   Jean, 860-463-9505&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presentation as follows:  &lt;br /&gt; 10-10:15 am  &lt;br /&gt;CT Department of Environmental Protection Boating Division Opening Remarks, including Eleanor Mariani, CT State Boating Law Administrator,  John Annino &amp;amp; Mark Chanski. Mark is an ACA accredited flatwater + kayaking instructor &amp;amp; also teaches the on-land DEP class "So you want to go for a paddle?". That presentation and lots of other good maritime info of interest to CT paddlers is on the DEP Facebook page.  &lt;br /&gt; Goal: paddling safety as part of Operation Paddle Smart. Operation Paddle Smart advocates:  &lt;br /&gt;1. wear life jacket. Legally required from Oct. 1 - May 31 in a manually propelled vessel in CT  &lt;br /&gt;2. awareness of immediate danger of cold water immersion  &lt;br /&gt;3. encourage boater &amp;amp; paddler education  &lt;br /&gt;4. to ID your canoe, kayak &amp;amp;rowboat  &lt;br /&gt;5. stress the importance of being a responsible &amp;amp; prudent boater.  &lt;br /&gt; Operation Paddle Smart is a multi-partnered endeavor. Besides the CT DEP, it includes the US Power Squadrons, the Coast Guard, and the Coast Guard Auxiliary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greg will now share with you some insight on kayak visibility on Long Island Sound. Ric has brought some lights, displayed on the table, to help you be more visible. Ric will mention briefly the Paddleports America class approved for use by the Auxiliary in an on-land lecture format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Time: 10:15 to 10:30am  &lt;br /&gt; Co-existing with Power Boats, a Survival Guide for Paddlecraft.  &lt;br /&gt; This presentation will look at specific changes every paddler can make every time they go out on the water to protect themselves from a close encounter Of the Worst Kind with a Power Vessel. Based on actual photos from recent events the talk will show why power boaters cannot see paddlecraft &amp;amp; will provide practical tips for getting noticed. We will also talk about planning organized events &amp;amp; steps that can be taken to warn boats that paddlers are operating in specific local waters.  &lt;br /&gt; Gregory J. Miller, Esq.    &lt;br /&gt;Greg Miller has been rowing and paddling small boats on Connecticut waters for over 30 years. When not paddling he is typically serving on a 32&amp;rsquo; Patrol Boat on behalf of the United States Coast Guard Auxiliary, Flotilla 72, Norwalk, CT or on a privately owned 46&amp;rsquo; powerboat out of Stamford Harbor. He has also served as sailing instructor and has operated vessels from the tropics to the arctic. His wife Jan is assisting with the presentation. She is an experienced paddler &amp;amp; a member of the US Coast Guard Auxiliary.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Time: 10:30 - 11:00 am  &lt;br /&gt;Kayak Fishing Tactics &amp;amp; Techniques for Safety &amp;amp; Success  &lt;br /&gt;This presentation will focus primarily on methods for successful kayak fishing in fresh, salt &amp;amp; brackish waters, while addressing common sense rules for avoiding the safety hazards inherent to the sport.  Included will be information concerning kayak designs, transportation, equipment &amp;amp; storage, as well as rods &amp;amp; tackle to help the novice or veteran kayak fisherperson to safely achieve success.  &lt;br /&gt;Phil Medeiros  &lt;br /&gt;An avid sportsman for over 35 years, Phil has been happily pursuing his passion for kayak fishing for the last ten.  he has a world of stories on everything from surviving 5 foot seas, to the secretive world of night angling, to warm water releases from power plants to ice fishing. His experience includes salt, brackish to fresh water, lakes + ponds, the Connecticut River &amp;amp; most of the shore of Long Island Sound. He also enjoys outdoor photography, He is happy to share his unique images with you. Experiencing these adventures in a kayak has led him to encourage both children &amp;amp; adults to participate in this wonderful way to gain exercise, camaraderie and some of the best of the outdoors Connecticut has to offer.  &lt;br /&gt; Time:  11:00 - 11:30 am  &lt;br /&gt; Cold Water Protection for Paddlers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hazards associated with paddling in cold weather and water + the definition and effects of hypothermia.  Learn how to minimize the risks of cold water. Examine some examples of cold water clothing. Time for questions, so don't be shy, please speak up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul J. Donoski has been a  Paddle Sports Sales Associate, North Cove Outfitters Inc., Old Saybrook, CT for over 8 years. He is a  Level 2 American Canoe Association Certified instructor and 3 Star British Canoe Union certified instructor.  Paul is an avid sea kayaker who paddles all year round in the CT River and Long Island Sound. During the past 10 years he's been in many portions of the Northeast coast from Canada to New York, as well as the Florida Keys.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Time: 11:30 - Noon  &lt;br /&gt; Safety Components of a Proper Sea Kayak  &lt;br /&gt; Safety components of a proper sea kayak - what is considered a good "KIT" in the sea kayaking world.  What to wear on you, what to bring on a day trip, and how to build on your "Kit" for multi-day journeys. Greg Paquin and Paula Reigel of Kayak Waveology, southern New England's premier sea kayaking instruction company, can help you learn paddle sports in your own waters and to discover paddling journeys to far away lands.  " Sea kayaking Instruction for those who are looking to do more."  &lt;br /&gt; Greg Paquin and Paula Reigel  &lt;br /&gt;Greg is a British Canoe Union (BCU) Level 3 Sea Coach, BCU 5 Star Sea Leader, and American Canoe Association (ACA) Level 5 Advanced Open Water Instructor. Paula is a  BCU Level 2 Coach, BCU 4 Star Sea Leader, ACA Level 4 Open Water instructor, and ACA Adaptive Paddler Instructor  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Time:  Noon - 12:30  &lt;br /&gt; SUPs - Stand Up Paddleboards  &lt;br /&gt;Join in the sport of Kings! With ancient origins in the Hawaiian royalty of the Pacific, stand up paddleboarding is now a New England phenomenon,  and some of the best boards are sold here in CT. A Norwalk company, C &amp;amp; C, will introduce you to the sport, including the safety aspects. C&amp;amp;C stand up paddleboards offer the opportunity to explore your natural surroundings while getting a full core workout that will fully challenge your mind and body. We are excited for you to begin that exploration with C&amp;amp;C. "Stand up with us and see everything around you from a whole new point of view."  &lt;br /&gt;Sean Corrigan  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Time: 12:30 - 1:00 pm  &lt;br /&gt; US Power Squadrons - America's Boating Club: Practical Safety Training for Paddlers  &lt;br /&gt; The upsurge in popularity of canoes and kayaks over the past 10 years has brought with it an alarming increase in accidents + fatalities.  The United States Power Squadron (USPS) has offered courses to boaters for decades to improve boater knowledge and safety. With our "America's Boating Course" &amp;amp; "Paddle Smart", "Using GPS" - "Chart Smart" seminars, the USPS can now offer paddlers a set of short courses with practical how-to features including an in-water pool session to practice self-rescue and braces, &amp;amp; course plotting using nautical charts &amp;amp; GPS for trip planning. This presentation provides highlights about the USPS, benefits of membership &amp;amp; our paddle safety courses.  For info, see www.USPS.org - www.usps.org/localusps/milford.  &lt;br /&gt; Bruce Ross  &lt;br /&gt;Mr. Ross has been a member of the Milford Power Squadron since 2003. Serving as its Commander for the past two years, he is involved in many facets of boating as a sailor and kayaker.  He is a member of several paddling organizations throughout the state of CT, and regularly conducts his Paddle Smart Kayak Safety Course with classroom &amp;amp; in-water pool training.    &lt;br /&gt; Time 1:00 - 1:30 Putting Fun in Kayaking &amp;amp;Canoeing  &lt;br /&gt; Got your kayak (or canoe)! Got your paddle! What more is there to know? Nothing if you enjoy hard work, muscle aches, fighting current and wind, worrying about what to do when you capsize and most of all, not getting the boat to go where you want is to go. If this does not seem like fun to you then join us as we discuss how to work less, paddle smarter, &amp;amp; share the secrets of efficient paddling.  &lt;br /&gt; Elizabeth O&amp;rsquo;Connor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Time: 1:30-1:45 Safety in Numbers  &lt;br /&gt; Meeting up can be lots of fun! There are great benefits to paddling with a group besides their usual barbecues &amp;amp; paddles around Connecticut, this group holds an annual  "Play in the Water to Self Rescue" when the water is warm enough at Bolton Lake. It is fun to practice rescues &amp;amp; recoveries + a great introduction to being at ease on the water because - sooner or later - every kayaker discovers that this is an in-water sport.  &lt;br /&gt; Al Reigins, Organizer of Hartford County Rivers &amp;amp; CT Shore Areas Kayaking Group,  Meetup.com  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Time 1:45 - 2 pm Adapting Paddling for Everyone  &lt;br /&gt; Paddling is a exciting sport for everyone, including people with disabilities. Adaptive Paddling is a specialization within the field that allows for changes in equipment + teaching techniques to accommodate most paddlers. Learn how you can get involved with Adaptive Paddling + other opportunities through New Haven's Department of Parks  &lt;br /&gt; Ranger Chris Guerette,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 2:00 - 2:30 pm The Safe Harbor - A Paddlers Source for Boater Safety in the NY/NJ Harbor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 2:30 - 3:00 pm (2 presentations)  Safer Kayaking with the Addition of Float bags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time 3:00 - 3:30 pm Kayak 101 Clinic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time 3:30 - 4:00 pm Using GPS - How it works, ? use it, ? get the most from it (using handheld units)  &lt;br /&gt; Bill Podlisny + Gil Alwang&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296484172000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>YOU CAN PARK IN EAST HARTFORD AND WALK OVER THE BRIDGE AS I AM DOING</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295667602000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Safety &amp; Boat Show "FREE Stop In"  @ Hartford Convention Center Seminar room 14.</name><id>16140265</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296313200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/16140265/</event_url></item>