<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wedeln will have a booth at the upcoming Boston Globe Ski &amp;amp; Snowboard Expo at the Bayside Expo Center, November 15-18, 2007.   The link below will give you more information on the event.  Note there is an event fee of $10 but I believe there is a discount coupon for $3 on the link below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.onthesnow.com/ots/images/bewi/bostonwebpage.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.onthesnow....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is your last chance to meet some Wedeln's locally before the start of the ski season.   There are a few more house memberships available for the season, do contact Julie or Jonathan if you're interested in joining!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in joining the Wedeln race team its $50 for the season and applications are due in by the end of the month...&amp;quot;November&amp;quot;.  (you don't have to be great, no skins required, levels A -expert - through D - beginner, BUT you should enjoy a bit of competition as we want to win!)  One side benefit of race membership is discounted lift tickets at the mountain hosting the race on day of race for YOU and YOUR FRIENDS.  So if the bf/gf isn't racing they can still enjoy time on the same mountain with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>4521773</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542600000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195003187000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet some Wedelns at the Boston Globe Ski &amp; Snowboard Expo at the Bayside Expo </name><id>6736700</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195246800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/6736700/</event_url></item>