<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Market St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02885</zip><lat>41.730804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>40`-247-4200</phone><name>2nd Story Theater</name><city>Warren</city><id>777424</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.281755</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Note:  Meetup details updated 01/21/09 with dinner details.  E-mail was sent to all who RSVPed yes.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Death of a salesman or the front page? Let's go with the second story. Chicago politicians battle with the fourth estate. Some things never change.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.2ndstorytheatre.com/playing.htm" target="_blank"&gt;2nd Story Theater&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this Meet-up we will return to the 2nd Story Theater in Warren, RI to see The Front Page, once a Broadway hit comedy first produced in 1928.  The following plot synopsis is borrowed from Wikipedia:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;The authors' expert plotting and rapid-fire, streetwise dialogue delighted audiences and made their play an instant classic. Hecht and MacArthur strongly influenced many other American comic writers, especially in Hollywood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The play's single set is the dingy Press Room of Chicago's Criminal Courts Building, overlooking the gallows behind the Cook County Jail. Reporters from most of the city's newspapers are passing the time with poker and pungent wisecracks about the news of the day. Soon they'll witness the hanging of Earl Williams, a white man and (supposed) Communist revolutionary convicted of killing a black policeman. Hildy Johnson, cocky star reporter for the Examiner, is late. She appears only to say good-bye; she's quitting to get a respectable job and be married. Suddenly the reporters hear that Earl Williams has escaped from the jail. All but Hildy stampede out for more information. As Hildy tries to decide how to react Williams comes in through the window. He tells Hildy he's no revolutionary and shot the police officer by accident. The reporter realizes this bewildered, harmless little man was railroaded — just to help the crooked mayor and sheriff pick up enough black votes to win re-election. It's the story of a lifetime. Hildy helps Williams hide inside a roll-top desk. Her daunting challenge now is to get Williams out of the building to a safe place for an interview before rival reporters or trigger-happy policemen discover him. The Examiner managing editor, Walter Burns, is a devious tyrant who would do just about anything to keep Hildy with the paper. Nevertheless, Hildy has no choice but to ask for his help.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $25.  Seating is General Admission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Each person is responsible for purchasing their own ticket.&lt;/b&gt;  For reservations, please call the 2nd Story Theater at 401-247-4200.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dinner Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time:  6:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crossroads Pub&lt;br /&gt;133 Market Street&lt;br /&gt;Warren, Rhode Island&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website (including menu): &lt;a href="http://www.crossroadsrestaurantri.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crossroads...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have sent an e-mail including my cell phone number to all who RSVPed &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;.  If you will not make it to the restaurant by 6:00 PM please let me know.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Dinner is optional and is not included in the price of the ticket.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a fairly large parking lot located next to the theater between Market Street and Route 114 in Warren.  A sign for Second Story Theater is on Route 114, although it's somewhat hidden.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be just inside the theater's main entrance at 7:30.  Seating is first-come;first-served, so please be prompt so we can all sit together.   When you RSVP, I will provide my cell phone number in case you're running late or get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that I've set an RSVP limit for January 20th.  This is to allow time for me to get dinner reservations for those that are interested.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Inside main entrance wearing black button-down shirt.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234047788000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229981762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Front Page</name><id>9377004</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232757000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/9377004/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/3/global_6290483.jpeg</photo_url></item>