<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>125.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please join us in welcoming Dave Jacke to Maine for this one-day workshop on Edible Forest Gardens&lt;/b&gt;.  We will examine the vision, theory, design, and practice of creating food-producing ecologies.  Lectures, field observations, and experiential exercises will reveal the nature of ecosystem architecture, social structure, underground economics, and succession. Participants will draw conclusions from these experiences, developing practical design principles, practices, patterns, and processes for garden design and management.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an introductory workshop for gardeners, designers, and students of gardening, ecology, and design.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that you are NOT REGISTERED until we receive your course fee.  Here is a link to the registration form:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/215138/2008%20ForestGarden_Registration%20Form.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dave Jacke&lt;/b&gt; has been a student of ecology and design since the 1970s, and has run his own ecological design firm (Dynamics Ecological Design) since 1984. Dave is an engaging and passionate teacher of ecological design and permaculture, and a meticulous designer. He has consulted on, designed, built, and planted landscapes, homes, farms, and communities in the many parts of the United States, as well as overseas, but mainly in the Northeast. A cofounder of Land Trust at Gap Mountain in Jaffrey, NH, he homesteaded there for a number of years. He holds a B.A. in Environmental Studies from Simon's Rock College (1980) and a M.A. in Landscape Design from the Conway School of Landscape Design (1984).&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave is the author of &lt;i&gt;Edible Forest Gardens&lt;/i&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.edibleforestgardens.com/about_book"&gt;http://www.ediblefore...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;:  $125 for the full-day workshop including lunch, am/pm refreshments, handouts, etc.  You will have an opportunity to purchase the two-volume set of Edible Forest Gardens directly from Dave at a discount.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A hearty vegetarian lunch, heavy on local and organic foods, will be provided.  AM and PM refreshments will also be served.  Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (dish/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin) A dish washing station will be provided.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress for the weather.  We will have access to shelter in case of rain but please come equipped with rain gear, sunscreen, bug repellant, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE&lt;/b&gt;:  Do not bring any nuts or corn products to this workshop due to a serious allergy situation on the part of an attendee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you would like to be put on the waiting list for this workshop, please RSVP 'No' with a comment that you are interested in getting a spot if one should open up.  Thanks!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220096398000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207427063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Edible Forest Gardens with Dave Jacke (Full Day)</name><id>7680686</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218889800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/7680686/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/global_3708325.jpeg</photo_url></item>