<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>161 Brighton Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.353202</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-782-8100</phone><name>Tavern in the Square Allston</name><city>Allston</city><id>1479967</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132668</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;At our monthly brunch, BA members get together to talk, joke, relax, and enjoy the fellowship and French toast. Since so many people in our community are returning to their campus jobs or fall semester classes in September, this is a great opportunity to reconnect or, if you're new, make new friends. Feel free to bring books or other swag for secular show and tell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NB: Over the past year, it's become our regular practice at our Sunday brunches to pass the hat for a charitable cause. This time around, I'm accepting donations to go to the Humanist Community at Harvard, earmarked for the Humanist Learning Lab -- the rough equivalent of a secular Sunday School. I can accept cash or check donations, to be folded into a single donation from me made via PayPal to the HCH. Alternately, you can donate directly, via the PayPal link at &lt;a href="http://harvardhumanist.org/harvard/humanist-learning-lab/" class="linkified"&gt;http://harvardhumanist.org/harvard/humanist-learning-lab/&lt;/a&gt;. If you do donate, please let me know, so we can make a record of the total raised -- we like to make known that though we don't believe in gods, we certainly believe in underwriting good works.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348334776000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346535930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blasphemy Brunch -- esp. for New Members</name><id>80423812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347807600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/80423812/</event_url></item>