<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's visit The De Cordova Museum and Ourdoor Sculpture Park today. There are several ongoing interesting exhibits and temporary ones also. There's a wonderful museum store and also a cafe where they serve light food and cold drinks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE: JUST ADDED BY REQUEST-  this is a great place to picnic!  So, I am adding another pot luck  &lt;br /&gt;                  picnic. f you'd like to participate, please bring a chair/blanket to sit on, a food item to share,&lt;br /&gt;                and your own water/ beverage.  Since it's pot luck, we will manage without a list. I'll provide  &lt;br /&gt;                utensils. plates, trash bags, etc. Let's hope for a nice day!  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sculpture park is an event in itself! At 1pm there is a tour although some may want to do it on their own. If I could pick any place  I really enjoy, the Sculpture Park is one of my favorites! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: $12.00 adult &lt;br /&gt;$ 8.00 senior &lt;br /&gt;www.decordove.org - for info about the museum and it's exhibits&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***NOTE:Make sure to wear comfy shoes as there will be outdoor walking. A meeting point will be designated within the visitor's parking lot. This is an adult only shared event with 3-4other meetup groups.   RAIN OR INTENSE HEAT MAY CANCEL THIS EVENT. PLEASE MAKE SURE TO CHECK FOR UPDATES BEFORE HEADING OUT. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;VERY IMPORTANT : &lt;/b&gt; At an event of this kind, due to the type of venue, members usually break off into smaller groups. If this is a problem for anyone? This may not be the best event for you to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there &lt;br /&gt;_Jo&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will all meetup just outside the museum store. Just off the visitor's lot</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244471965000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237404380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Day At The DeCordova Museum and Outdoor Sculpture Park </name><id>9982187</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244298600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/9982187/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/5/global_4254805.jpeg</photo_url></item>