<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; moderate, 4.5 miles, but steep hills&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/0/e/event_63409422.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quabbin Reservoir&lt;/strong&gt; is an 18-mile long Reservoir with many islands, and home to bald eagles, deer, and more. It's the second-largest (in surface area) man-made body of water in the world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Park, at the southern end, has paved (but hilly) roads with goregous views (including such far-way sights as Mount Monadnock and Hartford, CT).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start at the Visitor's Center in Belchertown, walk over the Winsor Dam, and continue partway through the park to Enfield Overlook. Whether we go further than that, or make a detour to the tower, depends on who attends and how far you feel like walking. (What I just described is 4.5 miles round-trip.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are bathrooms at the Visitor's Center and the tower, and outhouses (with sanitizer) at the overlook and other popular spots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll picnic at Enfield Overlook, or possibly some other location, depending how far we decide to hike. So bring some food and drink...and a camera!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very important park rules:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry-in, carry-out. (Take your trash with you...well, the Visitor's Center and tower have trash bins.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. (From the North, use I-290 to get to Route 9.) Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware and some steep hills, there's not much except scattered houses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Park has 3 entrances, but you can only get to the Visitor's Center via the West Entrance because you can no longer drive over the dams. You want the 3rd on on the right (going westbound). It takes 5 or more minutes to pass all 3 entrances. Please look for a white "Quabbin Reservoir WEST ENTRANCE" sign and a small blue "State Police" sign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google maps is messed up! (It shows the marker further west on Route 9 than it actually is.) (They have a police barracks in the park.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, after the 1st entrance, when there's marsh on both sides of the road, you can see Quabbin Tower on a hill in the distance, diagonally right. When you see the tower, there are 2 entrances to go. The West entrance is 1 hour west of Worcester by Route 9.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live closer to Route 31 or 122 than to I-290, just take the appropriate route South to Route 9, then follow directions "from Worcester" as above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points North and West (or Route 2):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the North (or from Route 2), take Route 202 South. Turn left and go East on Route 9. The West Entrance is the first entrance on your left. There's no landmarks I can think of, and maybe it's a mile or two (not sure). Please look for a white "Quabbin Reservoir WEST ENTRANCE" sign and a blue "State Police" sign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;F.Y.I., if you email me with questions, I'll already have left the house an hour ahead.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320588719000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320311941000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Park @ Quabbin Reservoir</name><id>39775652</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320501600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/39775652/</event_url></item>