<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Guest Talk: Trading Options for Income, by Dan Sheridan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noted options teacher, Dan Sheridan, will show how to trade options to generate consistent monthly income.&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;He will show how he trades options to take advantage of:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current market volatility and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The time decay of options.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Depending on market conditions, Mr. Sheridan will present options spreads like&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Calendars &lt;li&gt;Credit spreads, or &lt;li&gt;Straddles.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dan focuses on risk management; his approach to options trading is distinguished by  rules to adjust trades when the market goes against an options position.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr Sheridan will give a full-day CBOE workshop in Boston the following day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Sheridan is the trading coach for Mary, our member who organized this meeting.  Each week, she participates in a web meeting of her Sheridan mentoring trading group, and she can watch Sheridan's educational webcasts and mentoring sessions with other students.    When Mr. Sheridan reviews Mary's options trades, all his other mentoring students can watch.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: For 22 years, Dan was a market maker in the CBOE pit, where he worked with Jon and Pete Najarian, who appears on CNBC’s Fast Money.  For the past four years, he and his associates have taught individual options traders through Sheridan Options Mentoring.    Dan hosts the Chicago Board Options Exchange’s weekly webcasts, Options Safari, on CBOE.com and regularly gives webcasts for options trading brokers including OptionsXpress and Think or Swim.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Directions to the Meeting from a Walking Perspective&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=4" target="_blank"&gt;MIT Campus Map of Building 4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walk down Amherst Street, cross Ames Street and keep walking straight on the sidewalk. When there is a door on the left, enter it. (To the left should be the entrance to Hayden Library.) Turn to the right and walk until the 2nd stairwell. Go up to the 3rd floor and enter room 370.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243572953000</updated><rating><average>4.26999998093</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>100</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241400042000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guest Talk: Trading Options for Income, by Dan Sheridan</name><id>10329690</id><headcount>101</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243378800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/10329690/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/7/global_8472279.jpeg</photo_url></item>