<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our relationship to food is one of the most important relationships we have&lt;/strong&gt;, especially since we may not always be aware of it. And if our bodies are truly vehicles for the evolution of consciousness, then how we nourish them will have a profound impact in how we live and manifest the best part of ourselves. As such, eating right begins with cultivating some basic nutritional awareness, touching on multiple perspectives, into how awake we are to our relationship to food on a physical, emotional, psychological, and even spiritual level; into how culture influences our eating habits; and into how the socio-economic factors bear down upon our daily nutrition choices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tonight, we will explore nutrition from an integral framework, and explore many of the individual, cultural, and systemic issues that inhibit our freedom and developmental relationship to food.&lt;/strong&gt; We are truly excited to have an illustrious panel of experts, including: dietitian and founder of &lt;a href="http://www.integralfuel.com/"&gt;Integralfuel&lt;/a&gt;, Em Biever; acupuncturist &amp;amp; Chinese herb specialist and founder of &lt;a href="http://flourishboston.com/"&gt;Flourish Boston&lt;/a&gt;, Amy Jo Gengler; and master whole-foods chef &amp;amp; holistic health counselor and founder of &lt;a href="http://kosmic-kitchen.com/"&gt;Kosmic Kitchen&lt;/a&gt;, Katherine Miller!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will lay down some of the groundwork that will help us bear witness to a comprehensive relationship with our eating habits, thereby setting up the conditions for the real work of changing our actual day-to-day nutritional lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bios&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Em Biever&lt;/strong&gt; is a Boston-based dietitian specializing in pediatric, oncology and sports nutrition. She works with little ones and their families at The Floating Hospital for Children at Tufts Medical Center, and serves adults through her private practice, &lt;a href="http://www.integralfuel.com/"&gt;Integralfuel&lt;/a&gt;. Em loves combining nutrition science with her playfulness and passion for food during cooking demonstrations and mindfulness-based nutrition workshops. Em is a triathlete and avid strength trainer. She has been dancing amidst the Integral community for years and is a student of Diane Musho Hamilton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amy Jo Gengler&lt;/strong&gt; is a Licensed Acupuncturist, Chinese Herbalist, Nutritional Counselor, and Fearless Cook. Amy Jo combines her passion for real food nutrition with the profundity of Chinese medical principles to teach her clients how to create the best dietary strategy for particular health issues and fitness goals. She teaches classes on real food nutrition and leads guided tours through local health food stores and farmer's markets. Amy Jo holds a Master's degree in Oriental Medicine from Bastyr University in Seattle, and she is an instructor at the New England School of Acupuncture in Watertown, MA. She currently practices at &lt;a href="http://flourishboston.com/"&gt;Flourish Boston&lt;/a&gt; in Faneuil Hall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Katherine Miller&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a holistic health coach, master whole-foods chef, and the founder of &lt;a href="http://kosmic-kitchen.com/"&gt;Kosmic Kitchen&lt;/a&gt;. At the core of her work, Katherine guides individuals to a new, and liberated, relationship with food, health and healing. Both a practitioner and teacher of yoga and meditation, Katherine is an emerging voice in mapping the relationship between who we are and what we eat. She currently resides in Lee, MA with her husband and two dogs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362263372000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359670730000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Integral Nutrition: A Panel Discussion</name><id>102390092</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362183300000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/102390092/</event_url></item>