<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eddie Speed presents  &lt;br /&gt;"Alternative Financing for Today&amp;rsquo;s Economy"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During a lively overview Eddie Speed will discuss of the ultimate alternative financing tool - seller financing. You see the lucrative opportunities in brokering notes, creating notes on your own properties, and investing in seller-financed notes. He describes how the note busines works and how real estate investors can capitalize on the phenomenal growth in seller financing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the real estate investor, this growing demand for seller financing is creating a unique business opportunity with limitless potential. By becoming a Seller Finance Specialist, you can provide your expertise to realtors and individual property sellers alike&amp;mdash;and earn substantial commissions for your services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re a realtor, you can create seller-financed notes for your clients, to overcome financing short-falls and to speed up transactions. You can also provide fellow realtors with your expertise as a Seller Finance Specialist, and get paid for it. The nation&amp;rsquo;s leading expert in seller financing will show you how.  &lt;br /&gt;During the 90 minute presentation on Thursday February 17th, you will learn:  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;The mortgage meltdown has a silver lining . . . &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real Estate Investors can actually profit from the implosion, turning that silver lining into gold. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The collapse of conventional lending has created a void that's rapidly being filled by seller financing.  &lt;br /&gt;Increasingly, property sellers are carrying loans for their buyers. Increasingly, those notes are available for sale . . . and profit! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By creating real estate notes, investing in them, or simply brokering them, the investor can make substantial money with minimal expense. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The real estate investor requires very little additional knowledge in order to specialize in notes.  &lt;br /&gt;Note consulting and brokering offers flexibility and convenience. Set your own hours. Work from the comfort of your own home. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And the best part is, you can earn 10% commissions from seller-financed notes without spending your own money! &lt;/li&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting  &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM, Thursday, February 17, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doubletree, 400 Soldiers Field Road, Boston, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;free for members; only $25 for nonmembers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;free parking&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298435284000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>96</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295454711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association Monthly Meetup</name><id>kpdhqypdbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297981800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/16330252/</event_url></item>