<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>FREE every WEDNESDAY w/</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>promo T-Shirt</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>NEW Event: &amp;quot;Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; 08/22&lt;br /&gt;What: Comedian &amp;quot;Tres Croswell&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;When: Wednesday, August 22 - gather @ 6:15 PM&lt;br /&gt;Where: &amp;quot;FUNNY BONE&amp;quot; Comedy Club (within Manchester's Buckland Hills Mall)&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $10.00, or FREE with promo Tee-shirt - Must be over 21 - all are welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please read all details below and DO NOT hit reply or write directly.  I will only reserve seats for the first 24 who RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; (by 4:00 on the day of the event) via my FREE &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; MeetUp online calendar reservation system.  Only by doing so, can we hold a seat for you if running late.  (If applicable, please change your &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; by 4:00 on the day of the event to free up that seat for someone else!)  To cut down on emails, I will ONLY post updates, etc. on my MeetUp site and strongly recommend you check it for any changes after 3:00 on the day of the event.  You'll also see many other events that are going on and see who else has RSVP'd for this event, too!  Please go to:  &lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/"&gt;http://livemusic.meet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We gather 6-24 (some regulars, always some newbies, too!) from our combined MeetUp and Single Event &amp;quot;Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; Group at Manchester's new &amp;quot;Funny Bone&amp;quot; stand-up comedy club.  A fun and funny time is had by all!  Rather than pay the $10-20 admission fee each time, almost everybody purchases a promo Tee-shirt (only $15) to gain admission to this and (almost) all WEDNESDAY performances for FREE by showing your promo Tee-shirt at the Box Office - FOREVER (whether attending as part of our irregularly scheduled group, or not).  Such a deal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After RSVP'ing &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;, simply show up and gather in the &amp;quot;Funny Bone&amp;quot; BAR @ 6:15 (AFTER picking up your FREE ticket from the Box Office by buying and/or showing your promo Tee-shirt - telling the Box Office you have a reservation through &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; group).  This will give us a chance to gather, have a drink, chat, and enter as a &amp;quot;group&amp;quot;, thus allowing us to sit together as their policy is &amp;quot;first come, first seated&amp;quot;.  Look for Rob P. (55, 5'11&amp;quot;, 210#, brown hair, glasses).  When the Club doors open at 6:30, THOSE PRESENT will enter together so we can be assigned good tables together and optionally have appetizers, dinner, drinks (no minimum; separate checks have been pre-approved) and get to know each other while waiting for the show to begin at 7:30 (lasting to @ 9:00).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll &amp;quot;try&amp;quot; to hold seats ONLY for those who've RSVP'd &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; via my free MeetUp reservation calendar (see above), as no doubt some may need to run late, but I MAY give away your seat to someone else who arrives on time!  If entering after 6:30, please ask the ticket taker to assign you a seat with, or nearest to, &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All (over 21) are welcome to join us!  Invite your friends and encourage them to join the &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; www.TheSingleEvent.com and &amp;quot;MeetUp&amp;quot; www.MeetUp.com to be invited to these, and MANY MORE fun activities of all sorts!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please MapQuest directions to: 194 Buckland Hills Drive, Manchester, CT 06042.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Funny Bone&amp;quot; is located within the Buckland Hills Mall, on the first floor, between JC Penney and Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, via the external &amp;quot;Blue Turtle&amp;quot; entryway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Funny Regards,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI: I organize this, and many other events, as a volunteer but get inundated with numerous emails and phone calls asking about information clearly posted within my detailed announcements.  As such, I can no longer address you individually, but will post periodic updated information on my free MeetUp calendar.  Please RSVP ASAP, and check the online posting after 3:00 PM on the day of the event for any last-minute changes.  Join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please visit or call the Box Office (860) 432-8600 for info regarding the FREE &amp;quot;Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; Tee-Shirt promo and/or check their web site: www.HartfordFunnyBone.com for upcoming shows, general information, bios, etc. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188861806000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187713219000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Wacky Wednesday":  "Tres Croswell"!</name><id>6218536</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187820900000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6218536/</event_url></item>