<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Times Square</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10036-3906</zip><lat>40.757858</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Times Square</name><city>New York</city><id>5082992</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.987465</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>339.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you'd like to go, put yourself on the waiting list and I will get in touch with you. We have a full van going down on Friday but if you can drive or take the bus or train to New York, you're welcome to join us!   ~Lorenzo!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wild New York!  Spend a beautiful May weekend exploring the outdoors in the City of New York!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Big Apple is not all concrete and steel. There are also wonderful parks and natural areas to explore. We might squeeze in a museum, too, and there will certainly be restaurants to discover, but this will be a weekend to see New York's great outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/b/6/event_84932182.jpeg" width="323" height="250" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ We'll take a &lt;strong&gt;bicycle tour&lt;/strong&gt; of Central Park and other city landmarks. Over the past decade, New York has become a bike-friendly city with greenways and bicycles lanes, making two-wheeled travel a fun and safe experience. We'll rent modern, hybrid bikes, and tour the art, architecture, history, food, and parks of Manhattan. This will be an easy, flat ride of 10 to 20 miles. It's a novel and exciting way to see New York whether you're a first-time visitor or an old hand. We may even ride over the Brooklyn Bridge for another amazing perspective on the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ And we'll hike the new, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/c/3/0/event_84931792.jpeg" width="216" height="291" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Highline Trail - an old elevated railway that runs for 2 miles along the west side of Manhattan. It's newly planted with native trees, flowers, and grasses, punctuated with art installations, and studded with spectacular city and river views throughout. Much of the Highline runs through the Chelsea neighborhood, crammed with art galleries, restaurants, and the famous &lt;strong&gt;Chelsea Market&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ On Saturday evening, we can go to the theater, listen to live music, or just have dinner and walk around the city. (We'll discuss this prior to the trip so we can buy tickets if necessary.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate cost&lt;/strong&gt;: $339 per person - Price includes bicycle tour and two night's shared lodging in a budget hotel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transportation and schedule&lt;/strong&gt;: Depending on the size of the group, we'll either drive together or take a bus, departing mid-afternoon on Friday, to arrive in time for dinner. On Sunday, we'll depart in the afternoon to arrive home by about 8pm. Transportation expenses, whether for gas, tolls, &amp;amp; parking or for bus tickets will be about $50-$60 each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/e/4/event_84933252.jpeg" width="266" height="202" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Reservations: Group size will be limited to 6-8 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To hold a spot, RSVP here and send a check for $160/pp to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;~~ Larry Pilla 21 Baker St. Dover, NH 03820 ~~&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: This is a trip for a small, low-maintenance group. I'll do my best to ensure we have a fun, cohesive bunch of people.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rain Date:&lt;/strong&gt; If it looks like the weather is going to be an issue, we will try and reschedule for the following weekend, but hotel reservations may prevent that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release -&lt;/strong&gt; AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Unless otherwise specified, refunds for timely cancellations will be processed the day after the event.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337097375000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326129866000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wild in the City-Weekend in New York</name><id>47344022</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336759200000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/47344022/</event_url></item>