<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE TRIPLE OR QUADRUPLE RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kitty OSheas is an awesome spot to host another Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party for 160 members on Friday Oct 23, 2009. This is not a Singles Party. Meaning anyone can come which including couples. All are welcome to Party and Socialize.biggrin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kitty OSheas is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100 Website &lt;a href="http://www.kittyoshea.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kittyoshea...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2nd floor can hold 160 people. shock There are 2 Bars upstairs, 4 huge comfy couches, AC, its own DJ area with light machine and dance floor, plus its own bathrooms upstairs so we would truly have out own private party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Music will medium levels in main room upstairs. Music will be tuned very low in the back room so members can have a separate area to chat!&lt;br /&gt;Till about 9PM then the Dancing and music starts, then its gets loud . &lt;br /&gt;There will be 3 Bartender upstairs: 2 at the upfront Bar and 1 in the back .&lt;br /&gt;Some appetizers (Wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) are available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Please find Biagio at the party and please give him $5 to help cover the cost of the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After you get inside there is a Security at the stairs please tell them you are with Social Fun to get in (Even if you are with a different group) . If you say ANY other group they will not let you in. I had a few issues with this last time and Security did not let some people in, because they could not remember to say they were with Social Fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. After 9PM you will have to pay another $10 as a cover charge for the Bar Entrance fee to get in so that $15 total. $10 to bar and $5 to cover the cost to rent the 2nd floor.&lt;br /&gt;3. If you get in before 9PM you ONLY have to pay $5 to Biagio to cover the cost to rent.  Make sure you get there early!&lt;br /&gt;4. Tell Security you are with Social Fun to get in -Even if you are with a different group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 6 Meetup Groups that are invited to come:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Social Fun &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Happy Hour &lt;a href="http://nightlife.meet.."&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;    * Beantown and Beyond 20-40 Singles &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup."&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://euro.meetup.co.."&gt;http://euro.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Night Life Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) and/or Biagio from Social Fun group.  If need to, please call 774 232 0000</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256523622000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255574923000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mix and Mingle at Kitty O'Shea's. Huge Event with Other Great Groups!</name><id>11630937</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256338800000</time><rsvp_limit>46</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/11630937/</event_url></item>