<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>441 Daniel Webster Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03054</zip><lat>42.861343</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Watson Park</name><city>Merrimack</city><id>2487181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.493538</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Wimp Volleyball, Chatting &amp;amp; Cheerleading, BBQ &amp;amp; Swim&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, July, 17th. 3pm. to 7&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NH-Active-Adult-Friends-Meetup-Group/venue/2487181/?eventId=25011201&amp;amp;popup=true"&gt;Watson Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;441 Daniel Webster Highway&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;Merrimack&lt;/span&gt;, 
&lt;span&gt;NH&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;03054&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THIS EVENT IS CANCELED. IF IT IS RAINY, WINDY OR COLD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Obermiller 603-491-1962 ob@tds.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***THIS IS A KID AND DOG FRIENDLY EVENT***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an all day event from 12pm. to 7. Joan Dg7 is Hosting a Picnic Swim at 12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve O. will Hosting a Pot luck BBQ and Volleyball from 3 to 7.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Chatting Cheerleading will start at anytime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for Meetup sign on picnic table or call Joan at 603-305-7114&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a public park and it has access to the Souhegan River, and a beautiful swimming hole and beach. There is a large field for kite flying, playing frisbee or playing Volleyball. Picnic tables and grills.&amp;nbsp; Steve O. will have some charcoal and utensils. But, please bring your own charcoal. If you can?&amp;nbsp; Bring a picnic lunch and something to BBQ or just join us for a swim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring your own food &amp;amp; beverages,&amp;nbsp;chair, sun screen, water shoes, floats and water toys. No glass please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/e/b/event_4002987.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Volleyball:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please join Steve O. and friends at anytime for an afternoon of Chatting and easy exercise, or just come to watch &amp;amp; eat. Wimp Volleyball is a noncompetitive games. Totally for the fun of moving around trying to hit and return the ball. We will be following the rules. But, having fun, getting some exercise, and learning will be more important than winning. In these games, we work on trying to keep the volley going. Rather than trying to end the volley. We do not count the score. We count the laughs. The winners are those who sides hurt from laughing to much. We usually have a larger number attending. So, we will rotate everyone through. If we have enough of those people who must win to play, and follow exactly to the rules. We will have another net set up for them. So, bring your friends and teens, an your drinks to keep cool and hydrated and Bug repellent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CHATTING &amp;amp; CHEERLEADING REQUIRES A LAWN CHAIR, AND THE ABILITY TO CHAT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; This event developed from those people who planned to play Wimp Volleyball with us. But, found themselves either with less energy than they thought they had, or finding themselves chatting more than playing. So, bring your friends and your lawn chair, and come and chat. Oh yes! The Cheerleading is there to just to make the volleyball players feel the chatters are interested.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look 4 the Meetup signs and flag on our tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310933982000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310478221000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wimp Volleyball, Chatting &amp; Cheerleading BBQ. &amp; Swim</name><id>25449041</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310929200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/25449041/</event_url></item>