<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I have been to this &amp;quot;Walk&amp;quot; for a few years now! I really enjoy the people and activities here. It is in Concord, NH which is not that far away from Manchester. Its a great place to meet new people and their dogs. There are a few different walks for those interested &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Here is some useful information&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Concord-Merrimack County SPCA 14th annual “Walk for the Animals” is on Sunday, September 20, 2009 at the Northeast Delta Dental Soccer Field in Concord. Each year this fundamental fundraiser assists over 1700 homeless animals and the money raised gives us the opportunity to offer supportive programs to our community. We do not receive any federal or state funding; we rely strictly on donations. These funds help us operate our programs and the shelter throughout the year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Take Steps to Help Pets!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take part and put your best foot or paw forward!  Bring your friend!  Bring your family!  Bring your dog!  Plan for a day of fun filled activities.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop by and shop from local Pet Vendors and visit Breed Rescue Groups that will be on site to offer information.  &lt;br /&gt;Special Concord-Merrimack County SPCA retail items will also be available to purchase on the day of the event.  &lt;br /&gt;You can participate in our special “All Pet Photo” contest by bringing a picture of your beloved pet.  &lt;br /&gt;There are also contests for your canine to participate in-a special, “Best Costume” will be part of these contests, so be sure to pack your canines costume.  &lt;br /&gt;A special draw will be our Kids Korner, which will host several games, activities, a coloring contest and a Bouncy House.  &lt;br /&gt;A low cost microchip clinic ($20 per dog) to help keep you and your canine companion from being separated if they become lost.  &lt;br /&gt;Demonstrations include Ragtime Farm Herding Demonstration. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local Radio Stations will be on site too!&lt;br /&gt;                                                       The day is sure great fun for the entire family!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk entails a 1 or 3 mile walk on Sunday, September 21, 2008 to benefit the animals of the Concord-Merrimack County SPCA.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1-Mile Map                           3-Mile Map                      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Location&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northeast Delta Dental Soccer Field&lt;br /&gt;1 Delta Drive&lt;br /&gt;Concord, NH  03301&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Need directions?  Map to Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Schedule&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration begins at 10:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;Blessing of the Animals 10:45 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;Walk Kicks Off 11:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;Festivities begin at 12:00 &lt;br /&gt;Event ends at 3:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be available the day of the event with donations requested.  &lt;br /&gt;Demonstrations will be performed throughout the day.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Schedule will be available early September.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entry Fee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5.00 (waived with $50 in pledges)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I hope to see you there!!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You can meet Jamie and Comet at the Registration Table!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jamie</member_name><member_id>8350267</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254575168000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243648191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk for the Animals 2009</name><id>10527115</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253455200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/10527115/</event_url></item>