<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet outside Bertucci's at 7:00. This is near the Kenmore T station. Free parking can be found on Beacon St on the overpass just east of Comm ave. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will walk by the Frog Pond and have a look at people ice skating there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Commonwealth Avenue Mall &lt;br /&gt;Description&lt;br /&gt;Designed in a manner similar to Georges-Eugène Haussmann's Paris boulevards, Commonwealth Avenue is a parkway divided at center by a wide grassy mall. This greenway, called Commonwealth Avenue Mall, is punctuated with statuary and memorials, and forms the narrowest &amp;quot;link&amp;quot; in the Emerald Necklace. It connects the Public Garden to the Fens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where Commonwealth Avenue reaches Kenmore Square, the MBTA Green Line &amp;quot;B&amp;quot; Branch rises above ground and dominates the center of the roadway through the campus of Boston University and the neighborhoods of Allston and Brighton to the city of Newton near Boston College. The section in Newton is made up of two roadways separated by a grassy median lined with trees. The south side of the roadway contains the main, two-lane east-west roadway, with a one-way, westbound &amp;quot;carriage road&amp;quot; providing local access on the north side of the median.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;History&lt;br /&gt;The Commonwealth Avenue Mall was designed by Arthur Delevan Gilman.[1] Frederick Law Olmsted designed the Newton portion of Commonwealth Ave and included the parkway as part of the Emerald Necklace park system. The first statue on the Commonwealth Avenue Mall was erected in 1865 at Arlington Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Newton end of the roadway was constructed in 1895 with a line of the Middlesex and Boston Street Railway in the median. Train service was cut back to its present terminus at the Boston border in 1930 and buses last ran on Commonwealth Avenue in 1976. An amusement park and ballroom known as Norumbega Park was built at the end of the line on the Charles River in 1897 to increase streetcar patronage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Statuary&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Statue of Samuel Eliot Morison on the mall. Starting at the Public Garden, the following statues can be seen on the mall:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Hamilton, co-author of the Federalist Papers. &lt;br /&gt;John Glover, Revolutionary War soldier. &lt;br /&gt;Patrick Andrew Collins, former mayor of Boston. &lt;br /&gt;The Vendome Memorial, which honors nine firefighters killed in a fire at the adjacent Hotel Vendome in 1972. &lt;br /&gt;William Lloyd Garrison, abolitionist and journalist. &lt;br /&gt;Samuel Eliot Morison, naval historian and writer. &lt;br /&gt;The Boston Women's Memorial, with statues of Abigail Adams, Lucy Stone, and Phillis Wheatley. &lt;br /&gt;Domingo Sarmiento, former president of Argentina. &lt;br /&gt;Leif Ericson, first European discoverer of Newfoundland. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In popular culture:&lt;br /&gt;Black Francis wrote the Pixies song &amp;quot;Tame&amp;quot; about female students he saw on Commonwealth Avenue.[4]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234574420000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234136222000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Commonwealth Avenue Mall, Public Gardens and Boston Commons walk</name><id>9701449</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234396800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9701449/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/9/4/global_6019428.jpeg</photo_url></item>