<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have you developed automatic negative thought patterns?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you want to put hold on debilitating chatter in your brain?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have you tried to change your thought patterns by thinking positively, but could not change how you feel? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you want to know how to free yourself from an ongoing fear, anxiety or panic?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you said yes to any of these questions, come and learn EDR (Energetic Displacement Reintegration), a new and proven self-help system to stop anxiety and heal trauma.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need this information now more then ever and here is why - unfortunately medical science thinks that anxiety, panic and PTSD are a disorder and a decease of the brain!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am on a research committee of the Association of Energy Psychology.&lt;br /&gt;The latest news is that Minnesota scientists believe they have found a long-sought PTSD fingerprint by measuring electromagnetic fields in the brain.  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This shows that PTSD is a brain disease,&amp;quot; says Dr. Apostolos Georgopoulos, who led the research along with Brian Engdahl and a team from the Brain Sciences Center at the Minneapolis VA Medical Center and University of Minnesota. &amp;quot;There have been questions that this is a made-up disorder and isn't a true brain disease, but it is.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read more: &lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.time.com/time/nation/article/0,8599,1956315,00.html#ixzz0dvv2zQWw" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.time.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a truly scary conclusion and a move in a wrong direction. The argument for brain disease is of little benefit, and more harm, if you want to actually achieve energetic integration. &lt;br /&gt;What scientists see as a proof of a disease, is really a result of an energetic structural misalignment.  I discovered this long before Energy Psychology arose as a branch of knowledge and a movement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch more on &lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/TheAvitar3712#p/a/u/0/aRFbiCtJWgE" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our bodies are complex living systems and to enter into relationships with them we need to include and embrace it all - culture, spirituality, laws, medical science and technology.  It is time to re-discover that there is a mystery to energy systems, something not completely revealed, forms and live energies which are nearly imperceptible. And these system already have its norms, its rules and laws. They actually have scientific knowledge associated with them. Armed with this knowing we can restore the  electromagnetic field in the brain and the energy flow within.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Without making it a &amp;quot;Decease of a Brain&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come to heal and to rebalance the electromagnetic field of your brain.  You will not find this information anywhere else!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get techniques and tips to avoid energy loss and waste on therapies that do not work. And much, much more. Those who know me know that I am on a mission to alleviate unnecessary suffering and lead people to freedom from fear and trauma.  As long this information is not widely available there will continue to thrive medical treatments, which operate as a consequence of our ignorance of why and how our energy systems work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So join us for healing and support at the next meetup this Thursday, February 4.  Bring a friend.&lt;br /&gt;See you there,&lt;br /&gt;Warmly Yuliya&lt;br /&gt;a&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265501091000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264811657000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gain Control of Your life! Bring Your Brain into Balance with EDR </name><id>12463110</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265328000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/12463110/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/5/global_12859285.jpeg</photo_url></item>