<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>115 Empire St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821735</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-861-9190</phone><name>AS220 </name><city>Providence</city><id>483693</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join P-Collective member and renowned photographer Scott Indermaur and fellow artist, John Jacobson for an Artist Talk and film screening of - &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;REVEALED:Portraits from Beneath One's Surface.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.siphotography.com/blog/photography-news/as220-exhibit-and-artist-talk" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.siphotography.com/blog/photography-news/as220-exhibit-and-artist-talk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Info about the show from Scott below: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 My exhibit is a new body of work for me and touches on REVEALED and several other projects I have explored the past few years. The primary exhibit is based around my Blocked Chakra series I recently completed. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I have also set aside space with journal entries that shares the "behind-the-scenes" thought and emotional process of creating these projects. It's a very personal exhibit. The artist statement: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Exploring the inner depth of self - mine and yours &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Over the course of several years, I've taken a journey within – helping me discover more of who I am personally and creatively. I've created several projects exploring the depths of the inner self, both mine and yours. As these projects were created, I realized I could capture and project emotion and spirituality through photography. This process changed who I am, and along the way, changed my subjects and others as well. This series of creative photography displays the depth and breadth of our own spirituality, emotional journey, and along with the paradoxical truth that we are all connected. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The exhibit is at the Main Gallery for As220 at 115 Empire St, Providence, RI. This is a joint exhibit with artist John Jacobson. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Exhibit is from Jan. 5-26th... &lt;br /&gt;

 Artist talk is Thursday Jan. 24th @ 5:30pm and will include the screening of my REVEALED:Portraits from Beneath One's Surface film after the talk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is posted as an FYI - I will probably not make this one - again, but wanted you all to know about it. Please RSVP if you want to go, so others can find you!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359141967000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358914826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>P-Collective FYI - Artist Talk at AS220 - Photographer Scott Indermaur!</name><id>100950422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359066600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/100950422/</event_url></item>