<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>While I am a lifelong vegetarian who chooses to avoid eating meat primarily for ethical reasons, I have never been an in-your-face vegetarian and overtly political about it.  It’s not that I am apolitical; on the contrary I have strong political views about many issues.  However, while I personally see vegetarianism and animal protection as profoundly important moral issues I have, nonetheless, always been struck by the fact that there have been profoundly moral and intelligent human beings who choose not to be vegetarian.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What’s my point?  Am I trying to state a position that will alienate me from both my fellow vegetarians and meat eaters all in one fell swoop?!   Well, at least that is not my intention.  However, I am interested in a collective heart-to-heart discussion of this topic amongst folks who take this subject seriously even if they disagree. For example, some people believe that meat eating is natural for human beings and that animals cannot experience suffering like we do.  That poses a fair question and we should discuss it.  I for one have never bought into the statement by Ingrid Newkirk (of PETA) that  “A rat is a pig is a dog is a boy.”  The illogicality of that statement does not help the animal rights movement or the broader vegetarian cause.  What Newkirk, I think, was trying to say is that all animals are alive and feel pain and therefore on that moral  grounding we are equals.  Well, all animals are not equal but it does seem to me that all sentient creatures, especially ones than can experience pain, deserve to be treated with acts of compassion and kindness by human beings that claim a higher consciousness.  And isn’t the potential for higher consciousness and of the compassion of humankind the whole point?  This higher potential is the reason why a rat is not a pig is not a dog and is not a human.  We have the conscious potential to treat animals in a manner different than how they might treat us even though the fact is, as Schopenhauer says, human consciousness--far from being elevated--has been frequently debased by the outrageous &amp;quot;illusion that our treatment of them has no moral significance.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You see, I would like this discussion to escape the dogmatisms and ideological positions of the two sides and to reason from the attitude of an ethics whose foundation is ultimately nothing less than the essence of love and compassion made concrete by mindful intentionality and action.   The meat eaters may not become vegetarians after this discussion, and the vegetarians are not likely to go running for a Big Mack (God help us!) but in this discussion we might just edge closer to an understanding that goes beyond the mere advancement of a particular agenda. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RULES OF ORDER: 1) Menu selections: Gastronomic diversity allowed,  2) Conduct: A show of mutual respect is mandatory. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture. (Oh, I'm the 'Arthur' to the left)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280057444000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275534566000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>On the Eating of Meat</name><id>13680510</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279926000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/13680510/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/2/global_15473858.jpeg</photo_url></item>