<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6B, 191 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389534</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center for Arabic Culture</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1591495</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106071</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Home: Your War&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Friday, April 26 @ 7pm&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Suggested Donation: $5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please sign up only if you seriously plan on attending - thank you&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MY HOME – YOUR WAR offers an extraordinary look at the effect of the Iraq war through the eyes of an ordinary Iraqi woman. Shot in Baghdad over three years that span the time before, during and after the invasion of Iraq, this profoundly moving film brings a perspective that – until now – has rarely been available to U.S. audiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This film combines insightful interviews with Layla Hassan and her family, vibrant scenes of Baghdad and intimate footage shot by Layla herself to paint a compelling picture of how the war has affected average Iraqis. As Islamic fundamentalism takes hold in the chaos of Baghdad, her shy teenage son turns to militancy, her once-progressive sister dons the veil, and whatever freedom Layla once had under Saddam Hussein’s secular rule is steadily being eroded. While facts about the Iraq war garner much U.S. media attention, My Home – Your War is a deeply compelling account of something seldom discussed: how the Iraq war has created a situation where the rise of fundamentalism is putting women’s rights increasingly at risk.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hildreth </member_name><member_id>10532981</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367028254000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Arabic Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonArabic</urlname><id>1143990</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Area Arabic Language Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359407774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Movie Night at CAC</name><id>dtxdhfyrgbjc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367016300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonArabic/events/101842992/</event_url></item>