<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/5/a/event_60799802.jpeg" width="620" height="337" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Connors Farm Corn Maze Singles Night runs 6 to 11 PM on Saturday, October 6, 2012&lt;strong&gt;.  Dress in layers + boot/sneaker as it might get cold.&lt;/strong&gt; No rain for Saturday so far! &lt;strong&gt;Bring a flashlight!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First, I am sorry that the instructions have to be this long for this event, but we have so much going on this night I need EVERY MEMBER to read this TWICE to make sure they understand ok?..Even print this out beforehand so you have it to guide you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;This event is a go. Looks like no rain for most of the evening. There is a 20% chance it might sprinkle from 4-6pm so don't let that stop you ok?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was just told by Matt from Conner Farm he will be directing people for this event to reduce wait times in lines, They have hired extra staff too to help this run better, So lets try to stick to my schedule as best we can, working with the lead I listed in the event since it will be good too to go around this in a smaller group size! Please realize that the order in which we do events might change based on Matt’s direction Oh and I can' t use my bullhorn this time sorry. OK so this is going to be fun, we will break up into smaller groups so just go with the flow ok. Then in the end we can all regroup at the bonfire later in the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is going to be an &lt;strong&gt;Amazingly Fun Event&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;170+ members&lt;/strong&gt; coming from 3 Meetups groups, but with 170+ members going I need help. I &lt;strong&gt;need 11 leaders&lt;/strong&gt; to lead&lt;/span&gt; 12-15 members in your group --Groups to be  set at the time of your arrival &lt;strong&gt;so DO NOT be late&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;It is public so don’t be surprised if there are &lt;strong&gt;over 200 people&lt;/strong&gt; at this event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Admission is normally $20, &lt;strong&gt;but tell them you are with Social Fun Meetup to get the $15 discount&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;group rate&lt;/strong&gt;. This includes  a Hayride, the big 2012 Corn MAZE, a Haunted Cornfield which is more interactive and a bit scary and a large bonfire. The&lt;/span&gt; bonfire  part includes music, Hot + Cold Apple Cider, Apple Cider Donuts (which are oh so yummy) and fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;The PLAN:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;PLEASE arrive on time or EARLY like 5:10PM &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;if you can&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;….as you’ll miss intros and forming of the small groups. Parking at the farm stand and on the side of the road. It will be busy and crazy so the earlier you come the better it will be for you. The corn mazes are on one side of the street and the Farm Stands, Hay Ride and Bond fire&lt;/span&gt; is on the other side of the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;5:15PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;get there, park, buy your ticket at the farm stand. Then meet Biagio at the farm stand entrance near where you bought your ticket and meet the rest of the group and listen for important instructions from Biagio and the 11 other leaders&lt;/span&gt; there.. Socialize and meet your fellow members. Do not be shy now speak up and say HI!...Yes that include &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;New Members…so&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; speak up now and say &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Hi I am NEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Take a Hayride with your fellow members!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;They last about &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;15 to 20 minutes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;each.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;staggered the Hayride start times&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to make this event run smother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Staring at 5:15PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;I’m going to gather the &lt;strong&gt;first 50 members&lt;/strong&gt; to arrive and pay onto full Hay ride cart so you all can leave at &lt;strong&gt;5:30PM&lt;/strong&gt; sharp!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;next 50&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; will &lt;strong&gt;leaves at 5:45PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;last 50&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;leaves at 5:55PM&lt;/strong&gt;. -If you arrive late after 5:45PM that means you missed the hay ride sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;One you are done with the hayride&lt;/span&gt; head  to the road,  &lt;strong&gt;cross the street to the Haunted Maze&lt;/strong&gt; (on the right) and get in line for it.  &lt;strong&gt;Wait&lt;/strong&gt; time should be &lt;strong&gt;5 minute to 25 minutes&lt;/strong&gt; for this so as you wait say hi to other Meetup members in line and introduce yourself to strangers and tell them about our fun group if they ask. Be nice ok?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;6:15PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Cross the street and walk to the entrance of the Haunted Cornfield (which is on the right). Form groups of 5 or less no exceptions this is hard rule to enjoy this part. Yes we are starting early before it gets too dark so we do NOT have to wait an hour in line!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:30 to 8:00PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Re-gather in y&lt;/span&gt;our group to enter the big Corn Maze  ---OK at this point some members are tired want to skip this and go to the Bond fire and chill out which is cool so tell your leader you are doing OK?.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;·&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Now the &lt;strong&gt;Big corn Maze is tough and normal takes  30 minute to an hour&lt;/strong&gt;, but it is really fun and worth it in my mind &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;so try to finish this without cheating&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;!..lol..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;·&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Yes we all can just walk through a corn maze I know and so you don’t get worried as you really &lt;strong&gt;get lost in there since that IS half the fun&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;·&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;This is also the point where members leave you group and join others group so this is ok too as it &lt;strong&gt;cool to Mix N Mingle in the  corn maze&lt;/strong&gt;….wink wink!..lol..Trust me it way way too funny to experience  what happen in the big maze!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;·&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;One you get into the big maze the leaders duties are over. Let other take lead as the explore the big maze. &lt;strong&gt;Yes every member MUST take turns leading the group in the Maze!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;After finishing the BIG Maze:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;It is up to each member to &lt;strong&gt;carefully cross the street at night&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; Normally there is a cross guard person or cop there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Now is the time &lt;strong&gt;to go to your car and get an booze and cup you brought for the bonfire&lt;/strong&gt;..Just be respectful and please keep it cover in a bag etc and don’t get drunk and act like an ass in public cuz I’ll ask you to leave ok?!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Go to the &lt;strong&gt;bonfire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; behind the farm stand way in the back by the pond near where you go onto the Hayride.  &lt;strong&gt;Eat some cider donuts, drink some cider&lt;/strong&gt;. I’ll have a jug for rum spiked cider and  Red and White wines 5 liters each  (that is like 14 bottles of wine)  and a lot of cups etc. Of course this will cost me some money so I hope the members who drink any of the supplies I bring will slip me $5 for this..cool?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For the members who DO NOt drink any of the supplies I bring&lt;/span&gt; I’d still like $1 for the 10 pus hours I spent setting this up. The printouts I had to print up, the bull horn  and batteries  I had to but etc which still cost me ### OK cool?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Expect delays and extra wait times&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;as with this large of a MEETUP group going there are sure to be problems&lt;/span&gt; and delays so please bear with us as we'll do our best to accommodate you all to maximize your fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;8:30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to 9:00PM &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Re-gather at Bond Fire behind the farm stand&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; back by the pond near where you go onto the Hayride.  &lt;strong&gt;Eat some cider donuts, drink some cider&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;. Start socializing, there will be people not from Meetup so be sure to be nice and welcoming to them too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;YOU can &lt;strong&gt;bring some booze&lt;/strong&gt; since the owner is OK since it was 90% just MEETUP members the last time, but not in the open keep the booze covered / out of sight for the most part and do NOT let anyone under age drink it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll have &lt;strong&gt;a jug for rum spiked cider and  Red and White wines 5 liters each&lt;/strong&gt;  (that is like 14 bottles of wine)  and a lot of cups etc. Of course this will cost me some money so I hope the &lt;strong&gt;members  who drink will slip me  $5 for this..cool? ..&lt;/strong&gt;Members who do not wish to drink I’d still like $1 to cover the 10 plus hours I spent setting this up.. The printouts, signs,  I have to print, the bull horn  and batteries  I had to buy etc which still cost me money.. OK cool? &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Remember please clean up after yourself too, throw out your bottle and cans away. Be nice!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;PLEASE NOTE: I am also collecting &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;an extra $1 from everyone&lt;/span&gt; at this event to cover setting up this event. Also, note it would of cost you $20 instead of $15 if I did not set up this discount so you are all still saving $4 a person!!..... Thanks!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Expect delays and extra wait times&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;as with this large of a MEEYIP group going there are sure to be problems&lt;/span&gt; and delay so please bear with us as we do our best to accommodate you all to maximize your fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;For more information, visit &lt;a href="http://www.connorsfarm.com/maze.htm"&gt;http://www.connorsfarm.com/maze.htm&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader duties will include (Member need to read this too) :&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Relaying important &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;information&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and telling your group to go to the bathroom now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;2.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Keeping track of &lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Keeping your group&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;gathered&lt;/strong&gt; on the  Hayride, then getting your entire group to the Haunted Maze across the street and &lt;strong&gt;broken down into teams  of 5-6 people&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Re-gather your teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;back into a group again at the end of Haunted Maze --Remember&lt;/span&gt; Teams  go in 2 minutes  apart and you all come out 2 minutes apart so wait for your teams please at the end!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;5.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Take your group into the full big Corn Maze&lt;/span&gt; ---OK at this point members want to skip this and go to the Bond fire and chill out which is cool so tell your leader you are doing so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;a.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Now the &lt;strong&gt;Big corn Maze is tough and normal takes  30 minute to an hour&lt;/strong&gt;, but it is really fun and worth it in my mind &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;so try to finish this without cheating&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;!..lol..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;b.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Yes we all can just walk through a corn maze I know and so you don’t get worried as you really &lt;strong&gt;get lost in there since that IS half the fun&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;c.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;This is also the point where members leave you group and join others group so this is ok too as it &lt;strong&gt;cool to Mix N Mingle in the  corn maze&lt;/strong&gt;….wink wink!..lol..Trust me it way way too funny to experience  what happen in the big maze!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;d.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;One you get into the big maze your duties are over. Let other take lead as the explore the big maze.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Suggested Meetup leaders -Members please have a leaders in mind for when you get here!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 1 =Biagio Occhino&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 2 = Joana&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 3 = Joe Petringa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 4 = Kathy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 5 =Liam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 6 =Doug&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 7 =Dona R.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 8 = Carol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 9 = Chelsea for the Young Bostonians #1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 10 = Greg for the Young Bostonians #2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leader 11 =&lt;/span&gt; Mary  for the Greater Boston Divorced/Separated  #1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Back-up leaders if we need more: Joan, Tom, Dave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Also &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;try to carpool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; so everyone can park nearby. Remember 150 members, 1 per car = 150 cars, 2 per car – 75 cars  3 = 5- cars etc. Understand  the math. Lol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please please &lt;strong&gt;triple check you can still make this event&lt;/strong&gt; and make sure you &lt;strong&gt;leave extra time to get here&lt;/strong&gt; by car as there might be some &lt;strong&gt;additional traffic&lt;/strong&gt; due to the Topsfield Fair nearby, also find alternative routes to get there to get around that traffic so you do not get stuff. Based on where you are coming from.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Biagio at the farm stand entrance to buy your ticket and meet the rest of the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Biagio</member_name><member_id>3847345</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tammy</member_name><member_id>5354078</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349910392000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>27</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>136</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345753963000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Night at Connors Farm Corn Maze - Couples are welcome to come too!</name><id>79068702</id><headcount>125</headcount><duration>20700000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349558100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/79068702/</event_url></item>