<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/a/8/event_144748072.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Before signing up for this Meetup please read the entire write up. By signing up for this event you agree to the terms of the liability waiver below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well it looks as though we are finally going to get some warmer temps this week. Why not blow the dust and cobwebs off the bike and join me for a ride down the East Bay Bike Path. We will head South from Shaw's parking lot to Bristol. We will take a spin through Colt State Park and then head back. Sunset is 7:20ish. It would be a good idea to bring a head lamp if you don't have a light on your bike. This is my 1st ride this season. That being said we will ride at average speed of 13 mph overall. The entire ride should be about 15- 16 miles.Make sure you have a wind layer for when temps start to cool down. Everyone  really sholuld be carrying a spare tube or patch kit and a pump..YOU NEVER KNOW!  You may want a light pair of gloves as well. Bring water and snacks.  Hope to see you Wednsday. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will meet on the path at the far side of the lot near Citizens Bank.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365641009000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365374405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dust off your bikes and let's go for ride.</name><id>113188502</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365627600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/113188502/</event_url></item>