<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Athol Richmond Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01368</zip><lat>42.639093</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-249-9150</phone><name>Tully Lake</name><city>Royalston</city><id>788550</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.224652</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Tully Lake Recreation Area 2 Athol-Richmond Rd., Royalston, MA 978-249-9150 Paddle among dozens of islands on this spectacular lake. To the northeast follow the narrow Tully River to Long Pond for excellent wildlife viewing. Cartop boat access also available on Doane Hill Rd. Description: Tully Lake Recreation Area protects about four miles of the Tully River, including Long Pond, where the river widens, and the 200-acre Tully Lake, created by a flood-control dam. The wetlands and the forest support a wide variety of flora and fauna, lists of which are available online. The land and the lake offer numerous recreational opportunities, including camping, picnicking, boating, fishing, and hiking. A one-mile interpretive trail introduces visitors to both natural and cultural history; another trail loops around the lake and connects to scenic vistas and waterfalls. Part of this loop constitutes one leg of the Tully Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: From Rte. 2 take Exit 17 (Rte. 32N) and follow Rte 32 signs closely for about 6 miles to entrance, just past dam, on right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP for hiking or kayaking then we can all get together for a picnic around 1:30pm.
 &lt;br /&gt; Kayaks and canoes are available for rent at the campground and can be launched right there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you could bring any of the following it would be greatly appreciated.....a favorite dish, salad, jug of juice, desert, crackers and cheese, a few beers, some wine, something to cook on the grill(especially appreciated). I will bring the charcoals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Anyone have a volley ball, frisbees, horseshoes, table cloths for tables, board games or cards to share?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;We can go green by bringing our own plates, utensils, napkins, etc.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any of you guys can help out with sending invitations to women on a dating site, I'd be grateful. I have sent out a few invitations to men on Match. Also ladies, please feel free to send out invitations to men. Let's make this a great singles event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain date: Sunday, August 21, 2011, 9:45am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Royalston Falls Hike is a separate hike also scheduled on the same morning in the same area. Anyone choosing to go to the Royalston Falls hike is also welcome to the Singles picnic at 1:30pm but please RSVP to say that you are coming to the picnic only. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheryl&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356215576000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311897612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Hike or Kayak/ Picnic at Tully Lake</name><id>27428211</id><headcount>34</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313847900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/27428211/</event_url></item>