<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Soldiers Field Rd &amp; Everett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.364819</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Artesani Park along Charles River</name><city>Brighton</city><id>723026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.135521</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the river upstream in the afternoon.....then take a dinner break and enjoy the Boston area of the Charles with the backlight of the city. This is a night time paddle down the Charles River from Artesani Park to the Esplenade aka Hatch Shell and back to enjoy the city lights of Boston from the river at night. This is a very enjoyable trip of about 9-10 miles (slow pace) and a great photo opportunity. The route will take us from Artesani Park, down along the right bank of the river to the Esplanade. We'll travel the inner route pass the Hatch shell stop and watch a bit of the concert. Then back along the same route. &lt;strong&gt;7:00 - 9:30 pm WODS Concert - KC and the Sunshine Ban.&lt;/strong&gt; We will paddle in two groups (if there are 20 paddlers) Each paddler will have a partner that they must stay within sight of. The groups must absolutely stay together....NO stragglers or Olympic speed paddlers please. Required equipment: Kayak with bulkheads or float bags PFD (lifejacket) that must be worn paddle float pump &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.boat-ed.com/ma/handbook/lights.htm"&gt;http://www.boat-ed.com/ma/handbook/lights.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Massachusetts law requires: If less than 23.0 feet long, these vessels should: If practical, exhibit the same lights as required for unpowered vessels less than 65.6 feet in length. If not practical, have on hand at least one lantern or flashlight shining a white light as in Figure 3. So in addition to the above equipment you must have: a waterproof headlamp or flashlight and two (2) chemlight sticks of any color (one of these will tie to the bow of your boat, the other to the shoulder of your PFD. that way, in the event of a capsize, we can see the boat and the person on the water) Also Suggested: Bugspray VHF Radio Camera!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lots of cars with Kayaks racks on them</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314036883000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308916593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charles River Night Paddle</name><id>23358921</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313874000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/23358921/</event_url></item>