<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>911 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.845997</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-871-9300</phone><name>New England Pizza Restaurant</name><city>Vernon Rockville</city><id>318964</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.454155</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Third Tolland County CT Ron Paul meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion / agenda items:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign Party - A portion of this meetup will be needed to outline plans for sign-slogans / ideas / sizes for the sign party this Saturday. We have acquired a large quantity of the perfect banner material at a reasonable price which is scheduled to arrive from Fed Ex this Friday. This allows us to make not only a large amount of various-size signs, but also an 18 x 30 ft banner which will adorn a hot-air balloon at this years Plainville Balloon Festival. If we can make this happen will can easily generate some local press, a definite goal for this group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upcoming events - Another timely topic that needs pinning down. Which are most worth attending and in what capacity? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iowa - Those who reached out by telephone or mail should share their experiences so we can do it even better next time around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;National&amp;quot; meetup organization? - Working with other local RP meetup groups was on the agenda at our last meeting, and since then there has been discussion on larger RP forums about a &amp;quot;national&amp;quot; group to organize the state groups. The opinions seem split on this idea and we need find out how our group members feel about these options.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fund raising - It's going to need to happen fast if we want to make some of these events. I know we can count on donations from group members. If we can make the sign-party successful we can also raise money quickly by selling extras on eBay. It helps Paul supporters get the signs they need to spread the message where they are, and it helps us spread the message here. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;August 18th and 19th in N.H. - Depending on how many are going we may be able to coordinate travel to these events. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Earl L.</member_name><member_id>4314674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187836552000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185648726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tolland County CT August Ron Paul meetup</name><id>6090612</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186700400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/6090612/</event_url></item>