<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For this meetup we'll just be meeting at night at Harbor Park. The event the day before I'm sure will have drained us some. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be gathering around 8pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey guys!!  Summer is officially here and that means fun is most definitely authorized.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meet-up is going to be a regularly scheduled one every Sunday. As all socialites in CT know there is a certain favorite beach routine that occurs in the summers, and here it is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 12 noon we'll be meeting up in Old Lyme at Sound View beach, we'll gather at the flagpole at the center entrance off the main road.   We'll be basking in the sun, playing in the water, and talking away till 3 - 4pm.  At that time on the beach there is a bar called Pavilion.  They usually have a live band and we'll head inside to mingle.  We'll hang out till about 5 - 6 pm and then head home to change or not and proceed to our next location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 8pm we'll be at Harbor Park in Middletown.  Don' be surprised if a lot of the people you met at the beach end up here to, it a normal thing.  The unofficial daylong party.  We'll be outside listening to the band or inside dancing to the latest top 40's. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If on a Sunday it rains than the Day beach portion will be cancelled and we'll just meet up at night at Harbor Park.  Check the site for changes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP for these events so we don't miss you when gathering up at the beach or at Harbor Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions just send me an email or call me: 203-599-1120.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Roshi ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John </member_name><member_id>6728192</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310132409000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276064393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fun in the Sun &amp; Dance into the Night</name><id>lsrtnynkbhc</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280102400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/13746090/</event_url></item>