<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>675 Commonwealth Avenue </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.350052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston University, College of Arts and Sciences, Stone Building, Room B50</name><city>Boston</city><id>12783812</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Boston University's one and only spoken word poetry group is hosting a &lt;br /&gt;

 FREE show on Saturday April 27th featuring the unique poetry stylings &lt;br /&gt;

 of JON SANDS! Jon is based out of NYC, has competed in numerous &lt;br /&gt;

 National Poetry Slam Competitions, teaches and facilitates writing &lt;br /&gt;

 workshops with several different universities and organizations and is &lt;br /&gt;

 one of the most lovable poets in the game. Don't miss your chance to &lt;br /&gt;

 have your mind blown and your heart broken in the best way &lt;br /&gt;

 possible....and as always, the Speak For Yourself poets will &lt;br /&gt;

 openup the show with a set of their own!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FULL BIO: &lt;br /&gt;

 Jon Sands is a Brooklyn based author known for electrifying readings. &lt;br /&gt;

 He wrote, The New Clean (2011, Write Bloody Publishing), and starred &lt;br /&gt;

 in the award winning web-series “Verse: A Murder Mystery” from &lt;br /&gt;

 Rattapallax Films. He is an adjunct with the City University of New &lt;br /&gt;

 York, a Youth Mentor with Urban Word-NYC and heads two separate &lt;br /&gt;

 writing programs for Bailey House in Harlem (an HIV/AIDS service &lt;br /&gt;

 center). His work is published or forthcoming in Rattle, The Millions, &lt;br /&gt;

 Word Riot, Muzzle, Union Station, The Rattling Wall from PEN Center &lt;br /&gt;

 USA, and other cool places. He is a member of the groundbreaking live &lt;br /&gt;

 literature tours, “The Whirlwind Company” and “The SpillJoy Ensemble,” &lt;br /&gt;

 has represented NYC numerous times at the National Poetry Slam, and &lt;br /&gt;

 tours extensively, both nationally and internationally. Say yes to &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.jonsands.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.jonsands.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 BLURB: &lt;br /&gt;

 "With the groundbreaking and deftly crafted "The New Clean," Jon Sands &lt;br /&gt;

 has brashly shifted the landscape, changing what we know about the &lt;br /&gt;

 limits of stanzas that spill so helplessly from the self. These are &lt;br /&gt;

 poems of a city's insistent romances and our determination to root &lt;br /&gt;

 ourselves in its clutch, a clutch that nurtures us while taking our &lt;br /&gt;

 breath away. These are poems of backslap and revelation. No one but &lt;br /&gt;

 Jon could have done this." &lt;br /&gt;

 -Patricia Smith, National Book Award Finalist, author of "Blood Dazzler"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is free and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367114982000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365690047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jon Sands: FREE Spoken Word Poetry Show</name><id>113825232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367103600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/113825232/</event_url></item>