<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.363068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Innovation Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>5488072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083893</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Enterprise Social Networking -&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Apache Rave&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apache Rave is a new web and social mashup engine. It will provide an out-of-the-box as well as an extendible lightweight Java platform to host, serve and aggregate (Open)Social Gadgets and services through a highly customizable and Web 2.0 friendly front-end. Rave is targeted as engine for internet and intranet portals and as building block to provide context-aware personalization and collaboration features for multi-site/multi-channel (mobile) oriented and content driven websites and (social) network oriented services and platforms. For the OpenSocial container and services the (Java) Apache Shindig will be integrated. At a later stage further generalization is envisioned to also transparently support W3C Widgets using Apache Wookie. Apache Rave was initiated in 2010 at the previous ApacheCON in Atlanta and through subsequent discussions during the first European OpenSocial Event in Utrecht (The Netherlands), and thereafter created as a joint effort of several existing projects and individual participants. The Rave project thus provides an interesting case-study for bringing together multiple projects with already mature code bases. Rave members are also working together to reach out to other related Apache projects like Shindig and Wookie, to other potentially interested projects and developers both within and outside Apache, and most importantly to the many and diverse target communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matt and Tony will do a round trip of the Apache Rave project. Attendees are encouraged to bring their own laptops to play with the open source code and have a working demo to experiment and hack around with, during and after the talk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bio Matt Franklin &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; Matt has been working with Java technologies as a Lead Software Engineer for The MITRE Corporation. Matt&amp;rsquo;s broad development experience in collaboration and knowledge sharing applications using both commercial and open source technologies has led to his involvement with the Apache Rave community. As an initial member of Apache Rave (incubating), Matt is looking to the open source community to deliver a user-facing platform for integrating collaboration, information management, mobile and socially-enabled solutions. Follow Matt on: &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/mfranklin"&gt;http://twitter.com/mfranklin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bio Tony&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Carlucci&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tony has been working on various Java technologies, specifically in the Portal and Web Service realms, at the MITRE corporation as a Senior Software Engineer. &amp;nbsp;He became interested in the OpenSocial specification in 2008 and worked to incorporate it into his projects via Apache Shindig. &amp;nbsp;He became an initial member of the Apache Rave (incubating) project after discovering the large community of developers who were all working on similar OpenSocial based projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Havanna room on the the 5th floor.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Burc Oral</member_name><member_id>4238999</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mathijs Brand</member_name><member_id>12111377</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332355826000</updated><rating><average>4.09999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>78</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330462879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enterprise Social Networking - Apache Rave</name><id>54222922</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332196200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/54222922/</event_url></item>