<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1667 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381985</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 547-0759</phone><name>Lizard Lounge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669136</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119650</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I've gotten some requests to host a meetup at Lizard Lounge (which does happen to be my favorite venue!), so let's checkout Club d'Elf which is an interesting band with a unique sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Brownpapertickets.com: &lt;br /&gt;

 Mike Rivard's improvisational groove collective returns to the warm embrace of the Lizard Lounge with their usual stellar cast of musicians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music of Club d'Elf flies through North African trance, glitchy turntablism, freeform improvisation, and rock psychedelia, but it's playfully altered states of musical consciousness that truly guide the band. Witness founder Mike Rivard's first night in Morocco, the country that had fired his musical imagination for more than a decade: In a strikingly vivid dream, he felt himself swimming upwards in the air as fantastic landscapes, mountains, and tiled buildings stretched out beneath him. The bands rotating group of players, drawn from a pool that includes keyboardist John Medeski, DJ Logic, David Bowie's guitarists or any number of Moroccan musical icons, swims in the same dreamlike atmosphere, both live and on record.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The highlight for me is when they bring out the guy who plays a "wind-keyboard". The last show I attended with Mr. Rourke on the turntables served to be a nice combo of live and recorded music, and turned out to be a great one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest update to the event no longer has Mr. Rourke on the bill, but an opening act called Otis Grove.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group is quite avant garde, so I would suggest giving them a listen on Youtube to see how you like them. Also check out their myspace page to check out some of their songs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/clubdelf"&gt;http://www.myspace.com/clubdelf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also check out some of their music on their Facebook page:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/clubdelf1"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/clubdelf1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet at 9pm in the lounge downstairs, and we can grab some food/drink before the show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would suggest getting tickets ahead of time, as this group does have quite a following, and their shows usually sell out in this venue&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:00pm doors / 10:00pm show  &lt;br /&gt;

www.clubdelf.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10 pm: Otis Grove (feat The Dux)  &lt;br /&gt;

11 pm: Club d'Elf w/ Duke Levine (guitar), Sam Gilman (keyboards), Mike Rivard (bass &amp;amp; sintir), Dean Johnston (drums) &amp;amp; more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advance Tix ($11.34) can be purchased here:  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/389508"&gt;http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/389508&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kenny Hyde</member_name><member_id>11634784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369454547000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368677851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Club d'Elf w/ Duke Levine &amp; Otis Grove!</name><id>119651682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369443600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/119651682/</event_url></item>