<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Willow St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06109</zip><lat>41.699333</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Webb Elementary School</name><city>Wethersfield</city><id>5308652</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690895</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://italianstudies.nd.edu/assets/57090/pranzodiferragosto.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE NOTE LOCATION CHANGE TO WEBB SCHOOL AND TIME CHANGE TO 7:30&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We apologize for the short notice but our venue for Friday night's screening of &lt;span&gt;Pranzo&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;di&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Ferragosto&lt;/span&gt; has been changed from the Silas Deane Middle School to the Webb School in &lt;span&gt;Wethersfield&lt;/span&gt;. We have changed the time as well to accommodate our guests who might first arrive at &lt;span&gt;SDMS&lt;/span&gt; and need to drive to Webb. We will begin the screening at 7:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The best way to enter the Webb School auditorium is from the the parking lot that is visible from the corner of Welles Road (175) and Willow Street. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please contact me if you have any questions. Again we apologize for the inconvenience but look forward to seeing you tomorrow night at the Webb School, 7:30 pm  for our last film of the season. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us on Friday, April 5, 2013 at 7pm in the Silas Deane Middle School auditorium (Wethersfield) for the next screening in our 2012-2013 Italian Film Series. &lt;br /&gt;

Pranzo di Ferragosto (Mid-August Lunch), 2008 is a comedy about a middle-aged man who lives with his elderly mother in Rome. The film stars and is directed by Gianni di Gregorio. The main character, also named Gianni, finds himself staying home while his friends are departing for their yearly vacation on August 15th (Ferragosto), leaving behind their elderly mothers in his care. The film will leave you smiling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will begin the evening with an introduction of the film. After screening the film attendees are welcome to participate in an exchange of ideas and observations. We look forward to seeing you on Friday, April 5th at 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

EVENT: Italian Film Series &lt;br /&gt;

SCREENING: Pranzo di Ferragosto, 2008, Italian with English subtitles &lt;br /&gt;

EVENT DATE: Friday, April 5, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

EVENT LOCATION: Silas Deane Middle School Auditorium, Wethersfield, CT &lt;br /&gt;

EVENT TIME: 7pm &lt;br /&gt;

COST: FREE AND OPEN TO THE PUBLIC &lt;br /&gt;

EVENT SPONSORED BY: The Wethersfield High School Italian National Honor Society in cooperation with the Italian Culture Center of Education and the Wethersfield Chapter of UNICO &lt;br /&gt;

The evening is made possible by the generous support of Franco Cianfaglione, Agent, State Farm Insurance, Rocky Hill&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lorenzo</member_name><member_id>4408109</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365213795000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Amici Italiani</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>italian-452</urlname><id>535327</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>Connecticut's Viva Italia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365072812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Time &amp; Location change for Italian Film Series - Pranzo di Ferragosto Fri.Apr5</name><id>112625042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365202800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-452/events/112625042/</event_url></item>