<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;The Unfaithful Wife was released in 1968  and was  directed by Claude Chabrol who is often cited as the French 'Alfred Hitchcock'. From all accounts, this is one of his greatest works: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of Chabrol's mid-period masterpieces, a brilliantly ambivalent scrutiny of bourgeois marriage and murder that juggles compassion and cynicism in a way that makes Hitchcock look obvious. The obligatory cross-references are still there (blood in the sink; the exactly appropriate final use of simultaneous backtrack and forward zoom adapted from Vertigo), but they're no longer there to legitimise a vision now mature. Audran and Bouquet, as the first of Chabrol's recurring Charles/Hélène couples, are superb in discovering 'secret' parts of each other denied as much by complacency as convention.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Time Out London&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More from the AllMovie Guide: &lt;br /&gt; La Femme Infidèle is a tale of passion and adultery, but done with a much more distanced and ironic air than is typical of Hitchcock. Charles Desvallées (Michel Bouquet) discovers that his wife, Hélène (Stéphane Audran), is cheating on him. Methodically, he hires a private detective to have her followed, and discovers her lover's identity: he is Victor Pegala (Maurice Ronet), a writer. Driving to Pegala's apartment, Charles calmly introduces himself as Hélène's husband, and then kills Pegala with off-handed diffidence. The subsequent police investigation takes numerous and twists and turns, as is typical for Chabrol. But what interests the director here primarily is not the police inquiries, or even the moral questions surrounding Charles' guilt. What, Chabrol asks, will be Hélène's response to the crime? In the final analysis, Chabrol's film is more interested in matters of the heart than in questions of guilt or innocence, and becomes a psychological investigation of the situation surrounding the murder, rather than a typical policier. Born in 1930, Chabrol is remarkably prolific, with nearly 70 films to his credit, and at this writing still actively producing films, which are at once both commercially, and aesthetically satisfying. La Femme Infidèle is one of Chabrol's key early films, and a superb introduction to the work a master filmmaker who is interested not so much in suspense, but rather in the hearts and minds of those who inhabit his morally ambiguous universe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. The film is 100 minutes long so we should get to the restaurant by 9:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184972906000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182305358000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Unfaithful Wife- A French Suspense Classic</name><id>5911397</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184799600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5911397/</event_url></item>