<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Cushing Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.583423</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1285089</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802296</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In August we'll meet at our new favorite hangout, Chaibo in Fitchburg, to discuss Eat, Pray, Love. Chaibo has comfy couches and serves coffee, smoothies, Panini, cheesecake and many unique flavors of gelato. Yum!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a description of the book by an Amazon reviewer (condensed slightly!):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a spiritual book in the true sense of the word. Although I kept laughing throughout the book, its simplicity is deceptive. Between the lines, Gilbert is about so much more: vitality, coming into one's own, creating reality and matching the soul's aspirations to the delicious unpredictability of life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After divorcing her husband the author decamps for the fountains of Rome where she makes great friends, samples excellent food and learns about the pleasure of dolce far niente from the world's masters in this important art. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This book is essentially revolving about beauty - of friendship, inner life, good taste (and food) and, not least, the ever elusive bounty that is bestowed by a life that is lived well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In India Liz stays in a celebrity ashram north of Bombay where she has a couple of transcendent experiences whereas in Bali she befriends locals in the beautiful town of Ubud. In fact, her capacity for friendship - the genius of it - together with the honest and unflinching ability to face herself is something that I found very cool. So what if she has bad taste when it comes to men? To me, her naivete in all things male is simply a measure of her femininity and humanness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is it true that one can live one's life in an ever expanding circle of vitality and joy? Liz Gilbert gives us a resounding YES.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284289887000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281235613000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Eat, Pray, Love by Elizabeth Gilbert</name><id>14353555</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282863600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/14353555/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/1/global_11643361.jpeg</photo_url></item>