<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>449 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.349.4040</phone><name>Main Cambridge Public Library</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>767569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111112</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ferns have been around for 400 million years! And&amp;nbsp;the speaker, Don Lubin, grows 20 varieties in Allston. I'd like to hear why ferns are so successful&amp;nbsp;in keeping themselves going for so long.&amp;nbsp;The June and July lectures in this series were fantastic, and this one, the last in the summer series,&amp;nbsp;should be just as informative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This lecture is part of a public lecture series (Evenings with Experts: 2011)&amp;nbsp;that is a collaboration between the Cambridge Public Library and Grow Native Massachusetts. It is free and, of course, open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 
&lt;a href="http://www.grownativemass.org/"&gt;http://www.grownativemass.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;*****Native Ferns of New England&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Lecture by Don Lubin, noted fern expert, collector, and educator&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Learn about the life cycle of ferns and their evolutionary history, spanning 400 million years. From New England's 68 species, we will examine 20 of those most commonly found. This survey will include detailed photographs, techniques for field identification, and a look at the adaptive niche that each species occupies. Don Lubin has been teaching about ferns for over a decade, and he grows 44 species in his small yard in Allston. He has collected more than 50 herbarium specimens and has identified previously unrecorded taxa at several locales.*****&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lecture will last about an hour, with about 30 minutes afterward for Q&amp;amp;A (total time about 90 minutes). Doors open at 6:30 p.m.; 
&lt;em&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;the lecture starts at 7:00 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/em&gt; Seating is on a first-come, first-served basis. The closest T option is the Harvard Square stop on the Red Line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;I will be at the library between 6:15 and 6:30.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/em&gt; Meet me inside the library, inside the basement lecture room. We may not be able to sit together because seating is based on first come, first served, but if you can't find me, my bright red backpack, *and* my meetup sign inside the lecture room before the lecture, look for me afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for my bright red backpack *and* my meetup sign. I've been hearing&amp;nbsp;that a lot of people carry bright red backpacks, but how many of them are carrying meetup signs, too?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you Wednesday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marianne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my bright red backpack *and* my meetup sign. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312470504000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312042554000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lecture: Native Ferns of New England</name><id>27605181</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312410600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/27605181/</event_url></item>