<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The title of this topic could just as easily be &amp;ldquo;Enlightened by Science?&amp;rdquo;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I state this disclaimer from the outset because I don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone to get the idea that I am a neo-Luddite or anti-science and anti-technology.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; My true feelings are that science is extraordinarily enlightening but can also be blinding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his highly influential book, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Structure_of_Scientific_Revolutions"&gt;The Structure of Scientific Revolutions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Thomas Kuhn writes that paradigms of the conventionally accepted belief systems of science appear to be an&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;"&amp;hellip;attempt to force nature into the preformed and relatively inflexible box that the paradigm supplies.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; No part of the aim of normal science is to call forth new sorts of phenomena; indeed those that will not fit the box are often not seen at all.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Nor do scientists normally aim to invent new theories, and they are often intolerant of those invented by others.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Instead, normal-scientific research is directed to the articulation of those phenomena and theories that the paradigm already supplies." &lt;span&gt;(chapter 3) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hit song of the 1980s came to mind while five us were chatting at the Dunn Gaherins pub after the "Atheism, Theism, Deism and the Rest of Us" discussion last Friday (1/27/12).&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Bob suggested a discussion concerning the philosophy of science and the song popped into my head, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember the title but John came up with it.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Actually, the full name of the song is &amp;ldquo;She Blinded Me With Science.&amp;rdquo;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s basically a love song, but here are video and lyric presentations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2IlHgbOWj4o"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2IlHgbOWj4o&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; (audio + video)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBIps187MKk"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBIps187MKk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; (audio + lyrics)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, you can see the importance of a title!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; The song is not especially relevant,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; but I do love the song almost as much as I love the title.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; This discussion will be about both the dramatic way in which science and technology have impacted our beliefs about life and our relationship to the universe, and also how it can, paradoxically, also interfere with that progress.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We will discuss the ways and means by which science can both blind and impede, and enlighten and inspire.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; As Kuhn states, the very structure of science tends to block new theoretical perspectives and all other things that depend upon science.&amp;nbsp; It takes a paradigm shift of momentous significance to reframe existing paradigms.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Surely&lt;/span&gt;, science can overcome this egoistic and self-limiting state of being.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Whether it be health, astronomy, theoretical physics, new technologies, to name just a few broad fields, there are a whole lot of reasons for entrenchment in the old ways of thinking.&amp;nbsp; I personally believe that when science becomes more comfortable with serious consideration of ideas and theories outside the conventional paradigms it will more rapidly attain new understanding and the attainment of new paradigms.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; So let&amp;rsquo;s talk about scientific enlightenment and, also, the blinding of science!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people). &amp;nbsp; After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp; This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.&amp;nbsp; It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp; And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!&amp;nbsp; While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; expenditure of $10 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill is under $10 the balance will be added to the gratuity).&amp;nbsp; Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.&amp;nbsp; However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the restaurant and the little mall area close for the night. &lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330292159000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327956642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blinded by Science?</name><id>50277952</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330128000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/50277952/</event_url></item>