<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>109 Town Farm Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03086</zip><lat>42.824588</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>On the left about 0.1 miles after</name><city>Wilton</city><id>4081532</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.800717</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sheldrick Forest is a 227 acre tract&lt;/strong&gt; of old, extraordinary, high quality forest. Woodlands of this age, size, and species diversity, have virtually disappeared from virtually all of southern New Hampshire. It contains more than 6 natural forest communities. The topography of the land has stories to reveal about the area's glacial history. I found the scenery and lay of the land to be very fascinating and different because of the glacial ravines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will be doing (approximately) a 3 mile hike in the Sheldrick Forest.&lt;/strong&gt;  The terrain is up and down hill throughout most of the hike but nothing all that steep or strenuous.  The literature depending on the trails taken describes a hike there as easy - moderate depending on which trails you take.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Then we will use the adjacent Heald Tract (1040 acres) to hike another 3.5 miles&lt;/strong&gt; using part of the Camp Trail to do the Castor Pond Loop.  &lt;strong&gt;So the total hiking distance is 6.5 miles&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sheldrick Forest is owned by the Nature Conservancy and the adjacent Heald Tract is owned by the Society for the Preservation for &lt;em&gt;NH&lt;/em&gt; Forests.  Based on contour lines the elevations during the hike range between a low of 660 feet elevation to 880 feet of elevation (a difference of 220 feet) but the route is hilly so &lt;strong&gt;as far as I can figure the total elevation gain is only 640 feet which is not that bad as it is spread out over 6.5 miles so any steep sections are relatively short.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming from Route 101 turn onto Temple Road at Gary's Harvest Restaurant and proceed 0.3 miles.  Bear left to cross the bridge then turn an immediate left onto Town Farm Road where the sign in picture 1 is.  Proceed 0.7 miles on Town Farm Road (it becomes a dirt road) and you will turn left into an entrance to a field where the sign in picture 2 is.  From the road you can also see the kiosk in picture 3.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to The Nature Conservancy - Sheldrick Forest information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nature.org/ourinitiatives/regions/northamerica/unitedstates/newhampshire/placesweprotect/sheldrick-forest-preserve-wilton.xml"&gt;http://www.nature.org/ourinitiatives/regions/northamerica/unitedstates/newhampshire/placesweprotect/sheldrick-forest-preserve-wilton.xml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and a link to a map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nature.org/ourinitiatives/regions/northamerica/unitedstates/newhampshire/placesweprotect/sheldrick-forest-map-guide-for-web.pdf"&gt;http://www.nature.org/ourinitiatives/regions/northamerica/unitedstates/newhampshire/placesweprotect/sheldrick-forest-map-guide-for-web.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Heald Tract trail map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.forestsociety.org/ourproperties/guide/058/058_map.pdf"&gt;http://www.forestsociety.org/ourproperties/guide/058/058_map.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/6/a/event_65307242.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/6/4/6/event_65306182.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/6/a/event_65304682.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At 0.7 miles from the start of Town Farm Road turn left into the field were you see the sign and kiosk for Sheldrick Forest.  We will gather in the lower part of the field diagonally opposite the kiosk.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353286550000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350265235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sheldrick Forest/Heald Tract -  6.5 Mi. Hike - 640 Ft. Elev. Gain Easy/Moderate</name><id>86993362</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353250800000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/86993362/</event_url></item>