<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>94 Washington Sq. East </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.524908</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1 781 593 1417</phone><name>Knights of Columbus Hall</name><city>Salem</city><id>1015354</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.888378</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will be attending SESSION ONE which runs from 2pm-4:30pm.&amp;nbsp; I figure that way if people want to see all that Salem has to offer in October we can hang out a bit afterwards too.&amp;nbsp; I'm open to showing people around because I know quite a bit about Salem and things to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $25 in advance and $30 at the door (if available).&amp;nbsp; The first 600 visitors will receive a collectable Salem Harvest Fest tasting glass. Tickets are non-refundable.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;**You can purchase tickets online now via PayPal.&amp;nbsp; For some reason the site still says 2010 dates but when you click on the SESSION ONE link, it has the correct dates for this year.**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look just like my picture so I will be easy to find.&amp;nbsp; Parking can be a pain in Salem in October so I suggest we all park&amp;nbsp;at the train station, meet&amp;nbsp;at 1:45pm and walk over to the event together.&amp;nbsp; When it gets&amp;nbsp;closer to the date of the event, I will send out my cell number so that people can text me.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;More information about the event:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.salemharvestfest.com/"&gt;http://www.salemharvestfest.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for the&amp;nbsp;4th Annual Salem Harvest Fest, presented by Pamplemousse and Magic Hat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://thedejas.com/" target="_blank"&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://www.salemharvestfest.com/images/Dejas.jpg" alt="The Dejas" width="160" height="120" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;Harvest Fest is a celebration of wine, beer, mead, food and great live music by 
&lt;a href="http://thedejas.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Dejas&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your ticket is a passport to a journey of tasting the finest fermented beverages from Europe, the Americas, and Down Under.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants include Magic Hat (sponsor), Cody Brewing,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Classic Wine Imports, M. S. Walker, Mayflower Brewing, Still River Winery, Bay State Wines, Charles River Winery, Cape Ann Brewing, Ipswich/Mercury Brewing, Harpoon, Oskar Blues, Naragansett and Arborway, Clown Shoes, Blue Hills Brewery, Notch Brewing, Cima Collina, Charles River Winery, Oz Wines, Isaak's of Salem, Dogfish Head Brewing, Tigris Beverage and Left Hand Brewing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EpqEKoSotQo" target="_blank"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to see videos of last year's Harvest Fest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristin</member_name><member_id>11703298</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318996936000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315254334000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salem Harvest Fest - Beer, Wine, and Mead Tasting</name><id>32350492</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318701600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/32350492/</event_url></item>