<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Raymond Street - Apt. 1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.361900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 901-8871</phone><name>Jason's House</name><city>Allston</city><id>1376656</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134400</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you're struggling in any area of your life as a man, particularly in the area of relationships with women, then you need to check this out. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Here's what this is all about:  My friend Milt Evans has agreed to do a special "group coaching" event just for the men in this group.  This is an awesome opportunity to get personal feedback and help from someone who has decades of wisdom and a wealth of precise knowledge that he can apply to your specific challenges. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Milt has counseled and mentored hundreds of men in his life in all the areas that are important to us.  Things like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to be the kind of man that women find attractive and want to stay with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What to do when women start freaking out and becoming difficult.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to handle specific relationship challenges (bring your worst problem, and Milt will help you).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What to do if you're feeling "lost" as a man, and how to get back to discovering and living your life's purpose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And so much more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Milt is the one man whose advice I rely on whenever I'm faced with difficulties in life.  There's no point in relying on trial and error when you've got a friend who has seen your situation over and over again and knows how to steer you through it effortlessly.  He's helped me personally with things like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to handle and stand up to bullies without being violent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to be a more attractive, masculine man that women naturally want to spend time around.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He's pointed out specific errors in my thinking that were causing distance between me and women.  Once I made the corrections, those problems dissolved as if by magic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And plenty of other things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Milt does not get up on stage and lecture like I do.  He works in small groups by talking to one man at a time about his issues.  And even though I've learned tons by talking with him directly in these groups, I've actually learned MORE from listening to him coach other men, and you will too. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Now listen, I realize you don't know this man, and so you're going to have to make your decision based on your relationship with me... Jason.  If you trust me, and if I've helped you in the past, then you already know that, if I am endorsing this man, you can trust him as well. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

So if you want to become the kind of many who is living each day powerfully and is magnetically attractive to the kind of women YOU want, then I urge you to attend this one-of-a-kind coaching event being held at my place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;

HOW TO GET INVOLVED  &lt;br /&gt;

************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Where is it?&lt;/strong&gt; This event is going to be at my home in Lower Allston, right near Harvard Business School. It's very easy to get to both by car and public transportation, and there's plenty of on-street parking. Directions will be emailed to you. We will start the event promptly at 7:00pm and run until 9:00pm. Please plan on arriving by 6:45 so you have time to settle in and meet the other guests. You never know who you'll meet that can become a new friend and add a lot of value to your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;How much?&lt;/strong&gt; Cheap.  Milt's accumulated wisdom spans many decades.  For you to be able to get help with your personal challenges by a man as wise and experienced as Milt, you'd have to pay at least $100 for a private counseling session.  But because this is in a group format, you're getting in for much cheaper. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;So how much?&lt;/strong&gt; Because I want to help as many people as I can, I've decided to keep the price very affordable so that anyone who wants to come will be able to.  The cost for this event is only $20, which is very low considering the quality of training that you'll be getting. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Think about it...  &lt;strong&gt;that's 67 cents a day for a month&lt;/strong&gt;.  What else do you spend 67 cents on every day that makes no difference in your life whatsoever? I promise that this will be well worth your time, and like I said... you'll learn just as much (if not more) from listening to him coach other man as you will from him coaching you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt; Because this is class is being held at my house and not a large seminar room, I have to limit the size to only 10 students.  There are over 1,200 people seeing this message (and at least half of them are men), so be sure to put in your RSVP right now in order to lock in your spot. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot.  I'm looking forward to seeing you there. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Warmly,  &lt;br /&gt;

Jason &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My house is easy to find.  It'll be on the left side of my one-way street.  I'll have my blue rope lights lit on the porch to help you see the house.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357697561000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357174271000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>For Men Only - A Rare Opportunity To Get Coached By Milt Evans</name><id>97581522</id><headcount>9</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357689600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/97581522/</event_url></item>