<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>The Brewery Complex</address_2><address_1>284 Amory Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.314777</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-524-6060</phone><name>Bella Luna &amp; Milky Way Lounge</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>1010122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104599</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>“Somebody’s Gotta Do It” Story Slam on Sunday, January16, 2011  Bella Luna, 284 Amory Street  Jamaica Plain, MA Tel 617-524-6060.  6:30 PM doors open.  Stories start at 7:00PM Co-hosts are storyteller Robin Maxfield and former City Councilor John Tobin. For more information, contact Robin Maxfield at 617-293-8004 or stories@massmouth.com&lt;br /&gt;massmouth’s story slam season continues at Bella Luna with “Somebody’s Gotta Do It.”  Whether it’s a nasty job, obligation, responsibility or the misfortune to be in the wrong place at the wrong time, the ball landed in your lap. There is a story there, whether you know it or not. Bring it on Sunday, January 16 to Bella Luna’s in Jamaica Plain.  Doors open at 6:30 pm; stories start at 7:00 pm.  Co-hosts are storyteller Robin Maxfield and former City Councilor John Tobin. &lt;br /&gt;The special guest co-host, former City Councilor, John Tobin, served West Roxbury, Jamaica Plain and parts of Roslindale and Mission Hill as Boston City Councilor for nine years.  He is currently vice president of City and Community Affairs at Northeastern University.  He has emceed at Boston’s local comedy clubs for years and has some interesting stories to tell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;massmouth is an organization dedicated to promoting the timeless are of storytelling through social media, education and live performance.  This is massmouth’s second story slam season. At a story slam, participants tell five minute personal stories on the theme. Ten lucky tellers have their names drawn at random to tell and be judged by five volunteer judges.  massmouth awards prizes to the top two stories. Listeners will be engaged in story improv games between each five minute feature. On April 26th, 2011 all the winners will gather for a BIGMOUTHOFF story slam at Rabb Hall at the Copley Square Library. massmouth will award the lucky winner of this contest with a fabulous prize. &lt;br /&gt;If you have a life, you have a story. Bring it.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295282397000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>storytellers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>storytelling-28</urlname><id>1247871</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Greater Boston and MA Storytelling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294374024000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"somebody's gotta do it"  story slam in JP</name><id>15954473</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295222400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/storytelling-28/events/15954473/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/global_19848048.jpeg</photo_url></item>