<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facing Love has become one of the best interactive annual events in the city. The first half is discussion and the second half is a performance by&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KINDRED THE FAMILY SOUL. It's an all day event so you can drop in and leave at whatever times fit your schedule.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update: This is a ticketed event, starting at $40. tickets can be bought at Skippy white's or online&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://facinglove-eac2.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://&lt;/span&gt;facinglove-eac2.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event description copied below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;On SATURDAY, MARCH 9th, 2013, The Boston Society of Vulcans and 9 Alarms Entertainment (Firefighters of Color), in conjunction with Twins and Friends, K.I.Q. Tours, Delta Sigma Theta, United Sistas of Color, Muhammad's Mosque #11, 30 Plus, Diamond Educators and others, will be producing and hosting the SIXTH installment of the FACING LOVE community event at Hibernian Hall from 1pm to 7pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 FACING LOVE is a TV talk show-style symposium that focuses on the dynamics and intricacies of Black/Latino male and f&lt;/span&gt;emale relationships. Our goal is to strengthen lines of communication and empathetic perceptions between the genders, thus fortifying the family unit and our overall community. Facing Love works to elevate the number of marriages that occur between men and women of the Black/ Latino community, as most social data indicates integrity of the family unit leads to better quality of life. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Each of our symposium’s revolve around a central theme. Facing Love VI’s conversation will penetrate the bio/economic/political battles that Black/Latino people must fight on a HEALTH front. In addition, we will explore how HAIR CARE and IMAGE has contributed to any dysfunction in the Black/Latino community. We have enlisted the assistance of &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Jessyca Abena Marshall, Owner and Founder of Naturally Beautiful Hair Care. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Darrius Peace, Author of "My Hair Ain't Nappy" &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Nancy V Brown, NV My Hair &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We are absolutely elated to welcome our featured guests, Neo-Soul/R&amp;amp;B icons and married couple KINDRED THE FAMILY SOUL. Kindred enjoys inter-national popularity and their presence at FL VI is not only aesthetic...but functional. Their particular brand of therapeutic and instructional musical message could not be more complimentary to Facing Love’s doctrine. With that, they are more than deserving of the Oraka Award, the acknowledgement we bestow on one emblematic couple per year. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 As much of a breakthrough event as Facing Love V was, this upcoming iteration will undoubtedly propel our modest symposium to stratospheric proportions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We are committed to presenting a memorable, informational and engaging experience...one that will beckon placement into the annuls of history. Such events come few and far between in Boston. Take ACTION, the greatest form of love, in being on hand to witness FACING LOVE VI come to fruition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll designate a time and spot in the building for us to meet up</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cabral Thomas</member_name><member_id>9824758</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363313309000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359767536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Facing Love VI</name><id>102592922</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>25200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362852000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/102592922/</event_url></item>