<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Kneeland Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.349878</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 426-6397</phone><name>Splash Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>1171690</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We can meet at Splash Lounge around 5 PM or as soon as you can get there.  Dave posted the idea for Splash and said he will be there at 5 so that makes 2 of us.  The website says free appetizers from 5 till 7PM.  There are 4 other meetups attending, and 19 yes RSVP's from Social fun alone.  Anyone who wants can then head over to the MFA Friday Event around 7PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are INVITED to attend a ROOF TOP PARTY @ SPLASH 5pm - 9PM*  &lt;br /&gt;Hosted by Bostoneventguide.com and Rush Hour.  If you can get there early, please help grab some tables!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join members of Social Fun, Fun with Alcohol, Red Sox Natives and Boston Happy Hour for a Complimentary Food Buffet! Menu varies according to availability. Cash bar, private seating areas and pool tables available. I will notify the Boston Beanstalks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* In case of rain, try to grab the big corner table in the back behind the bar indoors. Social fun et al is planning to repeat this event every first Thursday and every third Friday, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: Limited parking available on the street but you'll have to feed the meter up until 8pm. Allow extra time for parking. T at South Station walk about 4 blocks on Atlantic Ave along South Station/Bus Terminal toward Kneeland street, turn right onto Kneeland two blocks on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279318494000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Tall Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostontallsingles</urlname><id>1235066</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Tall Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279176576000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Splash &amp; then MFA </name><id>14108991</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279314000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostontallsingles/events/14108991/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/global_7950177.jpeg</photo_url></item>