<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sage Park Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.842303</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 987-7888</phone><name>Windsor High School</name><city>Windsor</city><id>1119586</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.656895</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Romantic Comedy&amp;quot; play THIS SAT. 02/16 in Windsor, followed by a private house party in West Hartford. &lt;br /&gt;My lovely and talented daughter, Ellen, (17) will be performing in her final High School play this SATURDAY @ Windsor High School. You are welcome to join me and some of my friends gathering in the W.H.S. theater lobby @ 7:00PM so we can sit together and I'll hand out directions to the &amp;quot;adults only&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;party afterwards. The performance starts @ 7:30 (ending @ 9:30- 10-ish). Tickets are $8 for adults, at the door. Following this performance, we'll head back to &amp;quot;Bob &amp;amp; Rob's place&amp;quot; in West Hartford for a VERY CASUAL BYO party, typically featuring dancing, joking, eating, drinking, games, and making new friends! &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP if you are planning to join us for the Play &amp;amp; Party, indicating if you'll be meeting us @ W.H.S. or carpooling from our place in W.H., leaving @ 6:45. Thx. &lt;br /&gt;MapQuest directions to: Windsor High School, 50 Sage Park Road, Windsor, CT 06095 (NOTE: DO NOT confuse with the Jr. H. &lt;br /&gt;S. across the street) &lt;br /&gt;I hope you can join us! &lt;br /&gt;- Rob &lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney &lt;br /&gt;rep06110@yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;*** &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Romantic Comedy is a play by Bernard Slade, author of Same Time, Next Year. &lt;br /&gt;The plot focuses on Phoebe Craddock and Jason Carmichael, playwrights who meet and decide to collaborate just as he is getting married. Their relationship produces first a failure and then a string of successes, and their repartée remains sharp and witty as their unrequited interest in each other gathers energy over a nine-year period, until some resolution finally is in sight.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Rob Pudney is of our meetup members (see his profile below) and is leading this event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203379727000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203010985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Romantic Comedy", A Play, Windsor, party in W. Hartford afterward </name><id>7331141</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203206400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/7331141/</event_url></item>