<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CT REIA and Robyn Thompson presents: Buy, Renovate, and Sell Single and Multi-Family Homes For Huge Profits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://ctreia.files.wordpress.com/2011/02/robyn-thompson2.jpg?w=111&amp;amp;h=111" alt="Robyn Thompson real estate" width="111" height="111" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;February 21 &amp;ndash; 5:30 to 9:00 PM &lt;br /&gt; Crowne Plaza Hotel. 100 Berlin Road. Cromwell, CT &lt;br /&gt; FREE for CTREIA and AOACT members | $30 for guests&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Register and/or learn more about this event at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=329"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=329&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robyn  Thompson is the leading expert in buying, renovating and selling single  and multi-family homes for huge profits. &lt;strong&gt;Robyn has renovated and sold  over 304 homes in the past 14 years!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Are you tired of having more month than you have money? &lt;br /&gt; * Are you looking for financial independence? &lt;br /&gt; * Are you ready to start a business that will generate huge chunks of cash?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If  you answered yes to any of these questions, retailing ugly houses  is  for you!  Robyn has taught thousands of students how to achieve   financial independence by investing in distressed properties. Robyn has   made retailing homes a science and she knows every technique imaginable   to locate profitable deals, renovate distressed properties at  lightning  speed, minimize holding costs, and qualify good credit buyers  and  expedite closings so you can collect a big check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn Robyn&amp;rsquo;s  trade secrets for buying and repairing  distressed homes, as well as  selling and cashing out investment  properties, designed for both novice  real estate investors and seasoned  professionals.&lt;/strong&gt; Robyn has taught  hundreds of students already,  and now you have the opportunity to learn  everything you need to know  to begin retailing houses and making money  in your hometown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You Will Learn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * How to find the profitable homes that need renovation. &lt;br /&gt; * How to find and control the contractors to get the job done. &lt;br /&gt; * How to sell houses quickly for huge chunks of cash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5:30 &amp;ndash; Meet the Businesses Who Can Support Your Business&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:45 &amp;ndash; Early Bird Workshop: Speed Networking &lt;br /&gt; Discover Who You can Do Business With. &lt;br /&gt; Also&amp;hellip; Q&amp;amp;A Session: &lt;br /&gt; Ask Your Burning Questions and Get Local Up-To-Date Answers. Bring your business cards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:45 &amp;ndash; Deal Making &lt;br /&gt; Hear the hot deals our members are selling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 &amp;ndash; Robyn Thompson &lt;br /&gt; Find out how to buy, renovate, and sell single and multi-family homes for huge profits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Robyn Thompson&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Robyn  Thompson is the nations leading expert on buying, renovating and   selling homes for huge chunks of cash and is known throughout the  United  States and Canada as &amp;ldquo;The Queen of Rehab&amp;rdquo;. After spending 9  years  working a dead end corporate job, Robyn realized that her hard  work and  dedication for IBM was not going to provided financial  independence.   She walked away from her secure paycheck and never  looked back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over  the past 14 years since Robyn left IBM, she has bought, fixed  and sold  304 homes with price ranges as low as $8,000 to as high as  $4,000,000.   She has spent as much as $2,100,000 in labor and materials  in one year  to renovate properties with more than 22 contractors  working full time  to take the ugly homes she bought and turn them into  little castles at  lightening speed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robyn has taught thousands of students  throughout the United States  how to become financially independent. She  has shared the stage with  Donald Trump, Dr Phil, Mark Victor Hansen, Ron  LeGrand, Marshall Sylver  &amp;amp; many more legends. Robyn uses her  success in the real estate  business to help those less fortunate. The  most recent construction  project that Robyn completed was an orphanage  in Haiti for 165 children  that opened on February 21st, 2007.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298331868000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297110302000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA Monthly Meeting with Robyn Thompson - Real Estate Rehab Queen</name><id>16478294</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298327400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/16478294/</event_url></item>