<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>280 The Fenway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-566-1401</phone><name>Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum</name><city>Boston</city><id>698253</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098228</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Last year it was snowing for the December After Hours, which made it even more dreamy and lovely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;i&gt;As usual, I'll be somewhere on the first floor, probably sipping wine, until about 7pm and wandering the museum for an hour or so after that.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The thing about the Gardner After Hours is that although of course the museum is almost the same every month, there is always more art to discover + the monthly theme gives you a new way of looking at the art and the space.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: If you RSVP yes but change your mind, &lt;b&gt;please remember to change your RSVP to no&lt;/b&gt; so that I don't worry about us finding each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;December 18th, 2008 – A Solstice Soirée&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the end of 2008 approaches, celebrate the winter solstice on one of the darkest nights of the year. Explore pagan imagery in the throughout the collection and images of festive celebrations in the special exhibition The Triumph of Marriage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Courtyard Sounds: Renaissance party music – who knew? Listen to the sounds of Seven Times Salt (5:30 to 8:30PM)&lt;br /&gt;    * Gallery Travels: Visit the galleries with this self-guided tour highlighting some of the pagan objects in the collection.&lt;br /&gt;    * Viewfinder: Explore the art of marriage throughout the evening with ongoing Viewfinder talks in the Triumph of Marriage special exhibition gallery.&lt;br /&gt;    * Sketching in the Galleries: Create your own masterpieces with drawing in the cloisters and galleries (6 to 9PM)&lt;br /&gt;    * Artful Flavors: Indulge in the culinary arts, signature cocktails including the all-new Madame Gautreau, and more at the courtside bar and Gardner Café.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll probably be wearing a purple flower pin--I'll update closer to the event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cristin</member_name><member_id>603739</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230939645000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227380843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gardner After Hours--December!</name><id>9213213</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229641200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/9213213/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/3/b/global_5477691.jpeg</photo_url></item>