<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I know this is short notice for this event but information on the location and specifics has been slow coming. Organized by the Aussie expat group, inviting Brits, Kiwis, Yanks, we Canucks, and any one else you can think of!  &lt;br /&gt;Thought it would be great to give our cousins a hand.  Again short notice, and the day after our skating event, but a worthwhile cause. &lt;br /&gt;I want to give the Aussies our number estimate asap, so let me know as soon as you can. Here are the specifics:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who want to meet up beforehand, will be having coffee after 2 pm at Au Bon pain across the street from Kendall/MIT T station at 245 Main st. Will walk to consulate around 3 pm. My cell is 857-221 2041&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wine Tasting on the Charles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, 21 February, 2009&lt;br /&gt;3:00 – 6:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Consulate General of Britain&lt;br /&gt;Suite 1500, 1 Memorial Drive, Cambridge MA&lt;br /&gt;$20 entry (includes food and drink)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description from the Aussie event organizer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We come together to support to those who are suffering a result of the recent bush fires in Australia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For $20 donation at the door, there will be lots of fantastic, free Aussie, Kiwi, and European wines and food, and a magnificent view of the Charles River and Boston, thrown in for free by our kind hosts, the British Consulate. Bring your mates along for a great time to support an important cause!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be lots of exciting raffles and silent auction items up for grabs, so don’t forget to bring cash or your check book. We will provide more details of the items closer to the date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceeds will be donated to the Red Cross Bushfire 2009 Appeal and the RSPCA Victoria Bushfire Appeal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of security restrictions at the consulate, all attendees must be over the age of 21 and must register their names by 5pm, Friday, 20 February.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Canadian list of names will be emailed to the Aussie group before 5 pm, Friday, 20 Feb.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet up at Au Bon pain across the street from kendall T (look for Canuck flag)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce Turnbull</member_name><member_id>4018534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236987029000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234823654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Aussie BushFire Fundraiser</name><id>9754648</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235246400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/9754648/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/1/0/global_7347856.jpeg</photo_url></item>