<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color : #0a0101"&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;
        HBA Boston &amp;ndash; The Art and Science of Networking (Yes, There Is A Science!)&lt;/strong&gt;
      
    &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;

When: Thursday, July 19, 2011
Where: Shire Human Genetic Therapies, 700 Main Street, Cambridge, MA 02139
Register: 
&lt;a href="http://www.hbanet.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hbanet.org&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;(Onsite registration is allowed, and online registration is open through 11:59 PM on Monday, July 18, 2011. You are also welcome to join online.)&lt;/strong&gt;
In this highly interactive, fast paced session, we will learn about the science behind networking. We will draw on insights from researchers and practitioners in the social sciences and in business to learn about the networking practices of high performers. We will dispel the myth that people who want strong networks should never eat alone and, instead, we will learn about the simple actions that significantly contribute to the health of your network. We will also practice the art of networking so participants will leave with better connections and increased knowledge about what the HBA network in the room can offer. We will merge the art and science by mapping individual participants&amp;rsquo; networks, identify gaps, and develop plans for filling those gaps. It will be a jam packed session, so please come ready to learn and have fun!
Learning Objectives:
1. Increase your understanding of the science behind networking
2. Perform a preliminary strategic analysis of your own networks
3. Identify the gaps in your personal networks and develop ideas about how to fill those gaps
4. Gain real-time advising from peers about on the job challenges
Agenda:

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;5:30 &amp;ndash; 6:15 PM&lt;/span&gt; Registration/Networking Reception

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;6:15 &amp;ndash; 6:30 PM&lt;/span&gt; Welcome and Volunteer Recognition

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;6:30 &amp;ndash; 8:00 PM&lt;/span&gt; Program/Q&amp;amp;A

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;8:00 &amp;ndash; 8:15 PM&lt;/span&gt; Closing Remarks

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;8:15 &amp;ndash; 9:00 PM&lt;/span&gt; Coffee/Dessert
Eligibility:
Event is exclusively for HBA members only.</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311115178000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310014284000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HBA Boston – The Art and Science of Networking (Yes, There Is A Science!)</name><id>24859211</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311111000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/24859211/</event_url></item>