<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From the Brattle Theatre website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Engagement!&lt;br /&gt;Restored 35mm Print!&lt;br /&gt;Unseen For Over 10 Years!&lt;br /&gt;Let's Get Lost at 2:15, 4:45, 7:15, 9:45   &lt;br /&gt;(1988) dir Bruce Weber w/Chet Baker [120 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?He was bad, he was trouble and he was beautiful.? A James Dean lookalike pretty boy whose jazz trumpeting and melancholy crooning epitomized 50s cool, Chet Baker had become, when famed photographer Bruce Weber finally caught up with him after three decades of fandom, an alcoholic and a junkie, those petulantly angelic looks peeping out from behind a gaunt, valleyed and crevassed face that could have starred for Sam Peckinpah. How did he get there? We kind of find out, as Weber and crew follow Baker on a year-long trek on the road, from the West Coast, to the East Coast, to Europe ? including a stop at the Cannes Film Festival ? with interviews with Chet, colleagues and friends, including dueling insights from his third wife (a former British show girl who had dated Terence Stamp) and three children in Oklahoma, and from old flame Ruth Young, a sardonically throaty torch singer. Plus evocative photo montages of William Claxton?s iconic 50s photo sessions; clips from old movies featuring young Chet; rare performance footage, including a TV appearance introed by a would-be hip Steve Allen ? studded throughout is coverage of Baker?s tour, shot by D.P. Jeff Preiss in a stark, brooding film noir black &amp;amp; white, never more so than in the recurring close-up of Baker between two women in the back seat of a convertible hurtling down night streets, his long hair blowing over that now-seamy face. A popular and critical smash at its 1989 Film Forum [and Brattle Theatre!] premiere, but unseen since 1993 in any medium (rare copies of an early 90s VHS fetch impressive sums on Amazon), LET?S GET LOST has now been personally restored by Weber himself, its lush imagery providing a striking visual experience. ? Notes from the Film Forum, NYC &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?Magical? Weber?s visual intuitions are as lyrical and right as Baker?s melodic instincts? LET?S GET LOST isn?t primarily about Chet Baker the jazz musician; it?s about Chet Baker the love object, the fetish. Behind it all is a soundtrack made up of Baker recordings that span more than three decades ? the idealized essence of the man. And maybe because Weber, despite his lifelong fixation on this charmer, knew him only as a battered, treacherous wreck, in the two years before his death, LET?S GET LOST is one of the most suggestive (and unresolved) films ever made. It?s about love, but love with few illusions.? ? Pauline Kael&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?It?s the music doc as film noir, with a vampirish city-of-night gleam that suits the subject and his darkly romantic sound. All these years later, the inky shadows and stabbing high-contrast light of Jeff Preiss?s black-and-white camera work still look as if they?d been freshly dredged from the undertow of Baker?s long good-bye.? ? Jim Ridley, The Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the front near one side with my trusty Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>We'll head off to a restaurant after the movie where we'll hash and re-hash everything about it!</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199762239000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Get Lost at the Brattle</name><id>7059585</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201306500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7059585/</event_url></item>