<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Capitol Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.206304</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>NH State House</name><city>Concord</city><id>994320</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.537875</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Host: New Hampshire Coalition for Common Sense Marijuana Policy &lt;br /&gt;603-391-7450&lt;br /&gt;Matt@NHCompassion.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Final amendments to HB 648 have been approved by the legislative committee. Both houses of the legislature will be voting to approve the changes June 24, and then the bill will move forward to Governor John Lynch's desk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To demonstrate credible public support for the bill, we will be holding a rally at the state house from 8:15 to 9:45 a.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can attend and help us make a good impression on legislators and media one last time, we would love to have your support!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 8:15 to 8:45, we will be spreading out and holding our &amp;quot;Patients, not Criminals&amp;quot; signs so legislators will see them as they arrive, park, and enter the statehouse. We will have plenty of signs and stickers available for all, and because it is very important for us to stay on message, we are encouraging people not to create their own signs for the rally. Perception is everything in politics, and we'd like to continue with the excellent job everybody has done this year defying the usual marijuana stereotypes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 8:45 we will assemble directly in front of the statehouse and have a few good speakers. The House will begin its work at 10:00 a.m., so we will conclude the rally well before that time, and those of us who wish to do so will go inside to observe.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Todd Puterbaugh</member_name><member_id>4083337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246019095000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245785425000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rally for Compassion: Show support for the medical marijuana bill</name><id>10718081</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245845700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/10718081/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>