<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Northern Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.813284</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Plum Island Point</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>706565</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.814106</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join Ralphie B.. of R.B.Entertainment (Dj,Singer,Master Entertainer) for the biggest 4th of July celebration on the north shore. Saturday July 4, 2009 from 7pm-10:30 pm aboard the Capt. Lady. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;6/17 UPDATE: Sorry to send another update on this but I just talked to Ralph and he only has 16 tickets left, the ad went into the Herald today!  If you are planning on going to this event please call him and reserve your ticket! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6/14 UPDATE: I called to see how many tickets were available and he told me that he is about a little over 1/2 way sold out.  If you plan to come to this event I would get your ticket paid for!!  He also told me that he is putting an advertisement in the Herald this week (so it may get filled up fast!).  When you call in your reservation please tell him that you are &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;RSVPing w/Donna&lt;/span&gt;.  I have asked him to hold tickets for the Donna group and he will do this for us.  This should be a great time, so don't miss the fun!!  See you on the boat.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boat leaves from Plum Island Point in Newburyport, Ma for an unforgettable evening. Deluxe buffet, music, entertainment, dancing, and a double show of fireworks. So gather up all your family and friends and join the fun, as we all celebrate &amp;quot;AMERICA&amp;quot; Tickets are just $38.00 pp Call and reserve your tickets now by calling 978-973-4515 anytime. Tickets are limited, all major credit cards accepted. We don't want you to miss the boat. www.rbentertainment.com &amp;quot;Where All The Fun Begins&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of parking at the point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are responsible for ordering and paying for your own ticket.  Please update your RSVP when you have paid for your ticket!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on the boat! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be on the dock.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247357050000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244341943000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come watch the fireworks on the boat!!</name><id>10594195</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246746600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10594195/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>