<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;2046-its an apartment number and the year- is the second film that the Harvard Film Archive is presenting by director Wong Kar-Wai this month. And while this is a sequel (of sorts) to In The Mood for Love, 2046 can be appreciated on its own as a separate film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2046 continues the story of Chow Mo Wan (Tony Leung) from In the Mood for Love, a few years after his ephemeral affair with Maggie Cheung's Su Li-zhen. Set in late-1960's Hong Kong, Chow is now an out of work journalist and pulp-fiction writer living in a cheap hotel. Bruised and battered by love, he pursues a playboy lifestyle of zero commitment and one-night stands. He develops a passion for a beautiful call girl (Zhang Ziyi), enjoys a breezy summer with the hotel manager's eldest daughter (Faye Wong), and happens across the path of a professional gambler (Gong Li) who he met in Singapore some years before. In the meantime, Chow works on a science fiction novel about a mysterious hi-tech train that transports people to the year 2046 to reclaim their lost memories.  Heroic Cinema&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is a cinema more sensuous than that of Hong Kong's master of the exquisite image, Wong Kar-wai, I have yet to see it. His films are like seductive dances with his actors, only their practiced moves and elegant fashions serve as emotional armor. That description captures Wong's ostensible hero, Chow Mo Wan (the glibly charming Tony Leung Chiu Wai), right down to his lacquered hair and too-neat mustache. A pulp-fiction writer by day and lounge lizard by night, the smiling womanizer lives in a half-remembered, half-idealized projection of 1960s Hong Kong, gliding effortlessly as he changes partners whenever the dance becomes too intimate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zhang Ziyi is his showgirl neighbor in room 2046 of his ratty Hong Kong motel, the latest in a long line of conquests (Gong Li, Faye Wong and Carina Lau similarly pass through his arms). As Chow breaks her heart, he casts himself as the tragic hero of unrequited love in his latest work of fiction, an erotic sci-fi serial titled, of course, &amp;quot;2046.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though it's technically a sequel to Wong's previous film &amp;quot;In the Mood for Love&amp;quot; (with references to Wong's debut feature &amp;quot;Days of Being Wild&amp;quot;), &amp;quot;2046&amp;quot; exists in its own insular universe. The story is oblique at best, the narrative slips back in time and forward into fantasy, and the film circles back on itself, as if the emotionally unavailable Chow is doomed to an endless loop. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hazy intensity of the saturated images, the enchanting soundtrack of lush lounge music and Wong's way of tilting intimate scenes with his skewed visuals, all create an atmosphere thick with longing and loneliness. Cinematographer extraordinaire Christopher Doyle creates a tawdry glamour and vibrant texture for Wong's meditation on memory, regret and emotional paralysis. The result is rich, lush -- simply exquisite.   Seattle-Post Intelligencer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And you know what, this is a free screening at the HFA made possible by their VES department.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Once again Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200706394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wong Kar-wai's 2046 at the HFA</name><id>7147269</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203465600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7147269/</event_url></item>