<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;By Popular Demand: Celebrate the Holiday Season with a Black Tie Gala!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and see the men in formal black ties and the women in cocktail dresses. What a beautiful sight this will be! This will be Brunch &amp;amp; More's first ever Black Tie Gala event! And it's about time, right? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be plenty of fantastic company along with wine (at the cash bar), heavy hors d’oeuvres, prizes for the best dressed, and finally a complimentary champagne toast combined with an open-mic night where people can sing there favorite songs and/or read their favorite toast or poems and have an opportunity for impromptu jazz renditions of &amp;quot;Hilaaaaarious!&amp;quot; by RitAction and mouth trumpet by Bret Lazer. Intrigued? Curious? The only way to get the full scoop, to uncover the true identities of RitAction and Bret Lazer, is to experience the Black Tie Gala yourself! So come celebrate a special evening and the holiday season with good cheer and humor. Let’s gather together to revel in our wonderful community of friends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ticket Availability and Details&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The number of available spots at the gala is limited to 40. Tickets cost just $45. Included in the price is heavy hors d’oeuvres and a complimentary champagne toast, as long as you purchase your tickets before November 30th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to come alone or, if you wish, bring a friend or date. Your guest may be a member of Brunch &amp;amp; More or not. &lt;u&gt;However, each Brunch &amp;amp; More member is limited to bringing one guest because we want to make sure as many group members as possible are able to enjoy the gala.&lt;/u&gt; If you opt to bring a guest, you must pay for him/her via PayPal when you purchase your ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure to get your tickets early so you won’t miss out on a great night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What People are Saying&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sweet! First, the hat revolution is about to descend on Boston. Next, the black tie gala will take the holiday season by storm. Pretty soon Manhattan will be looking to Boston for style innovations!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- Bret Lazer (Come and find out who Bret Lazer really is!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sounds great! I have the perfect cocktail dress!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- Lauren (But which one? We have five!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For your reference, below is an abbreviated history of the black tie and Tuxedo, as well as, a slideshow of the design and evolution of the cocktail dress, and more. Get ready to party in style!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;History of the Black Tie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know that even in 1913 the Tuxedo or short dinner coat with a black tie was intended for warmer weather only and for stag dinners where women were not present. It wasn't until the end of the war and the subsequent Jazz Age providing numerous reasons to celebrate and the dinner jacket’s or Tuxedo's balance of traditional elegance and contemporary comfort that would gradually come to elevate it to an evening wear standard. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is impossible for the black tie to be fully appreciated or properly executed without being familiar with its history. Until a man understands evening wear’s original intention and aesthetic logic, he is likely doomed to a formal wardrobe that fails to meet its most fundamental objectives. Young men in particular tend to presume that simply having worn a suit intrinsically qualifies them to assemble a proper formal ensemble, but this is as naive as believing that writing a high school essay qualifies someone to author a novel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tradition of dressing up after dark has existed for centuries. Perhaps the most obvious evidence of this is the theater’s “dress circle”, a term derived from the 18th- and 19th-century grand European opera houses, which restricted this exclusive seating section to patrons who were properly attired. However, the definition of what constituted “dressing up” underwent a dramatic change about three hundred years ago. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George “Beau” Brummell (1778-1840) was a middle-class Englishman with social ambitions well beyond his income.  Because it was impossible – and unacceptable – for a man of his station to mimic the extravagant garb of the ruling class, Brummell devised a bold solution: change the rules. Through his influence on his good friend, the Prince of Wales, the consummate dandy was able to convince the aristocracy to reject the ostentatious fashions of the time in favor of solemn colors, superb tailoring and meticulous attention to detail. Brummell’s fashion revolution would have a profound impact on menswear in England and subsequently the Western world.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Introduction to America&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dinner jacket’s introduction to American society can be traced to an 1886 summer visit to England by millionaire New York coffee broker James Brown Potter and his actress wife Cora. Upon being introduced to the couple at a court ball, the Prince of Wales was taken with Cora’s renowned beauty and invited the couple to dinner at Sandringham. When James asked his host for advice on what to wear for such an occasion, the Prince referred him to his tailors to be fitted for the short jacket that he had recently taken to wearing. Mr. Potter then brought the innovation back home to Tuxedo Park, a private residential country club recently established by a group of prominent and wealthy New Yorkers led by tobacco heir Pierre Lorillard. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Why Black?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The philosophy of restraint and understatement in masculine attire was then taken to its furthest extent when the popularity of dark colors evolved into a preference for ebony. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to menswear historian James Laver, this trend was due to English politician and novelist Edward Bulwer-Lytton (1803-1873) who wrote in his 1828 novel Adventures of a Gentleman that people must be very distinguished to look well in black.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Origin of The Name Tuxedo&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eventually, after wearing the new jacket for dinner in Tuxedo Park, a private residential country club recently established by a group of prominent and wealthy New Yorkers led by tobacco heir Pierre Lorillard, some of the early members were bold enough to wear it one evening at a bachelor dinner at Delmonico’s, the only place in New York where gentlemen dined in public at that time.  Needless to say, the other diners at Del’s were astonished, and when they asked what it was the men in short coats had on, they were told, “Oh that is what they wear for dinner up in Tuxedo”.  Hearing Tuxedo mentioned, the curious diners quite naturally starting calling the new jacket by that name.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Origin of the Bow Tie&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bow tie originated among Croatian mercenaries during the Prussian wars of the 17th century: the Croats used a scarf around the neck to hold together the opening of their shirts. This was soon adopted (under the name cravat, derived from the French for &amp;quot;Croat&amp;quot;) by the upper classes in France, then a leader in fashion, and flourished in the 18th and 19th centuries. The French novelist Honoré de Balzac even wrote a book on the subject.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Origin of the Black Bow Tie&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The black silk bow tie and the short mess jacket are of military origin - black silk bow ties were and still are worn by British naval and military officers in ball dress and mess dress when their civilian counterparts are in white tie. Henry Poole &amp;amp; Co. of Savile Row claims to have made a &amp;quot;short smoking jacket&amp;quot; for the Prince of Wales in 1865. This appears to have been worn by the Prince with a black bow tie, and the fashion was copied.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;History of the Cocktail Dress&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cocktail dress rivals only the little black dress for importance in a girl's closet. The cocktail is feminine, fun, and sexy, and made for a night out — what's not to love about that? And so it's only fitting that it gets an entire book devoted to its history, curated and written by Style.com's Laird Borrelli-Persson. The cocktail dress traces the history of the piece, from its conception in the twenties to Dior's New Look interpretation to Audrey Hepburn's Givenchy number in Breakfast at Tiffany's to more recent couture looks. And, true to Borrelli-Persson's other image-heavy books, this one is filled with contributions by designers like Peter Som, Cynthia Rowley, and Isaac Mizrahi, and shows off dresses by Vionnet, Marc Jacobs, and more. Check out our favorite images from the book in the slideshow: &lt;a href="http://nymag.com/daily/fashion/2009/06/the_cocktail_dress.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://nymag.com/daily/fashion/2009/06/the_cocktail_dress.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://nymag.com/dail...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Famous Quotes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; Greatest Lines Ever Uttered by a Man in a Tuxedo&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Oh, the things I do for England.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- James Bond&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I think this is the most extraordinary collection of talent, of human knowledge, that has ever been gathered together at the White House, with the possible exception of when Thomas Jefferson dined alone.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- John F. Kennedy (Remarks at a Dinner Honoring Nobel Prize Winners of the Western Hemisphere)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I am the man who accompanied Jacqueline Kennedy to Paris, and I have enjoyed it.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;- John F. Kennedy (During Presidential Trip to Paris) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; Famous Quotes on Champagne&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Come quickly, I am tasting the stars!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- Dom Perignon, after he first tasted champagne.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I drink champagne when I'm happy and when I'm sad.&lt;br /&gt;Sometimes I drink it when I'm alone.&lt;br /&gt;When I have company I consider it obligatory.&lt;br /&gt;I trifle with it if I'm not hungry and drink it when I am.&lt;br /&gt;Otherwise I never touch it - unless I'm thirsty.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- Madame Lilly Bollinger&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Remember gentleman, it’s not just France we’re fighting for, it’s Champagne!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- Winston Churchill&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I drink Champagne when I win, to celebrate.&lt;br /&gt;And I drink Champagne when I lose, to console myself.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- Napoleon Bonaparte&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Champagne and orange juice is a great drink. The orange improves the champagne. The champagne definitely improves the orange.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;- Philip, Duke of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ritesh</member_name><member_id>4789957</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269911027000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257968285000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Black Tie Gala -- Copley Square --  A Night to Remember!!!</name><id>11852124</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269738000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11852124/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/global_11766009.jpeg</photo_url></item>