<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Redfern Arts Center</address_2><address_1>229 Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03431</zip><lat>42.927513</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(800) 572-1909</phone><name>Keene State College</name><city>Keene</city><id>442227</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.277500</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Valley 9/11 Truth is happy to support this event, sponsored by the Monadnock 9/11 Truth Alliance, Keene State College Political Science Department, Keene State Campus Ecology, &lt;a href="http://www.ae911truth.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth&lt;/a&gt;, and Student Scholars for 9/11 Truth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Gage, AIA, a Member of the American Institute of Architects, has been a practicing Architect for 20 years who has worked on most types of building construction including numerous fire-proofed steel-framed buildings. He is currently engaged in the design of a large urban project that includes high-rise office space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2006 he decided to bring his architectural training and experience to bear on what he believes is a key question for all building professionals to consider: How did World Trade Center Building Seven and the Twin Towers fail symmetrically and completely, collapsing at near free-fall speed?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Statements by more than 270 engineers and architects that are critical of the 9/11 Commission Report are now on record and can be viewed at PatriotsQuestion911.org. Alan Miller who collected these statements commented: ?Their collective voices give credibility to the claim that the 9/11 Commission Report is tragically flawed. These individuals cannot be simply dismissed as irresponsible believers in some 9/11 conspiracy theory. Their sincere concern, backed by their professional responsibilities related to building design, construction, and other areas of engineering, demonstrates that criticism of the Commission Report is not inherently irresponsible or illogical, and that, in fact, it can be just the opposite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COME TO HEAR RICHARD GAGE ON FEB. 9TH AND SEE FOR YOURSELF WHY A NEW INVESTIGATION IS URGENTLY NEEDED&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information contact: Gerhard Bedding, 355-2202, or Aaron Rothberg, 358-2590&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202774999000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>This information is critical in demanding a real investigation regarding the events of September 11, 2001 and its coverup, and unanswered questions of what really happened that day.</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200851055000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Richard Gage, AIA - 9/11 Blueprint for Truth</name><id>7157509</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202601600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/7157509/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/a/global_3019834.jpeg</photo_url></item>