<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>971 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.351646</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>701-331-0920</phone><name>Paradise Rock Club</name><city>Boston</city><id>512528</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119360</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Features are an awesome band from my native land Tennessee! They have a The Shins type feel and are just great indie pop. Check out the link to lala for a listen. So much fun! I will send out premeetup info closer to the date of the show.&lt;br /&gt;Jenn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lala.com/z1mE" target="_blank"&gt;http://lala.com/z1mE...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Features are a psychedelic rock outfit that plays fresh, off-kilter pop that sounds like a head-on collision between Ray Davies and Elvis Costello with the Elephan 6 Collective picking up the pieces and putting them back together in the American South. Formed in the small, hidden town of Sparta, Tennessee, guitarist and vocalist Matt Pelham, bassist Roger Dabbs, keyboardist Parrish Yaw, and drummer Rollum Haas began playing their quirky and contagious pop as the Features around Pelham's colorful personal ruminations.&amp;quot; - Allmusic.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We've never seen a drummer leap five feet above his stool and land perfectly in time before, or that much head nodding in the audience. If The Features dont break in the UK, it wont be their fault- this band possesses everything needed to go the distance.&amp;quot; Hit Sheet &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jenn</member_name><member_id>10142965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270166565000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267973132000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Features with Manchester Orchestra, Biffy Clyro and O’Brother</name><id>12806929</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269993600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/12806929/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/5/global_13497269.jpeg</photo_url></item>