<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>104 Shrewsbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.263909</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 752-3862</phone><name>Brew City Grill &amp; Brew House</name><city>Worcester</city><id>782731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.789524</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the unpreventable cancellation of Northworks - WE WILL NOW BE GOING TO BREW CITY - a one of a kind establishment that features a consistent, multiple award winning selection of beer that includes over 155 different beers with 40 on tap; local, craft brewed, domestic and imported. Now featuring 3 beer engines pouring limited edition cask conditioned ales. You can travel the world without leaving your seat! Our Big Beer Series features extreme and limited release ales and lagers in "Bomber" bottles. In addition to the great beer selection, Brew City offers unique and classic cocktails plus premium wines from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Casual dining with a flare! Enjoy Worcester's finest charbroiled specialties, creative pasta dishes, fresh seafood, grilled pizzas, appetizers and more all freshly prepared and served in a classy industrial-tech ambiance. Brew City also features Worcester's first "burger bar." Stop in to try the best burger you'll ever have. You can create your own burger from over 38 trillion combinations. &lt;em&gt;This is the ultimate burger experience!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Catch all of your favorite sports action in a comfortable bar and dining area with 18 TVs, including large screen plasma TVs. Play KENO, the Daily Race Game or your lottery numbers at the bar and enjoy our various forms of entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Brew City you'll be comfortable in jeans or a suit. Whether you're a local or just want to feel like one, no matter what you want to do, there's only one place in Worcester where you can do it all ... Brew City! &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>details to follow on Saturday morning</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298244061000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297897788000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northworks event - REPLACED WITH BREW CITY!</name><id>16593018</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298160000000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/16593018/</event_url></item>