<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Film starts at 8:00 PM at Coolidge Corner Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet around 7 before the film at Panera's Sandwich Shop across the street from the theater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ENCOUNTERS AT THE END OF THE WORLD&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Werner Herzog&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be hosting a meetup before this screening at 6:30 if this works out well for most people  Let me know by saying so in the Comment text-box. I'll wait until I see how many people are interested before choosing where we will meet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the execrable Rescue  Dawn, Werner Herzog has come back with hat in hand, forgiven  and fully  redeemed. While not the masterpiece of Grizzly Man,  the psychotic Kraut?s  latest documentary is a thrilling ride  nonetheless, as he visits the no man?s  land of Antarctica with  his usual obsessions and pet theories. As always, Herzog  narrates  the proceedings with his wry tone and heady revelations, and while  he  can often come across as a bit nutty, he?s surprisingly matter-of-fact  most of  the time, letting the scientists and adventurers of the  region speak for  themselves. And yes, quite a bit of data and  research appear onscreen, though  not to the point of alienating  the layman. After all, it?s less about ?the  facts? anyway,  as Herzog is not using this film to promote a political agenda or  environmental conversion (as much as the evidence of global warming  was on  display), but rather to signal the death knell of exploration  as a testing  ground for man?s self-worth. Once the frozen continent  was discovered and  ?conquered? (always a relative concept  given its vastness), the final frontier  was lost forever, a line  of demarcation as vital and unsettling as the closing  of the American  West. Now, as Herzog laments again and again, mankind is reduced  to pushing boundaries only in terms of their effect on the record  books or media  coverage. That?s not to say that ego and greed  didn?t drive the explorers of  old, but even then, it still seemed  as if man had something left to  prove.&lt;br /&gt;As expected, the photography  is  stunning and appropriately humbling, as vast stretches of both ice  and ocean  lay before us with eerie silence. And yet, a small community  has been  established; a veritable university of loners, eccentrics,  and vagabonds looking  for something just shy of normal. Important  work is being conducted here, but  from mechanics and cooks alike,  we also sense a need to escape the pressure and  responsibilities  of modern life, even if these people work as hard as they ever  have  in the ?other world.? This is no idle vacation; everyone must  pull their  own weight and act as a small, though essential piece  in a very odd puzzle.  Because we follow these people around as  they conduct business, there?s a  comforting routine in all we  see, as if we half expect a place like Antarctica  to be anarchic  and wild. These are the daily realities, this is what the rest of  us can learn from such a place, and here is where it all occurs.  And even though  Herzog promised he would not be making a film  about those ubiquitous penguins,  even he could not resist their  presence. Still, leave it to Herzog to be the one  man who would  focus not on the cutesy communities of penguin life, but rather  the solitary bird who appears to have been struck by a suicidal  impulse and the  subsequent journey it takes to the continent?s  interior, never to be seen again.  Perhaps Herzog half admires  the confused penguin, as if, instead of playing it  safe, it decided  to carve out its own unique path amidst the indifference of ice  and snow.  Ruthless  Reviews&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209681137000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>The IFFB ends with a bang with Werner Herzog's latest documentary.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208467870000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>IFFB Closing Night- Herzog's Encounters at the End of the World</name><id>7759458</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209508200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7759458/</event_url></item>