<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The TempleCon event is awesome, so make sure you sign up for it - www.templecon.org.  Pre-registration period ends on January 15th, and it's cheaper if you preregister, so you should do so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many centuries ago, a band of paladins fell from grace, turning against their brethren.  The black guards, as they were called, were defeated in a great battle and their grim fortress, the Iron Tower, was razed.  Among its ruins a crypt was to be built.  The Iron Crypt would serve two purposes:&lt;br /&gt;First, it would house the bodies of the heretical black guards.&lt;br /&gt;Second, it would serve as a store house for evil artifacts and cursed magic &lt;br /&gt;items that were brought back by questing paladins.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A small abbey was built nearby and generations of monks dedicated their lives to the creation of three impregnable vaults that would stand through the ages.  The world's greatest thieves, magicians, and seers were called together to design a series of puzzles and deadly traps.  They mixed eldritch wards, mighty clockwork traps, and multiple fail safes to ensure that the crypt would never be violated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After many years of dedication and labor, the Monks of the Saint had finally achieved their goal.  Construction of the Iron Crypt was completed and they sealed it and its wicked cargo for all eternity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unbeknownst to the brotherhood, their impregnable crypt had a single weakness: the very monks that had built it, for they knew its secrets.  Late one night, an unspeakable evil crept into the abbey.  The creature devoured the souls of half of its residents and terrorized the rest into submission. The creature forced the remaining monks to help it inside the crypt.  The monks obliged assuming the creature would be destroyed, but once inside, it successfully broke into the first of three vaults releasing an army of wights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your group has been enlisted to enter the Iron Crypt and put to rest the mysterious evil that has been awakened within.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the event coordinators where the game will be.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Hull</member_name><member_id>182922</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202173764000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Last year's game was awesome and so will this one.</why><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199504281000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>D&amp;D 3.5 Adventure - The Iron Crypt</name><id>7035332</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202000400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/7035332/</event_url></item>