<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>126 Myrtle St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.365486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-835- 2913</phone><name>Optimum Health Solution</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1450328</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.232065</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Live Washington DC advocate, Beth Clay replaces film on World Food Day, Oct. 16th. &amp;nbsp;Don't miss this lecture and Q&amp;amp; A.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #bd1a0d"&gt;You have priority. Register by email &amp;nbsp;now. &amp;nbsp;I inadvertently deleted registration list. &amp;nbsp;Please email me to register &amp;amp; be sure I confirm. &amp;nbsp;As you know, space is limited in my home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be informed and empowered about issues that affect you and your loved ones:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;KEEP OUR VOICES AND CHOICES ALIVE : T&lt;/span&gt;ake a stand and voice our rights to preserve our choice to seed, grow, buy, sell and eat organic vegetables, fruit, seeds, nuts, herbs, vitamins supplements. This is our lasting legacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;KEEP ORGANIC STANDARDS PURE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Pure organic foods hold the nutrients, enzymes, vitamins and minerals that gives us life. Protect the integrity of pure organic processes from farm-to-mouth without the use of toxins, pesticides, fertilizers, pasteurization, irradiation, preservatives, artificial ingredients, or GMO's.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;KEEP OURSELVES &amp;amp; OTHERS INFORMED &amp;amp; EDUCATED: E&lt;/span&gt;ducate ourselves and others about the impact and changes in national and international laws, FDA guidelines, CODEX standards and other marketplace actions that affect our freedom to make our own health choices, including labeling of food that is clear, consistent, and truthful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;TAKE ACTION TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Our legacy to our children, grand children and ourselves is to take action NOW and set a stage of certainty for health and vitality.&amp;nbsp; Besides immediate action on legislations and positions in hearings, there are many creative actions taken from grass roots to grass tops to be effective and&amp;nbsp;make a difference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beth Clay is absolutely delightful, well-informed activist with a wonderful sense of humor. &lt;strong&gt;Beth Clay, Senior Vice President of Capitol Strategy Consultants, Inc. represents the Hippocrates Institute and POP Campaign as their Washington, DC Government Relations Consultant. &amp;nbsp;An internationally recognized expert in integral health policy and dietary supplement regulations, Ms Clay has been at the forefront of protecting health freedom and advancing the cause of improved health through natural causes.&lt;/strong&gt; After spending 7 years&amp;nbsp;at the National Institutes of Health, including 2 years in the original Office of Alternative Medicine,&amp;nbsp;in 1998&amp;nbsp;Ms. Clay was invited to&amp;nbsp;lead the health care investigations for the House of Representatives'&amp;nbsp;Committee&amp;nbsp;on Government Reform and Oversight with then Chairman&amp;nbsp;Dan Burton.&amp;nbsp; Their initial&amp;nbsp;investigation&amp;nbsp;was the role of complementary&amp;nbsp;medicine&amp;nbsp;in our health care system.&amp;nbsp; Over the course of four&amp;nbsp;and a half&amp;nbsp;years,&amp;nbsp;29 hearings would be conducted looking at issues such as&amp;nbsp;complementary&amp;nbsp;therapies, dietary supplement regulations, the epidemic&amp;nbsp;rise of&amp;nbsp;autism&amp;nbsp;and vaccine injury.&amp;nbsp; While working for Congress, Ms. Clay&amp;nbsp;served&amp;nbsp;on the US Delegation to the CODEX Alimentarius Committee on&amp;nbsp;Nutrition and Foods for Special Dietary Uses.&amp;nbsp; She was instrumental two years ago in getting Senators Hatch and Harkin to state on the record in the United States Senate HELP Committee for the first time that the FDA does not&amp;nbsp;have&amp;nbsp;the authority to adopt CODEX guidelines affecting dietary supplements&amp;nbsp;without&amp;nbsp;Congressional approval.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When: &amp;nbsp;Sunday, October 16&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;5:30 - 6:30 pm &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;raw, vegan, organic potluck - bring a dish for 8 with utensils - for ideas see recipes on &amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #0000FF ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;www.optimumhealthsolution.org/forum.htm&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;6:30 - 8:30 pm Beth Clay,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;skyped from Washington, DC followed by Q &amp;amp; A&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where: &amp;nbsp;126 Myrtle Street, Waltham&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #0000FF ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;click here for directions (see 2nd location)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reservations required. &amp;nbsp;Email&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:bbski@stanfordalumni.org" target="_blank"&gt;bbski@stanfordalumni.org&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and be sure to receive confirmation or call Betsy at 617-835-2913. Tax-deductible Donations to Optimum Health Solution's kids program and expenses appreciated.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://bit.ly/nZ8yZe</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Bragg</member_name><member_id>5026531</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318805057000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314208837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck &amp; FREE Talk: Beth Clay</name><id>30738821</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318800600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/30738821/</event_url></item>