<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hingham, MA</address_2><address_1>250 Martin's Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.253262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>World's End</name><city>Hingham</city><id>161237</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.871613</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for a nice afternoon hike at World's End! Explore four coastal drumlins -- Pine Hill, Planter's Hill, and the double drumlins of World's End proper -- all connected by over four miles of walking paths that offer dramatic views of the Weir River, Hingham Harbor, and the Boston skyline. The Reservation's hills are traversed by tree-lined roads and dotted with tree groves. In between are broad grassy fields that attract butterflies and are managed to provide habitat for grassland-nesting birds.  We will also be able to enjoy some Fall Foliage on this Hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are providing a carpool from Braintree and highly recommend members carpool as parking will be limited especially if it's a nice day.  We will depart promptly @ 1:30pm as it's a 25 minute drive depending on traffic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to arrive a few minutes early. We will wait a few minutes (5-10) for stragglers. Once on the trails, you could catch-up with us, but you'd have to know which direction we have headed and the quickest route to catch-up.  We will plan to Hike about 1.5-2 hours or whatever the will of the Group is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring plenty of water. A hat is recommended as well.  You may want to bring bug spray and/or sunscreen.  Sneakers or hiking boots are recommended.  While this is a pet-friendly venue, this event is for adult humans only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginner-Friendly Hike @ World's End w/ Carpool - Take 2!&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 21st @ 2pm w/ 1:30pm Braintree Carpool&lt;br /&gt;World's End&lt;br /&gt;250 Martin's Lane&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA&lt;br /&gt;Phone # for Audubon: 781-740-6665&lt;br /&gt;Website: www.thetrustees.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $5 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: Annual Members - FREE, Members and Guests - $2 per person &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela and Julie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: At least 6 Yes RSVPs by 12pm/Noon on Thursday, November 12th.  Attendance is currently unlimited.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome!  Up to 2 per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Please finalize your RSVP by 8pm on Friday, November 20th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpools: The SSFMG is providing a Braintree Carpool.  If you want to carpool from another area please note it in your RSVP Comments or in the Talk About It Section and coordinate it with other Groups Members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: Heavy rains will cancel.  (We won't mention the 's' word just yet.)  Thurs. 11/19: Forecast calls for light rain on Friday and sunshine in the 50's on Saturday.  See you @ Town Hall or World's End!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to World's End: &lt;br /&gt;From Boston Area, &amp;amp; North: Take Rt. 93 to Exit 7, getting onto Rt. 3 South. Pick up below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 3: Take exit 14 and follow Route 228 north towards Hingham for 6.5 miles. Turn left onto Route 3A and follow for 0.4 mi. Turn right onto Summer Street and, at major intersection with Rockland Street, continue straight across. Road becomes Martin's Lane. Follow for 0.7 mile until it dead ends at entrance and parking area (70 cars). Parking in residential areas is not permitted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Braintree Carpool Lot: Posted on the &amp;quot;Directions to Frequently Used Venues&amp;quot; Discussion Thread which is pinned on the Message Board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***PLEASE NOTE: If you are planning to carpool please note it in your RSVP Comments and/or in the Talk About It Section.  Parking is limited to 70 cars.  Please consider carpooling with other GRoup Members in yoru area if the Braintree carpool is not practical.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet near the parking attendant's station and the trail map.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4336960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259186491000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255888762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginner-Friendly Hike @ World's End w/ Carpool - Take 2!</name><id>11654246</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258830000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11654246/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/7/global_4998583.jpeg</photo_url></item>