<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's make it a meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's an awesome movie screening on Sunday at Somerville Theatre and it's about improv.  Hope to see some of you there!  Afterwards, we should hang out in Davis, grab some food, or how about some candlepin bowling?  Or better yet, more independent movies!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's all the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trust Us, This Is All Made Up&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://tijn.mobi/" target="_blank"&gt;http://tijn.mobi/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://iffboston.bside.com/2009/films/trustusthisisallmadeup_iffboston2009" target="_blank"&gt;http://iffboston.bsid...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Alex Karpovsky in attendance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you think improvisation is all sketch comedy and drunken audience suggestions, you obviously haven’t seen a performance by TJ Jagodowski and Dave Pasquesi. This masterful duo takes the art of improv to radical new levels by crafting an entirely original, hour-long play each time they perform. A word or a look from one to the other is all that prompts the creation of a story that will never be performed again. The mental dexterity and stamina needed to form and perpetuate the narrative are astounding in themselves—particularly when one of the actors takes over a character the other originated. But the trust and intense understanding each has of the other’s tiniest communications make the feat even more unforgettable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRUST US, THIS IS ALL MADE UP documents a hilarious one-time comedy performance by TJ and Dave, following them as they prepare before the show and evaluate what happened afterward. With his previous films, WOODPECKER (IFFBoston 2008) and THE HOLE STORY (IFFBoston 2005), director Alex Karpovky used short-form improv as part of the scriptwriting process and presented us with obsessive protagonists fixated on one vital idea. In TRUST US, that vital idea is improv itself, but here the protagonists’ obsession results in a unique creative partnership—and the delight and wonder of their audience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Kristina Aikens&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Screening supported by AltCom Alternative Comedy Festival&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet right outside the theatre doors....I look goofy, easy enough.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241743253000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240589246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Awesome improv movie screening Sunday part of the Boston Independent Film Fest</name><id>10259339</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240780500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/10259339/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>