<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>[b]Update[/b]

I will be at the theater lobby by 7:20; the movie is at 7:50. I strongly suggest buying your ticket ahead of time at fandango.com. Be sure to pick the right date! It's Saturday! I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie is upstairs, I'll be waiting by the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where the tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand. We'll head into the move 10 minutes before showtime.

For new folks, if you miss the gathering before the film, no worries, we regroup after the film just outside the room where the film shows. And then we go out to discuss the movie over munchies and a beer. Or two. 

[b]Synopsis[/b]

In a land of mad scientists and diabolical inventions, what do you do when you're born with a hunch on your back?

You become an Igor.

A hilarious twist on the classic monster movie, "Igor" tells the story of one Igor who's sick of being a lowly lab assistant with a Yes Master's degree and dreams of becoming a scientist. When his cruel master kicks the bucket a week before the annual Evil Science Fair, Igor finally gets his chance.

With the help of two of his experimental creations - Brain, a brain in a jar who's a little light on brains, and Scamper, a cynical bunny brought back from being road kill, Igor embarks on building the most evil invention of all time, a huge, ferocious monster. Unfortunately, instead of turning out evil, the monster turns out as Eva, a giant aspiring actress who wouldn't hurt a fly.

Just when the load on his back can't get any heavier, Igor and his band of monstrous misfits uncover an evil plot that threatens their world. Now, they must fight to save it and prove that heroes come in all shapes and sizes.

Igor is directed by award-winning animation veteran Tony Leondis ("Lilo &amp; Stitch 2: Stitch Has a Glitch") and written by Chris McKenna ("American Dad!"). Exodus Film Group CEO John D. Eraklis produces along with seasoned animation executive and Exodus president Max Howard who has collaborated on such animated blockbusters as Disney's "Lion King" and "Aladdin," and Warner Bros.' "Space Jam" and "The Iron Giant."

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/SrSX8NYN2x4&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222818738000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219892837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Igor</name><id>8637664</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221952500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8637664/</event_url></item>