<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>73 Rocky Neck Ave</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.607269</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>73 Rocky Neck Ave</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>8203822</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.656036</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is an end of the 2012 summer ART Event that celebrates Nights on the Neck. It’s run from June thru September on the first Thursday of each month from 5:30 to 9pm. &lt;br /&gt;

Come with us and visit the quant galleries that host receptions with delightfully tasteful refreshments. There are Musicians, dancers, authors, historians and other entertainers that give performances and lectures throughout this scenic art colony. &lt;br /&gt;

The many folks that have done this visit always come back for more. It's just a really fantastic night out! We walk the neck, visit the open galleries, listen to music, watch entertainers, and then end up at one of the restaurants that overlook the quiet little, moon lit, harbor for drinks &amp;amp; food. This is a go-at-your-own-pace type of event where no one is ever that far out-of –sight. So come enjoy the night with us and share your enthusiasm for these fine art exhibits. &lt;br /&gt;

This is a shared event with other meetup groups. &lt;br /&gt;

*WE WILL MEETUP @ 5pm at The Rocky Neck Art Colony sign- the sign is at the public lot at the base of Rocky Neck Avenue. If you are unable to join us at 5, join us when you can. Contact # is: 978.289.7679 or 603.204.1657. This is a mostly outdoor event - therefore, weather dependant. Please make sure to check for an update if weather is questionable. If light rain or drizzle, umbrellas will work fine for the galleries are mostly all indoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**You can find the schedule and additional information for September 6th at: www.rockyneckartcolony.org &lt;br /&gt;

Entertainment Schedule- Thursday, September 6 &lt;br /&gt;

 5:00- 6:00 pm: At the park across from the public parking lot- The Adventure Chantry Singers &lt;br /&gt;

5:30-6:15pm: Elynn Kroger Gallery, 15 Rocky Neck Ave. - The Treetop Charlatans &lt;br /&gt;

6:00-6:45pm : The Goetemann Gallery, 37 Rocky Neck Ave. -Joe Ann Hall- Author &lt;br /&gt;

6:00 - 8:00: Sigrid Olsen Gallery- 42 Rocky Neck Gallery, Isla Beach House Party &lt;br /&gt;

 A Backyard Party &lt;br /&gt;

6:45- 7:30pm: Imagine Gallery, 43 Rocky Neck Ave. -Liz Framer &amp;amp; The Kickers &lt;br /&gt;

7:15- 8:00pm: The Rocky Neck Gallery, 53 Rocky Neck Gallery- Sylvan Roots &lt;br /&gt;

7:45- 8:45pm: Mad Fish Wharf, 77 Rocky Neck Ave. - Julie Dukas Jazz Band &lt;br /&gt;

8:45- 9:30pm: The Center, 6 Wonson St. -Clara Kebabian&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347028218000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346708269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nights On The Neck- Rocky Neck Art Colony- ART WALK in Gloucester</name><id>80675302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346965200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/80675302/</event_url></item>