<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sandra Wong and Ross Martin come together in a dynamic combination of nyckelharpa/fiddle, and guitar to explore music from all corners of the globe, including their own compositions. Sandra and Ross have been playing music together for 8 years and are now taking their duo on the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reaching into their individual roots of Classical Western, Bluegrass, Jazz, Scandinavian, Middle-eastern, Old-time American music and more, their arrangements honor each tradition while moving into new, unchartered territory. Whether it’s old-time tunes in 7, Bach on nyckelharpa and guitar, Swedish tunes from hundreds of years ago brought into a 21st century arrangement, original compositions or simply beautifully played renditions of traditional folk melodies from around the world; Sandra and Ross create a musical playground for everyone (both musicians and listeners) to explore, play, stretch, and grow in a joyful space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://sandrawongmusic.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://sandrawongmusic.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://rossmartinguitar.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://rossmartinguitar.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$9 +$1 preservation fee if reservation is received by August 1, $14 + $1 preservation fee thereafter. &lt;br /&gt;

reservation requests to notlobreservations at gmail dot com &lt;br /&gt;

notloB website - &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345258025000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342550712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sandra Wong (niclelharpa, fiddle) and Ross Martin (guitar)</name><id>73740512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345246200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/73740512/</event_url></item>