<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Chestnut St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.075863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Music Hall</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>671468</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.759360</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Solitary Life of Cranes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part city symphony part visual poem from director Eva Weber, 'The Solitary Life of Cranes' explores the invisible life of a city, its patterns and hidden secrets, seen through the eyes of crane drivers working high above its streets. Within the loose structure of a day, starting with the drivers climbing up at dawn and ending with them coming down after a nightshift, the film observes the city as it awakens with a bustle of activity, through the lull of midday and the manic rush in the evening, until it calms down again deep into the night. Throughout the film, the drivers share their thoughts and reflections on London and life in general. What emerges is a lyrical mediation about how our existence is shaped through the environment we inhabit, both for the drivers high up in the sky and the people on the ground they are watching.&lt;br /&gt;(U.K., 2008, 27m) Courtesy of Girl Out Prod.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://cityofcranes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Life of Cranes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Last Truck: The Closing of a GM Plant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Dec. 23, 2008, two days before Christmas, the General Motors assembly plant in Moraine, Ohio shut its doors. As a result, 2,500 workers and 200 management staff were left without jobs, while the closing is also sure to trigger the loss of thousands of related jobs and businesses. But the GM workers lost much more than jobs, including the pride they share in their work and the camaraderie built through the years. The Last Truck views the final months of the plant through the workers' eyes as they reflect on their work and consider their next steps. In revealing interviews with people who considered themselves more family than co-workers, the film reveals the emotional toll of losing not just a job, but a sense of self. Their stories are told with immediacy and a compassionate camera.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(U.S., 2009, 40m) Courtesy of HBO Films&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards, we'll meetup at The original Friendly Toast for Discussion.  Look for John standing with a Meetup Sign (maybe in Red, maybe not) out in front immediately following the film.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252287176000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Telluride by the Sea '09 - The Solitary Life of Cranes &amp; The Last Truck</name><id>11306640</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253383200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11306640/</event_url></item>