<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Morse Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01010</zip><lat>42.092870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quinebaug River</name><city>Brimfield</city><id>592002</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.172670</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Quinebaug River Canoe Trail- Brimfield MA.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet at 10:00 am for a shuttle&lt;/b&gt; - drive cars to takeout point, and ride a few back to put in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leader:&lt;/b&gt; Mark Roberts mroberts@cia.com 401-533-1883&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring a lunch&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Suitable for all levels of experience and boat lengths. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A change of clothes in a waterproof bag is required unless you have a dry suit or wet suit.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quinebaug River Canoe Trail Holland to East Brimfield, MA Shuttle &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Put-in at Holland Pond and paddle down the Quinebaug River Canoe Trail to East Brimfield Lake and Long Pond. In this area, the Quinebaug River winds through marshland filled with wildlife.  Stop for lunch at a rope swing on East Brimfield Lake.  Take out is at the Long Pond Boat ramp.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;GPS coordinates for put-in:  N 42 04 932    W 072 09 801&lt;br /&gt;                             for take out:  N 42 06 777    W 072 07 909&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Directions:  Take I-90 Mass Pike west, to I-84 west.  Take exit 3B to Route 20 &lt;br /&gt;toward Brimfield. Continue on Route 20 until you reach the intersection of Route 20 and Route 148 - about one and a half miles. Go straight through the light and continue on Route 20 for another 1 and 1/2 mile. Take a left onto Holland East Brimfield Road - there will be a sign for Holland and a large sign for the Quinebaug Cove Campground.  Continue approximately 2  miles and take a right onto Morse Road- there will be a brown canoe launch sign.  &lt;br /&gt;After 1/10 of a mile, take a sharp left down the hill on a dirt access road.  &lt;br /&gt;At the bottom of the hill, take a right following the canoe launch signs.  Put-in is 2/10 mile on the right before the Pond Bridge Road bridge.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Shaved head, 5'9" 200 pounds.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211206061000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Lovely scenic paddle through a long meandering narrow river [big creek really].</why><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209404629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quinebaug River Canoe Trail, Brimfield MA</name><id>7828477</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211032800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/7828477/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/d/1/global_3956513.jpeg</photo_url></item>