<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>172 N Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.209446</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.224.9534</phone><name>Holiday Inn</name><city>Concord</city><id>764609</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.537178</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am hearing it said by the Establishment and some in the media that the Tea Party has lost it's momentum.&amp;nbsp; That we are irrelevant.&amp;nbsp; I urge all that read this post and email to join in on Thursday (it's okay to be late) and support fair treatment of any and all Liberty Group members in public service or office.&amp;nbsp; Jack Kimball is being destroyed by a thousand cuts and most of them are falsehoods being spread to discredit him.&amp;nbsp; The actual charges against him are inaccurate and do not nearly rise to the level of problems former NHGOP Chairman have caused or been in.&amp;nbsp; The NHGOP is still paying off the huge financial costs caused by former Cullen's tenure,&amp;nbsp;there was no hearing to force him to resign.&amp;nbsp; This hearing is a lynching not a trial. We must stand up now and demand fair treatment not a media campaign bent on character assassination.&amp;nbsp; It is of great importance for all to attend this rally. The Rally isn't to say Jack is perfect but rather to demand fair and equal treatment.&amp;nbsp; This attack leveled at Jack Kimball was a poorly planned lynching and we must oppose the way this was done.&amp;nbsp; I will be there and stay until the kangaroo court is adjourned.&amp;nbsp; There are good people on the Executive Board but they are getting dishonest information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know why we formed this movement, self serving political decisions.&amp;nbsp;This is another bad decision and now their ego's can't admit their handling of this&amp;nbsp;is awful and they are our political leaders. No wonder we raised the Debt Ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must send a message to them to stop this action against Kimball whether you like him or not this is being pushed by dishonest rumors and some that want nothing more than to further their political careers.&amp;nbsp; I am convinced this move after it plays out will cost more careers than the conspirators of this ill conceived plan imagine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and make your stand for liberty with me this Thursday. "Live Free or Die, Death is not the worst of evils."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Semper Fi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jerry&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will Rally in front of the State House</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerry DeLemus</member_name><member_id>9270878</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314917073000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rochester-912-project</urlname><id>1452537</id><group_lat>43.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>Rochester 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314588192000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rally to Support Jack Kimball and to stop the Establishments Public Attacks</name><id>31337092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314912600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rochester-912-project/events/31337092/</event_url></item>