<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Memorial Boulevard</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02840</zip><lat>41.488660</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newport Yachting Center</name><city>Newport</city><id>1345873</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.290616</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>OK Gang we are going to go all the way :-) Sunday, Newport  R.I.  &lt;br /&gt;Let us enjoy a wonderful Champagne Brunch From 11 am to 12:30 at the Newport Yachting Center &lt;br /&gt;after we have tantalized our palette will we stroll over  to the &amp;quot;Grand&amp;quot; wine tasting and hob nob among those who know and those who act like they know, sipping our way through only the best wine's that Newport has to offer. We will then be Wowed and amazed by there International Chef's as they prepare delectable entrees for us to taste and watch them as they prepare there famous international cuisine.  At precisely 5 pm the &amp;quot;Grand&amp;quot; clock at the &amp;quot;Grand&amp;quot; Yachting center will strike 5 bells at this time we will make a mad dash to our car's before our fairy Godmother's spell wears off and we are turned back into New Haven Wine and Dining :-) Buy your tickets on line,&lt;a href="http://www.newportwinefest.com/tickets.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newportwin...&lt;/a&gt; below is a link for a bus schedule that goes out of New Haven to Newport.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bus Packages&lt;br /&gt;From Connecticut to Newport – by Premier Bus Lines&lt;br /&gt;Premier Limousine will also be providing transportation from Hartford and New Haven to the Yachting Center for $40 round trip. From the Hartford area, the bus will depart from the Main Street Commuter Lot in Glastonbury, CT. From the New Haven area, the bus will depart from the Commuter lot at the corner of Route 40 and Devine Street in North Haven, CT. Please contact Premier Limousine at  1-866 885-LIMO  1-866 885-LIMO  for more information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Private transportation by limousine or town car will also be available from Connecticut to Newport. For more information please contact Premier Limousine at 1-866 885-LIMO. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282678377000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281553879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"NEWPORT" Wine Festival  "You Don't Want To Miss"</name><id>14392741</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282489200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/14392741/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/1/global_4236481.jpeg</photo_url></item>