<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>NOTE NOTE NOTE :: WE HAVE BUMPED UP THE TIME. WE ARE STARTING AT 4 PM!! If you can't make it until 7, well, we will still be playing. BUT be cool and come out at four. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the spirit of the holiday, THANK YOU to all of you who come out at night and make frisbee so much fun. And since it is a holiday weekend after all... how about some more nighttime disc action! If you're in the Boston area and you can rouse yourself from your tryptophan-induced coma, come play with us on FRIDAY NIGHT at 4pm, in the usual spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet around 4 pm on Cambridge Common (outside Harvard Square), throw the discs around for a while and learn each other's names, then play ultimate starting around 4:30. All are welcome, regardless of skill level -- just as long as you want to have fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually call it quits whenever we get haggard and cold like dogs. We will have plenty of time to head over to Uno's or Herrell's for drinks, snacks or ice cream -- everyone is encouraged to come along, so that we can get to know some of the people we've been playing frisbee with in the dark.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;Jim&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196024648000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195678525000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Extra! Day-After-Turkey-Day Disc (NEW TIME! 4PM)</name><id>6784271</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195851600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/6784271/</event_url></item>