<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-325</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>447074</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Title: Opportunities in Green Investing &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP! &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/calendar/11425966/"&gt;RSVP link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Growing evidence suggests that the green economy is likely to be one of the most powerful engines of global economic growth over the next decade.  Enormous environmental challenges —climate change and resource scarcity — are perhaps the greatest challenges ever faced, and the solutions to these problems must be huge.  Climate change threatens our short-term prosperity and our long-term survival, and global policies are rapidly being developed to reduce carbon emissions.  Resource scarcity is also a huge issue facing society as populations and incomes grow, while finite supplies of key resources like energy, food, water, and other commodities dwindle as we struggle to meet ever-growing global demand. &lt;br /&gt;These environmental concerns have spurred massive societal efforts on renewable energy, energy efficiency and other solutions, creating a number of rapidly-growing, multi-billion dollar industries.   Winslow Management Company’s funds seek to capture these tremendous growth opportunities, by identifying the key green industries, technologies and companies that are driving this economic transformation.&lt;br /&gt; Featured speaker Matthew Patsky of Winslow will discuss these investment opportunities, and provide examples of the industries and companies that Winslow believes are best poised to capitalize on the green technology revolution.&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Patsky has over 20 years of investment research and management experience. He is co-portfolio manager of the Winslow Green Growth Fund and Winslow Green Solutions Fund.   Prior to joining Winslow in 2002, he served as Director of Equity Research for Boston-based Adams Harkness, Inc., where he supervised 21 research analysts focused on emerging growth technology, healthcare and consumer companies.  Mr. Patsky frequently speaks on a range of green investment topics, including renewable energy, climate change, and the organic and natural products industry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our Google Group - BostonIBD - for online discussion go to &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google..."&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;. .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join in our virtual trading, go to this link for instructions and signup links: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google..."&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own decisions about investing your money. Investment ideas and recommendations made in our meetings and our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255477387000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253542285000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BIG Special Speakers Meetup - Matthew Patsky - Opportunities in Green Investing</name><id>11425966</id><headcount>43</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254956400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/11425966/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/a/global_10828042.jpeg</photo_url></item>