<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Rhoades St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02124</zip><lat>42.285057</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-825-6877</phone><name>Chez-Vous</name><city>Boston</city><id>393607</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091450</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>includes skate rental</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://www.niagarafallsfamilyfun.com/skates.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you looking for like-minded progressives to skate with in Boston? Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns on wheels? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions while boogying to old school hits?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Socializing for Justice for Roller Skating for Justice at Chez Vous!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO PROGRAM.  NO SPEAKER.&lt;br /&gt;Just strap on your free rental skates and enjoy yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8PM to midnight, ALL AGES, EIGHT BUCKS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yep, that's right.  This is the same ROLLER BOOGIE you've read about in the Globe, Herald, Phoenix, and Weekly Dig.   These old school fundraisers are thrown together to keep Boston's last roller rink, Chez Vous, alive.  This time, DJs 7L, Knife (Marinate) and resident disco king Colbourne will be keeping you rolling.  (Yes, it is as fun as it sounds.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW DO YOU GET TO CHEZ VOUS BY PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION? Hop a quick bus from Forest Hills Station in JP - take the 21 or 31 and end up at the intersection of Morton and Blue Hill Ave.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP yes, maybe or no&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_______________________&lt;br /&gt;Socializing for Justice (SoJust) is for FEMINISTS, ANTI-RACISTS, QUEER PIONEERS, ENVIRONMENTALISTS, CLASS ACTIVISTS, GENDERBENDERS, ARTISTS,  and all people across Greater Boston working for justice. But it's not work! Instead, we're building a strong cross-issue network through fun social events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At SoJust events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social.  And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're putting the SOCIAL back in social justice!  If you think this group MIGHT be for you - IT IS.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1176143593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173151763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Roller Skating for Justice</name><id>5540897</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175817600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5540897/</event_url></item>