<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>259 Massapoag Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02334</zip><lat>42.059466</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-238-6566</phone><name>Borderland State Park</name><city>Easton</city><id>793864</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.166649</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet at the Visitors Center &lt;br /&gt;259 Massapoag Avenue&lt;br /&gt;North Easton, MA 02356&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please add a commentto your rsvp syaing if you can offer a ride or if you need one, and where you could meet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Borderland is one of the most historically significant tracts of publicly owned land in the Commonwealth. Created in the early 1900s by artist and suffragist Blanche Ames and her botanist husband Oakes, Borderland offers many of the same pleasures that the Ames family enjoyed: walking and horseback riding on woodland trails, fishing and canoeing in the ponds, or, in winter, ice-skating and sledding. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Borderland encompases 1773 acres of woodlands, fields, ponds and unique geological formations. The park is truly a “borderland” in that it lies between gradually rising hills to the north and much flatter land to the south. The result is a mix of habitats, supporting a rich variety of wildlife.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are three major ponds at Borderland and several smaller bodies of water. Lower Leach is 100 acres in size, created in 1825 to create water power for an iron works further downstream on the Poquanticut Brook. It has an average depth of five feet.  Pud's Pond was created by the Ames family in 1906 and named after Blanche's father. When walking next to the spillway you can see the white roads inlaid in the dam when it was repaired in 1926. Upper Leach Pond was created by the Ames family in 1939 for wildlife habitat and recreation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The glaciated cliffs and outcroppings on the northern side of the park make the geology of Borderland unusually interesting. Throughout the park are several easily discernible examples of glacial “erratics,” granite boulders that were torn loose from the bedrock and deposited some distance away. Another interesting feature is the glacial riverbeds, areas strewn with a multitude of boulders and stones. These areas are evidence of the ferocious energy produced by the run-off from melting glaciers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From north: Take Rte. 128 south to Rte. 95 south (towards Providence). Take exit 10 (Sharon, Walpole and Coney Street). Take a left at the end of the ramp and follow this road, two or three miles to the traffic lights in Sharon Center. Go straight thru this intersection and immediately bear right onto Pond St. Follow Pond St. for 1-1/2 miles until you come to a traffic rotary. Go half way around the rotary and continue onto Massapoag Ave. for three miles to the park entrance, on your left&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289059545000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287414860000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Borderland State Park walk</name><id>15146301</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288450800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/15146301/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/4/2/global_18857186.jpeg</photo_url></item>