<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>792 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Royal East</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669107</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097340</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>21.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It is important that you make your reservations by E-mail or telephone before June 23 with a call to our number, (617—547-1497).  Leave your name and telephone, and we’ll confirm within days. Now would be just the time to reply here at your computer or dial our number.  When you arrive present your check, (for $21.00 per person), and choose your seat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We always have a good time at these luncheons; and it’s a real pleasure to greet old friends and new. And the Chinese food is varied and plentiful and our hosts, Otto and Ken, are eager to please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A word on the program of the day:  Prof. Mark Lindley, a longtime member and friend of GBH, has just had his 3rd book on an Indian subject published. His original year-long stay at the Atheist Centre to write a book on Gandhi in conjunction with Lavanam, a son of Gora, was financed by HAM. The book documents Gandhi's  progression towards a more Humanistic viewpoint under the influence of Gora, who was greatly respected and praised by Gandhi, especially for his social betterment projects.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mark has also published a book about J. C. Kumarappa, a great innovator of the ecological approach to Economics.  His latest work, a biography of Gora, the great exponent of Positive Atheism, has just been published by The Gandhi Library. Mark will weave these 3 subjects together for us in what is sure to be a fascinating and informative talk.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277577498000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276802390000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Boston Humanists: Summer Solstice Luncheon</name><id>13832543</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277573400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/13832543/</event_url></item>