<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>One of the great things about having a White Mountain Forest season parking pass ($20 for 1/or $25 for 2 stickers) is that it includes some campgrounds that are first come first serve or $3.00 for the overnight access to a few camping areas. A pass can be obtained at many locations in the White Mountain Forest area.  After a tank of gas and a long ride up, it's nice to know there are still some bargains around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is primitive (but nice) camping with the car still close by. You will need to bring all of your camping needs, food/drink, water, and don't forget your hiking gear if your hiking the next day. There are pit toilets in the area, some deli food shops and gas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The area  I have in mind has roads and  hiking trails so we can plan an easy evening hike if you wish. We will be in the vicinity of many 4000Ft peaks and wooded trails. Remember that it is still cold at night. Look up Twin Mountain, NH for the weather forecast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Diane will be coming up after work about 5:30 pm Saturday.  This event can be extended from Friday evening or Saturday morning/afternoon. All we need to do is to park some cars earlier on a chosen site to claim it, and send some people over to meet the group at the Meetup location at 5:30pm. Please email me if you want to help plan this event and I will give you any information you need. Our public meetup location and time is needed because cell phone service is unreliable in the mountains.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members. Be packed and ready to keep your carpool on time.&lt;br /&gt;List your ride needs and offers in your RSVP comments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes from Mom:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Since this website is a public forum, our camping plans will only be emailed  to the campers who RSVP  &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to insure our privacy.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;4 yes RSVP's will be needed to create an official camping event if you don't know each other&lt;/b&gt;. I don't think we will have to fend off any bears, moose or other fears, but you know there is safety in numbers. Your RSVP response is very important- please keep it up to date and let some one know you are canceling so we know your not late or lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://bestsmileys.com/weather/3.gif" border="0" alt='' /&gt; Fowl weather like this cancels this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will email you where we will meet at 5:30 Saturday. The free campsites are first come, first serve so camp site location will not be announced here for this reason and our privacy. Early arrivals are welcome to take claim for our group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213047635000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Haven't you said already, " I wish I could just lay back &amp; enjoy this scenery a little longer"?  This is easy camping. No backpacking to camp, so test out your gear you bought for that wilderness trip &amp; the hike will be down the road in the morning</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210798353000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>White Mountain Forest Camp and Hike</name><id>7939278</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212874200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7939278/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/6/global_4125526.jpeg</photo_url></item>