<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>244 Walton St # 3</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.572140</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Back-N-Touch</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>5075042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.805145</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for an open Imbolc celebration to welcome back the light!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This celebration will be held at an awesome wellness center in Fitchburg, Mass....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet-n-Greet and appetizers will begin from 4:00- 5:00 pm, and the ritual will start promptly at 5pm, so don't be late! Doors will close at 5:00- no late comers!! No exceptions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be doing a guided meditation to go down to the Underworld to meet with the Goddess Brigid, to release that which no longer serves us in our lives...and to do some candle magick to bring about our wishes for the coming year, and to bring back the light!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After, we will have a pot luck feast, which always proves to be terrific, in the kitchen upstairs-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no stove, but plenty of outlets to bring crock pots and hot plates, as well as a refrigerator. PLEASE NOTE!! The Wellness Center must be clean and left as we find it, so that means that everyone needs to bring their own utensils, and take out- anything that you have brought, including the trash. As usual, everyone is expected to pitch in, with set up and clean up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission will be $5.00 per person, and will be collected at the door, to pay the wellness center, as well as a homemade pot luck dish for our feast. The sign-up sheet will be posted on the list a couple of weeks prior to the meet-up. Dress will be casual, and it will be bring-your-own booze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will provide all of the paper products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meet up is limited to 25 people, and will be lots of fun!! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
Your RSVP: Yes &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/47279652/"&gt;Change RSVP&lt;/a&gt; 1 attending  
&lt;p&gt;24 spots available&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/messages/send/?eventId=47279652"&gt;Email Attendees&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/47279652/"&gt;Tools&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/members/5511934/" style="display : block"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Event Host 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/members/5511934/"&gt;Tala&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Tala, Organizer</description><how_to_find_us>You will go through a residentual area, not far from the highway, pull around and park in back, come in the side door- more detailed directions will be comng, prior to the event :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328393685000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pagans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pagan-1307</urlname><id>1221723</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pagan Learning Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326081328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open  Imbolc Celebration</name><id>47280232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328389200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pagan-1307/events/47280232/</event_url></item>