<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Upstairs (between Knapp and Washington Streets)</address_2><address_1>3 Beach Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351558</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-451-2395</phone><name>My Thai in Chinatown</name><city>Boston</city><id>813594</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062557</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are trying our first Sunday meet-up in December...I'm curious to see how it goes.  Let's say 6pm for now, but that may change...stay tuned.  Location also is TBA...please let me know if you have any requests...we may head back to Mai Thai.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh yeah, the book...we're reading The Elegance of the Hedgehog - by M. Barbery &amp;amp; A. Anderson.  This was the winner by a slim margin...the runner-up will be Junuary's selection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Amazon.com/Booklist:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Elegance-Hedgehog-Muriel-Barbery/dp/1933372605/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1290013499&amp;amp;sr=1-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a bourgeois apartment building in Paris, we encounter Renée, an intelligent, philosophical, and cultured concierge who masks herself as the stereotypical uneducated “super” to avoid suspicion from the building’s pretentious inhabitants. Also living in the building is Paloma, the adolescent daughter of a parliamentarian, who has decided to commit suicide on her thirteenth birthday because she cannot bear to live among the rich. Although they are passing strangers, it is through Renée’s observations and Paloma’s journal entries that The Elegance of the Hedgehog reveals the absurd lives of the wealthy. That is until a Japanese businessman moves into the building and brings the two characters together. A critical success in France, the novel may strike a different chord with some readers in the U.S. The plot thins at moments and is supplanted with philosophical discourse on culture, the ruling class, and the injustices done to the poor, leaving the reader enlightened on Kant but disappointed with the story at hand. --Heather Paulson &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be the large group of people who collectively resemble a book club</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292461602000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290013927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Readers: The Elegance of the Hedgehog,  by M. Barbery &amp; A. Anderson</name><id>15477781</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292194800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/15477781/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/e/global_1450046.jpeg</photo_url></item>