<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Avenue of the Arts</address_2><address_1>465 Huntington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-9300</phone><name>Museum of Fine Arts </name><city>Boston</city><id>500439</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the Museum of Fine Arts site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfa.org/calendar/event.asp?eventkey=39697&amp;amp;date=11/4/2009" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mfa.org/ca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anime: Film and Discussion&lt;br /&gt;7 — 9 pm &lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, November 4, 2009&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Remis Auditorium&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Enjoy a brief discussion with anime experts, followed by a screening of the rarely available film &lt;b&gt;The Girl Who Leapt through Time&lt;/b&gt; (2006), an award-winning anime masterpiece about a Tokyo high school student with the power to travel through time. At first she uses her power recklessly, but soon she realizes how profoundly her actions adversely affect others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Ian Condry&lt;/b&gt;, MIT professor and author of Hip-Hop Japan: Rap and the Paths of Cultural Globalization; &lt;b&gt;Susan Napier&lt;/b&gt;, Tufts University Professor and author of Anime: From Akira to Howl's Moving Castle &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;MFA members, seniors, students $10; nonmembers/general admission $13&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I think we should buy our tickets beforehand. Last year's lecture sold out the day of the lecture. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be in the lobby outside the Remis Auditorium starting at 6:00 pm. We can get in the long line that will be starting to form at 6:30 pm to grab seats. There is an overpriced cafe across from the Remis Auditorium if you don't have time to grab a bite to eat before. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About The Girl Who Leapt Through Time (Wikipedia):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Girl_Who_Leapt_Through_Time" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Girl Who Leapt Through Time (Toki o Kakeru Sh&amp;#333;jo) is a 2006 Japanese animated science fiction film set twenty years after the events in novel Toki o Kakeru Sh&amp;#333;jo by Yasutaka Tsutsui. The film focuses on a high school girl who inadvertently gains the power to travel through time and begins using it frivolously to fix problems. It was produced by the animation studio Madhouse and directed by Mamoru Hosoda.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Critical response to The Girl Who Leapt Through Time was very positive, and it won numerous awards, including the Japan Academy Prize for Animation of the Year&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Even though it was not a massive hit at the box office, the film did exceptionally well at the various festivals into which it was entered. The Girl Who Leapt Through Time took home the Gertie Award for the best animated feature film at the thirty-ninth Sitges International Film Festival of Catalonia. It won the Animation Grand Award, given to the year's most entertaining animated film, at the prestigious sixty-first Annual Mainichi Film Awards. It was also awarded the first annual Animation of the Year prize at the thirtieth Japan Academy Prize&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ian Condry's website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/condry/www/" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I am a cultural anthropologist who specializes contemporary Japan, with a focus on media, popular culture, and globalization. My first book Hip-Hop Japan: Rap and the Paths of Cultural Globalization was published in October 2006 from Duke University Press. It is an ethnography of the Japanese rap music scene, exploring issues of race, gender, language, popular music history, and cultural politics primarily through the perspectives of Japanese musicians. Through fieldwork starting 1995-97, I focused on the &amp;quot;genba&amp;quot; (nightclubs, or &amp;quot;actual site&amp;quot;) of Japan's hip-hop scene. I argue that the paths of cultural globalization lead through specific sites of performance, such as nightclubs and recording studios. Such locations help us more deeply understand the dialogue between global/local, producer/consumer, artist/industry. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;My current research project is Global Anime: The Making of Japan's Transnational Popular Culture. I am interested in the making of global anime cultures, focusing on the creators in Tokyo studios, but also considering wider connections to Asia and the US&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Susan Napier:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tufts.edu/home/feature/?p=napier" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tufts.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Don't Call Them Cartoons&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As a child, Susan Napier was perfectly content to stay at home reading comic books and science fiction novels. She admits having no interest in culture, at least 'not the kind my parents would like'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A family meal at a Chinese restaurant in her native Cambridge, Mass., changed all of that. Napier expressed interest in what she recalls as 'a generic Chinese scroll of pagoda and cherry blossoms' on the wall. Soon, Napier's mother, an art historian at Harvard, was escorting her through the East Asian art collection at Boston's Museum of Fine Arts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What followed—falling in love with Asian art and haiku, learning Japanese, spending her senior year of high school teaching English in Japan and getting degrees in Japanese literature and culture from Harvard—has evolved into an academic career mainly focused on the study of the Japanese art forms of manga (printed comics) and anime (animated films). [ &lt;b&gt;MORE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.tufts.edu/home/feature/?p=napier" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tufts.edu/...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfa.org/visit/index.asp?key=4" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mfa.org/vi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Subway&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Because our limited parking fills up quickly--especially during popular exhibitions--we encourage you to take advantage of the MBTA, Boston's public transportation system (known by natives as the &amp;quot;T&amp;quot;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Take the Green Line &amp;quot;E&amp;quot; train to the 'Museum of Fine Arts' stop, or the Orange Line train to the 'Ruggles' stop&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257552605000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256158621000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Anime lecture: "The Girl Who Leapt Thru Time" @ Museum of Fine Arts</name><id>11680618</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257379200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11680618/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/9/8/global_11345784.jpeg</photo_url></item>