<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>149 Pond St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02180</zip><lat>42.464714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-989-2000</phone><name>Stone Zoo</name><city>Stoneham</city><id>669369</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095146</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Take a break from the shopping, crowds at the mall, let’s head on down to the Stone Zoo to help us get into the holiday spirit.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This winter wonderland attracts thousands of visitors each year who get into the holiday spirit by strolling along tree-lined paths lit by thousands of twinkling lights. Upon entering the Zoo, guests will visit Yukon Creek, which not only features dazzling holiday lights but is also home to bald eagles, porcupines, lynx, a gray fox and reindeer. Children will want to make sure they visit with Santa, who awaits their arrival in Santa’s Castle. Jolly Old St. Nick will be available for photos through Dec. 23. After visiting with Santa, enter a magical holiday world filled with fairy tale characters and dancing plush animals.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;ZooLights is open Thursday, November 25, 2010 (Thanksgiving) through Sunday, January 2, 2011. The hours are 5:00 p.m. – 9:00 p.m. ZooLights is closed on December 25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Prices:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Weekend Nights (Friday through Sunday)&lt;br /&gt;$6.00 per person- &lt;a href="https://www.zoonewengland.org/SSLPage.aspx?pid=536&amp;amp;nccsm=15&amp;amp;__nccscid=45&amp;amp;__nccsct=ZooLights+Weekend" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.zooneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5.00 per member - &lt;a href="https://www.zoonewengland.org/SSLPage.aspx?pid=532" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.zooneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Under 2 are free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; We will be at the entrance into the Zoo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who can attend this event: Children of all ages are welcome to come to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are responsible for purchasing your own tickets, remember to dress warm and wear comfortable shoes/boots seeing we will be walking around the zoo checking out all that is to be seen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special notes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nov/Dec:  November 1-Dec 11 we will be collecting donations for the Lazarus House in Lawrence.  If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna will have some of the Masspass books on hand so if you are interested in buying a book let her know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s that time of year again that if the weather is bad we may need to cancel this event remember to check back to see if anything has changed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always we look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the entrance to the zoo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291581797000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290302038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zoo Lights at the Stone Zoo.</name><id>15512775</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291501800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15512775/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/9/global_19760569.jpeg</photo_url></item>