<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>July 6, 2009&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;HI! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Peace and blessings to all!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am sure the last few days brought some extra joy in your life. After much rain, the sun was out... How was your 4th of July weekend? I hope your had a grand and relaxing time with family and friends. At the shrine, the sun enabled families and children to enjoy the grounds.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;On June 28, we had our last INTERFAITH BOOK CLUB MEETING. We decided to take a break for the summer and meet again on September 20th. However, in view of preparing our September meeting we decided to continue our reading, sharing and reflection on the book by Matthew Fox &amp;quot;One River, Many Wells&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On September 20th we will share on CHAPTER THREE: &amp;quot;JOY, SUFFERING, BEAUTY, SACRED SEXUALITY, SYING, RESURRECTION, REINCARNATION (pages 254-372). Enjoy, this summer reading and may we ask you a favor, as you travel and visit places, if you come across any other book you find inspirational for our group, don't forget to bring it along... It can become our next reading.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among the pages we read so far, I was particularly touched by the following: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meditation is about returning home, returning home and finding the greatness that was there all along. As Meister Eckhard put it, God is at home; it is we who have out for a walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To serve others is a work you do on yourself. Meister Eckhard calls this working without a why.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When enlightenment arrives, don't talk too much about it; just live it in your own way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most direct summary of this way of letting go and of mindfulness might be found in Eckhart's words: &amp;quot;the soul grows by subtraction, not by addition.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have considered emptying forms of meditation - those that empty us and take us to the formless center of our existence. Another kind of meditation centers on the experience of creativity and the focusing and gathering in that the discipline of creativity requires of us. This meditation takes us to the God of form. The two kinds of meditations are not exclusive. Creativity often takes solitude and silence and emptying. And true emptying often leads to creativity. But the first kind strives to still the mind (by not striving); the second fills the mind by digging deep into the imagination and honoring the images that are there as gifts of the Holy Spirit. It gathers them up and releases them into our work and into the world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The accessibility of the human to the Divine by way of imagination opens the door to the work of art and thinking, farming and building, crafts and dance as authentic avenues to the Divine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy your summer reading and see you in September.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPCOMING INTERFAITH BOOKCLUB MEETING is going to be on Sunday September 20, at 4:00PM.&lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY -  Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Even if your summer will be so busy as not to allow you to ready the material &amp;quot;assigned&amp;quot;, don't worry and come anyway. It has been my belief and my experience that our simple presence can still foster deep and creative interaction.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, mark your calendars and hope to see you at the meeting. Enjoy this book and continuous blessings on your and your loved ones... HAVE A GREAT SUMMER!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PEACE&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144&lt;br /&gt;pino.ma@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256236652000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246921768000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>INTERFAITH BOOK CLUB</name><id>10816732</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253476800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/10816732/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/a/global_4353546.jpeg</photo_url></item>