<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Marrett Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02421</zip><lat>42.435912</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 861-6559 </phone><name>National Heritage Museum</name><city>Lexington</city><id>796133</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.214696</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I'm staying in town for July 4th weekend, so I planned this patriotic day trip. The Liberty Ride is really fun, I did it once and loved it, it's the perfect tour for July 4th. I have already seen a lot of the sights on the tour, and you can hop on and off all day for your $25 ticket, so my plan is to see the historic stuff at Minuteman National Park and maybe walk around downtown Concord. People can join me or split up, I recommend the historic homes in Lexington and the Concord Museum. The tour features narration by a costumed tour guide. The tour starts at the National Heritage Museum in Lexington at 10 am, but please note the museum doesn't open until 12 pm that day.Free all-day parking; also accessible by the Red Line subway and MBTA bus #62 and #76 from Alewife T station. &lt;b&gt;The tour starts at the National Heritage Museum in Lexington at 10 am, but please note the museum doesn't open until 12 pm that day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minuteman Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/mima/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/mi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.libertyride.us/tours.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.libertyrid...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Liberty Ride: A Unique Trolley Tour of Lexington &amp;amp; Concord&lt;br /&gt;10am - 4pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the birthplaces of American liberty and 19th century literature! Board a classic trolley to ride along the historic Battle Road while your costumed guide recounts the exciting events of April 19, 1775 and the literary legacy that defined American identity and culture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Sites on the Tour&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Liberty Ride offers stops at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Lexington Battle Green, where the Lexington militia confronted 800 British Regulars as the sun rose on April 19, 1775.&lt;br /&gt;    * Buckman Tavern, where the Lexington militia gathered the night before the Battle. (Free admission with Liberty Ride ticket.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Hancock-Clarke House, which was Paul Revere and William Dawes' destination on the night of April 18th, 1775, to warn Samuel Adams and John Hancock of the coming of British troops.(Free admission with Liberty Ride ticket.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Munroe Tavern, which served as the British headquarters and field hospital. (Washington really dined here in 1789!) Beautiful garden with Colonial flowers. (Free admission with Liberty Ride ticket.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Lexington Visitors Center, offering information and hospitality, a diorama of the Battle of Lexington, and a memorial to USS Lexington ships.&lt;br /&gt;    * National Heritage Museum, which presents permanent and changing exhibits celebrating American history and culture from Colonial times to the present. Includes Heritage Café and Museum Shop. (Free admission and parking.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Minute Man National Historical Park. View &amp;quot;The Road to Revolution&amp;quot; (a moving multimedia presentation) and exhibits at the Visitor Center. Free admission and parking. The park includes:&lt;br /&gt;      --Paul Revere Capture Site. A monument marks the place where the famous &amp;quot;midnight ride&amp;quot; of Paul Revere came to an abrupt end.&lt;br /&gt;      --Hartwell Tavern. This historic home and tavern is brought to life with living history demonstrations.&lt;br /&gt;      --Battle Road. Walk the trail used on April 19, 1775.&lt;br /&gt;      --Meriam’s Corner, terminus of the Battle Road trail and place where British regulars first came under fire as they retreated to Boston.&lt;br /&gt;      --North Bridge where colonial militia men were first ordered to fire upon British regulars. See Daniel Chester French’s Minute Man statue, the grave of British soldiers, and other battle monuments.&lt;br /&gt;      --North Bridge Visitor Center at Buttrick Mansion features exhibits detailing the events in 1775, an information center and bookstore located in a home built by the descendents of Major John Buttrick, the colonial officer who gave the command to fire at the North Bridge.&lt;br /&gt;    * Orchard House, the home of Louisa May Alcott and her family and setting for the beloved Little Women. $$&lt;br /&gt;    * Colonial Inn, a functioning inn and historic landmark at the heart of the village green, the Inn was a part of the events of April 19, 1775 and was later home to Henry David Thoreau.&lt;br /&gt;    * Old Manse, home of minister William Emerson, his grandson Ralph Waldo Emerson, and the honeymoon home of Nathaniel and Sophia Hawthorne. $$&lt;br /&gt;    * Concord Visitor Center, located close to restaurants and shops, offers information, guided walking tours of Concord, and public restrooms.&lt;br /&gt;    * Concord Museum holds a nationally significant historical collection including the famed Revere lantern, Emerson’s study, and Thoreau’s Walden desk. Hands-on family activities, period rooms, and film “Exploring Concord.” $$&lt;br /&gt;    * The Wayside was home to the Alcotts, Nathaniel Hawthorne, and Margaret Sidney. $$&lt;br /&gt;    * Emerson House, where Ralph Waldo Emerson, foremost 19th century literary figure, lived and wrote from 1835 until his death in 1882. Original furnishings and family memorabilia are on display. $$&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scheduled Departures of 90-Minute Tour&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Departs daily at 10:00AM, 11:30AM, 1PM, and 2:30PM from the National Heritage Museum, 33 Marrett Road (Rt. 2A and Mass Avenue). Free all-day parking; also accessible by the Red Line subway and MBTA bus #62 and #76 from Alewife T station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Convenient features:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Stops at Lexington &amp;amp; Concord's historic sites and attractions.&lt;br /&gt;    * Easy on/off stops close to local attractions, hotels, shopping, and dining.&lt;br /&gt;    * Free re-boarding.&lt;br /&gt;    * 24-hour non-transferable pass&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free all-day parking in Lexington at National Heritage Museum and Minute Man National Historical Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket Information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets include admission to all 3 Lexington Historical Society houses:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * $25 Adults&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Liberty Ride tickets may be purchased on-board or at the following locations:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * National Heritage Museum, 33 Marrett Road/Route 2A, Lexington (Free parking available.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Lexington Visitors Center, 1875 Massachusetts Avenue, Lexington&lt;br /&gt;    * Buckman Tavern, 1 Bedford Street, Lexington&lt;br /&gt;    * Colonial Inn, 48 Monument Square, Concord&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounts with Ticket&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Liberty Ride ticket will entitle you to valuable merchant discounts.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture and will be wearing a Meetup button.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anna</member_name><member_id>404606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278281063000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275078981000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July 4 Liberty Ride and Historic Sites in Lexington and Concord</name><id>13626904</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278251100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13626904/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/7/global_15345591.jpeg</photo_url></item>