<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Ferry Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01835</zip><lat>42.772040</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-374-9683</phone><name>Crescent Yacht Club</name><city>Bradford</city><id>1120809</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073668</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Don't Call Me Shirley is a Great band, Crescent Yacht Club is a friendly and fun venue. Need any other reasons to come out and join us for a fun night of dancing?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Band:&lt;br /&gt;Don’t Call Me Shirley plays contemporary, popular, and classic hits from the 1960’s to today’s favorites. DCMS is a “wicked fun” band that entertains music lovers with a wide range of tastes from the folk rock of Simon and Garfunkel to the hard rock of the Rolling Stones. Shirley is a party band for the local lounge or the backyard summer blow-out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shirley came together in 2000 when Dave moved next door to Kevin, by the time we see them unfortunately Dave will have already moved back to California, but the remaining members of DCMS will continue with their music. They started with some acoustic duo work and soon found Ron Chane because all of their kids were in the same class. That made for some rockin’ Christmas gigs in kindergarten. After adding Ron on bass the next natural progression was to grab Matt Beard who was the drummer with Kevin’s other band The Catapillars. Mark Luchini was added in 2006 bringing electric guitar for those stadium gigs we play. Mark fills in the missing notes with great leads and riffs not to mention another level of vocal ability which has Shirley is now known for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Venue:&lt;br /&gt;Crescent Yacht Club is located in Bradford (a part of Haverhill), it is a private club which offers its venue as a public space for entertainment and local bands to play. Even if you don't dance come out, cheer us on, laugh with us and have a great time. The yacht club has a full bar but does not have food other than some munchies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our group saw Don't Call me Shirley at this venue on 12/18 and had a great time. The band was awesome and we danced all night. The dance floor was plenty big enough. The drinks were very reasonably priced and the members of the club were very friendly and inviting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the first event we did at this venue we found that the only downfall was that there was not food available. So this time when we go out lets all bring some munchies with us. Perhaps some dip/chips, cheese/crackers or some popcorn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan on bringing munchies with you please add that to your RSVP so that we don't have 20 bags of popcorn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no cover charge to get into the Crescent Yacht Club all that you will have to do is sign the guest book upon entering. The dress code is casual! Please remember that if you plan on bringing a snack to this event then include that on your RSVP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is: 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nov/Dec: November 1-Dec 11 we will be collecting donations for the Lazarus House in Lawrence. If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event. If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change. Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank You&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for your Organizers...we will try to get the tables in the left corner under the big screen tv"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289778854000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286657569000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dust off your dancing shoes....let's go boogie</name><id>15057198</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289610900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15057198/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/4/global_12333012.jpeg</photo_url></item>