<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>127 Smith Pl</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.393856</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mom and Paws Indoor Dog Park and Daycare</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6371142</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150406</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Mom and Paws (Indoor Dog Park and Daycare) would like to invite you all to a meet up for small dogs. We love all dogs, big small, white, brown!! We are a new business to Cambridge. We are run by dog lovers and dog owners. We would like you to feel at home and have fun while you are here. You may bring snacks, your own dogs toys, or anything that would help enhance your experience! (We have a human only area with retail items and chairs.) &lt;br /&gt;

The only requirement we have is that you bring your dogs vaccine records, so that we can verify that your dog had has his or her rabies and distemper (DHLP) vaccine. We want to make sure everyone is safe and protected :) &lt;br /&gt;

The owner Christine Creed will be on site to answer any questions you have. Please visit our website if you are interested in learning more about our services. www.momandpaws.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Because this event is on short notice, and we are eager to have you come see our facility we will be lowering the price for this visit. Usually a park pass is $7/per dog. At this event/meetup will will be asking for $3/per dog. We hope you are able to come, and look forward to meeting you all, sharing stories, drinking tea and coffee (complimentary) and playing with our furry friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julia &lt;br /&gt;

Mom and Paws Indoor Park and Daycare &lt;br /&gt;

127 Smith Place &lt;br /&gt;

Cambridge MA, 02138 &lt;br /&gt;

617-714-3551&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333208680000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>small Breed Dog Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>smallbreeddogs-41</urlname><id>404601</id><group_lat>41.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>The North Attleboro Small Breed Dogs Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332749492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Woof! Try something new!</name><id>57873772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333204200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/smallbreeddogs-41/events/57873772/</event_url></item>