<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Monica and I will be making a trip to Baxter State Park in February to go after a New England 4K Peak and and a couple of other peaks on the New England Hundred Highest - North &amp;amp; South Brother, Fort, and Coe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Don’t waste your time reading this if you only want to climb Katahdin and Hamlin or if you want to do the Knifes Edge – this trip is to the other side of the park and we have no plans of going after those other peaks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;There are no questions to answer during the RSVP - just sign-up for the waiting list and I will get in touch with you to talk more about the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;I initially reserved five spots but three people have had to drop out. There is one very small cabin that sleeps four and a number of four-person lean-tos. We have paid for all four spots in the cabin and one lean-to spot - but there are more lean-to spots available if more people are interested.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Since the cabin is very small we will not all be able to hang out inside but it will provide a place for people to warm up and dry out wet clothes. We are looking for two people to occupy the cabin with us and up to eight people to occupy the lean-tos.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Here is a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10151325628914114.499089.773704113&amp;amp;type=1&amp;amp;l=4e440d6774"&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to some pictures from our trip earlier this year – we will NOT be climbing either Katahdin or Hamlin as shown in these pictures. This will give you an idea of the sleds and the road conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;The cost without lodging in Millinocket the night before would be about $60 per person. We will figure out the other expenses like carpooling and any shared meals, as we get closer to departure date. We plan to drive up on February 20 and stay nearby so we can be rested and get an early start Thursday morning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary - Part I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;While the hike in to Nesowadnehunk should be pretty much a cakewalk this side of the park sees very little foot traffic. While the park roads will be packed out by the snowmobiles that travel to and fro, the actual hiking trails may need to be broken out. The route is mostly protected by trees so there will be more flexibility with how we decide to go based on the weather conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Here's the plan...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Climb the following mountains ... North Brother (#42 on New England 67 4,000 Footer List) ... Fort (#78 on New England Hundred Highest) ... South Brother (#68 on New England Hundred Highest) ... Coe (#90 on New England Hundred Highest) ... Doubletop Mountain (because it is there).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Wednesday February 20&lt;/span&gt;: Arrive in Millinocket, ME and stay at a local motel. (allows for a rested and early start on February 21).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Thursday February 21&lt;/span&gt;: Drive to winter parking area ... Hike to Nesowadnehunk Bunk House/Lean-To (about 6 miles and about 700 feet of climbing). There is snowmobile traffic on most, if not all, of this route so even if there is fresh snow chances are we won't have to break too much trail ... Hike and Explore ... Stay in Cabin/Leanto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Friday February 22 / Saturday February 23&lt;/span&gt;: Hike to N Brother, Fort, S Brother, and Coe on one day. The hike to and from Fort is a bushwhack in summer. Hike to Doubletop on the other day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Sunday February 24&lt;/span&gt;: Hike back to the cars and drive home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary - Part II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;While I have hiked these peaks in summer and have been to Baxter State Park in winter, I have not been to this side of the park or these peaks in winter. While I will surely offer any help and guidance I can (and will welcome any you can give me), you need to be COMPLETELY self sufficient and confident in your skills. This is a trip where every person has to be able to rely on every other person. If you would never think of doing this trip on your own this probably isn't the trip for you.Approximate Distances/Gains (Nesowadnehunk is at about 1,300')&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Nesowadnehunk to Doubletop Mountain (3,489) is about 12 miles roundtrip with about 2,500 feet of climbing. All most all of this is along a regular hiking trail so the trail might not be broken out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Nesowadnehunk to Marston Trailhead is about 3 miles one way and on the way we will lose about 300' in elevation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Marston Trailhead to North Brother (4,451'), Fort (3,856'), back to North Brother and then over to South Brother (3,970'), Coe (3,795'), and then back to the Marston Trailhead is about 10.5 miles roundtrip with about 4,500 feet of climbing if we do the whole loop at one time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Bring...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Besides regular winter clothing, gear, and equipment some of the things that you will need - a sled to pull your stuff, full mountaineering crampons and winter boots (you can probably get away with regular winter boots and not need rigid sole leather/plastics), and full mountaineering snow shoes. If you are in the cabin you can manage with (at least) a +15 degree sleeping bag and if you are in the lean-to you would want (at least) a -15 degree sleeping bag. There will also be group gear that we will need to carry on summit day and while I can carry some if it I can't carry it all - we will divy it up as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362022917000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359685519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Baxter State Park in Winter - Brothers, Fort, &amp; Coe</name><id>102435922</id><headcount>4</headcount><duration>298800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361448000000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/102435922/</event_url></item>