<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;September was our meetup's one year anniversary; and we want to celebrate and have some fun!&lt;/span&gt; Well, we &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; want to have fun, right?  This will also give us more social time to get to know one another even better.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Please take note of the change in our date, time and location from our usual plan. And this event is FREE, too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the current plan.  Feel free to send me more ideas, too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The party will be at our home in Framingham, from 5:00 pm - 9:00 pm&lt;/b&gt;, so we can use our yard, kitchen, etc. and be more comfy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Potluck dinner&lt;/b&gt; - In a mood of abundance and celebration, bring one of your favorite dishes to share.   We'll provide drinks and paper goods.  Feel free to bring your alcoholic beverage of choice, too.  Grill is available, if you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We'll have a table set up for making your own &lt;b&gt;creation box or vision board&lt;/b&gt;, if this interests you.  &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;We'll need magazines to cut out pictures - please bring some you're willing to let us use. Please also bring your own box or board.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; We could also use some more scissors and any other craft supplies you'd be willing to share to help out.  A creation box is similar to a vision board, except you can keep adding to it -kind of like a treasure chest.  And, you can put in pictures or written &amp;quot;requests&amp;quot; for what you are wanting.  It's like placing your order to the Universe; and then...it's done!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anyone know how to lead us through some improv games?  Or maybe we'll play some LOA pictionary! Other &lt;b&gt;game ideas are welcome&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;We'll have a &lt;b&gt;campfire&lt;/b&gt; in the backyard.  &lt;b&gt;If you play an instrument, please bring it&lt;/b&gt;.  We'd love to hear you!  And let's do &lt;b&gt;some drumming around the fire, too!  Bring any percussion instruments you can &amp;quot;drum&amp;quot; up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We live in the beautiful, historic, rural part of Framingham, which is full of farms and conservation land with hiking trails (Callahan State Park and Sudbury Trustees Land) .  You might want to give yourself some time before our event to enjoy the area.  There is much to be grateful for here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun.  Please join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Note: It's very important to us that if you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;, to please show up. People have been getting better about this, and it is so helpful. Remember, if you need to change your plans, please change your rsvp or let us know. It really helps us with our planning, having less waste (handouts and food), and in being able to start on time. Thank you so much for cooperating with this!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're down a very long driveway.  Look for our mailbox on the road.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256247321000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253060070000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> October Meetup - our one year celebration!</name><id>hwpzkymnbwb</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255813200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/11382623/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/c/global_10923340.jpeg</photo_url></item>