<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Wow, this happened 2 times in a row. Since When in Rome's last show tomorrow night is playing at 4:30, we're switching movies to Valentine's Day. But good thing there's another romantic comedy in the wings. &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810094501/info" target="_blank"&gt;Valentine's Day&lt;/a&gt; is chock full of stars and their mini-dramas look to turn out to be quite funny. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;br /&gt;A diverse group of Los Angelenos navigate their way through romance and heartbreak over the course of one Valentine's Day. Couples and singles experience the pinnacles and pitfalls of finding, keeping or ending relationships in a day in the life of love. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:15, so let's meet in the ticket lobby at 6:45 and head in from there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the movie change alters your RSVP, please update on the site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;We're due for a comedy! Too many dramas came out and I'm scratching for a good laugh. So let's &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810014226/details" target="_blank"&gt;go to Rome&lt;/a&gt; together! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Disillusioned with romance, an ambitious New Yorker travels to Rome, where she plucks magic coins from a special fountain. The coins attract an assortment of odd suitors, including a sausage merchant, a street magician and an artist. But, when a persistent reporter throws his hat in the ring, she wonders if his love is the real thing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for When in Rome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266870842000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264966277000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Valentine's Day, was When in Rome</name><id>12475275</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266535800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12475275/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>