<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Modern Times&lt;/b&gt; USA 1936 87 minutes   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;Late Update&lt;/b&gt; Tom will not be able to host this event. Please see the posting on the Message Board for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In &lt;b&gt;Modern Times&lt;/b&gt; (1936), the still-silent Tramp, with his familiar small Derby hat, mustache, large boots, baggy pants, tight jacket and cane makes his last screen appearance. Filmed between 1932 and 1936, it was directed, written, scored, and produced by Chaplin himself - and he also starred in his own 'one-man show' with his current wife and kindred spirit Paulette Goddard. This was Chaplin's first film after his successful City Lights (1931), released nine years after the advent of 'talkies.' Tom Dirks Greatest Films. org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chaplin's satiric dissection of the economy circa 1936 looks downright prescient.  Salt Lake Tribune&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remains Chaplin's most sustained burlesque of authority.  Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie Chaplin is the Orson Welles of comedy. One of his funniest silent films is &lt;b&gt;Modern Times&lt;/b&gt;, a brilliant spoof on technology that's more stinging today than back in its 1936 release year.  Sun Newspapers of Cleveland&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles Chaplin's last &amp;quot;silent&amp;quot; film hilariously satirizes Depression-era social ills through the Tramp's disastrous encounters with the industrial age. Chaplin turns his factory worker's nervous breakdown into comic set pieces involving an automated feeding machine, an inability to stop tightening bolts, and, most famously, his entrapment in machinery gears. In a potent satire of authoritarian idiocy, Chaplin repeatedly ends up in jail for stumbling into worker riots and &amp;quot;Communist&amp;quot; protests, yet his ability to quell a prison break while accidentally hopped up on cocaine (!!) earns him the sheriff's respect. Paulette Goddard's fetching Gamin helps Chaplin find work as a singing waiter, but police intervention leaves their togetherness as their only hope. Accompanied by a Chaplin-composed score (including Smile) and synchronized sound effects, numerous bits of business showcase Chaplin's silent gift for physical comedy, including a department store roller skate and maneuvers with a food tray. In a send-up of talking pictures and technology's dehumanizing effects in general, the only voices heard in the movie (save for Chaplin's gibberish song and his fellow waiters' warbling) come from the factory's Orwellian telescreen P.A. system, a phonograph, and a radio. Three years in production, Mo&lt;b&gt;dern Times&lt;/b&gt; became another international success for Chaplin (though it was banned in Germany and Italy) and one of the signature works of his career. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No Derby hat, but I'll be holding a Meetup Sign near the front row  after the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265762591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chaplin's Modern Times</name><id>12565651</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266620400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12565651/</event_url></item>