<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>AMC Auditorium, 4 Joy Street, Boston MA&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM potluck, 7:00 PM slideshow &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Silvia for a slideshow about her first trip as a co-leader for AMC Major Excursions to her native Bulgaria. View photos of ancient monasteries, remote peaks, and beautiful landscapes and learn about it's history, destinations and cultture.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Founded in 681, Bulgaria is one of the oldest states in Europe. It is a small country of 7.5 million inhabitants, located on the Balkan Peninsula, the crossroad between Europe and Asia. It is the home of several UNESCO World heritage sites and it boasts the highest peak on the Balkans. It is also an up and coming vacation destination offering outstanding opportunities to ski or go to the beach at a fraction of the cost of other European destinations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan to attend, please RSVP to AMCBostonSlideshows@gmail. For those who wish to participate in the potluck at 6:30pm, feel free to use the following guidelines: last names beginning with A-J bring appetizer or side dish, K-S bring a main dish, T-Z bring drinks/dessert. Homemade dishes are welcome, store bought goodies and takeout are equally welcome. Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (stovetop, oven, microwave, sink, fridge, etc).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285251725000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283306067000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Balkan High Peaks and Monasteries (Slideshow &amp; Potluck)</name><id>14612993</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285194600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/14612993/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/e/global_17632414.jpeg</photo_url></item>