<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello Networkers! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm very excited about the New Year and the meetups we have planned in the next few months. On Tuesday we will be reviewing our definitions of success and the BRBN principles, then discussing the value of visitors and the inviting mindset to help our group grow. Bring plenty of business cards, or small brochures explaining what you do. Please do not bring too much material on your business because everyone will have a turn to give their 15 minute presentation in future meetings. Right now our key focus is getting to know one another so we can create success more effectively and efficiently.  &lt;br /&gt;At the end of the meeting we will have a feedback discussion so bring any questions, comments, or ideas you have to benefit the group.  &lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to meeting all of you!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Depending on how many people RSVP we may order pizza and snacks so it is important that you honor your RSVP!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please meet us at the Pearl Street Entrance in the lobby promptly at 7:00. Everyone needs a pass to go up the elevators so it is important you are on time, Thanks!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201219696000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Energy Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1402</urlname><id>654497</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Green Business Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200618380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Success is a ladder that cannot be climbed with your hands in your pockets</name><id>7139913</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201046400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1402/events/7139913/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/d/global_2663805.jpeg</photo_url></item>