<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a new hike addition for the group. A looping hike of lower to moderate difficulty. We will hike about 6 miles over a roughly 4 hour period on portions of the Mettabesett trail and the Bear Hill Loop Trail. There will be some cliffs we will walk along, streams and other bodies of water to see, some short steep ups and downs. Overall an interesting trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to go should have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* A daypack - To carry trail food, water, and any extra items. &lt;br /&gt;

* Hiking boots&amp;nbsp;advised &lt;br /&gt;

* 1 quart water &lt;br /&gt;

* Bug spray (advised as swampy in some sections)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meetup will be at 9 AM on/off the shoulder of Aircraft Rd. &lt;strong&gt;Parking may be limited&lt;/strong&gt; so carpooling is encouraged. We would finish up at about 1 PM and some lunch out if the group feels like socializing more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General directions&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

* From Rte. 9, take Aircraft Rd. from exit 10 &lt;br /&gt;

* Go straight at traffic light onto Aircraft Rd. &lt;br /&gt;

* Go 0.8 mile and look for oval Mettabesett Trail sign on left (North) side. &lt;br /&gt;

* Park on shoulder (try to pull at least half up onto grass to be out of the road)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aproximate location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; to trailhead shoulder parking (roughly 400 Aircraft Rd., Middletown, CT): &lt;a href="http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?city=Middletown&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=400+Aircraft+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06457-5725&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.514286&amp;amp;longitude=-72.577442&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS"&gt;http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?city=Middletown&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=400+Aircraft+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06457-5725&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.514286&amp;amp;longitude=-72.577442&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map is in "&lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Walk Book: East&lt;/strong&gt;" 19th ed., by Connecticut Forest and Park Association as map &lt;strong&gt;MB-2&lt;/strong&gt; on page 20 or in "&lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Walk Book: West&lt;/strong&gt;" 19th ed. as map &lt;strong&gt;MB-2&lt;/strong&gt; on page 104.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Count Me In" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green old Dodge Caravan or silver Honda Accord, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319115359000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317742620000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Bear Hill in Middletown CT</name><id>36095202</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318770000000</time><rsvp_limit>29</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/36095202/</event_url></item>