<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 635-4505</phone><name>Boston Common Frog Pond</name><city>Boston</city><id>795283</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>So sad that rollerblading season is just about over.  It's too dark in the evenings to skate and it's pretty cold otherwise.  I figure since so many of you ice skate I'd try adding a couple of ice skating events this season so the group isn't inactive for the next six months.  (If anyone has info on indoor rollerskating/rollerblading rinks pass it on.  I think there's one in Saugus and one in Dorchester.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opening day at the Frog Pond is November 19. The Mayor will be there, some professional skaters will be there, there'll be some demonstrations, etc., plus admission is free this night.  It all starts at 5:30 p.m. which is kind of early for some so I thought we could meet at 6:30 p.m., watch a little, skate a little and then get something to eat.  Throwing out the idea of chinese food since Chinatown is right there, but open to other places including just getting coffee or hot chocolate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI the Frog Pond (www.bostoncommonfrogpond.org) isn't actually a pond for those of you who don't know.  It's just an outdoor rink that's frozen from underneath.  I know some people don't skate on ponds for fear of ruining their blades.  Also, if you don't have skates they do rent them.  I believe it's $8.00.  Not sure if they will charge to rent skates on this night or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location is T accessible by Park Street on the red and green lines.  If you are driving you can pay to park at the Boston Common Garage or drive around the Public Gardens no more than three times and you should get a metered spot.  (I always get one there.)  Just be aware if the meters go until 8:00 p.m. instead of 6:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm giving the option to RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;no&amp;quot;.  Please update your RSVP if your plans change.  I'll also be combining this event with the Social Fun group since I'm an organizer for them too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dee&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will meet at the Frog Statues.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234735862000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224691901000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Frog Pond ICE SKATING &amp; Chinese Food</name><id>9010896</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227137400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/9010896/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/7/global_5983303.jpeg</photo_url></item>