<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Spring St., Floor 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.366043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>Watertown Center for Healing Arts (Charles River Room)</name><city>Watertown</city><id>2074041</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184196</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you get nervous about approaching someone new and starting a conversation with them? Do you wish you knew how to approach people that you're attracted to, and talk to them in a way that will make them interested in getting to know you? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 If you answered yes to either of those questions, then you're going to love this workshop. You'll learn simple, proven conversation starters that are non-threatening, and practically rejection proof. Once you master this simple skill, you'll have the confidence to approach people in any situation, and you will know what to say to get them talking. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Imagine being at a Meetup event and gliding around the room talking with anyone and everyone. You'll surprise yourself with how easy and effortless it is to strike up conversations with total strangers and get to know them. Once you have this skill, you'll be able to make friends and attract lovers anywhere you go, anytime you want. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN: &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************  &lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;3 simple, proven conversation starters you can use in almost any situation (including one that works REALLY well in places like coffee shops and malls, and another one that works almost 100% of the time at parties and social gatherings).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New For 2013:&lt;/strong&gt; I've created a special exercise that inoculates you against rejection so you can approach anyone without fear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;What to actually talk about after you start the conversation (and which topics people find interesting).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to be more approachable so others come up and start conversations with you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;How you can quickly become confident at meeting new people so it's never scary again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Little-known places where people are more friendly and open to being approached.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;A proven method for ending a conversation that will leave people feeling good about you. If you've ever wanted to end a conversation with someone, but were worried about offending them or hurting their feelings, then this is perfect for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;And much more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 WANT TO JOIN US?  HERE'S HOW: &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is it?&lt;/strong&gt; The seminar is conveniently located at the Watertown Center For Healing Arts which is a beautiful facility for an event like this. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;What time?&lt;/strong&gt; Please plan on arriving by 6:45pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members. We start promptly at 7:00pm and go until 9:30pm (with a break in the middle).  There are plenty of bus lines that go to the center, and there is also lots of parking both on the street and in a big parking lot near the center.  The bottom of this page has details: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://watertowncenter.net/directions-2/"&gt;http://watertowncenter.net/directions-2/ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;How much?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Cheap.  If you took a class like this through an adult education center, you'd easily pay more than $50 to attend, and that's assuming there even&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;a class that could offer you all this, which there isn't.   &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;No other class offers you this kind of cutting edge training that's based in real world results.  This stuff WORKS!  What if one small change is all it takes to immediately and effortlessly begin attracting high-quality friends and dating prospects into your life?  I've seen it happen many times in this group, and it can happen for you too.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;So how much?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Because I want to help as many people as I can, I've decided to keep the price very affordable so that anyone who wants to come will be able to.  The cost for this event is only $20, which is very low considering the quality of training that you'll be getting. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Think about it...&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;that's 67 cents a day for a month&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;.  What else do you spend 67 cents on every day that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever? I promise that this will be well worth your time. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;In order to make sure I can personally help as many people as possible, the class is limited to the first 50 people who RSVP.  This is not a lecture.  We are going to be moving around and doing lots of fun exercises, so I have to limit the size.  I'm listing this event in two groups, so there are over 7,300 people seeing this listing.  If you want in, then be sure to put in your RSVP right now in order to lock in your spot. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude, and a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot.  I'm looking forward to seeing you there. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Warmly,  &lt;br /&gt;

 Jason &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363613193000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>76</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362865681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DATING SEMINAR:  How To Approach People And Start Conversations</name><id>108462422</id><headcount>55</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363561200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/108462422/</event_url></item>