<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/a/1/event_20266497.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;It is time again to build our gingerbread houses, and then decorate them until the gingers' homeowners association complains. Sign up and help us with our Extreme Gingerbread Makeover.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Everyone is required to bring decorating candies, Etc. to help with the design and construction of the houses.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 snacks and BYOB per usual....This is more snack than meal event. Think bites and hand food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be building and decorating up to four houses. We will work on them in loose teams of three more or less. Paul and Angela will be keeping one of the houses because Paul is constructing all the house pieces for us and providing the platforms/foundations for the houses. Caryl will be keeping one house because she is hosting the decorating effort. Other houses will be raffled off by drawing names of those in attendance from the Cat in the Hat hat. Anyone who has won a cooking club drawing in the past or is loosely&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;related&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to a past winner is not eligible for the house drawing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to the fun - see you on the construction site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326503618000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320893240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gingerbread Houses</name><id>40638322</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323640800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/40638322/</event_url></item>