<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Cross-posted with "Fellowship of the Tortoise" MeetUp!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did this hike in the late fall and people commented on what a great snowshoe hike it would make! (Hopefully, we'll have some snow!) Two pretty ponds ringed by mountains make a beautiful hike. You get views of the ponds as well as the mountains and cliff faces towering over the water. This route starts from Kancamagus Highway and follows Greeley Ponds Trail south to the ponds. Although Greeley Ponds Trail continues all the way to Waterville Valley, we will turn back at the second pond and retrace the same path back to Kancamagus Highway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 4.5 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 Elevation gain (cumulative) 430' &lt;br /&gt;

 Tortoise Time: 5 hours (depending on if we hang out at the pond for lunch!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no summit to this hike, but a very pretty walk in the woods with nice scenery! &lt;br /&gt;

 Description and trail map here: &lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/GreeleyPonds090207.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hikenewengland.com/GreeleyPonds090207.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I will be staying at the White Mountains Hostel for the weekend and have listed that as a separate Meet Up here:&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Fellowship-of-the-Tortoise/events/46257502/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Fellowship-of-the-Tortoise/events/46257502/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 NOTE: This is definitely a winter hike. Please be sure you have proper gear: over pants, a warm jacket, hat and gloves, wool socks (bring an extra pair) and waterproof hiking boots. Hiking poles highly suggested. There are a couple of stream crossings. You will need snowshoes and/or microspikes...even if the weather has seemed warm! Bring at least 2 liters of water and HEAT the water. An insulated water holder is recommended. Don't use a water-bladder; the water will freeze. See the listing of suggested winter gear above under the "pages" tab. Dress in layers and NO COTTON. Seriously. NO COTTON.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com/cgi-bin/findweather/getForecast?query=zmw:03812.1.99999&amp;amp;bannertypeclick=wu_bluestripes"&gt;&lt;img src="http://weathersticker.wunderground.com/cgi-bin/banner/ban/wxBanner?bannertype=wu_bluestripes&amp;amp;airportcode=KMWN&amp;amp;ForcedCity=Bartlett&amp;amp;ForcedState=NH" alt="Click for Bartlett, New Hampshire Forecast" width="160" height="90" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS: The northern Greeley Ponds Trailhead is located on Kancamagus Highway (Rt. 112) in Lincoln, New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From I-93: Take Exit 32 off I-93 and follow Kancamagus Highway (Rt. 112) East for 9.7 miles. Turn into a small parking area on the right-hand side of the road. This turn is after Big Rock Campground (which is on the left) but before the hairpin turn at Hancock Overlook. If hiking in the winter, be careful to avoid the cross-country ski parking area for Greeley Ponds which is 0.2 mile before the hiking lot. Greeley Ponds Trail leaves from the southeast corner of the parking area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Rt. 16: From Rt. 16 in Conway, follow Kancamagus Highway (Rt. 112) West for about 26 miles. Turn into a small parking area on the left-hand side of the road. This turn is after the hairpin turn at Hancock Overlook. If hiking in the winter, be careful to avoid the cross-country ski parking area for Greeley Ponds which is 0.2 mile beyond the hiking lot. Greeley Ponds Trail leaves from the southeast corner of the parking area.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Greeley Ponds Trail leaves from the southeast corner of the parking area.  Look for Diane's gold Honda CRV</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328656109000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326235367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snowshoe hike! Greeley Ponds from the Kanc!   class 1 easy</name><id>47570312</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328454000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/47570312/</event_url></item>