<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/7/7/event_45582871.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;Come on, haven't you wanted to see this movie on the big screen.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I confess I saw it on tv the first time I saw it.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A classic, creepy horror film, staring the fabulous Jack Nicholson, how can you beat that?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Overview:&amp;nbsp; In one of Stanley Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s most iconic films, the Torrance family - Jack (Jack Nicholson), Wendy (Shelley Duvall), and Danny (Danny Lloyd) - become haunted by an evil menace while isolated for the winter season in the glorious Overlook Hotel.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Stanley Kubrick co-adapted this script from the Stephen King novel, and turned the story of Torrance family into one of the most chilling and masterful horror films of all time.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Kubrick melds vivid performances, menacing settings, dreamlike tracking shots, and shock after shock into a milestone of the macabre. As the ghostly inhabitants of the Overlook slowly drive Jack insane, his wife and son may have a much more tangible threat to worry about...&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;This is a one night only showing and I strongly advise you to buy your tickets in advance.&amp;nbsp; Please indicate in your rsvp when you have purchased your ticket.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;To view the trailer and buy tickets go to:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/content/shining"&gt;http://www.coolidge.org/content/shining&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;After we will gather outside the theater and anyone interested for dinner and drinks, we will go to Zaftig's Deli, which is right nearby.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;They have lots of traditional Jewish Deli Fare and also sell beer and wine.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin and will be standing in line outside the ticket booth by 6:15.  We will head in for seats when they let us, probably around 6:30</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314322942000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312467729000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Shining</name><id>28241451</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314051300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/28241451/</event_url></item>