<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>My quest on the Appalachian Trail continues.  I have planned a two day, overnight event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a 22 mile thru hike from Jerusalem Road, Tyringham Mass to Jugg End.  The first day we will meet at the parking area on Jugg End Rd 9:00 a.m.  From there we will take a vehical to the starting spot on Jerusalem Rd in Tyringham Mass.  I hope to be on the trail by 10:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first day will take us past Sky Hill and Mt. Wilcox.  We will over night at the Tom Leonard lean to.  Day two we will finish the 11 mile section that will lead back to the car on Jugg End Road.  Obviously we then have to get back to the car in Tyringham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I do not have a time frames for the time we will finish.  There are too many variables that include what time we break camp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email me any questions about this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is where the hike will begin but not where we will meet.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Tyringham&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=%5B100-157%5D+Jerusalem+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=01264&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.25045&amp;amp;longitude=-73.2279&amp;amp;geocode=STREET" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the meeting point, Jugg End Road, there is a parking area and a trail sign before you get to Guilder Hollow Rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Great+Barrington&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=Guilder+Hollow+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES == &lt;br /&gt;* Full pack &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in  &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of cloathing -Avoid cotton as it stays wet. Plus second day's clothing. &lt;br /&gt;* Hat &lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/jacket -just in case &lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag &lt;br /&gt;* Light bedcloaths -(Shorts, Tee) To deal with heat/humidity &lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp -LED version best &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking tent -Or share &lt;br /&gt;* 3 quarts water -No defined safe water source except campsite &lt;br /&gt;* 4 meals for on the trail -DAY-1: lunch, supper; DAY-2: breakfast, lunch (all trash to be packed out!). High energy meals should be planned. Only supper may be cooked but if getting up early (6:00 AM) then breakfast can be cooked too. &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;* Bugspray -Essential! &lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle &lt;br /&gt;* Bear bag and 15' min. light weight rope -Hang food at night &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR == &lt;br /&gt;* Water filter -To restock water &lt;br /&gt;* Compass &lt;br /&gt;* Camera and extra batteries &lt;br /&gt;* Pocket knife &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking first aid kit -For blisters and such &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproof matches -For cooking, campfire, emergency fire (warm up, signal) &lt;br /&gt;* Mess kit -If needed &lt;br /&gt;* Camping utensils -If needed &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking stove and fuel -If cooking &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252933626000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251592086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Two day AT hike, Tyringham MA to Jugg End Road </name><id>11234875</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252760400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11234875/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>