<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This past weeks Movie Night went well, so we'll give it another shot.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come visit the 360 State Street Screening Room, for a showing of:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;V for Vendetta (2006)&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Description from IMDB: A shadowy freedom fighter known only as &amp;quot;V&amp;quot; uses terrorist tactics to fight against his totalitarian society. Upon rescuing a girl from the secret police, he also finds his best chance at having an ally.   &lt;br /&gt;Stars: Hugo Weaving, Natalie Portman, John Hurt   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0434409/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The date is appropriate, so I had to chose this for the movie on the 5th of November, also known as Guy Fawkes Night... &amp;quot;Remember, remember the Fifth of November, The Gunpowder Treason and Plot,   &lt;br /&gt;I know of no reason Why the Gunpowder Treason Should ever be forgot...&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I can get at the wires to hook it up properly, we'll watch this on my &lt;b&gt;HD-DVD&lt;/b&gt; Player.  (Figure it might be an extra draw for any BETA nerds out there in the collective, otherwise I have an normal disk too.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I Set the time for 6:30, but we will not start showing the movie until shortly after 7.  Don't plan to be any later though.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Important Notes:&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately I have to limit RSVP's to 18 for theater size.  Please only respond Yes if you're sure you can make it.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're &lt;u&gt;RSVPing Yes, I will need your full names&lt;/u&gt; if I don't already have (or remember) them for the Concierge to let you in, and you may need ID.  Please either put your name in your RSVP or e-mail it to me. (If you live in the building just let me know instead.) &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Bring your own Snacks and Beverages.  (Just please be careful and responsible.)  Sharing is encouraged.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry, 360's Parking Garage is not available to the Public yet.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The concierge should be able to let you in and direct you, make note of the directions near the call box.  I will also try to post signs.  My Cell if you have problems is 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289317102000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288399570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie: "V for Vendetta" on Guy Fawkes Night</name><id>15275146</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288996200000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15275146/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/3/4/global_19167380.jpeg</photo_url></item>