<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>132 Newbury St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351120</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(617) 578-0089</phone><name>Thai Basil</name><city>Boston</city><id>467220</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076890</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This popular Thai eatery is conveniently located in the downtown area between Clarendon and Dartmouth St.  The menu prices are reasonable about $6-$10 for many dishes.  There is street parking around there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Table Tennis Center is located in Medford at 407R Mystic Ave.  Tel: (617) 953-0707.  The fee is $8 per person for the afternoon.  We plan on being here at 2 PM. &lt;b&gt; For those attending Ping Pong only, please look for a Meetup Organizer when you arrive at the Boston TTC if this is your first time and you are not sure where to go. &lt;/b&gt;  IMPORTANT:  &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please wear sneakers or tennis shoes to Ping Pong ! This place doesn't allow&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;black sole shoes because it will mark up their wood floors&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please indicate in your RSVP if you are attending both Thai Lunch &amp;amp; Ping Pong or just one event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Ping Pong Location&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving from Boston&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 North to exit 32 (Medford Sq., Malden).  Go around the rotary and get on I-93 South. &lt;br /&gt;Please go the link below for further directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonttc.com/Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonttc....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation&lt;br /&gt;Take the Route 95 West Medford bus from the Sullivan Square T stop. It should be less than a ten minute ride.  Service is limited; the bus runs only once an hour after the evening rush hour (route and schedule). Ask the driver to let you off at the stop on Mystic Ave. closest to Hicks Ave. From there, it is a five minute walk to the BTTC. Walk down Hicks Ave. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The distance is approximately 12 miles from the Restaurant to the Ping Pong place.  I suggest driving if you can because the bus schedule is limited on weekends.  If anyone needs transportation, please indicate so and we'll try our best to accomodate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see everyone there !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fred&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285975188000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Someone in our group mentioned recently that since this is an "Asian" Professionals Meetup Group we should explore different asian cultures, so I think a good way to do this is by trying Thai food with good company and enjoy an activity afterwards !</why><group><who>Asian Professionals</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Asian-Professionals</urlname><id>431528</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Asian Professionals Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199427736000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thai Lunch &amp; Ping Pong</name><id>7028358</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200157200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Asian-Professionals/events/7028358/</event_url></item>