<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Darius Jazayeri, lead software developer at Partners in Health (&lt;a href="http://pih.org" target="_blank"&gt;pih.org&lt;/a&gt;), will lead a discussion of OpenMRS at the  Dcember JAVA meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Darius says:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;OpenMRS is a community-developed, open-source, enterprise electronic medical record system framework. We've come together to specifically respond to those actively building and managing health systems in the developing world, where AIDS, tuberculosis, and malaria afflict the lives of millions. Our mission is to foster self-sustaining health information technology implementations in these environments through peer mentorship, proactive collaboration, and a code base that equals or surpasses proprietary equivalents.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presentations/discussions are held at MIT's EHS Office, 265 Massachusetts Ave, upstairs from the MIT Museum; the office is on the 4th floor of the building; please use the door that is noted in the following picture:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/johnarch/2341265278/sizes/m/" target="_blank"&gt;presentation location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation we will head over to The Asgard, a restaurant/bar at the corner of Mass Ave and Sidney Street (350 Mass Ave):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=350+massachusetts+avenue,+cambridge,+ma&amp;amp;sll=42.366487,-71.098816&amp;amp;sspn=0.008815,0.022745&amp;amp;g=Massachusetts+Ave+%26+Sidney+St,+Cambridge,+Middlesex,+Massachusetts+02139,+United+States&amp;amp;layer=c&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.366963,-71.097186&amp;amp;spn=0.008815,0.022745&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;cbll=42.362981,-71.099593&amp;amp;panoid=VqQEj12CG6gv-yL4iXehHQ&amp;amp;cbp=1,178.60443018981482,,0,-0.8543880653277005" target="_blank"&gt;asgard location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the past, some of you may have parked your car in the lot adjacent to my building, but unfortunately the lot has since become a 24-hour tow zone for non-MIT vehicles. There is usually parking on Windsor street alongside my building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are personal, engaging and everybody is sharing in the topic at hand. Come and share your experience with your peers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.: Thank you to the many members that RSVP (one way or another). This helps your humble organizer to manage the crowd at the venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>265 Massachusetts Avenue, Cambridge, across from Sunoco gas station</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Archambault</member_name><member_id>2399674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233014228000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226968504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Java December Meetup: OpenMRS</name><id>9181738</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229383800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/9181738/</event_url></item>