<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>-</address_2><address_1>ADDRESS LISTED In Event Listing</address_1><lat>41.603222</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>SEE DETAILS IN EVENT WRITEUP</name><city>City LISTED In Event Listing</city><id>9726362</id><country>re</country><lon>-73.087746</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;HI Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I encourage all First Time Kayakers and Biginners to get to this or similar safety lectures and demo events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this time i have decided to personally skip this event and go directly to the Hebron Event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wish you all a good and safe day at the Events and learn as much as you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This Kayak Info Event is  GOOD FOR YOU TO GO ALONE ALSO BECAUSE YOUR INTERESTS MAY BE BETTER ADDRESSED BY THE PRESENTERS VS GOING AS A GROUP which may distract you from some exhibts that you want to spend more time at personally ...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read all the details below carefully and go to the promoters website for any changes or updates or further info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IN THE PAST SOME OF US HAVE GONE TO THESE   SAFETY EVENTS    AND FOUND THEM TO BE GOOD FOR THE GROUP MEMBERS THAT HAVE  *NOT*  GOTTEN A CHANCE TO JOIN US ON OUR PADDLING EVENTS, SEEN OR DONE OUR SELF RESCUE EVENT &lt;span&gt;at Bolton Lake. The water Demos are of very good value to you if they have them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ITS REALLY GOOD FOR A FIRST EXPOSURE OR IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN KAYAKING FOR THE FUTURE wether joining this group, andother, or just paddling alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AL-R&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check out the promoters website below for updates/changes or other data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The info i got is for an actual invitation for our group to participate as a entity, but we are not that kind of group that needs to solicit new memberships, show what we do, or show off some boats. We do our own learning from each other and practice at Bolton Lake in the spring with fellow paddlers you will be on trips together with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://us.f1411.mail.yahoo.com/ya/download?mid=2%5f0%5f0%5f1%5f173593%5fAJztHkgAAUWrUQGxPQ27E3m3Wyk&amp;amp;pid=1.2&amp;amp;fid=Inbox&amp;amp;inline=1&amp;amp;appid=YahooMailNeoCL" alt="CTLogo" width="96" height="52" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctpaddlecraft.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.CTPaddleCraft.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Changing Tides PaddleCraft LLC and New Haven Parks and Recreation invited you and your organization to the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;2nd Annual Southern Connecticut Small Craft Symposium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To be held March 9th at the Wilbur Cross HS at 181 Mitchell Drive New Haven, Connecticut 06511 from 10:00 am to 5:00 pm.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission is free with a suggested donation of $5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the event is to promote safe maritime skills and awareness of environmental issues that affect our waterways. The event will be focusing on the manual powered vessels and the conditions and equipment that affect their safety on the water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still in the planning stages for this event and looking for input. There will be 4 classrooms available for presentations, a pool for on water demonstrations, and a display area for organization to set up to promote their cause or business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lectures:&lt;/strong&gt; We are beginning to put together our lecture program.  We will provide class room space to hold educational presentations.   Talks are typically 45 minute in length unless otherwise requested. I f you would like to participate please fill out the attached form.   Because time is short please send it back to me as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a suggestion for a topic or a speaker please forward us the information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demonstrations:&lt;/strong&gt; We have access to a full size pool for demonstrations.  We are seeking interested candidates for kayak and canoe skills, maneuvers, rescues, etc.  If you or your group is interested in providing a demonstration please contact us with your topic and details on the size of your team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Booths &amp;amp; Displays:&lt;/strong&gt; I would like to invite you to attend and set up a display about your origination. Tables and chairs are provided and there is no fee for display space. We do ask those wishing to sell merchandise to please bring a donation that we can raffle off to help pay for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support:&lt;/strong&gt; we do need help with support to help with registrations hand out agendas and direct attendees to various locations.  If you would like to aid us in putting on this even we would greatly appreciate the help.  Please let us know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advertising:&lt;/strong&gt; We are getting the word out, but today viral advertising is easily the most effective method.  We are asking if you all could help spread the work about this event by sending a copy of the poster to people on your e-mail list.  We ask those with the capability to put a posting on their website as well.  We encourage you to print copies of the poster and post them in your shop and hang them in public spaces in your local area where paddlers might encounter them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions please let me know.  Stay warm and we I hope to see you on March 9th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Elizabeth O'Connor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Changing Tides PaddleCraft LLC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;PO Box 3165&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;New Haven CT 06515&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;203-903-5705&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://us.f1411.mail.yahoo.com/ya/download?mid=2%5f0%5f0%5f1%5f173593%5fAJztHkgAAUWrUQGxPQ27E3m3Wyk&amp;amp;pid=1.2&amp;amp;fid=Inbox&amp;amp;inline=1&amp;amp;appid=YahooMailNeoCL" alt="CTLogo" width="96" height="52" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctpaddlecraft.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.CTPaddleCraft.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a Event that needs no Meetup Organizer, The Promotor is running the full event and its Good</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362873470000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359132519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>KAYAKING LECTURES &amp; DEMONSTRATIONS (See INFO in write up)</name><id>101345392</id><duration>25200000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362841200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/101345392/</event_url></item>