<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>245 Whiting Farms Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.175727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Holiday Inn at Ingleside</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>906244</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.641467</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Develop your own Audio Logo or Slogan and practice with colleagues. How many times have we been at a networking event with only 30 seconds to do our intro? What if we were in an elevator with a prospective client? What would we say to him or her, in between floors, to make that connection? In both instances, how do we leave them wanting to know more? Remember, this first impression will determine whether or not he or she does business with us.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;On March 18th, Sally White will be leading us in creating and refining our business slogans or, as she calls them, Audio Logos. In this dynamic program you will determine who your target audience is and what it is they need. By the time you leave the program you will be ready to deliver your own &amp;quot;Audio Logo&amp;quot; anytime, anywhere. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;'Close the gap!'  Author, speaker, trainer, Sally White helps clients lower attrition and increase profitability through the development of harmonious, goal-aligned teams.  With over 20 years experience bringing culturally diverse and multi-generational business teams together, Sally’s clients reaffirm the value of ‘I’ messages versus ‘You' messages in daily communication.  Experience her ‘Get it Done’ work philosophy, and close your communication gaps through Sally’s training sessions.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269085805000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268704813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Breakfast Meeting- Your Audio Logo</name><id>12887013</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268912700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/12887013/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/5/3/global_13690435.jpeg</photo_url></item>