<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>How many of us have searched Source Forge for a project that appears to fit our needs only to find there's no community or documentation behind it; or the code is really poorly written; or the project is about to fork...Sometimes selecting an open source project is like renting B-grade movies at the video store; it's not so much the cost that concerns you, but rather the time wasted if you select a dog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join BostonPHP as we continue our panel discussion on PHP frameworks this time showcasing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Andromeda - Kenneth Downs (founder)&lt;br /&gt;    * Drupal - Moshe Weitzman (core-developer)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: All BostonPHP events are free as in &amp;quot;beer&amp;quot; and open [to all] as in &amp;quot;source&amp;quot;, but please RSVP so we know how many party hats to order ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andromeda:  Some frameworks aim to manage and regulate the labor of software development, but Andromeda seeks to eliminate labor. Anything that can be done automatically is done automatically. In this way Andromeda fundamentally changes the cost dynamics away from tedious repetitive technical matters and allows you to focus entirely on customer service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;more information: &lt;a href="http://docs.secdat.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://docs.secdat.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drupal is a free software package that allows an individual or a community of users to easily publish, manage and organize a wide variety of content on a website. Tens of thousands of people and organizations have used Drupal to power scores of different web sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;more information: &lt;a href="http://www.drupal.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.drupal.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178318417000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1175729453000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PHP Frameworks part III</name><id>5638628</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178145000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/5638628/</event_url></item>