<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Alex has generously offered to host a churrasco in his home. His address is only being shared with our group. Everyone (including any guests who accompany you) is expected to be respectful and considerate of his gracious hospitality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;This will be a potluck meal with an emphasis on Brazilian dishes. You're encouraged to find a dish on which you can collaborate with another member. You can do the prep work at your home and combine the ingredients at Alex's or just bring your completed dishes with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;This will be a friendly laid back gathering with Portuguese conversation, which is a wonderful way for us to get to know each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;To be fair everyone who wants to attend must RSVP and contribute either food, drink, napkins, plates, utensils, music or whatever you think is needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;You must post what you're bringing after the RSVP question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;If you're able bring, something to sit on such as a chair and/or pillow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Please feel free to post suggestions, questions, clarifications and/or concerns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;There is parking if you drive and Alex's home is across from Oak Grove orange line train station in Malden.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Suggest you use Google maps, your GPS or MBTA.com for directions</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex</member_name><member_id>14284292</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342964957000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341952800000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Churrasco Potluck</name><id>72782002</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342897200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/72782002/</event_url></item>