<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rocky Neck Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.605629</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rocky Neck Art Colony</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>8044532</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.657387</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE 8/2: &lt;/strong&gt;  Ive uploaded a file for this event. If interested, it's an invitation to Sigrid Olsen -Isla Beach House Party on Rocky Neck Avenue - this file also includes a coupon if there's something you may wish to buy. To access it- go to top of meetup page, click on MORE, then FILES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From June to September, celebrate Nights on the Neck on the first Thursday of the month from 5:30 to 9pm. Many galleries host receptions with refreshments. Musicians, dancers, authors, historians and other entertainers give performances and lectures. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I've done this several times, and it's always been a great night out. We can walk the neck, visit the open galleries, listen to music, and end up at one of the restaurants for drinks &amp;amp; / food. This is a combined event with other meetup groups. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

*WE WILL MEETUP @ 5pm at The Rocky Neck Art Colony sign- the sign is at the public lot at the base of Rocky Neck Avenue- there are maps and brochures there. If you are unable to join us at 5, join us when you can. My contact # is: 978.289.7679. This is a mostly outdoor event - therefore, weather dependent. Please make sure to check for an update if weather is questionable. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

**You can find the schedule  and all info at: &lt;a href="http://www.rockyneckartcolony.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.rockyneckartcolony.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  8/2 schedule of events kicks off at 5pm with The Adventure Chantey Singers- across from the public parking lot.... and ends with Jazz from 8:45 - 9:45 at the Center on Wonson St.  www. rockyneckartcolony.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>please read description for where to meetup</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344753476000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341426486000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nights on the Neck - Gloucester - multi-group night out at Rocky Neck Art Colony</name><id>71952062</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343941200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/71952062/</event_url></item>