<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 East Wheelock Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03755</zip><lat>43.703922</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hopkins Center for the Arts</name><city>Hanover</city><id>3537492</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.282280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Looks to be kind of iffy weather tomorrow, so I'm gonna take in another flick in the Telluride at Dartmouth series. I'll meet folks in the front lobby again (oppostie Dartmouth Green). Not sure about a post movie discussion, but maybe. Pretty intense movie, so make sure you read the description. It has violent content. In this exquisitely realized adaptation of Lionel Shriver&amp;#146;s bestseller, Tilda Swinton (I Am Love) and John C. Reilly play an estranged couple whose 15-year-old son commits a sociopathic act of violence. Swinton, in a tour-de-force performance, masterfully inhabits the lonely world of a guilt-riddled survivor, split between horror and responsibility. As the details of their son&amp;#146;s crimes are revealed, the intricacies of marital and parental relationships are examined with a narrative pace that is both foreboding and deliberate. A sensitive psychological study that nevertheless packs a powerful and provocative punch, this film asks unsettling questions about the nature of violence. Director Lynne Ramsay relates a horror story through a lens of harrowing and confrontational realism in this deconstruction of suburbia and the modern American family. (UK/US, 2011, 112m) Courtesy Oscilloscope&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316991690000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316880063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie:"We Need to Talk about Kevin" at the HOP, Hanover, 4pm</name><id>34791712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316980800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/34791712/</event_url></item>