<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Sagamore Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01601</zip><lat>42.281723</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Center for Crafts</name><city>Worcester</city><id>392627</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.807526</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join the Worcester Center for Crafts on Thursday, November 4th, 2010 for a conversation with three of Central Mass' best known photographers. Stephen DiRado, Peter Faulkner, and Ron Rosenstock will come together to discuss their perspectives on how to get prepared for a Juried Photography Exhibit. Paul Dumanoski, Photography Instructor at the Worcester Center for Crafts, will serve as moderator.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This workshop will be an informative conversation with three professionals that will be offering their personal insights along with answering questions from the audience. This event is perfect for any photographer either experienced or just entering into the profession that has questions or just wants to learn more exhibiting their work. This talk is being held in anticipation of the Worcester Center for Crafts' upcoming juried photography exhibit, &amp;quot;Centering Yourself: A Look at How the Individual and the Community are 'Centered' through the Arts.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is free and open to the public, although a $5 donation is suggested. All proceeds go directly to the support programming at the Worcester Center for Crafts.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I am not sure about the time on this event- as they sent the info with out it I suggest you call the Craft center to be sure about the time!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about this event you can contact the Worcester Center for Crafts at 508.753.8183 or look for us on the web at www.worcester.edu/wcc&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289047245000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288110127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to get prepared for a Juried Photography Exhibit</name><id>15234530</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288911600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/15234530/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/c/global_9339132.jpeg</photo_url></item>