<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Lincoln St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03833</zip><lat>42.980938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Good Karma Cafe</name><city>Exeter</city><id>7212802</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.957634</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a walker/runner newbie or wannabee?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;… or do you want to just get in shape for the nicer weather?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are committed to getting into better shape this spring and would like to add walking or running to your program, please join us on Thursday Night, April 25th, from 6:30 PM to 8:30 PM at the Good Karma Café (Upstairs Lounge), 56 Lincoln Street in Exeter, NH (adjacent to the Amtrak Train Station) for a night of information and inspiration regarding walking and running training programs that range from the certified couch potato to the marathon-runner-in-training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal for the evening is to present local resources and alternatives for people who want to add walking and/or running to their routine, or would like to get involved with local walking/running events. This is not intended to start a separate running group, but simply to introduce you to the groups, events, web links and resources that are plentiful in the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Particular emphasis will be placed on the Seacoast Road Race Series, which is a series of 8 local events and an optional half marathon, which range from 5Ks to 10Ks, and for which if you complete 6 of the 8 events, you get a really nice running jacket (we’ll have several jackets there from prior years). We will also talk about the recent surge in WALKING for those who prefer, and emphasize that the series applies equally to walkers and runners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agenda: &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30 – 7:00: Meet &amp;amp; greet. We will have limited appetizers, and delicious and nutritious menu options are available for purchase. See menu link at: www.goodkarma-cafe.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 – 8:00: Presenting the film “Marathon Challenge” – a PBS/NOVA special about 12 non-runners who were trained to run the Boston Marathon in 9 months&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:00 – 8:30: A few words and Q&amp;amp;A with certified trainer Mike Davis and founder of &lt;a href="http://www.nofinishlinerunning.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.nofinishlinerunning.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 Raffle for all participants (no purchase necessary) – some cool items to help you on your journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you can expect:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• A great evening of information and inspiration at one of the “hidden gems” of Exeter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Chat with “regular” people who have started as non-runners and have gone on to run half marathons, and others who are accomplished runners and trainers of marathon runners&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Detailed information, including links and contacts for the local groups, events, and resources available, including everything necessary to run the Seacoast Road Race Series&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Everyone will get a free 2013 New England Running Calendar, and a 10% off discount courtesy of Runner's Alley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• The chance to win one of several valuable items courtesy of Runner's Alley at the raffle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking Forward to Seeing You There!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Thomas</member_name><member_id>10331124</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366936756000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366817080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walker/Runner newbies, wannabees, or just interested in learning more</name><id>115952462</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366929000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/115952462/</event_url></item>