<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Simsbury CT</address_2><address_1>2 Wilcox St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06070</zip><lat>41.874070</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>860-408-1234</phone><name>Amelia's American Bistro</name><city>Simsbury</city><id>537576</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.802050</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>So when I saw a page on Amelia's menu dedicated to its origins (and the verses of a song, to boot), you can imagine my reaction. After reading the story behind Amelia's, however, and after two dinner visits to the charming Simsbury restaurant, I've changed my fussy tune. If dining at the table of the restaurant's namesake (chef-owner Anthony J. Camilleri III's grandmother) was anything like dining at Amelia's, then the world was made a better place for it. Many places talk about the strong culinary bond of the family unit; few actually exhibit it. But from the welcoming salutations to the sincere &amp;quot;come back again&amp;quot; ? and every step of the dining experience in between ? I got the sense that Amelia's truly was guided by a caring, familial force that is so rare in today's cookie-cutter dining concepts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whatever Camilleri and his partners are doing is working. The staff couldn't be nicer. The food ? luxe American comfort dishes with French, Italian and Mediterranean leanings ? is accomplished. The wine list is inviting. And the atmosphere is warm, genuine and without any airs, given the menu's worldliness. What a lucky neighborhood to have this sweet spot in it Midst.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The look: Spare but sophisticated, with barn-red and marigold walls. Comfortable chairs and booths were made with adults in mind. The bar, set at a jaunty angle, is an inviting place to dine. Overall, the look is attractive without being flashy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The vibe: Amelia's is congenial and unpretentious. The service staff seems sincerely interested in making customers happy. A thoughtful wine list marries well with the menu of lusty comfort dishes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The eats: Starters include raw bar oysters, artisanal cheeses and house-made charcuterie. Among the appetizers are bacon and onion tart, diver scallops with bacon, crab cake, mussels and fries, salads and French onion soup. Entrees include steak frites, lamb shank, monkfish, macaroni and cheese with duck confit, rigatoni bolognese, and fish and chips. There also is a chophouse selection of entrees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The verdict: Chef Andrew Camilleri must have been paying attention at his grandmother's table (and on his game when he was in the kitchens at Anna's on Main, Pastis and Grants). His house-proud menu and service display a sure hand and a warm heart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The kitchen has a rich palette. The menu is dotted, like a truffle-studded pâté, with lusciousness: foie gras, pork belly, house-cured bacon, duck confit and great lashings of butter. Those, like me, who worship pork will be in hog heaven. The kitchen does its piggy parts proud. The strip of bacon covering two meaty diver scallops is so marvelous, you want to order another starter just for the velvet slice. The warm bacon lardons as big as board game dice made fine company with roasted mushrooms and goat cheese in a salad of baby spinach and frisée. We forgive the dry-tasting iceberg salad because the crispy bacon bits are so yummy. A chef who loves his bacon so much obviously would lavish attention on house-cured meats. Amelia's charcuterie (cured meats and terrines) is a welcome example of an artisanal craft that is enjoying a renaissance in the United States.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several of Amelia's entrees seemed tailor-made to the cold, snowy days of my visits. A braised lamb shank ? Fred Flintstone-enormous ? could barely hold onto its fork-tender meat. The big, meaty bone sat on a luscious stew of white beans so rich that only a few spoonfuls were possible. On another night, wine-stoked boeuf bourguignonne  was melt-away tender. Too bad the potato soufflé that came with it was dried out. The potato-chip-crusted cod (the fish component to a &amp;quot;fish 'n' chips&amp;quot; entree) was moist but almost flavorless. Not so the monkfish schnitzel, a delicious hunk of crispy, panko-crusted fish wearing a generous cap of warm lobster meat. Wonderful. The kitchen should be commended for taking such good care of the vegetables on the plate: Not a single carrot, potato, asparagus spear or haricot vert was overcooked. The one entree named for Amelia ? rigatoni cosseted with a heavenly Italian &amp;quot;gravy&amp;quot; of beef, veal, pork, tomato and red wine ? would make Grandma proud.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I wasn't wild about the directionless tuna tartare ? pretty sashimi that lost its way. Nor did I care for the blue cheese potato au gratin (grayish, lukewarm, slightly mealy). And one dessert, an atypical baked Alaska, bothered me. But the caramelized banana split was a nifty diet-buster. The kitchen threw in a profiterole, vanilla eclair and a berry tartlet, each of which was as delicious as it was precious. On one visit when the weather kept us from staying for dessert, we were sent home with house-made truffles and fruit jellies (thank goodness someone is still making honest wigglers) that were a pleasure to eat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those sweet gestures are no doubt an Amelia legacy. They also serve to define the character of this comfortable, caring and immensely likable American bistro.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservation will be under West Hartford Meetup.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209408092000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Because we are fun.
http://ameliasamericanbistro.com/philosophy.htm</why><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205007501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Amelia's American Bistro Fine Dining and Jazz</name><id>7492383</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209164400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/7492383/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/0/global_2943360.jpeg</photo_url></item>