<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cumberland Center</address_2><address_1>574 Pleasant Valley Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.660000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pleasant Valley Farm</name><city>Portland</city><id>276921</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.260002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>RAINDATE: Now June 9th, from 9am to 12pm, with Winter Cache.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who want to carpool, you can meet at the People's Free Space (144 Cumberland Ave) at 8:30am. Directions are pasted below.  We recommend that people bring lawn chairs or picnic blankets, as we will not have access to any inside facilities.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winter Cache will gather the basic materials (manure, seaweed, straw, newspaper), but it would be great for anyone to bring what they have (coffee grounds, food scraps, etc). As far as the area to cover, we figure we can just do what we can with the materials and time we have.   Any opinions or suggestions on initial plantings for &amp;quot;newly sheet mulched areas&amp;quot; would be appreciated by Winter Cache.   The woods nearby are the only &amp;quot;facilities&amp;quot; available so please take prior measures!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will follow the morning's work with a relaxing potluck lunch!!  Suggested potluck breakdown: &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with A-G main or side dish to share &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with H-M bring salad or veg or dessert &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with N-S bring whatever you want &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with T-Z bring bread or beverage &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you all there and working with another local sustainable organization!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions to Pleasant Valley Acres Farm&lt;br /&gt;574 Pleasant Valley Rd., Cumberland Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-From 295, get off at Exit 10 towards Route 9/Cumberland&lt;br /&gt;-Merge onto Bucknam Rd, towards Rt. 9&lt;br /&gt;-Turn right onto Rt. 9/Middle Rd. and go approx. 5.5 miles&lt;br /&gt;-Stay on Rt 9 until 4-way traffic light with big white church on left&lt;br /&gt;-Turn Left onto Blanchard Rd&lt;br /&gt;-Go approx. 1 mi, then turn right onto Bruce Hill Rd&lt;br /&gt;-Bear left onto Valley Rd.&lt;br /&gt;-Valley Rd dead ends onto Pleasant Valley Rd. and the farm is straight ahead. Pull into the driveway or turn left and park on the right side of the road!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-From 295, get off at Exit 15: US-1 towards Cumberland/Yarmouth &lt;br /&gt;-Turn right at US-1&lt;br /&gt;-Take a sharp left at Portland St&lt;br /&gt;-Continue on Middle Rd&lt;br /&gt;-Turn right onto Tuttle Rd&lt;br /&gt;-Continue on Tuttle Rd straight through intersection with Rt 9&lt;br /&gt;-Go approx. 1 mi, then turn right onto Bruce Hill Rd &lt;br /&gt;-Bear left onto Valley Rd.&lt;br /&gt;-Valley Rd dead ends onto Pleasant Valley Rd. and the farm is straight ahead. Pull into the driveway or turn left and park on the right side of the road!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181567506000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179507648000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UPDATED Sheet Mulching Work Party with Winter Cache</name><id>5792834</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181394000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/5792834/</event_url></item>