<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>deposit</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello my name is Anthony Pasquale I have owned few different businesses. For many years before my success I was not very good at anything but procrastination. What I have learned is how to understand &amp;quot;The Power of Personal Intent&amp;quot; and to put your success in action and to understand how to deal with rejections and also how to deal with Success too. This what I know,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Train yourself everyday. &lt;br /&gt;Recognize the fear and transform it into power. &lt;br /&gt;Know exactly what you want. &lt;br /&gt;Make a powerful decision. &lt;br /&gt;Clear limiting beliefs. &lt;br /&gt;Stay accountable to yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Listen if you have recently joined an MLM, Direct Sales Company, Network Marketing, Home based Business, well then congratutions, because these companies DO WORK if you know these principles behind success. I am doing an Eight Program with Gail Jones and you are invited to come here and see for your self. Want more details: RSVP Today&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our last meeting was attended by 19 people who desire a change! It was such a powerful and successful workshop that we got slammed with the request to do a series! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So here we go! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; Is Fear stopping your Success&amp;quot; Series &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Life coach Gail Jones and I are working very hard on this series of lessons that Will Instill all of the various tools that we spoke about during our last workshop &amp;quot;Beyond the Vision Board&amp;quot; and will bring your life's Purpose and Vision together, once and for all! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Imagine all the support of a Master Mind Group, Education for ongoing success in every aspect of your life, tools to break through the unknown and known fears that stop us from moving forward towards a destiny of wealth and abundance, to feeling confident that YOU CAN DO, Be and Have the life you want, NOW! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So listen as to how this is going to work : We only have 20 seats for this series, ONLY TWENTY people will go through this with us. These are the same tools that have really set my life in a direction of Purpose and Passion. We will be doing eight sessions with this group from November through January (taking some time off to honor the upcoming holidays). Each session will be coordinated with the schedules of group participants and the leaders. Each session will meet at the same place and the cost is 25.00 per session. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now imagine having the tools to wake up every morning knowing what your path is, what your purpose is, what you truly want out of life. Imagine having these tools to help make an empowered decision --feeling like you could conquer the fears that stop you. What is this worth? To me, it is priceless! Sign up today and let's begin. A $50 deposit is required to secure a place in the series. To register, please call AJP Enterprises/Beyond the Vision Board at 1-800-820-7632. Or click on the RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Pasquale &lt;br /&gt;AJP Enterprise &lt;br /&gt;A Mindful Wealth Group &lt;br /&gt;United Martial Arts Center &lt;br /&gt;Osanna Seminars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Live with Purpose and Passion Everyday&amp;quot; !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ideal Business Center &lt;br /&gt;20 Locust Street, Suite 100 &lt;br /&gt;Danvers MA 01923 &lt;br /&gt;(978) 836-6501&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289067540000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New to Network Marketings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1342126</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Network Marketing Support Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288122762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Is Fear stopping you from SUCCESS!</name><id>15237588</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289062800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group/events/15237588/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/4/7/global_7342935.jpeg</photo_url></item>