<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before signing up for this event, Please read the entire Write Up and understand and agree to the enclosed Liability Waiver.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Event Rating: Easy &lt;br /&gt;

 Distance: 2.75 Miles &lt;br /&gt;

 Time Duration: 1.5 Hours &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Blaze Orange: Required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/2/0/event_190755392.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The Durfee Hill WMA hike is a short 2.75 mile hike on a mix of woodland trails and forest roads. The hike will bring us through woodlands, by Grist Mill Pond, and by a historic cemetery. This is hike #25 in Ken Weber's "Weekend Walks in Rhode Island". There is no blazing on the trails of this hike, so navigating it without a reference like the Weber book would be a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The terrain is mostly flat, with some mild hills. There will be some wet spots, and what should be an easy stream crossing so boots are recommended. As always, bring water and snacks for the hike. For this hike you need an item of blaze orange clothing (hat or vest), since we will be in a wildlife management area and it is spring hunting season. Bug spray and sunscreen are two other items to bring with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike will follow the hike at nearby Pulaski Park, and the 12:00 start time should work out well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to Durfee Hill:&lt;/strong&gt; From the Providence area, take Route 44 West, passing through the village of Chepachet. Continue until you reach Rt 94 (also known as Reynolds Road). and take Rt 94 South for 1.3 miles. The parking lot will be on your left, and has a "Durfee Hill" sign.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liability Waiver As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Safety First!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John H.</member_name><member_id>14299089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367800200000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367530251000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Durfee Hill (Ken Weber Hike #25)</name><id>117420072</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367769600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/117420072/</event_url></item>