<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 302</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03598</zip><lat>44.216328</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dry River Trailhead</name><city>Crawford Notch</city><id>1014240</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.411018</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are planning a day hike to Mount isolation via the Davis Path, returning by way of the Dry River trail, starting and ending at Route 302.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the trailhead for the Dry River trail on Route 302 at 7 AM sharp where we will leave one or two cars. We will then drive to the Davis Path trailhead and begin our hike. After two fairly easy stream crossing the trail climbs steeply to the spur trail for Mt Crawford, a 3000 footer with 360 degree views on a nice day. After a quick trip to the summit we will return to the trail and continue on past the old Resolution Shelter to Mt Stairs. Leaving Mt Stairs we move on to Mt Davis, and finally onto Mt Isolation. If we hike a little faster than booktime and keep our breaks short on the summits, we should be able be on Isolation by 3 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leaving Isolation we continue to climb another hour to the Isolation Trail where we will start the long downhill return to the Dry River trail and Route 302. 2 miles from the end of the trail we will need to cross the Dry River whose bridge is closed. Tevas or water shoes, and poles may be needed as the stream us @ 100 foot wide and can be waist deep in spots. The water can be moving quite fast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is @ 19 miles incluing the spur trails to Mt Crawford, Stairs, Davis, and Isolation. Water along the way is very limited - bring plenty and a filter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike has several river crossings that could be dificult if high water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We aim to maintain booktime including stops in order to complete this hike in @ 12 hours, however be sure to bring a head lamp along.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anybody considering this hike should be confident in their abilities and endurance, understand the principles in HikeSafe. (&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees are responsible for reading, understanding and agreeing to the hikers responsibility code and waiver which can be found on this site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact us driectly with questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in a larger green suburban</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob &amp; Geri</member_name><member_id>4842806</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250695513000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247852094000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Isolation plus 3 - 19 mile Day Hike</name><id>10898465</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250420400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10898465/</event_url></item>