<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>91 Hampshire Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.368736</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Art &amp; Soul</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1549881</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094551</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;Are you feeling a little tired and overwhelmed, after the long winter? Do you feel like your mind and body needs a little tune up? Come to this 3-hour workshop focusing on increasing your energy, letting go of tension and bringing more balance into your life. This event will address multiple aspects of your mind-body wellness, and it is led by a group of experienced holistic health practitioners. It will include guided meditation and yoga, to help you identify and work with areas of potential growth and renewal within yourself. You will also learn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;how to welcome in the new season with foods that can help bring your body and mind back into balance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Please reserve your spot by registering here: www.BackintoBalance.eventbrite.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Workshop Leaders:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;Seetal Preet K. Cheema&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;is a physician, board certified in anesthesia and pain management.  She also trained in acupuncture at Harvard Medical School, and is a yoga instructor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;Pam Grewal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;Pam's yoga practice merges influences from the UK, India and California. In 2011, she completed the 200hr CorePower teacher training program in San Diego with a focus on vinyasa flow yoga. Her longstanding vocation in biomedical research has incorporated an interest in strong alignment with practical applicability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;Emilia Sabatowska&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;is a psychotherapist in private practice, specializing in mindfulness-based approaches. She has an extensive training in the area of stress management and health psychology. She has led many successful workshops on the topics related to personal growth and meditation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;Michelle Vinciguerra&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #691414"&gt;is a Certified Holistic Health Counselor accredited by the American Association of Drugless Practitioners. She is a graduate of the Institute of Integrative Nutrition and is passionate about food and its ability to transform one’s health and life. She offers individual and group nutritional health counseling.programs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please see the website for directions: http://www.artsoulyoga.com/Art_%26_Soul/Directions.html</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilia</member_name><member_id>1728643</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365368884000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>whole-living-center</urlname><id>1384267</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Whole Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363366134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Back Into Balance</name><id>109419372</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365357600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/whole-living-center/events/109419372/</event_url></item>