<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396492</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 623-0661</phone><name>Mr. Crepe</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669358</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122440</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The International/Art House Meetup Group is making this year's Independent Film Festival Boston a community event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members are going to gather before films to greet familiar faces, meet new members, and talk about experiences at the festival.  Grab a cup of coffee, or a quick snack, and go into the theater accompanied by friends.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opening Night Fim is the East Coast Premier of &lt;b&gt;Transsiberian&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;n,&lt;/b&gt;Directed by: &lt;b&gt;Brad Anderson&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, Apr 23, 2008 7:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;Somerville Theatre - Screen 1&lt;br /&gt;111 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The connection between cinema storytelling and trains is timeless. Train travel evokes a certain old-world mystique--a sense of foreignness coupled with nostalgia. The possibility of intrigue looms, as strangers are crowded into small, claustrophobic quarters. The legendary Transsiberrian Railway is the longest track in the world and serves as the only overland route that completely spans Russia. This arduous, week-long journey, traversing two continents, provides the backdrop for a taut new thriller from director Brad Anderson (THE MACHINIST; SESSION 9; NEXT STOP WONDERLAND.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A married American couple, Roy (Woody Harrelson) and Jessie (Emily Mortimer), board the train in Beijing after participating in a church-sponsored program to aid children in China. When it reaches the Russian border, their four-berth compartment gains two more passengers: flirtatious, sly Spaniard Carlos (Eduardo Noriega), and stony-faced, enigmatic American Abby (Kate Mara). The two couples mingle and carouse as the train heaves through the bleak, lifeless Siberian landscape toward Moscow. Jessie begins to suspect that Carlos and Abby are other than what they appear to be when she is left alone with them after Roy misses the train at a routine stop. After pragmatic, hard-nosed, narcotics inspector Grinko (Ben Kingsley) embarks, Jessie's suspicion that Carlos and Abby are engaged in nefarious dealings is confirmed. Jessie's and Roy's lives begin to derail as machinations surge and their own less-than-model pasts are revealed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;TRANSSIBERIAN is a daring, high-speed ride across a panorama of moral impediments and deception. Complex and intelligently written, this contemporary update of the train-thriller genre would do Hitchcock proud.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Callista Burns&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This film is certain to sell out well in advance&lt;/b&gt;.  Do not RSVP unless you purchase a ticket at &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://prod1.agileticketing.net/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?evtinfo=7485~de23b9ff-cbee-43c2-8d80-d797d9eef094&amp;amp;epguid=5ddf12be-cd3c-4edc-82b4-c55d0331f0f9&amp;amp;" target="_blank"&gt;http://prod1.agiletic...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The International/Art House Meetup Group's plans for the Festival will be posted soon, including a Post Pow Wow for the weekend following the Festival to give everyone a chance to talk about all the films.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Mr. Crepes is next to the Somerville Theater, the location of Transsiberian and many of the IFF films.  We are meeting as early as 6:15 in order to have time to pick up Festival tickets at the box office.  We will plan to enter the theater by 7:00</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949521000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><why>One movie Ticket: $9
Large Bucket of popcorn with professionally layered butter: $4
Coffee, Coke, or other caffenaited beverage: $2.50

Friends to meet and talk about all the great films at the IFF:  Priceless</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208284332000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Independent Film Festival Opening Night - Transsiberian</name><id>7744868</id><headcount>34</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208988900000</time><rsvp_limit>500</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7744868/</event_url></item>