<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>162 Winn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.504240</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>American Legion Hall</name><city>Burlington</city><id>486621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.185790</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt; Looks like the storm predicted for Friday will make it necessary to postpone our event. I am working with the band and hall and hope to reschedule on the weekend of January 10. More details will follow. I am sorry for any inconvenience and hope everyone has a great holiday! &lt;br /&gt;:-) &lt;br /&gt;Sandy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Save the date to celebrate the holidays with old friends and new at a special holiday party for meetup group members and their friends. There will be entertainment and dancing with Four on the Floor. We have rented the American Legion Hall in Burlington (right off of 128) from 7:30-11:30 PM with help of our good friend Brian. There is a $10.00 charge which should cover the expenses and some snacks. There will be a cash bar. You are welcome to invite family or friends, but please include their payment when you sign up (adults only, don't have to be single). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please reply at the MV Friends website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/mvsinglefriends/calendar/9033756/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you pay online please indicate that you have done so on your reply, it will help me keep track of who is attending. I appreciate your help with this. If you prefer to mail me a check please email me and I will send you my address but indicate on your reply, &amp;quot;paying by check&amp;quot; and I will let you know when I receive it. All checks must be received by December 12th. There is a limit of 125 people for the hall so please reply as soon as you know you can attend. If you have already replied yes, please make your payment asap so we can cover the hall deposit, and update your reply to reflect your payment.&lt;br /&gt;Last year we had a gift exchange which was alot of fun and some good laughs. Same rules will apply, bring a wrapped gift you can take a gift...nothing too expensive but something you wouldn't mind receiving yourself.&lt;br /&gt;Hope it will be a special night for all of us. I hope you will come.&lt;br /&gt;Sandy&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229906139000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225033371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>POSTPONED: Holiday Party with Four on the Floor</name><id>9033749</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229733000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9033749/</event_url></item>