<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will continue Kant with his 3rd critique: Critique of Judgement. The entire text probably would cover two meetings of ours however we plan to spend a single meeting on it, selections from the work for our meeting will be posted soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you John (Butler)for your guidance:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you feel at home in the Kantian idiom and want to read his views at the time of this work about how his various pieces fit together, then read the Preface and the Introduction in their entirety, but be prepared for many Kantian minor subtleties coming fast and furious.  Others should skip this rather than risk getting bogged down in Kant's preparatory arrangements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first section that is really required reading is Introduction, section IV, &amp;quot;Of Judgment as a Faculty of Legislating a priori&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introduction section V will be interesting to those who have a solid grasp of the First Critique and want to follow a detailed discussion of the emergence of empirical scientific laws, as Kant sees it.  Others may skip it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would suggest reading, or skimming, from Introduction Section vii to the end of the Introduction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would suggest reading most or all of the First Part Critique of the Aesthetical Judgment, but if you find it dragging after you are a little into the Analytic of the Beautiful, then be sure to also read some of the Analytic of the Sublime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the Second Part Analytic of the Teleological Judgment, Sections 61 to 68 and then 74 to 78 should convey the main ideas.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the philosophy group from the staff.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235092184000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231708940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kant: Critique of Judgement</name><id>9500303</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233878400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/9500303/</event_url></item>