<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer - Joe Ciarcia 415.480.4335&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DO NOT RSVP unless you are attending this hike. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. &lt;strong&gt;Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===&lt;span&gt;==&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The plan is to climb two of the 4,000 footers in NH - &lt;strong&gt;Jackson (#38 @ 4,052')&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Pierce (#27 4,310')&lt;/strong&gt;. Starting at the Crawford Station Parking (immediately south of the AMC Highland Center, please do not park at the Highland Center) we will hike the Webster Jackson trail to our first peak, Mt. Jackson. From the summit of Jackson we will head north on the Webster Cliff Trail to the AMC Mizpah Spring Hut (closed for the season) to stop for a bite. From Mizpah we continue along the Webster Cliff Trail to Mt. Pierce. From the summit of Pierce we continue north to the end of the Webster Cliff Trail where we will begin our return (west) on the Crawford Path which will bring us back home. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;on this hike given the current conditions. This may be revised as we get closer to the date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need things like warm layers, wind protection, goggles, &lt;strong&gt;snow shoes&lt;/strong&gt;, and traction &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;(bring microspikes or hillsounds trail crampons)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Also, the forecast is for a significant amount of rain this week. If it ends up freezing Friday night we may encounter icy conditions so throw your full &lt;strong&gt;mountaineering crampons&lt;/strong&gt; in the car (I will decide if they are needed at the trailhead). I will update everyone if weather conditions dictate that we bring more than what is described here. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions contact me. While we may not see signs of winter around us, the conditions on higher elevations may be different. Recent trail reports site some significant snow drifts at higher elevations so snow shoes are still required. I will update as we get closer to the date and see current trail conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a winter day hike&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. &lt;strong&gt;If you don't have the required items you put yourself and everyone else at risk. &lt;em&gt;If you do not have the required items, you will not be allowed to participate in the hike.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; out and back trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 8.5 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,206 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. It should take an average hiker &lt;strong&gt;about 5 hours 39 minutes to complete this trip (this does not include time for rest breaks or account for winter-like conditions)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com/"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.1992623&amp;amp;lon=-71.38218259999996&amp;amp;site=all&amp;amp;smap=1&amp;amp;searchresult=Webster%20Cliff%20Trail%2C%20White%20Mountain%20National%20Forest%2C%20MOUNT%20WASHINGTON%2C%20NH%2003589%2C%20USA"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(weather.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will meet in the Crawford Station parking lot. The Crawford Station lot is immediately south of the AMC Highland Center. Do not park at the AMC Highland Center. It will take about 2 hours and 38 minutes and is ~161 miles from Boston, MA. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.215221,-71.407902(Webster-Jackson+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.215221,-71.407902&amp;amp;sspn=0.007597,0.018818&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFbWrogId4ma--w&amp;amp;oq=boston&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;customizable driving directions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(google.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Mazda 3 wagon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ciarcia</member_name><member_id>40840452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365894635000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365205930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jackson, and Pierce (Intermediate/Advanced)</name><id>112922162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365856200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/112922162/</event_url></item>