<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>545 Pawtucket Ave Suite A104</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.859196</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Untapped Games</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>1572849</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.397934</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Enter our April Facebook contest for a chance to win half a booster box of Avacyn Restored or $25 in Store Credit! Just like us and answer the April Contest question at the top of our timeline to enter! &lt;br /&gt;

*** &lt;br /&gt;

Come to our Avacyn Restored Prerelease in Rhode Island! &lt;br /&gt;

The Helvaut opens April 28!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Untapped Games for our MTG Avacyn Restored sealed tournament on Saturday, April 28th, 2012 at 1pm. New players and MTG veterans are all welcome! The cost for the tournament is $15, in which you recieve 6 Avacyn Restored booster packs in order to play in the Sealed Deck tournament. These prerelease cards are yours to keep! Each player adds two Avacyn Restored packs to the prize pool and everyone receives a special pre-release promo just for playing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This set comes with the special Helvault promotion - an ominous artifact that unlocks as you complete special Prerelease achievements! Upon opening the Helvault, each player gets free mystery prizes just for participating!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ADDED BONUS! &lt;br /&gt;

Plus, if you want a chance to win even bigger prizes you can enter with a $5 buy-in that adds two booster packs to the prize pool!*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on our location, click HERE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Extra prize support of Avacyn Restored booster packs depends upon supply. All Prerelease materials are first come, first served! &lt;br /&gt;

***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*As an Authorized Internet Retailer of Wizards of the Coast, we may only ship sealed Magic: the Gathering products within the United States. As an Authorized Internet Retailer of Wizards of the Coast, we cannot sell sealed Magic: the Gathering products business to business.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335898319000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335312275000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pawtucket, RI @ Untapped Games-Avacyn Restored Pre-release!</name><id>61988642</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335632400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/61988642/</event_url></item>