<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://statementarts.votridea.com/contests/a-single-drop-of-water/about" target="_blank"&gt;http://statementarts....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Contest&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Water — No other natural resource is more important to us. We are looking for images that capture this essential element, and celebrate its beauty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Statement Arts is proud to announce the first annual ‘A Single Drop of Water’ photography competition. We invite you to join our international community of photographers and show your photos to our panel of distinguished judges. Winning entries shall be exhibited in New York City as part of the World Water Day celebration. Become part of the conversation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deadline: &lt;br /&gt;December 15, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entry Fees: &lt;br /&gt;$25 per photograph (all categories except youth)&lt;br /&gt;$15 per youth category entry&lt;br /&gt;Early Bird Special, get $10 off your entry fee if you enter before November 7, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prizes: &lt;br /&gt;Grand Prize - $1,500&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All Category Winners (except Under 25 category) - $500&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Under 25 Category Winner – Canon Digital Rebel SLR Kit Donated by Calumet Photographic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peoples' Choice Award - Canon Digital Rebel SLR Kit Donated by Calumet Photographic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Categories: &lt;br /&gt;A Single Drop of Water&lt;br /&gt;Photos depicting one or more drops of water.&lt;br /&gt;Water in our Daily Lives&lt;br /&gt;Photos depicting everyday interactions between people and/or animals/pets and water.&lt;br /&gt;Water Scapes&lt;br /&gt;All formats encouraged, including panoramic images.&lt;br /&gt;Clean Water Initiative&lt;br /&gt;Examples of initiatives might be:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Providing access to drinking water in a third world community.&lt;br /&gt;Removing pollutants from an existing body of water, whether it be river, ocean, lake, or similar.&lt;br /&gt;The water filtration process. An example of how water is filtered and cleaned of pollutants.&lt;br /&gt;Under 25&lt;br /&gt;For contestants 14 years or older but under 25 years on December 15, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;Open to all water related images.&lt;br /&gt;Photos will be assigned to the most appropriate category by Statement Arts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Peoples' Choice award will be granted to the entry that receives the most votes. It may come from any category.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notification of Winners: &lt;br /&gt;Winners will be notified via email by December 27, 2010. Winning entries shall be exhibited in New York City in Spring, 2011.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or, if you don't want to enter a photo, but you'd still like to support our project, please consider donating to Statement Arts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About A Single Drop of Water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Single Drop of Water is an environmental awareness project that uses the arts, specifically photography, to document the journey of water. Our goal is to raise awareness about this importance resource, it’s scarcity in some communities, and water pollution. The project will provide photographers with a platform for sharing their images and stories. Winning entries shall be exhibited in New York City, and will be used in future Statement Arts education materials to teach students about water and inspire them to produce their own artistic work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Statement Arts Mission&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Statement Arts is a not-for-profit organization dedicated to bringing the creative visual &amp;amp; performing arts to underserved and/or low-income individuals. We channel creativity to educate, to enhance intellectual performance, to empower and guide, and to build self-esteem. Statement Arts is committed to giving our students an intercultural and interdisciplinary arts experience to which they do not have access. Statement Arts believes in the power of art to inspire social, cultural, and environmental education to further a legacy of responsible global citizenship. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.statementarts.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.statementa...&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about Statement Arts.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Harding</member_name><member_id>9811788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292461810000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289491279000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>'A Single Drop of Water' Photography Competition -- Submission Date</name><id>15415410</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292457600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/15415410/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/global_14013533.jpeg</photo_url></item>