<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;RSVPs for this event will close two days before it is scheduled to occur.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first event of the Random Hikers New York Chapter! We will be hiking three of the Catskills 3500 ft mountains: Thomas Cole, Blackhead and Black dome. If you're want to embark on a new hiking list, here's a way to start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan is to go up the Black Dome Range Trail, over the three peaks, and then down Batavia Kill Trail. The route is about 7 miles and 3000 ft. Approximate book time is 5hrs without breaks, but this can vary depending on the terrain and pace of the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike is rated intermediate due to it's length, pace and elevation. No beginners please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trails may be icy, so you should be comfortable hiking in winter conditions. Some kind of traction, such as microspikes, is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "Catskills Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;list of items needed for a day hike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Appalachian Mountain Club&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://goo.gl/maps/Ameca</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emily Singer</member_name><member_id>7452900</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353202908000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351621738000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Catskills Hike - three 3500 peaks</name><id>89203932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353162600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/89203932/</event_url></item>