<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is very short notice but anyone I thought some people may be interested in seeing this film plus a photography slideshow. There are several art exhibits on view as well. Let me know if you would like to carpool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mystic Vision, Sacred Art&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday October 26 at 2 pm&lt;br /&gt;This film introduces the art of creating thangkas, which are sacred Tibetan&lt;br /&gt;Buddhist paintings created in the Kathmandu Valley of Nepal. It shows the&lt;br /&gt;step-by-step the process of creating the scrolled devotional paintings,&lt;br /&gt;offers insight into the symbolic and religious meaning of thangkas, and&lt;br /&gt;explains their importance in Tibetan Buddhist life. Most of the artists in&lt;br /&gt;the film are Tibetan refugees who have devoted their lives to preserving&lt;br /&gt;this sacred tradition. (Documentary Educational Resources. 1996. 28 minutes)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Landscape and Belief: A View Camera in the Himalayas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday October 26 at 3 pm&lt;br /&gt;For two decades Kenneth Hanson has been taking dramatic black-and-white photographs of the Himalayas. The regions he visited stretch from the Karakoram of Pakistan to Kangchenjunga in eastern Nepal. The mountains provide a unique experience—call it beauty, joy, terror, awe—that points beyond our reasonable world and takes us to the boundary between life and death. For the people of the mountains, this encounter is woven into their beliefs. There is a dialog between an older shaman-led sacrificial culture and various forms of Tibetan Buddhism. Increasingly the modern world intrudes. Hanson will discuss these interactions and show photographs from his book, Himalayan Portfolios.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tibetan Events and Exihibits at the Benton Museum&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Benton Museum located on the UConn campus in Storrs provides the academic community and the general public with diverse and widely acclaimed exhibitions, films and lectures. This November 2008, two monks from Namgyal Monastery, namely Thupten Woser and Lobsang Tashi, will be in residence at the Benton to create a Sand Mandala of Enlightenment in the East Gallery. Other ongoing events and exhibits include ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MAKE A PRAYER FLAG PANEL!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come in and make your own prayer flag panel as we prepare to welcome the monks of Namgyal Monastery to The Benton in November. We provide the fabric panel, stamps and pens, you provide the creative design and prayers. Panels will be hung outside the Benton in a growing colorful display of flags.&lt;br /&gt;Donation $1.99 per panel.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sera: The Way of the Tibetan Monk&lt;/b&gt; (Photo Exhibit runs August 26 – December 19, 2008 )&lt;br /&gt;In 1998, when Sheila Rock, an established fashion and portrait photographer, first encountered the monks and life in the Sera Monastery, she was struck by the quietude and serenity of the place and the individuals. The following year, with the permission of the abbot, she returned and began photographing the monks and novices individually and in groups.She also has taken photographs of the monks in their rooms, at work, at prayer, at play, or ceremonially gathered. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bound by Tradition and Religion: Tibetan Tangkas&lt;/b&gt; (Painting Exhibit runs October 21 - Decmber 19)&lt;br /&gt;The traditional Tibetan art of tangka painting is still practiced today. These scroll paintings, or tangkas, depict that various Buddhist and Bon divinties of the Tibetan religion. Also used as a form of meditation, observers can focus on the painted figures of the tangka to strive for liberation and enlightenment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will contact people.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225506992000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224953537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mystic Vision, Sacred Art -Tibetan Tangka Painting</name><id>9029545</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225044000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/9029545/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/a/global_6015338.jpeg</photo_url></item>