<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1227 Burnside Avenue Suite 1</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.783787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-888-4314</phone><name>The Conduit Center</name><city>East Hartford</city><id>1228246</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.585075</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;The Essential Breath&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Achieving Health &amp;amp; Vitality through Transformational Breathwork&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part 1:&lt;/b&gt; Foundations of Breathwork - Sunday April 18&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part 2:&lt;/b&gt; Opening to the Breath - Sunday May 2 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Many of us may remember a time in our youth when we breathed with relaxed, open bellies and as a result felt an almost unlimited supply of energy. The Taoists refer to this type of breath as &amp;quot;baby's breathing.&amp;quot; Now as we get older, we find that our breath has become restricted due to stress and poor breathing habits. Looking for ways to again cultivate our diminished energy, we turn to exercise, diet regimens, stimulants, vitamins, herbs, etc... but ironically the answer to recovering this lost sense of abundant vitality lies within us all ... in the total and infinite breath that we had as a child.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breathing is the best and most readily accessible resource you have for cultivating and maintaining your vital energy. Opening up the breath establishes a powerful connection to vital life force energy that can then enter into the body. This is what we would call the &amp;quot;essential&amp;quot; breath. To open our breathing, is to approach our life without hesitation, to become a channel for the breath as spirit. In the language of many cultures, the words &amp;quot;breath&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;spirit&amp;quot; are synonymous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most people are not even aware that their breathing has become restricted. In research on breathing techniques, studies have shown that using a slower, deeper breath will alleviate most health problems such as headaches, chronic pain, high blood pressure, asthma, menopausal symtoms, depression or anxiety. And altering the pattern of our breath can eventually affect the nervous, hormonal and metabolic systems within the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Part 1 of the Essential Breath Workshop, we will explore our breath perception to discover our own personal breathing patterns. Common breath holding patterns will be identified in a supportive group environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Foundations of Breathwork (Part 1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Introduction to the Breath&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;   What is Breathing?&lt;br /&gt;   The Breath Connection&lt;br /&gt;   Inquiry into the Essential Breath &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exploration of the Breath&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Using Breath Perception&lt;br /&gt;   Inquiry into Breath &amp;amp; Movement&lt;br /&gt;   How Do I Breathe?&lt;br /&gt;   Where Do I Breathe?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Catching the Breath - An Analysis of Breath Holding&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;   Causes of Common Breath Holding Patterns&lt;br /&gt;   Reverse, Chest, Collapsed, Throat, Grabbing and Frozen Breathing Patterns&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Part 2 of the Essential Breath Workshop, we will experiment with changing our breathing patterns to open the body's energy centers and channels. Breath meditation will be discussed and practiced to create balanced, calm, fluid, and effortless breathing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Opening to the Breath (Part 2&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Freeing your Breathing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Breathing into the Back&lt;br /&gt;   Organ Breathing &amp;amp; Self-Massage&lt;br /&gt;   Body/Breath Synchronicity during Postures&lt;br /&gt;   Opening the Center of the Body&lt;br /&gt;   Opening the Lower and Upper Channels&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meditation &amp;amp; Breath - Cultivating Stillness&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Mindfulness Practice&lt;br /&gt;   History of Our Breath&lt;br /&gt;   Life &amp;amp; Death in Breathing&lt;br /&gt;   Entering into Stillness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Essential Breath Part 1 will be held at The Conduit Sound Mind &amp;amp; Body Center in East Hartford, CT on April 18 from 4 to 6:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;Cost $25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Essential Breath Part 2 will be held at The Growing Green Wellness Center in Hartford, CT on May 2 from 4 to 6:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;Cost $25.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or register for both sessions and pay only $40. Participants are encouraged to bring a blanket and pillow. Space is limited to 12 participants. For more information contact Christine through her email link under Asst. Organizers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271871128000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268691336000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Essential Breath - Part I</name><id>12884740</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271620800000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12884740/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/b/global_13685835.jpeg</photo_url></item>