<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;New stuff: The movie is now scheduled to start at 6:45 p.m., so please plan to meet&amp;nbsp;right at&amp;nbsp;6:30 p.m. in the outer lobby of the AMC Framingham. Sometimes it's crowded on Friday nights, so I'm going to want to take a count of who is there at 6:30 and get in line to get tickets for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discount tickets: I will have discount coupons available so we can get tickets for $8.00 each. (Retail price is $10.50.) I will collect $8 in cash from each person and then I'll get in line to buy tickets for all. Exact change is helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movie, those who want to are welcome to go out to a local restaurant to chat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Film description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"X-Men: First Class" follows the classic Marvel mythology, charts the epic beginning of the X-Men saga. Before Charles Xavier and Erik Lensherr took the names Professor X and Magneto, they were two young men discovering their powers for the first time. Before they were archenemies, they were closest of friends, working together, with other Mutants (some familiar, some new), to stop the greatest threat the world has ever known. In the process, a rift between them opened, which began the eternal war between Magneto's Brotherhood and Professor X's X-Men. &lt;br /&gt;

Cast: James McAvoy, Michael Fassbender, Rose Byrne, January Jones &lt;br /&gt;

MPAA Rating: PG-13 &lt;br /&gt;

Length: 2 hr. 11 min. &lt;br /&gt;

Genre: Action/Adventure &lt;br /&gt;

Director: Matthew Vaughn&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the outer lobby, off to the right as you come in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>6039490</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309011625000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308183917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framingham Movie Meet-up:  X-Men: First Class</name><id>22377271</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308955500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/22377271/</event_url></item>