<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Belver Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02852</zip><lat>41.592552</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quonset National Guard Base</name><city>North Kingstown</city><id>1592762</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.426376</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are not Racing (nor Flying), but this fits right in with our spirit of Speed &amp;amp; Thrills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;b&gt;20th Anniversary Rhode Island National Guard Open House &amp;amp; Airshow&lt;/b&gt; offers the finest aerial and static displays along with activities for people of all ages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission to the show and parking is FREE!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a $10 donation collected at the entrance gates to support Hasbro Children's Hospital but it is purely voluntary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take a look at their &lt;a href="http://www.riairshow.org/faq.html" target="_blank"&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt; page to know what to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Schedule:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;0900 - Gates Open&lt;br /&gt;1000 - Opening Flag Jump - Black Daggers&lt;br /&gt;1010 - Tucker Teaser - Sean D. Tucker&lt;br /&gt;1020 - Kevin Coleman Air Shows&lt;br /&gt;1030 - Kent Pietsch&lt;br /&gt;1040 - Rhode Warriors - C-130J Demo&lt;br /&gt;1055 - John Klatt - ANG&lt;br /&gt;1110 - F-18 Hornet Demo&lt;br /&gt;1125 - Mike Goulian&lt;br /&gt;1140 - Kent Pietsch&lt;br /&gt;1150 - Black Daggers&lt;br /&gt;1200 - Vandy 1 - Hak Hickman&lt;br /&gt;1215 - Red Bull Air Force Jump Team&lt;br /&gt;1225 - Kent Pietsch&lt;br /&gt;1235 - Chuck Aaron - Red Bull Helicopter&lt;br /&gt;1250 - John Klatt - ANG&lt;br /&gt;1305 - A-10 Demo&lt;br /&gt;1320 - Mike Goulian&lt;br /&gt;1335 - F-18 Hornet Demo&lt;br /&gt;1350 - Sean D. Tucker&lt;br /&gt;1405 - Combined Arms Demo&lt;br /&gt;1430 - Thunderbirds&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions From Points North:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Providence, Boston) - Take I95 South to Exit 9 - RT 4 South, North Kingstown, East Greenwich (left exit). Off of RT 4, take Exit 7B (Quonset) Stay on RT 403. RT 403 will become Roger Williams Way. After the 3rd traffic light on Roger Williams Way take a left onto Conway Street. Follow signs to Air National Guard Base.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send out my cell number to the members attending.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deepak</member_name><member_id>2592822</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277766331000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Racing Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>racing</urlname><id>1209048</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>Racing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277312939000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AIR SHOW</name><id>13887979</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277643600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/racing/events/13887979/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/5/global_15923941.jpeg</photo_url></item>