<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Welcome to our own Sano Café! Our commitment to providing our community and customers with the highest quality and freshest natural and organic products available is fully evident the moment you are seated in our cozy dining nook. We take great pride in the creativity and 30+ year's experience of our kitchen, deli and bakery team. They have developed innovative recipes that are nutritionally balanced as well as downright delicious! We use only the finest natural organic produce, herbs, grains, seasonings and expeller-pressed oils in our kitchen's creations. In addition, multi-pure filtered water is used during all food preparation stages, including rinsing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We welcome your special dietary requests and will be happy to accommodate them. We encourage you to share your appetite with us and are confident you will enjoy your wholesome dining experience as much as we enjoy creating it for you. The Sano Café was voted best vegetarian restaurant in Worcester!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come by and make this group grow! It's an open forum and we encourage any ideas or suggestions for topics etc.. Whether you just want to network and meet local vegans like yourself, share recipes, if you are looking for support in making or maintaining this change in your life, want to discuss challenges and success or if you just want to try some yummy food...you are most welcome! I attached a link, go to &amp;quot;Sano Cafe&amp;quot; and there will be a link to the full menu. It's also a great place because the cafe is attached to the store, so you can go and do your shopping before or after as well!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.lefoods.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lefoods.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lefoods.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Dunne</member_name><member_id>1339538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1149444471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp July Meetup</name><id>4964003</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1151859600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/4964003/</event_url></item>