<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's enjoy some warmth and sunshine! I would love a long walk to get a good, stretch/warm-up after the crazy days at work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; moderate, but &lt;strong&gt;long&lt;/strong&gt; (11.25 miles...doing the whole park). &lt;em&gt;Please do not atttend unless you are fit and capable of a long, brisk hike!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/0/e/event_63409422.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quabbin Reservoir is the most beautiful place in Massachusetts!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's an 18-mile-long Reservoir with many islands, and home to bald eagles, deer, and more. It's the second-largest (in surface area) man-made body of water in the world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Quabbin Park&lt;/em&gt;, at the southern end, has paved (but hilly) roads with goregous views. Our hike takes us over both dams...almost from one end of the park to the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start at the Visitor's Center in Belchertown, MA and cross over Winsor Dam. From there, we hike past the boat cove, then uphill for 1.5 miles through the rotary (near the viewing tower). Shortly after that is Enfield Overlook, a gorgeous spot with a great view of Mount Monadnock and the former location of the town of Enfield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The park road continues past Hank's Meadow...often a great spot to see white-tailed deer. A ways before it hits Route 9, we'll take the loop over and behind Goodnough Dike (where I took the photo above). Finally, we go back through the park to the Visitor's Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This typically takes me 3.5 hours with no lunch break; by myself, I walk &lt;strong&gt;very&lt;/strong&gt; fast. &lt;em&gt;In a group, figure at least 5, but I will try to keep up a brisk pace!&lt;/em&gt; Bring your camera...there will be many awesome views! Also, pack a lunch and drink. At a group pace, you'll want a lunch break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are bathrooms at the Visitor's Center, and outhouses (with sanitizer) at popular spots. We'll probably picnic at Hank's Meadow or the Goodnough Dike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PLEASE DON'T WORRY BECAUSE THE EAST AND MIDDLE ENTRANCES ARE CLOSED. The park road is closed to vehicle traffic during the storm cleanup, but not to hikers and bikers. The WEST entrance never closes! I've walked though the park a couple times already.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very important park rules:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry-in, carry-out. (Take your trash with you...well, the Visitor's Center and tower have trash bins.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. (From the North, use I-290 to get to Route 9.) Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware and some steep hills, there's not much except scattered houses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Park has 3 entrances, but you can only get to the Visitor's Center via the West Entrance (and the others are closed during cleanup). You want the 3rd entrance on on the right (going westbound). It takes 5 or more minutes to pass all 3 entrances. Please look for a white "Quabbin Reservoir WEST ENTRANCE" sign and a blue "State Police" sign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google maps is messed up! (It shows the marker further west on Route 9 than it actually is.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, after the 1st entrance, there's marsh on both sides of the road, and you can see Quabbin Tower on a hill in the distance, diagonally right. When you see the tower, there are 2 entrances to go. The West entrance is 1 hour west of (western) Worcester by Route 9...maybe a little longer with line crews working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live closer to Route 31 or 122 than to I-290, just take the appropriate route South to Route 9, then follow directions "from Worcester" as above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points North and West (or Route 2):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the North (or from Route 2), take Route 202 South. Turn left and go East on Route 9. The West Entrance is the first entrance on your left. There's no landmarks I can think of, and maybe it's a mile or two (not sure). Please look for a white "Quabbin Reservoir WEST ENTRANCE" sign and a blue "State Police" sign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;F.Y.I., if you email me with questions, I'll already have left the house an hour ahead.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320884847000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320554158000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Park (whole thing) @ Quabbin Reservoir</name><id>40117342</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320678000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/40117342/</event_url></item>