<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>215 Great Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01464</zip><lat>42.578570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-425-4311</phone><name>The Bull Run</name><city>Shirley</city><id>380565</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.642235</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>COST:$18.00 in advance&lt;br /&gt;          $22.00 day of the show&lt;br /&gt;FOR TICKETS: Call The Bull Run to order by credit card: 978-425-4311&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME:  CONCERT : 7:30(music begins at 8pm) or whenever you can join us1 &lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROOMFUL OF BLUES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having long established themselves as an American blues institution, Roomful of Blues celebrated its 39th anniversary in 2008. Roomful, which is famous for their Jump blues style ? that infectious blend of swing jazz and urban blues, is universally referred to as the &amp;quot;best little big band in America.&amp;quot; Now numbering eight players and remaining one of the most versatile, hard?swinging blues bands around, Roomful was first formed in 1967 by Duke Robillard. When Robillard left the band in 1979, Roomful grew from seven to ten pieces. Over the years, they have recorded &amp;quot;twenty or so&amp;quot; albums, including recordings with Eddie&amp;quot;Cleanhead&amp;quot; Vinson and Big Joe Turner; albums which won back to back Grammy nominations in 1983 and 1984 in the category of Best Traditional Blues Album; not to mention the record Roomful made with Earl King (Glazed), which won the Grammy for Best Contemporary Blues Album in 1988. In 1991, Roomful provided the muscle on Pat Benatar's True Love. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Aim the beat at their feet!&amp;quot; is the tireless maxim that expresses the character and guiding principle of Roomful of Blues, &amp;quot;the most danceable swinging blues band on the planet,&amp;quot; writes Frank?John Hadley. &lt;br /&gt;Roomful's upcoming release &amp;quot;Raisin' a Ruckus&amp;quot;, on Alligator Records, will hit the streets on January 15, 2008. By the time of this show it will be in stores and on the air. So look for some brand new material at this one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opener: The Matt Zeiner Band - There's nothing typical about a &amp;quot;typical&amp;quot; night's performance by the Matt Zeiner Band. Driven by Zeiner's startling and powerful vocals, their sound is an organic blend of rock, soul, funk and roots?all driven by Matt's melodic, inspired and deeply personal songwriting which conjures names like Billy Joel, Ray Charles, Michael McDonald and the Allman Brothers. The latter is no stretch for Zeiner, who toured and co-wrote with Dickey Betts for four years following Betts' departure from the Allman Brothers.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you phone to  purchase your ticket, please ask to be seated at the Meetup table(s).</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206964755000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>The Bull Run has some great shows and this is one of them</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201413656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ROOMFUL OF BLUES @ The Bull Run</name><id>7204410</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206743400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7204410/</event_url></item>