<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Hunt Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.836670</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Amesbury Sports Park</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1486796</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.945374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;This event will require prepayment. It'll cost $45 per person. I suggest you pay as soon as possible before they fill up. Here is the link to sign up. &lt;a href="http://www.feemania.com/events/register/16"&gt;http://www.feemania.com/events/register/16&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.spartanrace.com - the main site &lt;br /&gt;..............................................................................  &lt;br /&gt;SPARTAN SPRINT: Challenge&amp;rsquo;s a Spartan&amp;rsquo;s Agility&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spartan Sprints are muddy 3+-mile events with 10 or more obstacles. The challenging sprint races are a great way to get off your couch and start living. Beginners to hardcore warriors, and marathon runners alike come out to test themselves on the insane obstacles! 99.9% of all people who try this event will finish, and 100% will have their thirst for mud fully satisfied! Top 3 Males and top 3 Females at each Spartan Sprint qualify for a free entry into a Super Spartan of his or her choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you get?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spartan Race T-Shirt  &lt;br /&gt;Spartan Race Finisher Medal  &lt;br /&gt;One free beer (must be 21 or older)  &lt;br /&gt;Food Vendors  &lt;br /&gt;Music/MC  &lt;br /&gt;Awards Ceremony  &lt;br /&gt;Top finishers receive free entry into a Super Spartan of their choice  &lt;br /&gt;Completion earns you Spartan Agility certification (Black Level)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;............................................................................  &lt;br /&gt;Spartan Race is on a mission to get you active, healthy, excited about change, and return to our ancient roots where running through woods, getting dirty, and facing adversity was part of everyday life. Our events are all about challenging today&amp;rsquo;s perception of normal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having experienced many different racing events, we wanted to make adventure racing more accessible to everyone, but do not be fooled by the word &amp;lsquo;accessible&amp;rsquo;, as our events have a challenge for everyone&amp;rsquo;s needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spartan Race now introduces a level for everyone beginning with the entry level Spartan Sprint, intermediate level Super Spartan and the &amp;lsquo;99.9% need not apply&amp;rsquo; extreme level Spartan Death Race.  &lt;br /&gt;Whatever your level, Spartan Race will test your strength, stamina, and sense of humour.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll figure that out as we get closer to the date</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315840372000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Cuz it's gonna be fun... Please sign up on their website ASAP... the spots are fllling up fast. those who have signed up are starting at 930.</why><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294744963000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spartan Race - Spartan Sprint</name><id>16005698</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314451800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/16005698/</event_url></item>