<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join Stevie from the &lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Providence French Language Group&lt;/span&gt; on &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;March 24 at 6.45 pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; for &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Persepolis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, the 2nd film of the &lt;b&gt;Salve Regina French Film Festival held in Newport RI&lt;/b&gt; between &lt;b&gt;22 March to 2 April 2009&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films are being shown to the public for no charge thanks to the support of the French American Cultural Exchange (FACE), the Cultural Services of the French Embassy and the French Ministry of Culture (CNC). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An RSVP limit of 15 will ensure we have enough seats in the theater given its freely available to all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the film&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Persepolis&lt;/b&gt; is an animated film set during the Islamic Revolution in Iran.  The Salve Regina French Film Festival website shows the following details for the screening of this film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Persepolis&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Date &amp;amp; Time: &lt;b&gt;7 p.m. Tuesday, March 24&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• Location: &lt;b&gt;Bazarsky Lecture Hall, O'Hare Academic Center&lt;/b&gt; (located on the Salve Regina Campus, Ochre Point Road, Newport RI)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;An inspiring and humorous coming-of-age story of a young girl in Iran during the Islamic revolution. Multiple award-winning adult animation like you've never seen.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;b&gt;FACE Tournees Festival&lt;/b&gt; website (&lt;a href="http://www.facecouncil.org/tournees/fichesfilms/persepolis.html" target="_blank"&gt;facecouncil.org/tournees/fichesfilms/persepolis.html&lt;/a&gt;) describes Persepolis as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Persepolis is the poignant story of a young girl coming of age in Iran during the Islamic Revolution. It is through the eyes of this precocious nine year old, Marjane, that we see a people's hopes dashed as fundamentalists take power - forcing the veil on women and imprisoning thousands. Clever and fearless, she outsmarts the “social guardians” and discovers punk, ABBA and Iron Maiden. Yet when her uncle is executed and bombs fall around Tehran, during the Iraq/Iran war, the daily fear that permeates life in Tehran is palpable. As she gets older, her parents worry for her safety and decide to send her to school in Vienna when she turns fourteen. Vulnerable and alone in a strange land, Marjane endures the typical ordeals of a teenager. She also has to combat being equated with the religious fundamentalism she is trying to escape. Over time she finds acceptance and even love but remains terribly homesick. Marjane decides to return to Iran to be close to her family. After a difficult period of adaptation, she enters art school and gets married, all the while continuing to speak against the hypocrisy she witnesses. At age 24 she realizes that although she loves her country she cannot live there anymore and she decided to leave for France.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DIRECTOR&lt;/u&gt; – Marjane Satrapi &amp;amp; Vincent Paronnaud&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;SCREENPLAY&lt;/u&gt; – Marjane Satrapi &amp;amp; Vincent Paronnaud&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;VOICES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Marjane: Chiara Mastroianni&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Marjane's mother: Catherine Deneuve&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Marjane's grandmother: Danielle Darieux&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Marjane's father: Simon Abkarian&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Young Marjane: Gabrielle Lopes&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;AWARDS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jury Prize, Cannes Film Festival (2007).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Best animated feature, New York Film Critics Circle (2007). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Best Adaptation and Best First Film, Césars Awards (2008).&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Running time&lt;/u&gt;: 95’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Production&lt;/u&gt;: France, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rating&lt;/u&gt;: PG-13&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gauge&lt;/u&gt;: 35mm, DVD (B&amp;amp;W)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;GENRE&lt;/u&gt; - Animation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DISTRIBUTOR&lt;/u&gt; - New Yorker Films&lt;br /&gt;___________________&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is being organised by Stevie Worthington as part of a &lt;b&gt;6 part Meetup event&lt;/b&gt; for the &lt;b&gt;Providence French Language Meetup group&lt;/b&gt; held in NEWPORT RI. If you can't make this night, hopefully you can make it to at least one of the other films in the Newport French Film festival on either 22 Mar, 26 Mar, 29 Mar, 31 Mar or 2 April. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, send Stevie an email - merci!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be inside the lobby from 6.30pm wearing a pink jacket holding a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238108866000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>providencefrenchlanguage</urlname><id>1145546</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Providence French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236707333000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Film Festival in Newport - Film 2 "Persepolis"</name><id>9924121</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237935600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providencefrenchlanguage/events/9924121/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/f/global_7623487.jpeg</photo_url></item>