<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a hike that our single members might enjoy. Charlie's Active Singles hikes are for active single people in their 30's through 50's and average up to 100 people per event! These events have been found to be fun and well planned!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet-up is at 9:00 AM at location of the hike. Hikers are usually split up into 3 different hiking skill levels (something like advanced, novice, and social) and the difficulty of the hike corresponds. The hike starts at 9:30 AM and usually lasts about 2 hours. Afterwards, dinner facilities are arranged for refueling and socializing. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS (a bit sketchy but best I have -Contact Charlie for clearer directions): &lt;br /&gt;From Hartford and/or points east of Danbury:&lt;br /&gt;* Take Rt. 84 West to exit 9-Rt. 25 North towards Brookfield.&lt;br /&gt;* In Brookfield, take a right onto Rt. 7 North approximately 25 miles to the Bull?s Bridge Inn.&lt;br /&gt;* You are there when... approaching a stoplight, you see a gas station / food mart followed by the Bull?s Bridge Inn (large white house) on the right.&lt;br /&gt;* Cross the covered bridge and park in parking areas and along the right side of road past the second bridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get there from Boston and New England:&lt;br /&gt;* I-90 West (Mass Turnpike) to Exit 2 ? Lee/Pittsfield&lt;br /&gt;* Left off ramp follows signs to Rte 7 South&lt;br /&gt;* Stay on Rte 7 South through the towns of: Stockbridge, Great Barrington, Sheffield, Canaan, Falls Village, West Cornwall and Cornwall Bridge&lt;br /&gt;* Continue South on Rte 7 towards Kent for 2.5 miles to the Cornwall Inn on the right.&lt;br /&gt;* Cross the covered bridge and park in parking areas and along the right side of road past the second bridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions per MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/bulls+bridge:Kent+CT/#a/maps/l:Bulls+Bridge+Covered+Bridge::Kent:CT::US:41.675926:-73.509567:address:/m:null:12:41.675926:-73.509567:0::/io:0:::::f:EN:M:/e" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Singles is a 10 year old, non-profit Connecticut organization that brings together singles who enjoy participating in a variety of outdoor activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: Charlie (organizer of Active Singles) 860-489-9611&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership is planned to be at this hike. Just mingle with the other Active Singles (you're one!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO Children or Dogs, Singles only (this doesn't mean you can't have a boyfriend or girlfriend). Wear Hiking Boots. Bring water. Optional Brunch follows each hike. Non hikers can join us at the restaurant. Call Charlie early to reserve a spot for Brunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.activesingles.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.activesing...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>May not be any hiking group leadership at the event... event is run by Active Singles organization.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207754379000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Lots of people to socialize with and at least three skill levels to choose from!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205808451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Active Singles Hike to Bulls Bridge in Kent CT</name><id>7553740</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207486800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7553740/</event_url></item>