<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Our next meeting is Monday, June 23rd from 7:00pm to 9:00pm at the Prudential Mall food court.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to talk about a variety of topics as well as do an exercise or two to help strengthen our communication.  Here's the agenda for the meeting:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Introductions and icebreakers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Field reports and news from our members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lesson:&lt;/b&gt; How to attract your ideal mate using the law of attraction&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exercise:&lt;/b&gt; We'll do an exercise based on the law of attraction that will move you closer toward attracting your ideal mate (or friends, jobs, roommates, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exercise:&lt;/b&gt; Personality feedback&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exercise:&lt;/b&gt; We'll end the meeting with a little bit of structured mingling&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Munchies:&lt;/b&gt; I always go to Legal Seafoods after the meeting. Anyone who wants to come along is welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you find yourself getting frustrated with the whole dating process, because you're not sure how to attract the kind of people into your life that you really want, then you're going to love this month's meeting.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why you keep attracting the wrong kind of people into your life and what you can do about it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What you should do after you have a bad date (the answer might surprise you).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A simple process for becoming clear on exactly what kind of partner you want to attract (this also works for attracting friends, business colleagues, jobs, roommates, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You'll walk away from the meeting feeling much clearer about the kind of people you want to meet, and you'll know what to do next in order to draw them into your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we'll go into one of the most valuable sections of the meeting.  We'll break up into smaller groups, and each person will have an opportunity to receive direct, honest (and extremely rare) feedback on how you can improve the way you come across.  Be prepared for a fun, interactive meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's important that I get an accurate head count, so please RSVP if you plan on coming.  I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. - There's just a $10 materials fee payable in cash when you arrive.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"I will email everyone who is RSVP'd and let you know where I'll be sitting in the food court. I'll also send you my cell phone number."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214435016000</updated><rating><average>3.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>There is simply no other place that focuses on the self-improvement aspect of your social life. This isn't just a social networking opportunity. It's a chance to improve your social networking skills.</why><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212234695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Social Skills and Dating June Meeting</name><id>8047873</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214262000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/8047873/</event_url></item>