<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Long Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.359778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-720-9200</phone><name>Boston Harbor Cruises</name><city>Boston</city><id>732009</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050870</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;David Goldstein of the &amp;quot;Taste of Chocolate Walking Tour&amp;quot; and the comedy dinner theater &amp;quot;Mystery Cafe&amp;quot; is giving a discount to Nerd Fun members to their new Mystery Cafe show &amp;quot;Marriage Can Be Murder&amp;quot;, only $42 per person instead of the usual $64.95. Need to buy tickets for your guest? Call the box office since online ticketing only offers the discount code &lt;b&gt;MarriageMayhem&lt;/b&gt; to the first person on the set of tickets.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; option for RSVPing will be dropped a week before the event to get a more accurate headcount. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Mystery Cafe site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mysterycafe.com/95/mystery-cruise" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mysterycaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Blend two Boston treats together and experience theatre on water. Take in a first-class production while smoothly cruising around the harbor. Let a mystery cruise inject intrigue into the air, as all the other passengers suddenly look guilty in this classy whodunit! You might be surprised at how excited people become during the game, racing from bow to stern in the hunt for the next clue.”&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;b&gt;Travelsense.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The world famous Mystery Café cordially invites you to attend the wedding that will end all weddings with “Marriage Can Be Murder!” Celebrate the nuptials of Jessica Pitch and Aaron Fishman on a mystery cruise around Boston Harbor, complete with food, fun, music, mayhem, and…murder!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The mother of the bride has planned for the perfect wedding, but before her beautiful daughter can even say 'I do' a bloody killing mars the happy day! It is up to you, the wedding guests, to find the killer, determine their motive, and make sure that love lives 'happily ever after.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Was it the groom, the wedding planner, the mother-in-law, or one of the guests? Who is hiding a sordid past? Who has a secret love? Who’s been holding on to a grudge? Everyone is a suspect – including you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As soon as you step on board, you will become part of the mystery and the fun. Do the chicken dance, catch the bouquet, question the suspects and solve the crime – you could even become the evening’s 'super sleuth' and win a prize!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;So welcome aboard for a wedding experience you’ll never forget: 'Marriage Can Be Murder!'&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher -- 5 foot 7, short brown hair, blue eyes, &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag -- will be waiting inside the Long Wharf Mariott in front of the Starbucks section starting at 6:30 pm. Feel free to drop by! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can board the boat at 7:00 pm, which will be docked in front of the Mariott near the Boston Harbor Cruise ticket booth, and explore onboard. If this is like the Mobfather, we will be greeted as if we are friends of the bride or the groom by some of the CharActors. Remind me to bring little discreet red MEETUP stickers we can wear to tell our group apart.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Purchase Tickets:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The ticket price includes the show, dinner, tax, and gratuity. There is a cash bar available for beverages. Dress code is casual, though we do recommend rubber soled shoes and suggest you bring a wind breaker, as the harbor does get chilly in the evening&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;By Phone&lt;/u&gt;: Call the box office at 781-784-7469 and mention you have the code &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;MarriageMayhem&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;. You need to call the box office so you both can get the discount. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Online:&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Go to &lt;a href="http://secure.mysterycafe.com/reservations/new?performance_id=152" target="_blank"&gt;http://secure.mystery...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Enter your billing information and purchase a single ticket for yourself. More than one? Call the box office.  &lt;br /&gt;* Enter the Group Name of ‘Nerd Fun’&lt;br /&gt;* Proceed to checkout; &lt;br /&gt;* In the Promotional Code box, enter &lt;b&gt;MarriageMayhem&lt;/b&gt; and click Check Code – it will apply your special group discount to that one tickets in your reservation, making it only $42.00.  &lt;br /&gt;* Enter your payment information and complete the reservation!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;After You Purchase Your Ticket:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please update your RSVP that you purchased your ticket on the Meetup.com page, so T.J. Maher knows (without bugging David) how many people have purchased a ticket and are definitely going. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Stationary plates of assorted cheeses -- camembert, brie, pepperino, havarti, gorgonzola, feta, cranberry-cinnamon chevre, all natural chevre, and buffalo mozzarella salad tossed with sundried tomatoes and fresh basil. &lt;br /&gt;* Stationary plates of fruits and vegetables&lt;br /&gt;* Shrimp, crab cakes, spring rolls, chicken fingers, potstickets, and beef terriyaki skewers passed out&lt;br /&gt;* Wedding Cake for dessert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dinner is served buffet style so there is no need to select an entrée. We encourage interaction with our actors and the other guests so we provide special plates that allow you to walk around with your meals. There are limited tables for those who need them&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We recommend parking at the 75 State Street Garage as we can give you a $3 off coupon when you board the boat, making parking only $11 for the entire night. Visit &lt;a href="http://75statestreetgarage.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://75statestreetg...&lt;/a&gt; for directions. For information on additional paid parking garages nearby, visit www.northendboston.com/parking-garages.htm. If you are using public transportation, you can ride the Blue or Orange MBTA Lines to nearby Boston Aquarium or State Street&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborcruises.com/Directions.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boat will be docked in front of the Marriott - Long Wharf hotel, near the white Boston Harbor Cruises ticket booth, across the street from Legal Seafoods. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We are typically on the Ft. Independence which is a three deck boat with one deck enclosed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Boarding begins at 7:00pm and the boat will depart at 7:30pm. The cruise is usually over around 10:00pm. The Mystery Cruises run in rain or shine. No tickets are required as you will be on the guest list&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Train&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Take the MBTA Blue Line to Aquarium Station. BHC is located right beside the east end of the station (Follow the exit signs for the Aquarium)&amp;quot; ... Or you could walk from Faneuil Hall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Drive&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;From North&lt;/i&gt;: Take 93 S to exit 24A bearing right on off ramp (Government Center). Follow signs to Aquarium Wharf. BHC is located between the Aquarium and Marriott Hotel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;From South&lt;/i&gt;: Take 93 N to exit 23 (Government Center). Follow signs to Aquarium Wharf. BHC is located between the Aquarium and Marriott Hotel&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277624938000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274901837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Harbor Mystery Cruise "Marriage can be Murder" @ Mystery Cafe</name><id>13604250</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277593200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13604250/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/9/global_15315721.jpeg</photo_url></item>