<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Derby Street Shoppes</address_2><address_1>94 Derby Street, Suite 213</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.180252</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-749-3800</phone><name>Greater Boston Running Company</name><city>Hingham</city><id>973455</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.907761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Get ready for the Couch to 5K with new sneakers!  I know I need a new pair and I can’t wait for this event.   &lt;br /&gt;Our sponsor, The Greater Boston Running Company is hosting a Gait Analysis and Sneaker Shopping Clinic for the SSFMG. Come learn about proper biomechanics, what your individual foot strike is like, and what type of sneakers would best fit your individual needs. Try on sneakers from a variety of brands until you find the perfect fit!  &lt;br /&gt;GBRC is offering 20% off all merchandise purchased at the event (excluding electronics) so a $100 pair of sneakers will only cost $80. In addition, with the purchase of sneakers, I will be passing out at least 5 $10 coupons to be used for a later purchase. &lt;br /&gt;This is one fun event you will not want to miss.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gait Analysis and Sneaker Shopping Clinic  &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, April 13th at 6:30pm  &lt;br /&gt;Greater Boston Running Company  &lt;br /&gt;94 Derby Street Shoppes  &lt;br /&gt;Suite 213  &lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043  &lt;br /&gt;781-749-3800  &lt;br /&gt;www.greaterbostonrunningcompany.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: There is no minimum. The maximum is 30 people. &lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per member &lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Please finalize your RSVP by NOON on Tuesday, April 13th &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;Directions:  &lt;br /&gt;Overview: Located in the Derby Street Shoppes off Route 3 at Exit 15. Greater Boston Running Company is in the row of shoppes near Whole Foods, located to the left of Rustic Kitchen. &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 3 to Exit 15/Derby Street, Hingham. Driving Northbound, take a left at the end of the ramp; Southbound, take a right at the end of the ramp. Take a right at the next light into the Derby Street Shoppes &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4336960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271513118000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268754687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gait Analysis and Sneaker Shopping Clinic</name><id>12891111</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271197800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/12891111/</event_url></item>