<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1741 S Willow St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.953915</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-668-5557</phone><name>Barnes and Noble</name><city>Manchester</city><id>759357</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.436569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our book for October and November is &amp;quot;Unlimiting Mind - The Radically Experiential Psychology of Buddhism&amp;quot; by Andrew Olendzki. This book was published this year by Wisdom Publications in Boston. It has been highly praised by several prominent Buddhist teachers and leaders in the United States. Wisdom Publications describes the book as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Both broad and deep, this eye-opening book is one of the best overviews available of the radical psychological teachings that underlie the Buddhist approach to living a life of freedom and peace. Sophisticated without being daunting, brilliantly clear without becoming simplistic, Andrew Olendzki’s writing is filled with rich phrases, remarkable images, and the fruits of decades of careful thought. Grounded in deep scholarship, psychological sophistication, and many years of teaching and personal practice, this much-anticipated collection of essays will appeal to anyone looking to gain a richer understanding of Buddhism’s experiential tools for exploring the inner world.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ANDREW OLENDZKI, PH.D. was trained in Buddhist Studies at Lancaster University in England, as well as at Harvard and the University of Sri Lanka. The former executive director of IMS (Insight Meditation Society), he is currently the executive director of the Barre Center for Buddhist Studies (BCBS) in Barre, Massachusetts. He is editor of the Insight Journal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the October meeting, we will discuss Chapters 1 through 4. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286893678000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263227236000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Unlimiting Mind" by Andrew Olendzki - Part 1</name><id>12286852</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286838000000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/12286852/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/d/d/global_17932573.jpeg</photo_url></item>