<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Billy Wilder (Some Like it Hot, Witness for the Prosecution, Sabrina, Double Indemnity,Stalag 17) may have been Hollywood's greatest director during its heyday. In 1961 he directed this overlooked comedy :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Wilder's rapid-fire comedy ferociously satirizes the Cold War divide between East and West. Featuring a peerless James Cagney in his last starring role and set in West Berlin, the breathless farce sends up everything from soft drink capitalism to Communist hypocrisy, Soviet disorganization, male lechery, female giddiness, postwar Germany, and American pop culture. With a relentless stream of one-liners and numerous comic set pieces, such as a prisoner tortured with endless plays of Itsy-Bitsy Teeny-Weeny Yellow Polka-Dot Bikini and a mad tabletop striptease that shakes a portrait of Stalin off its perch, Wilder and Cagney never let up the pace for a moment, down to the final Pepsi Cola punchline.&amp;quot;  Quoted from the All-Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, I'll be holding a Meet-Up sign near the front row and then we'll all go to get a coke or a pepsi&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1166400344000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163907851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Billy Wilder's Overlooked Cold-War Satire:One, Two, Three</name><id>5277899</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1166227200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5277899/</event_url></item>