<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Next Tuesday (the 11th), we're going to be starting a new DnD 3.5 campaign, to last at least till the beginning of the Fall semester. All you need to bring is a DnD character of 6th level, which can include rules from the following books:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All 3.5 Core Rulebooks&lt;br /&gt;Players Handbook 2&lt;br /&gt;Dungeon Masters Guide 2&lt;br /&gt;Forgotten Realms Campaign Setting&lt;br /&gt;Magic of Faerun&lt;br /&gt;Silver Marches&lt;br /&gt;Spell Compendium&lt;br /&gt;Eberron Campaign Setting&lt;br /&gt;Sharn: The City of Towers&lt;br /&gt;Complete Warrior&lt;br /&gt;Complete Divine&lt;br /&gt;Complete Arcane&lt;br /&gt;Complete Adventurer&lt;br /&gt;Unearthed Arcana (check with me to see what variants are used)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to play a unique or rare race, make sure to contact me beforehand. Otherwise, only things from the above books can be used. NO EXCEPTIONS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im not going to spoil the campaign itself, but keep in mind its a somewhat traditional published adventure series, so you may have played it before. First, I am changing the events somewhat. Second, as all my games are, it may change during play. Lastly, even if youve played it before, dont spoil it for the others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since its the summer session, the normal $1 fee for non-students is waived.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is normally found in the student lot, to the left of the main building. There is a guest parking area, but it's limited to 30 minutes only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is on the first floor, in room 1128. A map of the campus can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.ccri.edu/floorplans/warwick/01.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ccri.edu/f...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2295622</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1152120129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CCRI Roleplayer's Guild DnD Game- First Campaign Adventure!</name><id>5009075</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1152633600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/5009075/</event_url></item>