<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>320 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.356823</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crowne Plaza</name><city>Newton</city><id>1131770</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.186908</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Glidden is a world renowned Naturopathic physician. If you are sick of prescriptions meds and are looking to focus on nutrition, this is a must see seminar!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;World Renowned – Dr Peter Glidden is coming to Boston, MA!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://snack.to/oXyOcI"&gt;Listen to Healing is easy!&lt;/a&gt; by Dr. Glidden&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHEN:&lt;/strong&gt; Feb 2, 2013 9am – 4pm &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WHERE:&lt;/strong&gt; Crowne Plaza, 320 Washington St., Newton, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specifics:&lt;/strong&gt; Dr Glidden is extremely generous with his time and will stay to answer specific health question. The teachings he follows helped Jenn lose 70 lbs, keep it off and avoid the complications surrounding obesity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/1/4/event_200285652.jpeg" width="215" height="233" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;RSVP: An RSVP is required as seating is limited. You are encouraged to bring friends with you. However, please RSVP with Bernadette Trafton at dette101@gmail.com as soon as possible with subject line – “I would like to RSVP for Dr. Glidden″.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to expect:&lt;/strong&gt; Registration and Networking will begin at 9am. We will do an overview of the business at 9:30 am and Dr. Glidden will begin his revolutionary health lecture afterwards. At the end of the lecture, there will be ample time for you to get your personal health questions answered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Dr. Glidden:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an outspoken advocate of Wholistic Health, Dr. Glidden has lectured to thousands of people over the last 2 decades. He delivers over 60 Free Lectures each year, and is a regular speaker at Health Freedom Expo &amp;amp; Youngevity Regional Meetings. He has appeared on TV, is a regular guest host of the “Dead Doctors Don’t Lie” Health Talk radio program, and gives free weekly seminars all over Chicagoland. His new book, The MD Emperor Has No Clothes, is an eye-opening, groundbreaking, jaw dropping exposition on the shortcomings of conventional MD directed medicine and the unrivaled excellence of Wholistic medical treatments.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359825176000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>54</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359555547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dr. Peter Glidden Feb 2nd</name><id>102128162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359813600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/102128162/</event_url></item>