<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Laurel Marsh Trail (3.52 mile loop): Long, mostly easy walk, many wet areas, a few hills, great marsh views, water birds, mature forest, giant white pines, beautiful mountain laurel, need boots &amp;amp; bug spray. Short stonedust loop -- 0.75 miles within longer loop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow trail to right toward Hockanum River, cross bridge over river, along boardwalk, turn left on trail along marsh near I-84, downstream under three I-84 bridges, cross river on third highway bridge bikeway, under three bridges upstream, leave bikeway and take trail upstream through woods, along I-384 path, then left into woods over two long boardwalks, upstream along view to Hop Brook, up brook path, left across brook on road toward sewer plant, left downstream along Hop Brook, around stonedust loop path either way to starting point. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park at Laurel Marsh lot on south side of Middle Turnpike West (Route 44) just east of I-84, Exit 60, and meet there at 6:30 PM. Watch for Kevin's blue Dodge Grandcaravan Sport. He'll have a red/white Meetup sign on the window of the van for easier spotting. The hike should take about 1.75 hour. No meal is planned after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;)  is leading on this one so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1155564262000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1154530142000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kevin's Laurel Marsh Trail Hike in Manchester CT</name><id>5057063</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1155249000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5057063/</event_url></item>