<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>21 West Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02601</zip><lat>41.647582</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-775-5630</phone><name>Cape Cod Melody Tent</name><city>Hyannis</city><id>922107</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.297545</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I realize this requires playing hookie for many of you, but for those who happen to be off on Tuesday and are looking for a fun afternoon into evening event (heh, and who have not yet committed to the multitude of sweet meetups already scheduled throughout meetup that evening), I present to you, Irishness!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a future posting for the Newport Irish Festival over Labor Day weekend (definitely a must do event!!), but for those who just can't wait, the Sons of Erin in Cape Cod are throwing an Irish Festival at the Cape Cod Melody Tent. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details and ticket information available at:&lt;a href="http://www.capecodiri.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.capecodiri...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are 25$ for the full day including the evening concert, are general admission and can be purchased through ticketmaster and/or via the Melody Tent Site (all linked from the above website and &lt;a href="http://www.melodytent..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.melodytent...&lt;/a&gt;. Can't speak for all the musicians, but I can tell ya the Screaming Orphans alone are worth the trip. Think Dixie Chicks under the influence of some seriously strong irish whiskey :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For any interested, I'm up for carpooling into Hyannis from our side of the bridge, and will shoot to meet folks at the Bourne park and ride between 2-2:15 pm. &lt;a href="http://www.ctps.org/b.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctps.org/b...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Otherwise, as per the norm, will send out my cell number to my yes's and maybe's the night prior. The phone will be on and available for the times surrounding the original meetings (probably 2-3:30ish), so please indicate if you are planning on meeting us later. Will try to keep my ears peeled for any later calls, but certainly with music playing, conversations can be tough :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jointly posted with Social Fun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, hit me up! &lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280262493000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279892946000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Cod Irish Summerfest</name><id>14189900</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280257200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/14189900/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/e/global_9846494.jpeg</photo_url></item>