<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Union Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.361110</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Purple Shamrock</name><city>Boston</city><id>1556553</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056860</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE: I think we are going to head to Harp (near North Station) around 830. &amp;nbsp;I called, and they have dancing and a 10 dollar cover at 9pm. If we leave at 830, we can prolly beat the cover. Plus, the last time I went to Coogans, the music sucked and these frat-guys were acting like they owned the place. Sound good?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's the New Year and it's time to stop being single! Here's how I view dating: Have fun and at a minimum, you're guaranteed to make some new friends :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet at the Purple Shamrock in Faneuil Hall (check this the day-of in case I need to change locations). &amp;nbsp;We'll head to Harp around 830&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is going to be democratic-We go where the group wants and if anyone wants to go dancing someplace else, that's cool too. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Age guidelines:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;This is a single's event so please keep that in mind. I will never turn away anyone, and couples can come, but please don't complain to me if your significant other gets hit on (unless you're a swinger, in which case, I doubt you'll complain). &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is welcome of all races, creeds, orientations and any other category (except pedophiles, we're probably too old for you anyway :) &amp;nbsp;The age guidelines are not rules but are there to make it easier for you in deciding to come or not. So, 20's and 30's is the age category for this. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please get to the Purple Shamrock before we leave. If you try to find us on the dance floor you're going to have a hard time and I don't want to see any single-Bostonians get left out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sure as hell cannot dance (guys: I know I'm not alone with this) so the pre-gaming at the bar should not be skipped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the bar - where else would a drunk be?</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave </member_name><member_id>10064486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326333495000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>71</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322947496000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drink &amp; Dance: 20's and 30's</name><id>43282972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325980800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/43282972/</event_url></item>