<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Longwood Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.336981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Armenise Ampitheatre - Harvard Medical School</name><city>Boston</city><id>725373</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103103</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The &amp;quot;Science in the News&amp;quot; (SITN) seminars have to be the most in-depth and thorough science lectures outside of grad school, and it's a shame I have missed most of them this Fall due to my hectic schedule. Each lecture is divided into three parts with three different grad-student presenters who lay the groundwork on the topic they will discuss, go into more intermediate levels of detail, then spin off into advanced branches of the topic. With the handouts and the ability for attendees to raise their hand &lt;i&gt;at any time&lt;/i&gt; and ask questions, it feels like you are back in grad school. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The topic for Wed, Nov. 18, 2009 at 7pm: &lt;u&gt;The Silence Behind the Sound: How Your Brain Hears&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be sitting on the benches outside just before the main entrance of the Courtyard Cafe (see map at &lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/images/maps/quadmap.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt; ) by 6:15 pm. T.J. is five foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. We can go grab seats at 6:40 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Anybody up for Bertucci's after? It's located at 1 Blackfan Circle in Boston, right around the corner near Children's Hospital on Longwood Avenue. If you care to go, update your RSVP. Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Fall seminars are held in the Armenise Ampitheatre at Harvard Medical School, 200 Longwood Avenue, Boston. The school is located in the Longwood Medical Area of the Fenway neighborhood of Boston. Parking after hours in the vicinity of campus is not usually a problem; there are a number of parking garages along Longwood Avenue. In past years, the least expensive parking options were found in the MASCO parking garage near the Bruegger's Bagels and Temple Israel, about a 10 minute walk from the Medical School along Longwood Avenue. Handicapped and physically disabled parking is available at the medical school directly; please contact us for further assistance&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Map from &amp;quot;E&amp;quot; Longwood Green Line stop: &lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/images/maps/quadmap.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A "Hello My Name is T.J." nametag and a red MEETUP sign on a black messenger bag.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258838054000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257190022000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Silence Behind the Sound: How Your Brain Hears @ Harvard Medical School</name><id>11772750</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258588800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11772750/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/b/global_11609339.jpeg</photo_url></item>