<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>970 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.761542</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-521-8495</phone><name>COSI</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>867623</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.743376</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A friend, who is starting a meetup group, asked me to post this and since what his group is doing may interest some members here I said sure! (
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/InnerCharm/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/InnerCharm/)Discover&lt;/a&gt; how to make our everyday interactions more charismatic by unlocking the inner charms that are within each and every one of us. Find out how to become the people magnet, reconnect with your kids, have clients find more ways to do business with you just because they value your company so much, improve relationships, win friends and become an influential and ethical person. When you come to the event, you'll find that many things we are going to learn and practice will be already familiar, which means that most of us already are sweet and charismatic people, and just need a little practice to learn how to tap in to that charm at the right time and place - be it when you are helping your friend deal with difficult time, motivating your kids to do better at school, or even asking your boss for a raise. Our commonality is a beginner's dedication to learn conversational hypnosis! Because we all bring different experiences to the table, we will all learn from each other (and quite possibly from guest speakers.) To get things started our study group will use Igor Ledochowski's 2007 program 'The Power of Conversational Hypnosis' as a foundation and go from there. Plans are flexible and together other ideas/programs will be introduced to the group - such as for sales, personal change work, persuasion, &amp;amp;/or relationships. This our group so sign up, join together, and lets unlock our inner charisma! Call me 305-423-9524 and I'd be happy to talk to you and look forward to meeting you on Thursday, Aug 4 at 7pm. Andrew&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be at a table in the back of resturant</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joseph W</member_name><member_id>12053798</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312582683000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Smiling Happy Faces</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford</urlname><id>1498492</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Eat, Laugh, and Be Merry in West Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312134494000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Unlocking Your Conversational Charisma Meet &amp; Greet</name><id>27702611</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312498800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford/events/27702611/</event_url></item>