<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Medford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.414890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-646-4849</phone><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While you are encouraged to RSVP here on the Random site to communicate and coordinate with other randomites, you will need to purchase your own tickets from the Regent Theater (information below).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Created 36 years ago, the Banff Mountain Film and Book Festival has become the premier event of its kind in the world. The Festival showcases the world&amp;rsquo;s best films, books, and photographs on mountain subjects &amp;ndash; climbing, culture, environment, wildlife, exploration and adventure, and sport. It also attracts the biggest names in mountaineering, adventure filmmaking, and extreme sports as presenters and speakers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;More than 70 films were screened during the nine-day festival and the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour brings Banff to audiences around the globe. Immediately after the Festival ends, a selection of the best films go on tour across Canada, the United States, and internationally from Scotland to South Africa to China, Japan, New Zealand, Antarctica, and points in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Each year, the films travel to 32 countries reaching more than 245,000 people at over 635 screenings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Host organizations in each tour location choose a program that reflects the interests of their local audiences from a selection of films on exploration and adventure, culture and environment, and mountain sports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The proceeds of many tour screenings benefit a local outdoor program, community cause, or a non-profit such as youth adventure and outdoor pursuit programs, search and rescue operations, climbing clubs, adaptive sport programs, conservation groups, and trail maintenance organizations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;There are three nights of films - different films will play each night. Go to one, two, or all three nights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Monday February 20 @ 7:00 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Tuesday February 21 @ 7:00 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Wednesday February 22 @ 7:00 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Tickets will be on sale soon - click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/details/banff_mountain_film_festival_2012"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for the link to purchase tickets from the Regent Theater. Contact the Regent Theater at (781) 646-4849 if you have any questions or if you want to purchase tickets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.banffcentre.ca/mountainfestival/worldtour/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more information about the film festival itself, including a full listing and movie clips from the films that will be on tour.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329787374000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324524149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Banff Mountain Film Festival 2012 (Monday)</name><id>45197572</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329782400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/45197572/</event_url></item>