<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;These events are being listed to let you know about a great opportunity to join outdoor experts Sheri and Randy Propster as they bring the pages of Backpacker Magazine to life. Use this page to communicate with other randomites who are going.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's Happening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;"Get Out More" is a one-of-a kind mobile tour that brings the pages of Backpacker to life for audiences nationwide. From April to December, Backpacker’s experienced "Get Out More" road team will travel the country to educate consumers about the skills and equipment they need to "Get Out More"!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Check-out the latest in outdoor gear and apparel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Learn essential skills from the experts at Backpacker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Win great outdoor prizes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's the Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Before you go you should contact the local store to make sure the event is going to held as scheduled - they WILL NOT be posting any information to this event listing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Thursday, June 28, 2012 @ 6:30 pm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;REI&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;22 Chapel View Boulevard&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Cranston, RI 02920&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;(401) 275-5250&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Registration required: www.rei.com/cranston&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Tuesday, July 10, 2012 @ 7:00 pm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;REI&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;375 Cochituate Road&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Framingham, MA 01701&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;(508) 270-6325&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Registration required: www.rei.com/framingham&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Wednesday, July 11, 2012 @ 7:00 pm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Eastern Mountain Sports&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;100 Arthur F Brady Drive&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Portsmouth, NH 03801&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;(603) 334-6141&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;www.ems.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Thursday, July 19, 2012 @ 7:00 pm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Eastern Mountain Sports&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;1498 White Mountain Highway&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;North Conway, NH 03860&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;(603) 356-5433&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;www.ems.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet Sheri &amp;amp; Randy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Sheri and Randy Propster embody passion when it comes to getting out more. Randy and Sheri met as college freshman over thirteen years ago and have been working as a team ever since. At the completion of their collegiate athletic careers, the couple focused their passion on the outdoors. In 1999, Randy and Sheri took on the challenge of thru-hiking the Appalachian Trail. The 222 days they spent hiking from Georgia to Maine confirmed their love for each other as well as their passion for the outdoor lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Randy and Sheri’s love for backpacking eventually led them away from the coast and into the Blue Ridge Mountains of Virginia. They lived within walking distance of the Appalachian Trail where they trained for their next long distance adventure. In early March of 2006, the couple embarked on a thru-hike of the American Discovery Trail. Their ocean to ocean adventure led them through thirteen states and the Nation’s Capital as they backpacked for 253 days, enduring everything four seasons of living in the outdoors has to offer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Randy and Sheri have been exposed to a multitude of wonderful adventures thanks to their outdoor centered lives. They take great pride in knowing that their passion to seek out the next adventure will allow them to continue to Get Out More.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;After completing their Appalachian adventure, Randy and Sheri were hired by the Department of Defense as Outdoor Recreation Specialists working out of the Outdoor Adventure Center on the Navy’s Dam Neck Base located in Virginia Beach. This position enabled them to organize and guide a variety of outdoor adventures including: kayaking the beautiful waters of the Chesapeake Bay; rock climbing at the New River Gorge; rafting the Gauley River; spelunking the caves of West Virginia; surfing the waves at Cape Hatteras; and hang gliding the dunes of Kitty Hawk, North Carolina. When they weren’t out in the water or deep in the backcountry, they spent their time facilitating life enhancing confidence and team building techniques to Navy Pilots, government personnel and school and community groups on the Navy’s Rope Course and Climbing Tower.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343713146000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338857215000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Backpacker Magazine's "Get Out More" Tour (REI Framingham)</name><id>67768202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341961200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/67768202/</event_url></item>