<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Event Description: NEW Event: &amp;quot;Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;Who: Combined MeetUp and Single Event &amp;quot;Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; Group.&lt;br /&gt;What: Comedian (see below).  Followed by a nearby Fire-Pit after-party!&lt;br /&gt;When: Wednesday, September 5  - gather @ 6:15 PM.&lt;br /&gt;Where: &amp;quot;FUNNY BONE&amp;quot; Comedy Club (within Manchester's Buckland Hills Mall).&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $13.50, or FREE with promo Tee-shirt (see below) - Must be over 21.&lt;br /&gt;Misc.:  Click the link below to RSVP, see who's attending, and/or for updated details!&lt;br /&gt;Please read all details below and DO NOT hit reply or write directly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I reserved 24 seats together on a ?first RSVP, first served? basis via my FREE &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; MeetUp online calendar reservation system:  &lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/"&gt;http://livemusic.meet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rather than pay the $10-20 admission fee each time, almost everybody purchases a promo Tee-shirt (only $15) to gain admission to this and (almost) all WEDNESDAY performances for FREE by showing your promo Tee-shirt at the Box Office - FOREVER (whether attending as part of our irregularly scheduled group, or not).  Such a deal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After RSVP'ing &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;, simply show up and gather in the &amp;quot;Funny Bone&amp;quot; BAR @ 6:15 (AFTER picking up your FREE ticket from the Box Office by buying and/or showing your promo Tee-shirt - telling the Box Office you have a reservation through &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; group).  This will give us a chance to gather, have a drink, chat, and enter as a &amp;quot;group&amp;quot;, thus allowing us to sit together as their policy is &amp;quot;first come, first seated&amp;quot;.  Look for Rob P. (55, 5'11&amp;quot;, 210#, brown hair, glasses).  When the Club doors open at 6:30, THOSE PRESENT will enter together so we can be assigned good tables together and optionally have appetizers, dinner, drinks (no minimum; separate checks have been pre-approved) and get to know each other while waiting for the show to begin at 7:30 (lasting to @ 9:00).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If entering after 6:30, please ask the ticket taker to assign you a seat with, or nearest to, &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; group, if still available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All (over 21) are welcome to join us!  Invite your friends and encourage them to join the &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; www.TheSingleEvent.com and &amp;quot;MeetUp&amp;quot; www.MeetUp.com to be invited to these, and MANY MORE fun activities of all sorts!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please MapQuest directions to:&lt;br /&gt;194 Buckland Hills Drive, Manchester, CT 06042.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Funny Bone&amp;quot; is located within the Buckland Hills Mall, on the first floor, between JC Penney and Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, via the external &amp;quot;Blue Turtle&amp;quot; entryway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Funny Regards,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI: FOLLOWING THE SHOW: rather than go to a bar, we'll gather around a propane-fueled ceramic &amp;quot;Fire Pit&amp;quot; and listen to some music, dance, chat, gaze at the stars, or just relax with friendly company at a private, nearby outdoor location, just 5 minutes away.  (We have permission from the owner, so no issue with being asked to leave!)  Please bring some snacks, beverage of choice, and a beach chair or blanket for this casual gathering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please visit or call the Box Office (860) 432-8600 for info regarding the FREE &amp;quot;Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; Tee-Shirt promo and/or check their web site:&lt;br /&gt;www.HartfordFunnyBone.com for upcoming shows, general information, bios, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;Phil Palisoul is a rapidly rising, hard working, very funny young comedian, bound for great success. Phil began his comedy career in Denver, and quickly became one of the top acts in the city. Soon he was headlining comedy clubs across the country, and in 1994 he moved to Los Angeles. There he became a regular at the World Famous Hollywood Improv and the legendary Pasadena Ice House, as well as starting a successful career as a television writer. In addition to landing a spot at the prestigious 1999 HBO U.S. Comedy Arts Festival, where he received rave reviews for his performances, Phil has continued to perform his stand-up routine on such shows as, The Tonight Show with Jay Leno, NBC's Friday Night!, Louie Anderson's Comedy Showcase, VH1's Stand-Up Spotlight and Fools For Love, and A&amp;amp;E's Caroline's Comedy Hour. Although Phil is a regular television performer, his first love is still performing for live audiences. Once you've seen Phil's act, the reason for his popularity is obvious: he's hilarious! Building his show with a playful and silly mixture of life experiences, Palisoul has made a name for himself touching on childhood memories (growing up in a typical suburban neighborhood, in a typical suburban family) and married life, which have made him a favorite in television, corporate shows, comedy clubs an colleges.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189203630000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188926198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEW Event: "Wacky Wednesday" &amp; "Fire-Pit" 09/05</name><id>6296021</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189030500000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6296021/</event_url></item>