<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Alright, ladies and gentleman, one of the obstacles of living up in the north shore is that it can be difficult to stay connected with others, particularly when we can't just walk down the street to see one another as if we were living in Boston.  It also can feel overwhelming when we are surrounded by suburbia to feel like there are others like us and who are interested in working on the same projects as we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So it's time to get together and represent!  The new year has started and we should remind ourselves of all the cool people that make up our local community, what our talents are and what we can do to bring ecological vitality to our lives and neighborhoods.  We can show that the North Shore is quite impressive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what I propose we do this afternoon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are a new member, come on over and do a little meet and greet to see your neighbors &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm some projects we could tackle and try to schedule some of our awesome ideas posted into actual meetups &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share information about resources in our area (such as local farms, artisans, time trade circles, trading posts, good businesses we should be shopping at, etc.) so that we can maintain a strong sense of community &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm hosting this at a location at the intersection of Route 1 and Route 95, a convenient location for all points north shore.  I'll provide some light refreshments but please feel free to show off a favorite snack or recipe of yours!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note if you would like to attend this event, but can't make the date, please let me know!  I want to schedule something that will work for the most people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks! :-)  Happy Permaculturing!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296525722000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295032607000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 2011 Northshore Vitality Kickoff!</name><id>16049899</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296327600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/16049899/</event_url></item>