<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;WHERE:&lt;/b&gt;  DCR HATCH SHELL, Boston - on the Charles River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/hatch_events.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PRICE:&lt;/b&gt;  Free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FOOD:&lt;/b&gt;  Bring your own food in a cooler or bag (no cooking or alcohol allowed, sorry), or use the concession stand at the Hatch Shell.  (I will probably get a &amp;quot;snack&amp;quot; from Chinatown after work and take it with me).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEATING:&lt;/b&gt; Bring a beach towel, blanket - if you have a small, &amp;quot;portable&amp;quot; camping chair you like to use, great - bring that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHY FREE?&lt;/b&gt;   Summers in Boston include free concert series on Wednesday evenings at the &amp;quot;Hatch Shell&amp;quot; organized by the Landmarks Festival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.landmarksorchestra.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.landmarkso...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WESTERN CLASSICAL MUSIC?  HOW DOES THAT CONNECT WITH CHINA??&lt;/b&gt;  Well, the concert isn't about Chinese culture, but China, for me, is about the sounds of life - people speaking in musical tones, people making language and food dance, and people drawing magical characters on paper that become even more magical sounds when read.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, bring yourself and guests if you like - meet me near the entrance and we'll grab a spot for the group.  This place fills up with people fast, so try to be on time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Red Line&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to Charles Street/MGH Station - walk the footbridge over Storrow Drive to the Charles River side - west along Storrow Drive - the Hatch Shell is not far.   About 15 minutes walking between the station and the Shell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Green Line&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a bit more time and energy - take to Arlington Street Station - walk along Arlington Street/Public Gardens to Beacon Street - cross over Beacon Street - take Arthur Fiedler foot bridge over Storrow Drive to the Hatch Shell.  About 15-20 minutes walking from the station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=42.361279%2C-71.070493" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADELE'S LINK TO HATCH SHELL IF YOU WANT IT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;a href="http://chinese.meetup.com/35/venue/931749/?eventId=10921320&amp;amp;popup=true"&gt;http://chinese.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*******************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO IS PERFORMING:&lt;/b&gt;    Youth Orchestra of America &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://yoa.org/"&gt;http://yoa.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW DID I CHOOSE THIS PERFORMANCE?&lt;/b&gt;   A LONG time ago, I played cello.  I've enjoyed watching Benjamin Zander do so much work with young performers over the years and this orchestra is a good example.  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.benjaminzander.com/"&gt;http://www.benjaminza...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Also, Dvorak and Bernstein wrote great music here in the U.S. - in fact, Bernstein was born about 20 miles north of Boston in Lawrence, Massachusetts (though he wasn't here long after that!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And then there is &amp;quot;Rachmaninoff's Second Piano Concerto&amp;quot;, one of the more popular and famous of Rach's piano concerti - a lot of people consider this a romantic and &amp;quot;brooding&amp;quot; (great word for any ESL students) piece.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will bring the Mandarin Meetup sign and wait near entrance gate - inside or outside of gate.  Also, will provide contact # to RSVP'ing mambers.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249078883000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247605603000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE CONCERT, Classical Music  - HATCH SHELL , BOSTON</name><id>10876579</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248905700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/10876579/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/6/global_9672102.jpeg</photo_url></item>