<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1228 Riverdale St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.137860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>On The Border Mexican Grill</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>669419</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.625950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Shack (William P Young)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Chosen&lt;i&gt; by Jeanne&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Shack revolves around Mack (Mackenzie) Philips. Four years before this story begins, Mack’s young daughter, Missy, was abducted during a family vacation. Though her body was never found, the police did find evidence in an abandoned shack to prove that she had been brutally murdered by a notorious serial killer who preyed on young girls. As the story begins, Mack, who has been living in the shadow of his Great Sadness, receives a strange note that is apparently from God. God invites Mack to return to this shack for a get together. Though uncertain, Mack visits the scene of the crime and there has a weekend-long encounter with God, or, more properly, with the godhead.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Lemon Tree: An Arab, a Jew, and the Heart of the Middle East&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;i&gt;Chosen by Sarah F&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The title of this moving, well-crafted book refers to a tree in the backyard of a home in Ramla, Israel. The home is currently owned by Dalia, a Jewish woman whose family of Holocaust survivors emigrated from Bulgaria. But before Israel gained its independence in 1948, the house was owned by the Palestinian family of Bashir, who meets Dalia when he returns to see his family home after the Six-Day War of 1967. Journalist Tolan (Me &amp;amp; Hank) traces the history of the Israeli-Palestinian conflict through the parallel personal histories of Dalia and Bashir and their families—all refugees seeking a home. As Tolan takes the story forward, Dalia struggles with her Israeli identity, and Bashir struggles with decades in Israeli prisons for suspected terrorist activities. Those looking for even a symbolic magical solution to that conflict won't find it here: the lemon tree dies in 1998, just as the Israeli-Palestinian peace process stagnates. But as they follow Dalia and Bashir's difficult friendship, readers will experience one of the world's most stubborn conflicts firsthand. 2 maps. (May) &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291233975000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287356997000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November Book Discussion: The Shack &amp; The Lemon Tree</name><id>15140335</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291158000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/15140335/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/f/0/global_19131568.jpeg</photo_url></item>