<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>295 Hale Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.554829</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wylie Inn and Conference Center at Endicott College</name><city>Beverly</city><id>7510522</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.850418</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For the past 2 years I have been working on a masters degree program in meditation through the Institute for Applied Meditation (IAM), a school founded within the Sufi spiritual tradition.  Now Susanna Bair, one of the founders of the school, is coming to Boston to give a workshop.  I have had a wonderful experience in this program and would like to share some of it with you by inviting you to attend this workshop on the beautiful ocean-front campus of Endicott College.  Susanna is a very special teacher and you will have a rich experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In the program announcement below you will notice a second day for a limited number of people.  I am not sponsoring that day, but if you are gung ho and there is still room, feel free to sign up.  The cost for one day is $39 and you will need to register at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.appliedmeditation.org/seminars/oyh/beverly.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.appliedmeditation.org/seminars/oyh/beverly.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.  Then drop me an email at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:drschneider200@comcast.net"&gt;drschneider200@comcast.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; if you would like to join up for dinner afterwards.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The following is from Susanna Bair:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OCCUPY YOUR HEART:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Spiritual Revolution Through Heart and Breath&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The world is going through a catharsis&lt;/strong&gt;, which affects us all. This is a great opportunity for each one of us to transform ourselves, thereby affecting the whole. How do we do that? By occupying our heart. Through four particular spiritual practices we will move into our hearts, exploring relationships, meaning and purpose, and joy and love. By renewing ourselves and occupying our heart fully and completely, we create the spiritual reconstruction of this world…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;a paradigm shift in the relationship between the individual and the universe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;By occupying your Heart, you become stronger and clearer, moving into that inner place that holds your resources and your source of renewal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you take away from this seminar? A four-way spiritual practice that can be done daily in 20 minutes that will affect your whole heart, focusing on:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Your identity and how you understand your individuality,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Your relationships with others,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Your work, career, accomplishments, and the very purpose of your life,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. And bringing spiritual renewal through reconnecting your heart to the Source.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our aim is to heal and integrate all aspects of the self so that we can assist in the spiritual reconstruction of the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This workshop will be led by Susanna Bair, co-founder of IAM Heart and co-author of &lt;em&gt;Follow Your Heart, Living from the Heart&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Energize Your Heart&lt;/em&gt;. Susanna is a European mystic, a master teacher of the Culture of the Heart, and is recognized as a spiritual leader in Universal Sufism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Day 2 takes you deeper into your heart and you will receive an individualized darshan from Susanna. You will experience four additional practices using sound which will help you occupy your heart with a new kind of power. Register now for your opportunity to study closely with this wonderful Sufi master. Only &lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; spots available.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Register at:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.appliedmeditation.org/seminars/oyh/beverly.php"&gt;http://www.appliedmeditation.org/seminars/oyh/beverly.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;or call: (520) 299-2170&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Day 1: $39 for 1 person, $49 for two. June 23rd 9am – 5pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Day 2: $199 per person (day 1 is required). June 24th 9am – 5pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUESTIONS?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Event host: Doug Schneider&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Email: drschneider200@comcast.net&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Melody Bohl</member_name><member_id>11345513</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340486215000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338655980000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Occupy Your Heart' meditation day</name><id>67426842</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>28800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340456400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/67426842/</event_url></item>