<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is open to all Artist. Meets in the SOWA building in the South End (450 Harrison Ave). The fee to participate is strictly voluntary. The purpose is to give students and Artist with limited resources a place to go draw from life. There will always be at least one model but often we have multiple models that take turns on the model stand. There is ample parking on the East side of the building in the parking lot. Entrance from Albany Street. Security requires that the building remain locked after 6pm so you must call to be let into the building. The number to call is 617-266-5140.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; This is not a male only drawing group. &amp;nbsp;Like some groups are focused on drawing the female nude, this group is focused on drawing the male nude. &amp;nbsp;We may include a female model from time to time in addition to the male but there will always be at least one male model for this meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATTENTION MODELS:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;If you would like to participate in a future session of Drawing the Male Nude, please contact me to get into the rotation. &amp;nbsp;We are limiting the models to no more than two participants each week. &amp;nbsp;I am managing a list and would be happy to include you in a future session if you are interested in participating. &amp;nbsp;Just send me an email at ebarron99@gmail.com. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ed</member_name><member_id>7904010</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327942674000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Art Models and Artists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>NE-artists-models-group</urlname><id>408475</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>New England Artists/Models Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327257628000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drawing the Male Nude -  Sunday Evenings in South End</name><id>qsrdlcyqcbmc</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327879800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-artists-models-group/events/49143552/</event_url></item>