<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>For the past three and half years, the Salem Board Games Group has been wonderfully rewarding, filling our calendars with fun and our lives with friends. This great group certainly warrants some year-end celebrating. Prepare to dust off your holiday duds and your good cheer for a Yuletide soiree! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing makes the holidays more festive than spending an evening with good friends and good food. So, let's have a night of it on Saturday, December 18. The party will start at 5:00 and last until the tinsel falls or David falls asleep. Please, bring a dish or appetizer for a buffet; alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages will be provided.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, for those who are feeling extra festive, there will be a Yankee Swap. (The last time the Meetup group did this, everyone really enjoyed it.) Should you please, bring a gender-neutral gift under $10 for an exchange game. There will also be door prizes and surprises throughout the evening, celebrating another great year we have had as a Meetup group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the evening, we'll pass on the board games, but get excited for some party games with prizes and socializing with some people you might not have met at previous Meetups. If this will be your first Meetup with us, prepare to have a great time and meet some fabulous people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a $5 fee for this Meetup.  You can pay it in person in advance of the Meetup, the night of the Meetup, or in advance through Paypal.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* You should know that we are a household with cats (one of whom was recently named the Official Cat of Salem!), but they will be locked up for the evening. The house is also home to a hopefully well-behaved 2 year old, who will obviously not be locked up for the evening, but she will eventually go to bed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it is tight. There is generally more parking available toward Orne St., and more parking is available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*In case of a snow emergency, please make sure to check the website or your e-mail for any updates.  You are always welcome to call the contact number as well.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292852651000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287367084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2010 Yuletide Soiree</name><id>15142087</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292709600000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15142087/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/e/global_18836078.jpeg</photo_url></item>