<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've registered a team for Reach The Beach Mass. on Friday May 17 and Saturday May 18 and am looking for more teammates. We'll have a team of 12 runners in two vans for this relay style event covering approximately 200 miles in two days. Check it out! -&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://ma.rtbrelay.com/home.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://ma.rtbrelay.com/home.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key Facts: &lt;br /&gt;

 -The run is from Princeton, MA (Wachusett Mountain) to Westport, MA (Horseneck Beach State Reservation). &lt;br /&gt;

 -Each runner will run 3 legs in roughly 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 -The milage for each runner ranges from a total of 11 miles to a total of 22.5. (We'll decide which legs everyone will run once we have more team members.) &lt;br /&gt;

 -Registration is $120 per runner, plus we will need money for van rentals, gas, food, etc. Please budget a minimum of $200 for this event. I will be booking vans soon and will know more on the cost then. &lt;br /&gt;

 -Note that this event starts on Friday, and thus you'd need to take the day off of work. &lt;br /&gt;

 -Note that you're not likely to get much sleep during this event, and will likely run one leg during the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal will simply be to finish the race and have a great time. Runners of all speeds are welcome. If you're interested, please sign up here and then I'll discuss further details with you. Please only sign up if you are serious about this event, as we need a dedicated team to cover the cost and miles of the relay. We'll also have a team meeting once our roster fills out. Just let me know if you have questions. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Jason&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason Stokinger</member_name><member_id>34593802</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368926136000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Waltham-Trail-Runners</urlname><id>1479223</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Waltham Trail Runners</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365468072000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reach the Beach, MA (team relay)</name><id>113391762</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>140400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368784800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Waltham-Trail-Runners/events/113391762/</event_url></item>