<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well, we had to cancel November's meetup due to weather, but are people still interested in meeting throughout the winter?  If so, I assume we'd meet with snow on the ground, but not storm weather.  Perhaps I should make this a poll, but I'll just schedule the December Meetup and see what kind of reply I get.  Please try to RSVP as soon as possible, even if it's a maybe.  You can add comments to say under what circumstances you'd be willing to come out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So let's try Leslie's Retreat Park in Salem, MA again.  It isn't as pretty as Salem Willows, but it is fenced in.  :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Park is kind of hard to find.  I think the street it's on is called Commercial Street, but if you click on the Meetup Info/map link above, there are two Commercial Streets (right next to each other) and it shows the location on the wrong one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The other funny thing is, on Google, the regular map looks different than the streets actually are.  So I had the brilliant idea of looking at the satellite map on Google and sure enough... it shows the area &amp;amp; location more accurately.  So I uploaded both maps - one to show the street names and the other so you can see how the roads (and parking area) actually are.  The links below are to the regular map and the satellite view.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://Map showing Leslie's Retreat" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/510192/Dog%20Park%20at%20Leslie%27s%20Retreat.gif"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://Satellite View of Leslie's Retreat" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/510192/Dog%20Park%20at%20Leslie%27s%20Retreat%20Satellite%20View.jpg"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you still have any questions about the location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>790021</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196723543000</updated><rating><average>3.20000004768</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194105846000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Shore Cavalier King Charles Spaniel December Meetup</name><id>6669288</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196524800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/6669288/</event_url></item>