<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Instead of meeting at Borders this week, we have decided to have our workshop in a more intimate, comfy environment--Nora's family apartment, which is located on the MIT campus. We will be meeting on Thursday this week, instead of Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the doors of the MIT Coop bookstore at 6 PM. The MIT Coop is right at the Kendall Square / MIT T stop on the red line and is next to a Marriott hotel. After browsing the bookstore, we will procede as a group to Nora's parents' apartment. (It is somewhat difficult to get to, since it is in a student dorm, so we will be meeting at the bookstore first and then heading over there together.) Call Nora or Zachary if you have any difficulty meeting us or you plan to join us late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The apartment is a cosy, book-lined place, very suitable to workshopping, conversation, and nibbles. My parents have graciously lent me use of the apartment since they are away for the week. Bring poems and drafts, as usual (and, of course good conversation, books and journals, if you have any of interest, and so on). We will be cooking up something simple for dinner, but feel free to bring snacks or drinks to supplement, if you like.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the MIT Coop bookstore at 6. Call Nora (857-221-2140) or Zachary (617-935-4951) if you have difficulty finding us, or if you plan to be meeting us late.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206828231000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206375373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop</name><id>7592106</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206655200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/7592106/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/5/global_187765.jpeg</photo_url></item>