<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to everyone intrigued by neuro-linguistic programming (NLP). Here are the details of the May meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight's topic: Superhero Training (aka Using NLP without calling it NLP)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NLP is amazingly effective, but is sometimes limited by its very name. When people hear NLP, or the full name, Neuro-Linguistic Programming, or even worse, some of our jargon (well-formed outcomes, trans-derivational search, nominalizations, etc) they can go running for the exits. It is very useful to be able to use NLP with calling it NLP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this month's meetup, I will take you through a personal development workshop I created called Superhero Training (see the description at the end of this message), and then we will review the workshop to show how NLP is at the core.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've been wanting to introduce friends, neighbors, family or colleagues to NLP, this would be a good session to bring them to. I've given the Superhero workshop to many audiences, and they unanimously found it both fun and useful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular. I will stay for a while after the meetup, if you want to discuss specific issues that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Workshop: Discovering the Superhero in You&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Superheroes! They save lives, promote justice, right wrongs, and protect the weak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, beyond their obvious powers like great strength, flight and invulnerability there is something&lt;br /&gt;more that defines a superhero - their determination to make the world a better place through the use of their special gifts. This means that any of us, through the exploration of our own special gifts, can&lt;br /&gt;discover the &amp;quot;superhero within&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through a series of exercises, you will choose the superpowers you've dreamed of having, and bring&lt;br /&gt;them into your everyday life. You will gain clarity on your life goals, find the internal motivation needed to achieve those goals, and have a deeper appreciation for the gifts you bring to the world.&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx&lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner&lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP&lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training&lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go straight back to the large studio (after 7pm)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273845697000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270263885000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP May Meetup - Superhero Training!</name><id>dlfdnynhbbc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273792500000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/13073755/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/d/global_4983357.jpeg</photo_url></item>