<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 York St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.311540</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203- 562-5694</phone><name>Toad's Place</name><city>New Haven</city><id>664418</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.929350</lon></venue><fee><label>Cover charge</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per kook or spook</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>EVENT DETAILS HAVE BEEN UPDATED (late Tue. night)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to &lt;a href="http://www.toadsplace.com/home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Toad's&lt;/a&gt; annual Kooks &amp;amp; Spooks costume party!  Drinking, dancing, cool costumes, and a contest!  Those who went last year I'm sure will never forget the 10 ft tall demon, the NBC peacock, or Amil sucking on Sascha (photos &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/photos/?photoAlbumId=108257"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alexis &amp;amp; I will be grabbing a bite around 8-ish so we should get to Toad's around 9-ish.  If anyone can get there earlier and would like to take over as contact/host, please let me know.  The doors open at 8.  Last year the doors opened late, and it was pretty quiet for a while after that before it filled-up and got rocking.  The costume contest will happen once it gets full, they think around 10:30/11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We may try to start by gathering together in the back bar (to the right of the stage).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perhaps we can all hookup by text message?  If you arrive early, at the least, if you text me, I can probably give you the # of an NHCer that is already there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are rumors that there may be free passes to be had downtown.  Keep a lookout, and if you see any, grab a bunch, I know of at least 8 NHCers that said they wanted to do something on Halloween.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alexis &amp;amp; I will be leaving Toad's early (11:30?) because we're going to the funky annual Yale midnight Halloween multi-media extravaganza. I &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/calendar/6642014/?from=list"&gt;posted this&lt;/a&gt; as an Event too (read more about it there).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOST: &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/members/2254163/photos/"&gt;Jason&lt;/a&gt;, cell 203-901-4957.  Since it's a noisy place, you might want to try texting me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POST-PARTY: Nothing says Halloween like going to a diner in costume, and this might even happen.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194048172000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193721154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wed 10/31 - Halloween Hi-jinks at Toad's!</name><id>6641948</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193875200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6641948/</event_url></item>