<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Professors Row &amp; Packard Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.406731</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tufts University</name><city>Medford</city><id>583134</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121915</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As many of you may have read, I sent an email out earlier in the week asking for people's thoughts about having a Meet &amp;amp; Greet along with a little tennis and a little picnic.  Your responses were greatly appreciated.  It seems that Sunday afternoon worked for most of you, so let's aim for that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the bulk of our Meetups take place at the tennis courts at Tufts, I think that's probably the easiest place for everyone to meet.  The field there doesn't offer much else in the way of amenities, but there are lots of courts so that will give us the best opportunity to be able to occupy some of them if people want to hit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now - for the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to meet at 1PM and we can all get to know each other over a picnic lunch.  Please come with any suggestions on how we can all get the most out of this group.  There were some thoughts about then breaking up into groups by skill level - or even spending some time on the courts assessing skill level.  I'd like to hold off on that for a little bit.  It's the first time a lot of us are getting out on the courts in a while so I'd like this to just be fun and informal.  For those of you who already know your skill level, I would like to enlist some of you in helping to assess the rest of the group in the coming weeks.  For tomorrow - let's just keep it light and fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP, you'll be asked what you'd like to bring to the picnic.  I'll collect the answers and if we have too many repeats, I'll let people know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need some food, some drinks, some paper-goods, etc.  This is not required by any means - so don't feel compelled to bring anything but yourself (and maybe a tennis racquet).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's plan to meet up in the park space next to the tennis courts (near the practice wall).  I'll probably bring some &amp;quot;My name is&amp;quot; tags just so we all know who each other are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you all there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW - I set the limit to 100 RSVP's - if there are more that wish to attend, perhaps we'll split it into two days or we'll just be a big group :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be gathering in the park area near the far side of the courts near the practice wall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Kenger</member_name><member_id>4819069</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270302260000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Tennis Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tennis-240</urlname><id>432728</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Somerville Tennis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268961915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring has Sprung - come join the first Meetup of 2010</name><id>12928620</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269190800000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tennis-240/events/12928620/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/2/global_8966354.jpeg</photo_url></item>