<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Batterymarch Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.357452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Battery Park Bar and Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>2350361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054070</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:  Apparently, they've moved the start time of this game BACK to 1:00pm EDT. Sorry for any confusion. Yesterday, both Patriots and NFL websites said it was a 5:00pm start.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==========================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to the wonderful Red Sox Natives Viewing Party at The Scoreboard in Woburn, I'll also be hosting a Viewing Party in Boston's Financial District.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't want to drive to Woburn? Live South Shore or Boston Metro and feel like coming into Boston?  COME ON DOWN to Battery Park, conveniently located in the Financial District in Boston.  Greg, the most excellent manager, will reserve space/tables just for our group. They have plenty o' TVs and will have sound on for the game. I should be there in plenty of time for the 1:00pm kick-off.  The Patriots and Ram are playing at Wembley Stadium in the UK!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Battery Park has great selection of beer and the food is great! (I recommend the Shepard's Pie!)  BP is a short walk from Downtown Crossing (Red and Orange Lines), Gov't Center (Green and Blue Lines), and Aquarium (Blue Line).  Everyone is responsible for their own food and drink. PLEASE MAINTAIN A SEPARATE TAB OR PAY AS YOU GO.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture, or just ask the bartender who I am.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351492447000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349959428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patriots Viewing Party at Battery Park - Patriots/Rams in the UK</name><id>86510232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351441800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/86510232/</event_url></item>