<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Actual address is 550 but wrong on Google</address_2><address_1>550 Peverly Hill Rd.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.049259</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 431-2334</phone><name>Seacoast Family YMCA</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>874846</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.778389</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Cheri Perry &amp;amp; Turner Wilson have offered the opportunity to teach anyone who wants to learn Greenlandic, rolling, bracing or sculling skills at the Portsmouth YMCA this coming Saturday. See the information below then RSVP for this event if you'd like to attend as well as contact Cheri &amp;amp; Turner to reserve a spot if you'd like instruction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheri Perry &amp;amp; Turner Wilson of Kayak Ways LLC,  &lt;a href="http://www.kayakways.net" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.kayakways.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will be at the pool session this Saturday, Feb 13th from 3-6.&lt;br /&gt;Come and practice your skills or take instruction on all skills Greenlandic, rolling, bracing or sculling. We also teach rolling to folks who use other blades.:)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Practice:&lt;/b&gt; $25 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Instruction:&lt;/b&gt; - Kayak Ways LLC will offer instruction, one-hour slots, 2 to 1 maximum ratio, use of a low-volume rolling kayak, Greenland paddle and norsaq, and a tuiliq for the hour, or your own kayak and equipment, plus the additional pool time that day for $80.&lt;br /&gt;Time slots are 3pm, 4pm or 5pm for hour long lessons. You may, of course, sign up for a two hour slot if you are game!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in the instruction option, please email Cheri &amp;amp; Turner to reserve your spot, (give us your available time options). Email us at &lt;a href="mailto:info@kayakways.net" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;info@kayakways.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Please also let us know if you plan on coming just to practice, so we can get an approximate head count.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please, do not forget, bring clean kayaks to the pool!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We welcome any and all observers. If you are learning to roll, or learning to teach, and just want to watch to pick up pointers, please feel free to observe. The atmosphere will be fun and social!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;Cheri &amp;amp; Turner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=shmB005wJQI" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Click here to view Cheri's Video Clip from This is The Sea 3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266269284000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265758902000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opportunity to learn to Eskimo Roll Greenland Style with Cheri &amp; Turner</name><id>12565069</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266091200000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/12565069/</event_url></item>