<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 4</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05751</zip><lat>43.641800</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Shelburne Pass Trail Parking Lot on Rt 4 (Killington North)</name><city>Killington</city><id>4360072</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.768669</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;*** IMPORTANT*************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read entire event description before you sign up.&amp;nbsp; When you sign up, you'll be asked several questions.&amp;nbsp; Answering to my questions is NOT an option during your RSVP process on my hiking event.&amp;nbsp; If you omit it, you'll be eventually moved out from "On-Going" list by the event organizer.&amp;nbsp; But you'll receive reminder to answer to the questions through e-mail before you'll be removed from participation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Meetup location &amp;amp; Time:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We need car spotting. (= we need at least 2 cars).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We meet at Sherburne Pass Trail Parking Lot on Rt 4 at 8AM.&amp;nbsp; This parking lot is located approx. 1.4 miles West on Rt 4 from Junction between Rt 4 and Rt 100 in Killington, VT.&amp;nbsp; We'll leave some cars there for car spotting, then, we drive the rest of cars to the parking lot of Bucklin Trail on Wheelerville Road to start hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Hiking Route &amp;amp; Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm planning to hike Killington Peak, Pico Peak and Mendon Peak Southern&amp;nbsp;VT section of Long Trail and others.&amp;nbsp; All 3 peaks are listed in NEHH (New England 100 Highest).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike includes &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;bushwhacking&lt;/span&gt; because Mendon Peak is trail-less peak and elevation of each peak is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;Mendon Peak&amp;nbsp;(3840 ft)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Killington Peak&amp;nbsp;(4235 ft)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Pico Peak (3957 ft)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start hiking old logging road near Bucklin Trail to aim Mendon Peak. Bushwhacking on steep hill eventually starts.&amp;nbsp; After reaching Mendon Peak, we bushwhack toward East, we may or may not try to reach Little Killington (3939 ft) on the way to get to Long Trail. Total bushwhacking mileage will be 3.3 to 3.7 miles. Once we reach to Long Trail, next&amp;nbsp;mountain we visit&amp;nbsp;is Killington Peak (4235 ft) which is one of 5 4K footers in VT.&amp;nbsp; After eating snack or lunch, we go on Long Trail North, then take Shelburne Pass Trail to reach to Pico Peak (3957 ft). After then, the rest of the hike will be&amp;nbsp;3.1 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The total hiking distance is approximately 11 miles or so.&amp;nbsp; I'll hike with slow to moderate pace (1.5-2 mph pace) but will spend enough time to take a break or take some pix on the way to the multiple summits.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This is my usual hike as I take a lot of pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Rules to follow:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please don't bring your friends who are NOT the member of this meetup group as I need to make sure liability as well as hikers capability who are going to join my hike in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Weather Check Point:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather check point will be done on Nov 11th (Fri), 7PM.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Note:&amp;nbsp; At the higher elevation, temp might be colder than you assume.&amp;nbsp; Please don't underestimate the cold weather in higher elevation and make sure to bring appropriate gear such as waterproof/windproof jacket (in case of rain) etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please bring enough water, snack and lunch.&amp;nbsp; Bring First Aid Kit for your use.&amp;nbsp; I carry gear for myself, not for everyone's use.&amp;nbsp; Needless to say, please bring your headlamp, although I'd like to come back to the parking lot before getting dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions (what to bring, what kinds of cloths you wear etc.), please feel free to drop me an email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assistant Organizer &amp;amp; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hiking-490/"&gt;HSV Organizer&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomoko&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My Car is Honda CR-V(Blue, VT plate)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321353637000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320844725000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike/Bushwhacking at 3 NEHH Peaks (Killington, Pico and Mendon Peak) in VT!</name><id>40536012</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321189200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/40536012/</event_url></item>