<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>JOIN US FOR NIGHT OF FUN!&lt;br /&gt;Boston Karaoke is the best place for you to practice and perform in front of a friendly audience.  Most of us are amateurs who simply enjoy singing Karaoke and watching others sing their favorite songs.  If you are a little shy, that's ok, there is no pressure and you can just relax and enjoy the company of new friends.  Please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; for a fun night, you don't have to sing like an American Idol!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: LIMELIGHT BOSTON&lt;br /&gt;The Limelight is the premier Karaoke venue in Boston with excellent song selection, flexible lighting controls and very friendly staff.  It's located in the Theatre district in Boston just minutes from public transportation.  If you are coming by car there is plenty of parking available.  Don't miss out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP NOW!&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to bring a friend or two, they are most welcome!  Just include the number of friends you plan to bring in your RSVP.  RSVP right now, if your plans change later, you can simply update your choice.  If you are not sure, then RSVP &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot;.  In any case, I hope you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Members who RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot;by August 4th, the $5.00 Fee will be waived.  RSVP NOW!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Phil&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***IMPORTANT CLARIFICATION***&lt;br /&gt;I've had some questions about the cost of coming to the August Boston Karaoke Meetup and if you RSVP right here before August 4th, then it will be free for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do not RSVP, you are still welcome, but the cost is $5.00 per person.  So RSVP now, you have nothing to lose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So far, we have almost 20 people who might be there.  Please sign up now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.limelightboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.limelightboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.limelightb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip L</member_name><member_id>1522860</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159922590000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonkaraoke</urlname><id>212993</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Karaoke Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1153565484000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Karaoke August Meetup!</name><id>5036464</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1154820600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonkaraoke/events/5036464/</event_url></item>