<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I will be at the theater between 6:45 and 7, ( I will be seeing another movie just prior to our meetup) we should go in for seats at 7:10, movie time is 7:35.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is playing upstairs, so I will try to snag a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If you get there before me, grab a table for the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you miss the group, come look for us after the movie.   The group will gather outside the room where the movie has just been shown, to discuss the film, allow for restroom breaks and get a head count of all who are interested in heading to the Rockbottom for munchies, beverages and lively conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My picture is on the website, check it out so you can recognize me.  I will be wearing a meetup pin and will also have a meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Times:&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: December 22, 2010 (3D/2D theaters) &lt;br /&gt;Studio: 20th Century Fox &lt;br /&gt;Director: Rob Letterman &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Nicholas Stoller, Joe Stillman &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Jack Black, Emily Blunt, Jason Segel, Amanda Peet, Billy Connolly, James Gorden, Catherine Tate, Chris O'Dowd &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Action, Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: In a contemporary re–imagining of the classic tale, Jack Black stars as Gulliver, a big–talking mailroom clerk who, after he's mistakenly assigned a travel piece on the Bermuda Triangle, suddenly finds himself a giant among men when he washes ashore on the hidden island of Lilliput, home to a population of very tiny people. At first enslaved by the diminutive and industrious Liliputians, and later declared their hero, Gulliver comes to learn that it’s how big you are on the inside that counts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If movie is upstairs, I will be at a table near the windows at the top of the escalator.  If movie is downstairs I will be by the ropes near the concession stand.  I will be wearing a meetup pin and have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294086082000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288625897000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gulliver's Travels</name><id>15296300</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293752700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/15296300/</event_url></item>