<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;** Due to the advanced and strenuous nature of this event it is not suitable for beginners **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Prior experience with above timberline travel during winter conditions is required **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** All hikers will be prescreened **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** You must contact the organizer of this event in order to RSVP **&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us on a winter ascent of Mt. Madison !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We begin our day at the Appalachia trailhead &amp;amp; parking area. We will ascend via the Valley Way to the Madison Hut. At the Madison hut we will take a short break and prepare for our summit push. From here we ascend Mt. Madison via the Osgood Trail where amazing 360 degree views wait for us on the summit!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will descend back to our cars via the Valley Way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 8.05 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time: 8 hr&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain: +4213 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** IMPORTANT NOTES *****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers will be prescreened.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please add your name to the waiting list and you will be contacted by the organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is categorized as STRENUOUS and is not for beginners. You must have prior above tree line experience in winter conditions to join this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive early and be prepared to start up the mountain promptly at 8 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will assess weather, time, trail conditions and the physical condition of the group during our climb. Changes can &amp;amp; will be made as necessary. Standing on the summit is optional, returning to the trailhead safely is mandatory. Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Being prepared, traveling with the appropriate gear &amp;amp; knowing how to use it is your personal responsibility.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;By joining this event you certify that you have read and agree to the terms of the NEHAG &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/Disclaimer"&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like this guy ---&gt;</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Milton</member_name><member_id>4294409</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233061636000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231160002000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Madison - Peter's 48th !!</name><id>9447838</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232888400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9447838/</event_url></item>