<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Every 2nd Saturday of each month at 11 A.M. in  their  ongoing Elements of Cinema series, The Brattle screen an important film with a guest speaker. Usually our group does not host these as group events.      &lt;b&gt;Black Girl&lt;/b&gt; , the first feature film by Ousmane Sembene ( Moolaadé, Ceddo) is an exception as it is so rarely shown in the USA.  This 1965 film has a running time of 65 minutes while the guest speaker is to be announced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ousmane Sembène, a pioneer of African cinema, first gained international attention with this story of the legacy of colonialism, adapted from the true incident of an African maid's suicide in France. An illiterate in a strange country, Diouanna is at the mercy of her white French employers; while Diouanna's refusal to speak makes her even more inscrutable to her boss, Sembène lends insight into her hopeless situation through her interior monologues and flashbacks to Senegal. Despite technical limitations, Sembène's location shooting pointedly, and poignantly, contrasts the flow of life in Dakar with Diouanna's claustrophobic existence in the French apartment, literalizing her entrapment. Black Girl's worldwide acclaim rendered it the first major work of African cinema, and it established Sembène as the foremost filmmaker in sub-Saharan Africa. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Senegalese woman is eager to find a better life abroad. She takes a job as a governess for a French family, but finds her duties reduced to those of a maid after the family moves from Dakar to the south of France. In her new country, the woman is constantly made aware of her race and mistreated by her employers. Her hope for better times turns to disillusionment and she falls into isolation and despair. The feature film debut of the leader of the New Wave (or first wave) of African cinema, Ousmane Sembene who, sadly, passed away last year. Brattle Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, each of The Elements of Cinema films at The Brattle are free. I mention this fact at the end of the posting , cause gee (!) I really hope this isn't the reason you RSVP Yes and with that in mind, since it is free please consider becoming a Brattle Member or at the least, visit their concession stand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film and the Q&amp;A session Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local eatery to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208185810000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207010325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ousmane Sembene's Black Girl</name><id>7644241</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208012400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7644241/</event_url></item>