<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>60.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;******THERE IS A WAITING LIST. If you wanted to sign up, but didn't, please RSVP anyway. Some people who RSVP'd already may back out. Also, priority will be given to those who have attended Meetups in the past year. Thanks!******&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Announcing a special Boston ASL Meetup event, for people levels ASL 3 and above: an ASL Immersion Weekend led by Deaf ASL teacher, Rob Nielson (WestwoodASL.com).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9AM-6PM on Saturday, July 16th and Sunday, July 17th, Rob will lead a group of up to 10 of us in a combination of classroom-style instruction and experiential learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although this Meetup is "located" at Starbucks in Davis Square, that's actually just the meeting point. We will be traveling all over Boston by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will explore Boston like we're tourists, and also receive instruction on topics suited to our strengths and weaknesses, possibly including the following, but tailored to group interests and needs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) ASL grammar--how does ASL grammar differ from English grammar? Rob will explain and help us learn the importance of facial grammar.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) Descriptive classifiers--building on what participants already know, Rob will help us use this "ASL paintbrush" to describe the world, precisely.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) Storytelling/role shifting--Rob will help us break out of our linear storytelling habits and show us how to tell stories the Deaf way.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike our regular Meetups, this program costs $60 for the weekend (or $30 per day). This fee is for the instruction. Meals and transportation costs (subway fare, bus fare) are NOT included. You may attend just one day, but it is recommended to attend both days to get the maximum educational benefit out of the experience. Payment is by cash or check, either to myself or to Rob Nielson, on the day(s) you attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING: Saturday, park at the Alewife T stop (all day, flat rate, $8:00), one stop from DAVIS SQUARE, which is the T-Stop closest to our Starbucks meeting place. Sunday, you can park in Davis Square if you want: parking is free on Sunday&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for people signing!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erika Wentworth</member_name><member_id>487803</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311005318000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>ASL Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonasl</urlname><id>1298565</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston ASL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309383584000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ASL Immersion Weekend</name><id>24013061</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310821200000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonasl/events/24013061/</event_url></item>