<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Okay... for $19 you'd think they'd make this website more user friendly.  (Decide to make one change, and you lose ALL your info.  Who runs this thing... a union?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be the first Boston Ayn Rand meetup in some time.  My goal is for all of us Objectivism fans to meet one another, discuss what drew us to Ayn Rand and how her philosophy has impacted us, and determine how this group should be.  I am open to anyone's thoughts of what it should entail, what its goal/objective is, etc.  Just bring your thoughts and ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For now, as you'll notice on this posting, I have selected Starbucks at 443 Boylston in Boston (at the corner of Berkeley St.)  It's close to the T's Green line (Arlington Station).  I am fully aware of the difficulty that parking brings, so I am open to suggestions for the next meet up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My plan, assuming Starbucks hasn't undergone some major renovation of which I am unaware, is to be on the downstairs level - latte in one hand, &amp;quot;Capitalism: the Unknown Ideal&amp;quot; in the other.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at 5PM on Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have to pay meetup.com $19.00 per month to use their site, so if I could recoup any of that, it would be great.  We can also discuss this aspect of the meetups as well.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>2499401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273539931000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1128737881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Ayn Rand November Meetup</name><id>4778661</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1131314400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/4778661/</event_url></item>