<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our group is always great support for understanding your dreams and their symbols, so if you're ever stuck for what a dream means or would just love to share the wonder of a memorable dream with more people who value the real night life (ha ha yes!) then please feel welcome to come to a meeting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This month in addition to the usual open dream sharing, we will look at the kinds of creative inspiration that can come from our dreams.  Have you ever awakened with an image to draw, a melody to sing, a poem to write, a movement to dance, or a ritual to perform?  Artists have long been motivated by their dreams, with one famous example being the Beatles melody for "Yesterday", which Paul McCartney composed entirely in a dream one night.  He ran to the piano when he woke up before he could forget it, and then thought it sounded so great he must have subconsciously picked it up from elsewhere.  When everyone assured him it sounded original, he started writing lyrics to fit, the first version being not "&lt;span&gt;Yesterday, all my troubles seemed so far away" but rather in true&lt;/span&gt; dream-like style &lt;span&gt;"Scrambled Eggs, Oh my baby how I love your legs!"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we'd love to hear about what gifts of creative inspiration you've received in your dreams. What's more, if you find yourself wanting to share beyond the group, the Mystical Art and Talent Show is coming on Saturday October 13 at the Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel as well!  See details online at &lt;a href="http://www.soulstirring.org"&gt;SoulStirring.org&lt;/a&gt; for this wonderful annual event that we've been running since 2001.  Members of the dream group have shown art or performed based on their dreams there, so let Carl know if you're interested in presenting.  Or just tell your friends and consider attending because it's a unique inspirational entertainment experience that you won't want to miss!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At any rate, for this 3rd Tuesday dream group for September Carl will be leading, who also leads the 4th Tuesday &lt;a href="http://www.cosmicdocent.com/"&gt;Cosmic discussions group&lt;/a&gt; in the same location. Payment is $10 to help rent the space and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/members/1741395/"&gt;contact Carl&lt;/a&gt; before attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 There is a small parking lot, and enter on the left side of the chapel. For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350175977000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347246199000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dreams and the Creative Inspiration</name><id>81665442</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348009200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/81665442/</event_url></item>