<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 68</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01331</zip><lat>42.575361</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jacob's Hill and Spirit Falls</name><city>Royalston</city><id>985974</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.131063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Jacob's Hill &amp;amp; Spirit Falls is a moderate hike with some strenuous areas along the falls. Please wear appropriate foot wear. It is slippery in some areas. The falls are beautiful after all this rainfall. There are connecting trails throughout the area. Please be prepared with food and water. We may be out there for 3-4 hours. I'd love to be out there even longer. It is gorgeous!&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt; Please RSVP by 9 am the day of the event. We do wait for 15-20 minutes if we have people whom have RSVPd &amp;quot;yes that are not there yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Activities Prohibited&lt;br /&gt;* Mountain biking&lt;br /&gt;* Available Information&lt;br /&gt;* Brochure&lt;br /&gt;* Online&lt;br /&gt;* Paper map&lt;br /&gt;* Facilities&lt;br /&gt;* None&lt;br /&gt;* Fees&lt;br /&gt;* No fee&lt;br /&gt;* Land Owner&lt;br /&gt;* The Trustees of Reservations&lt;br /&gt;* Parking&lt;br /&gt;* 8 cars&lt;br /&gt;* Yes&lt;br /&gt;* Pets&lt;br /&gt;* Pets OK&lt;br /&gt;* Recreation Activities&lt;br /&gt;* Fishing&lt;br /&gt;* Hiking&lt;br /&gt;* Hunting&lt;br /&gt;* x-country Skiing&lt;br /&gt;* Season&lt;br /&gt;* All Seasons&lt;br /&gt;* Signage&lt;br /&gt;* Trailhead sign&lt;br /&gt;* Trails marked&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warwick Rd., Rte. 68, Royalston, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dramatic waterfall and ridgeline vista.&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jacobs Hill is one of the gems of the Tully Trail, affording magnificent views of the Tully River and Long Pond, as well as of Tully Mountain, Mt. Grace, and the Berkshire Hills to the west. By following the rectangular yellow blazes of the Tully Trail one way and round yellow blazes the other, visitors complete a 2-mile loop that passes a lovely swamp along the Tully River. Halfway along is Spirit Falls, where a stream splashes dramatically down a steeply angled slope to Long Pond. (A trail down the slope at this point is strenuous.) The source of Spirit Falls is Little Pond, a classic bog of open water ringed by sphagnum moss and then by spruce and tamarack; the bog is visible from a pull-off a short way south on Rte. 68.&lt;br /&gt;We can also check out other local trails since Doane's Falls and Royalston Falls are in the same area. We'll get plenty of hiking in.smile&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Royalston center, follow Rte. 68 north 0.5 miles to parking and entrance on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By RSVPing &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group members and their guests and the Western Mass Singles Group members and their guests attending any of our meet-up events agree to release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, and/or death, including those caused by negligence and or other reasons. You also agree to assume all risk associated with each meetup you attend and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for any event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group and the Western Mass Singles Group for and related to any event which I attend. I attest and verify that I (and any guest(s) I bring are) am physically fit to participate in any portion of each event I attend. I grant Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of all events for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a Maroon Chevy Monte Carlo</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253483781000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Western Mass Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>western-mass-singles</urlname><id>414498</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>The Western Mass Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247487249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jacob's Hill &amp; Spirit Falls</name><id>10863812</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248015600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/western-mass-singles/events/10863812/</event_url></item>