<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I did a checkout paddle Monday (4/19) and the currents get quite high on the river. It is definitely not for boats shorter than 12' because they are too slow to go against the currents. There are also several quick water parts requiring exact boat control to steer around downed trees and rocks in high currents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet at 10:00&lt;br /&gt;Launching at 10:30am.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip organizer: Mark Roberts 401-533-1883 cell or email:  hrmmark@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A wetsuit or drysuit is absolutely required to paddle with us during the off season.&lt;/b&gt; Changes and cancellations to trips will be posted here and on the RICKA flatwater message board by 8 AM the day of the paddle. Please check the board before leaving for any trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suitable for experienced paddlers with good boat control, Boats should be at least 12', bring a lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope Landing Access. Rt. 116 to Hope Furnace Road, access to upper Pawtuxet River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may paddle up to the Scituate Reservoir and back again. The water is very clean, coming directly from the reservoir.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from the North, travel on Route 116 South into the village of Hope, in the town of Scituate. Just past the junction of Rt. 115, look for the bridge crossing the river. Turn right onto Hope Furnace Road. The access to Hope landing is down a short gravel drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from the South travel on Route 116 North into the village of Hope, in the town of Scituate. The access, Hope Landing, will be on your left just after entering Scituate, before the bridge crossing the river. Drive down a short gravel drive onto Hope Furnace Road.  GPS Coordinates: N41 43.868  W071 33.930&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATION:&lt;/b&gt; Will be posed by 8:00 AM day of paddle to&lt;br /&gt;RICKA Message Board: &lt;a href="http://members.boardh.." target="_blank"&gt;http://members.boardh...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;FaceBook: www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=10150121077980596&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our leaders provide directions as a courtesy to paddlers however, you are responsible to refer to a map and familiarize yourself with the trip location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272290719000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269022941000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Upper Pawtuxet River - Scituate, RI  </name><id>12934084</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272117600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/12934084/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/0/global_6975552.jpeg</photo_url></item>