<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Hazard Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06082</zip><lat>41.989895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hazard Grille</name><city>Enfield</city><id>950610</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.579881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Pirate Latitudes-Michael Crichton&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;From one of the best-loved authors of all time comes an irresistible adventure of swashbuckling pirates in the New World, a classic story of treasure and betrayal.  &lt;br /&gt;The Caribbean, 1665. A remote colony of the English Crown, the island of Jamaica holds out against the vast supremacy of the Spanish empire. Port Royal, its capital, is a cutthroat town of taverns, grog shops, and bawdy houses.  &lt;br /&gt;In this steamy climate there's a living to be made, a living that can end swiftly by disease—or by dagger. For Captain Charles Hunter, gold in Spanish hands is gold for the taking, and the law of the land rests with those ruthless enough to make it.  &lt;br /&gt;Word in port is that the galleon El Trinidad, fresh from New Spain, is awaiting repairs in a nearby harbor. Heavily fortified, the impregnable harbor is guarded by the bloodthirsty Cazalla, a favorite commander of the Spanish king himself. With backing from a powerful ally, Hunter assembles a crew of ruffians to infiltrate the enemy outpost and commandeer El Trinidad, along with its fortune in Spanish gold. The raid is as perilous as the bloodiest tales of island legend, and Hunter will lose more than one man before he even sets foot on foreign shores, where dense jungle and the firepower of Spanish infantry stand between him and the treasure....  &lt;br /&gt;Pirate Latitudes is Michael Crichton at his best: a rollicking adventure tale pulsing with relentless action, crackling atmosphere, and heart-pounding suspense. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Still Alice-Lisa Genova&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Still Alice is a compelling debut novel about a 50-year-old woman's sudden descent into early onset Alzheimer's disease, written by first-time author Lisa Genova, who holds a Ph. D in neuroscience from Harvard University.  &lt;br /&gt;Alice Howland, happily married with three grown children and a house on the Cape, is a celebrated Harvard professor at the height of her career when she notices a forgetfulness creeping into her life. As confusion starts to cloud her thinking and her memory begins to fail her, she receives a devastating diagnosis: early onset Alzheimer's disease. Fiercely independent, Alice struggles to maintain her lifestyle and live in the moment, even as her sense of self is being stripped away. In turns heartbreaking, inspiring and terrifying, Still Alice captures in remarkable detail what's it's like to literally lose your mind... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shawna</member_name><member_id>10937608</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294594895000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287357070000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December's Book Discussion: Pirate Latitudes &amp; Still Alice</name><id>15140345</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293577200000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/15140345/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/5/global_19992933.jpeg</photo_url></item>