<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Granite St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.355717</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lindstrom Field</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433265</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111530</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Do you feel like sometimes running can be a chore? Do you get tired doing the same old routine? Then this is the meetup for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ultimate Frisbee is a sport that not only can help improve your stamina, but strength and speed as well. Plus its fun to compete while getting in shape. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lindstrom Field @ 9:30 PM (40 Granite St. Cambridge MA 02139)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Map&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;q=40+granite+street+cambridge+ma&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;split=0&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;ei=xAeMSr3DOpDDlAe4lci6CA&amp;amp;z=16" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Rules&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   1. The Field -- A rectangular shape with endzones at each end. A regulation field is 70 yards by 40 yards, with endzones 25 yards deep.&lt;br /&gt;   2. Initiate Play -- Each point begins with both teams lining up on the front of their respective endzone line. The defense throws (&amp;quot;pulls&amp;quot;) the disc to the offense. A regulation game has seven players per team.&lt;br /&gt;   3. Scoring -- Each time the offense completes a pass in the defense's endzone, the offense scores a point. Play is initiated after each score.&lt;br /&gt;   4. Movement of the Disc -- The disc may be advanced in any direction by completing a pass to a teammate. Players may not run with the disc. The person with the disc (&amp;quot;thrower&amp;quot;) has ten seconds to throw the disc. The defender guarding the thrower (&amp;quot;marker&amp;quot;) counts out the stall count.&lt;br /&gt;   5. Change of possession -- When a pass in not completed (e.g. out of bounds, drop, block, interception), the defense immediately takes possession of the disc and becomes the offense.&lt;br /&gt;   6. Substitutions -- Players not in the game may replace players in the game after a score and during an injury timeout.&lt;br /&gt;   7. Non-contact -- No physical contact is allowed between players. Picks and screens are also prohibited. A foul occurs when contact is made.&lt;br /&gt;   8. Fouls -- When a player initiates contact on another player a foul occurs. When a foul disrupts possession, the play resumes as if the possession was retained. If the player committing the foul disagrees with the foul call, the play is redone.&lt;br /&gt;   9. Self-Refereeing -- Players are responsible for their own foul and line calls. Players resolve their own disputes.&lt;br /&gt;  10. Spirit of the Game -- Ultimate stresses sportsmanship and fair play. Competitive play is encouraged, but never at the expense of respect between players, adherence to the rules, and the basic joy of play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Expect&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Bring light colored clothing&lt;br /&gt;*Ultimate involves a lot of back and forth running, similar to soccer&lt;br /&gt;*I will provide two different colored glow sticks to differentiate team members&lt;br /&gt;*The Frisbee itself lights up to make it fun and easy to catch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be the best run ever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ill be the one in the shirt.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy - ti.mer.see - Marx </member_name><member_id>6766032</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251595979000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251220114000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TMIRCE LATE NITE ULTIMATE FRISBEE</name><id>11196686</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251423000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/11196686/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/4/global_2413972.jpeg</photo_url></item>