<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Cummings Center, Suite 435-K</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.558906</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 864-7076</phone><name>Eternal Balance</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1226709</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887042</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;em&gt;With &lt;a href="http://workshopsforabetterlife.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Dunja Carlson-Moeller&lt;/a&gt; Ph.D.&lt;/em&gt; &amp;nbsp; This is a two hour Art of Natural Breathing class where you will learn the foundation of breathing in a circular and open manner. Learning to take in deep inhales and relaxing on the exhale mirrors how we receive and let go of anything in our lives. Aside from bringing lots of oxygen to our circulatory system and our internal organs, which has incredible healing potential, prana energy also travels on the breath. &amp;nbsp; Our soul and life force respond immediately to conscious breathing and reward us in connecting us to our essence and purpose. &amp;nbsp; Especially during times of transition, personal or seasonal, our breathing tends to get sluggish. Breathing in a group setting increases the life force energy and reconnects you to a more authentic expression of your life. 
&lt;p&gt;Come find out that breathing is the essence of joy, bliss and laughter and one of the best forms of healing!!&lt;/p&gt;
Dunja Carlson-Moeller Ph.D. has done extensive research and clinical training in medical anthropology. She wrote "Gentle Medicine", a book on anthroposophical medicine. She has worked at the Center for Psychology and Social Change at Harvard Medical School, where she chaired an academic and interdisciplinary forum addressing healing and social change. Her expertise lies in an integral approach, bridging the world of western medicine and alternative health. She is both a Body Memories and The Art of Natural Breathing Master Practitioner and teacher, is certified in Postural Integration (deep tissue structural bodywork), and graduated from the Lynn Andrews Center for Sacred Arts and Training. Her private practice is located in Billerica, Massachusetts. Breathing fully and sharing it with the world has become a way of life for Dunja. &amp;nbsp; Class is limited to 10 people. &amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;When:&lt;/strong&gt; Friday, September 23, 7:00 - 9:00pm &lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;$40</description><how_to_find_us>Please check Directions page at www.eternal-balance.com if you have not been to the studio before.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olga </member_name><member_id>10158912</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316823230000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members with unlimited potential</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club</urlname><id>1467921</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Holistic Lifestyle  Women's Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316545034000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art of Natural Breathing</name><id>34297382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316818800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club/events/34297382/</event_url></item>