<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In this busy world we need to have basic things that we just do automatically and not have to think it through every time. Like,... I want to breathe health air all the time. I want to know when I have&amp;nbsp;a drink of water it is the best water and I do not have to wonder about any toxins in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two things we must have to be healthy and alive are water and air. So we need them to be there constantly and consistently with nothing but the highest quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally I gotta say.I love the fact I work in a building where I know I don't even have to think about the air quality and every time I have a glass of water I never have to wonder what's in it? I know I have done my homework and I have it already set for my long term health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you want to enjoy some of the comfot that I enjoy daily come in teh center and listen to Gary explain the nitty gritty details!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Gary Domurad as he introduces some of Nikken's newest products to keep you with Healthy Air, Healthy Water and Healthy Body with Magnetic Therapy. See product demos, learn why to use these products and how they can significantly improve the health of yourself, your family and your home.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>www.thehsccenter.com</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335309384000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332943681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healthy Air and Healthy Water- Where to find it?</name><id>58212722</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335304800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/58212722/</event_url></item>