<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>144 Temple St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.305830</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(203) 752-0450</phone><name>Playwright New Haven</name><city>New Haven</city><id>209742</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.927505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;**Ok so I goofed. I used last month's description because I accidentally deleted the email about this months' meeting. Somehow I clicked-through the &amp;quot;delete forever?&amp;quot; message...and instantly regretted it. Heh. Jeanie gave me the scoop. The correct info is below:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The monthly gatherings, held at various Elm City locations from 6-7:30pm, invite drinkers and non-drinkers alike to chat about all things eco-sustainability, corporate social responsibility, biking to work, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't Miss this Wednesday's New Haven Green Drinks Event with Justin Pegnataro of Two Coyotes Wilderness School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wed. March 19, '08&lt;br /&gt;6pm - 7:30pm  *or later if you'd like*&lt;br /&gt;at the &lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;Playwright&lt;/span&gt; Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;(downtown on Temple St. - just South of Chapel St.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We'll have our own bar and free buffet&lt;/b&gt;, courtesy of the manager, Damien. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Come and hear Justin speak about his wilderness school which offers classes in the New Haven area. I guarantee you'll learn something extremely useful.  Justin Pegnataro is Director of Two Coyotes Wilderness School.  He leads outdoor educational programs designed to develop a sense of place in their students. Two Coyotes programs integrate nature awareness, wilderness skills, storytelling, and guided exploration to provide unique and transformational experiences for children and adults. See www.twocoyotes.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drink a few for St. Patty's Day as well. (Sorry no green dye for the beer is planned).&lt;br /&gt;Be there to find out the latest in what green stuff is happening in New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Debra Lombard and Justin Elicker&lt;br /&gt;New Haven Green Drinks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They also promise to buy you a drink &amp;quot;if you bring your mom&amp;quot; along to the event. To sign up for the New Haven Green Drinks email list, contact co-hosts Justin Elicker and Debra Lombard at newhavengreendrinks@gmail.com. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*From Eric: I have been to two of these happy hours, and after meeting a local business owner, I interviewed for a job at his company. It's a networking AND educational event! Come join the fun! &lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Also, if you missed any of the St Patrick's Day parties, wear some 'green' for this meetup!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see &lt;a href="http://www.biothinking.com/greendrinks/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.biothinkin...&lt;/a&gt; for details on these international happy hours!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>2576129</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206136952000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205893121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*Location Update*New Haven Green Drinks Monthly Happy Hour</name><id>7560540</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205964000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7560540/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/9/global_3535737.jpeg</photo_url></item>