<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1/4 mile South of the Pheasent Lane Mall  in Nashua., NH.</address_2><address_1>355 Middlsex rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01879</zip><lat>42.669186</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Roller Kingdom</name><city>Tyngsboro</city><id>345153</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.418060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Indoor Roller Skating / Roller Blading 4 Adults&lt;br /&gt;Sunday Jan. 16th. 7-10:30 pm.&lt;br /&gt;Skate 3 Roller Kingdom&lt;br /&gt;355 Middlesex Road.&lt;br /&gt; Tyngsboro Mass.   (978) 649-3440&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Cost: $7. admission $3., skate rental.&lt;br /&gt;Skate rental are available roller or inline skates.&lt;br /&gt;It is suggested:&lt;br /&gt;   That you bring two pairs of socks when renting any type of boots.&lt;br /&gt;Also: If you have wrist guards? Bring and wear them.&lt;br /&gt;   Because this is a controlled setting.&lt;br /&gt;No other safety equipment is needed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Host: Steve Obermiller 603-491-1962 ob@tds.net&lt;br /&gt;      Please join Steve O. and friends for an evening of exercising, socializing and music. Don't want to skate? They will still charge you to get in. But, then you can meet some old and new friends, hang out, sit and talk and watch. This is an indoor adult setting, no kids. This is also a great place to learn to skate, roller or inline skates. It is also a great way to improve your skiing and skating skills,and to just get out and about. Steve O. is an Free dance Inline Skating &amp;amp; Skiing instructor, and teaches a skate to ski program. He can teach skiing at the same time he is teaching skating. This is because, skies are just long skates. So, if you ask Steve? He will be happy to offer you some free help to get you started. Come and see skating in an all new way and do it at your level. There will be music,and people of all ages. There is a snack bar, skate shop, and a places to dance or just sit.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>look for the Meetup sign on our tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295227093000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294886837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indoor Roller Skating / Roller Blading 4 Adults</name><id>16030684</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295222400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/16030684/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/2/global_18494882.jpeg</photo_url></item>