<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A full moon makes a perfect night for meditation &amp;amp; yoga. Lots of energy and opportunities for abundance!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This November evening, the moon will be full within just one day (Nov 2 at 7:15 pm). Named the Frosty Moon, this will be the first full moon to occur after a cold frost has covered the ground. This month's full moon is also called, Beaver Full Moon, because the beavers are now active in their preparation for winter ... building strong dams for hibernation and storing fat for energy during the long winter months. Therefore, the night's mediation will be a guided visualization focusing on breath awareness and personal intentions for creating good health and sustaining energy throughout the winter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Combined with deep yoga stretches to circulate warmth and energy, an infrared sauna will be available for use to aid in clearing blockages and toxins from the body and internal organ systems. Purifying teas, juices and water will be provided for cleansing and hydration. &lt;b&gt;Massage therapy will be available in 10-30 minute sessions. Please arrive promptly at 5:30 to sign up for massage or the sauna! First come, first served. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later in the evening, we will have a bonfire with drumming under the Full Frosty Moon. Bring your positive energy to share with the group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$2 donation requested. Use of the sauna is optional for a $10 donation. All donations are to support the operations of the Growing Green Co-op's community center and healing arts space.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257287900000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253061259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November Full Frosty Moon Meditation, Yoga &amp; Wellness Night</name><id>11382876</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257114600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/11382876/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/b/4/global_10720276.jpeg</photo_url></item>