<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Community Boating, Inc. (CBI) welcomes the Boston Sailing Meetup community to join us on our Spring Work Party to kick off the season right. We'll be working hard to put all our boats into the water, mast them, rig them, and maybe even tune them. Lunch will be provided and absolutely no prior experience is necessary. Come join a fun and lively community of volunteers (most of which are members) who are eager to be outdoors, get some exercise, and get the boathouse ready for the spring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mission of Community Boating is the advancement of sailing for all by minimizing economic and physical obstacles to sailing. In addition, CBI enhances the greater Boston community by using sailing as a vehicle to empower its members to develop independence and self-confidence, improve communication, foster teamwork, and acquire a deeper understanding of community spirit and the power of volunteerism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to join our new Meetup group to stay tuned for future events! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SailCBI/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/SailCBI/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363461124000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363197470000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer on the Charles with CBI to splash boats, step masts, and rig em</name><id>109085332</id><duration>18000000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363442400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/109085332/</event_url></item>