<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>358 Springside Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.338080</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-389-4333 ext 213</phone><name>Common Ground High School</name><city>New Haven</city><id>283040</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.958240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Guys - &lt;br /&gt;So, Rock to Rock is a wonderful event in New Haven - a bike ride from West Rock to East Rock in celebration of Earth Day and a fundraising benefit for several great organizations in the city. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I didn't get a chance to do it last year, so this year I'm being a little more proactive and forming my own &amp;quot;team&amp;quot;   Team &amp;quot;New Haven Climbers&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So... two things, &lt;br /&gt;First, you should come to the event and ride with us.  It'll be totally fun. &lt;br /&gt;Second, you should join the team and make a small donation in addition to the $25.00 registration fee.  Remember, its for a good cause...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ride itself is a leisurely 8 miles, with optional rides up to the tops of both East and West Rock.  Along the route there are stops at many of New Haven's parks for food, music, and fun.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So... to sign up go here:  &lt;a href="http://www.rocktorock.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rocktorock.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rocktorock...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and click on the button to register today.   There's also a bunch more detailed information up there, so check it out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join our team and donate.  On the registration page which comes up, click on &amp;quot;join a team&amp;quot; - There is a fee of $25 ($15 for 18 and under) to join in on the event.  Once you go through the whole registration thing - JOIN OUR TEAM - I think it will either be called &amp;quot;New Haven Rock Climbers&amp;quot; or under my name &amp;quot;Daniel Jeanette.&amp;quot;  I know, I know... registration fee and I'm asking for more donation money... suck it up.  Giving $5 isn't going to kill ya, that's like one beer for a good cause.  DONATE!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternatively, if you can't make the event you should DONATE by visiting this page:  &lt;a href="http://www.firstgiving.com/newhavenclimbers" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.firstgiving.com/newhavenclimbers" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.firstgivin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So - there - bike ride, fun, food, music, benefit for a good cause... what more could you want.  I'm still waiting to hear back on this, but there is a very good possibility that they will have bikes available for rent at the event.  I'll post an update when I have it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Hmm...  I'll be the guy with the bike! hah.   No, call my cell if you need help finding me:  203-687-6864.  I'll try to make myself noticeable.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Jeanette</member_name><member_id>8934370</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272390191000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctrockclimbing</urlname><id>1388805</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>CT Rock Climbing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269454989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rock to Rock Earth Day Bike Ride</name><id>12980833</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272115800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctrockclimbing/events/12980833/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/d/global_13483469.jpeg</photo_url></item>