<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/d/b/d/event_50320381.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The showtime is 6:55 PM.&amp;nbsp; I will be at the theater by 6 and we will head in for seats around 6:25.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Judging from the number of you who have signed up and the extensive add campaign that has been going on this is going to be a very popular movie.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;I strongly advise you buy your tickets in advance.&amp;nbsp; You have been warned! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie is showing upstairs, so look for me at the tables by the windows at the top of the escalator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With such a large group, I am not sure how we are going to be able to handle an after event.&amp;nbsp; We may have to split up, but we will worry about that when it happens.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;If you do plan to go to the after event though, please bring cash.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, the last Sherlock Holmes movie was fun, but I didn't like what they did to the Watson character much.&amp;nbsp; However, how can you resist seeing Robert Downey Jr. and&amp;nbsp;Jude Law together in an action flick?&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Movie Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; December 16, 2011 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Warner Bros. Pictures &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Guy Ritchie &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; Michele Mulroney, Kieran Mulroney &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Robert Downey Jr., Jude Law, Noomi Rapace, Jared Harris, Eddie Marsan, Stephen Fry &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Adventure, Mystery &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://sherlockholmes2.warnerbros.com/" target="_blank"&gt;SherlockHolmes2.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; Sherlock Holmes (Robert Downey Jr.) has always been the smartest man in the room... until now. There is a new criminal mastermind at large&amp;mdash;Professor Moriarty (Jared Harris)&amp;mdash;and not only is he Holmes' intellectual equal, but his capacity for evil, coupled with a complete lack of conscience, may actually give him an advantage over the renowned detective. When the Crown Prince of Austria is found dead, the evidence, as construed by Inspector Lestrade (Eddie Marsan), points to suicide. But Sherlock Holmes deduces that the prince has been the victim of murder&amp;mdash;a murder that is only one piece of a larger and much more portentous puzzle, designed by Professor Moriarty. The cunning Moriarty is always one step ahead of Holmes as he spins a web of death and destruction&amp;mdash;all part of a greater plan that, if he succeeds, will change the course of history.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324399003000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314036552000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sherlock Holmes:  A Game of Shadows (6:55 PM Show)</name><id>30448411</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324162800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/30448411/</event_url></item>