<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The following reviews are from the website:  &lt;a href="http://www.metacritic.com/film/titles/orphanage?q=the%20orphanage" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metacritic...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chicago Sun-Times Roger Ebert &lt;br /&gt;Deliberately aimed at viewers with developed attention spans. It lingers to create atmosphere, a sense of place, a sympathy with the characters, instead of rushing into cheap thrills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chicago Reader J.R. Jones &lt;br /&gt;Despite a few bloodcurdling shocks, this handsome Spanish ghost story from producer Guillermo del Toro follows in the suggestive, richly romantic tradition of the old Val Lewton chillers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New Yorker Anthony Lane &lt;br /&gt;You exit the cinema in a fever of melancholia, wondering how long it will take you to shed the sensation of alarm. The film is less of a shocker than an adventure in anxiety, testing and twisting some of the classic studies in infantile curiosity. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newsweek David Ansen &lt;br /&gt;A great horror movie is like a good shrink--and a lot cheaper, too. It purges us through petrification. That horror movie, thankfully, has arrived. It's called The Orphanage,&amp;quot; and it is seriously scary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Brattle website:&lt;br /&gt;Repertory Series: Recent Raves&lt;br /&gt;The Orphanage at 7:30  &lt;br /&gt;(2007) dir Jan Antonia Bayona w/Belén Rueda, Fernando Cayo, Roger Princep [100 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately marketed as some kind of follow-up to Pan's Labyrinth, to which it bears little resemblance, THE ORPHANAGE is, on its own merits, a very effective ghost story. A couple and their young son move to the Spanish coast to start a school for sick and disabled children. However, the building they have chosen holds dark secrets and some frighteningly playful ghosts. Full of wonderful, old-fashioned haunted house atmospherics, sporting a passionate performance by Belén Rueda, and stylishly directed, THE ORPHANAGE is a real treat on the big screen.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the front on the right side as the credits roll.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>We'll purge ourselves of our anxieties afterwards at a local eatery.  Hope to see you there.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203604624000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Orphanage at the Brattle</name><id>7377954</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206660600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7377954/</event_url></item>