<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are going for a great hike (one of Kevin's favorite) up Chauncey Peak and over to Lamentation Mt.  The beginning is, well, straight up.  Its a short distance though and once you reach the top it is a stunning view.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start out In the Giuffrida Park parking lot and hike past the dam for Crescent Lake. This part may be a little wet as we have to cross below the dam where the trail crosses the spillway. Then we hike up the steep side of the ridge and climb only an easy 15 feet or so of traprock. The path to climb like steep stairs. The reward is great though as at the top, on Chauncey Peak, is a WONDERFUL vista!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail follows the cliff edge to the north with a great view of the lake below and Lamintation Mtn. on the other side of the lake. We will head over to Lamentation to at some mileage to the normally brief experience.  We finish by heading down the trail on the back side of the lake and back to the cars.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since it is winter you will need non-cotton layers, hiking boots, water snacks, traction devices (we recommend microspikes).  As with me, no dogs or children.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the *unmarked* park entrance can be found via MapQuest:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Meriden&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=800+Westfield+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chauncey Peak is near the northwestern end of the Mattabesett Trail system. A good map can be found in the &lt;i&gt;Connecticut Walk Book&lt;/i&gt;, 19th Ed., in either the East or West editions, as map MB-8b as published by the Connecticut Forest and Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail map:&lt;br /&gt; Association  &lt;a href="http://www.scrcog.org/Trails_files/TrailMapGuiffridaPark.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.scrcog.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The link provided below takes you to a topographic map of the area centered on Chauncey Peak. A number of maps (this topo link included) list the lake as being named Bradley Hubbard Reservoir. You can zoom out on the map by changing the View Scale on the left to 1:50,000 or a little higher to get a context.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a general topographical map, see:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.topozone.com/map.asp?z=18&amp;amp;n=4603131&amp;amp;e=686860&amp;amp;s=25&amp;amp;size=l&amp;amp;datum=nad83&amp;amp;layer=DRG25" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topozone.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266248200000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265546468000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Chauncey Peak, Lamentation Mt, Meridan CT</name><id>12542065</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266073200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/12542065/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>