<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Main St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06051</zip><lat>41.665353</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-229-2072</phone><name>Trinity on Main</name><city>New Britain</city><id>1460942</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.781108</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADVANCE TICKET DISCOUNT</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FRIDAY APRIL 5 *Joined Forces with Jimi Bell &lt;br /&gt;

 plus Back in Black AC/DC TRIBUTE BAND&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rock Out and Meet New Friends in the RESERVED CTPartyClub.com section - LIMITED TICKETS AVAILABLE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We have only 20 seats available in the RESERVED CTPartyClub.com section - &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Tickets are $20 at the show&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

ADVANCE TICKET DISCOUNT - $15 While Supplies Last&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTPartyClub.com"&gt;http://www.CTPartyClub.com&lt;/a&gt; * (860) 977-3337&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;at the Beautiful &lt;br /&gt;

 Trinity on Main &lt;br /&gt;

69 Main Street &lt;br /&gt;

New Britain, CT 06051&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JOINED FORCES with Connecticut Guitar Legend JIMI BELL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rock n'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #d19728"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/e/8/event_217190152.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Roll was born to be raw, dangerous and sexy. If there was ever an origin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;al rock act from CT that fit the bill and lived the lifestyle that band would be CT rock heroes Joined Forces. The history of this band is long and colorful. Actually one could write a book on this bands history and its members.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Born in 1984, Joined Forces paved the way for all the other original rock acts in Ct.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;to follow. Lifelong friend guitarist Jimi Bell and bassist Mark Franco felt it was time to do their own music. So along with vocalist Marc Diamond and drummer Michael Karpiak, they decided in their own words, “Fuck cover shit, we’re only playing our original music and no 3 set bullshit; one set of our music, that’s it”. The club owners said it couldn’t be done, the band told the owners to kiss their ass, “we’re doin’ it our way” the plan was an immediate success, it seems the CT. rock climate was as ready as the band for something new.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sometime in bands first year original drummer Michael Karpiak was replaced by Joey Aparo at which point Joined Forces exploded on to the scene.... they became CT’s “must see band”. In ‘86 the band was featured in the movie “The Light of Day” starring Michael J Fox and Joan Jett. The band already had a working relationship with Joan having toured with her. With managers Joe Lennane and Scott Bernstien leading them, it looked like there was no stopping Joined Forces .&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #d19728"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“I’m good friends with Jimi, he kicks ass” “Jimi is a sick ass guitar player”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #d19728"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Zakk Wylde&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #d19728"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BACK in BLACK – the WORLD’S BEST AC/DC Tribute Band&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/5/6/event_217190262.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The Black in Black tribute band is an incredible, exciting, high energy reproduction of a concert performance of AC/DC . All the members of Back in Black live in Dallas/Fort Worth area and are experienced musicians not only dedicated to the sound and look, but also capturing the power and excitement of AC/DC. We stand above the other AC/DC tributes because we include tribute performances of both Bon Scott and Brian Johnson. Back In Black was formed in late 2000 by former LA bandmates Mike Mroz (Angus) and Darren Caperna (Bon &amp;amp; Brian). Mike had always recognized the potential of this project due to Darren's uncanny ability to transcend both the spirit of Bon Scott and Brian Johnson into his voice. Ken Schiumo (drums), Scott Lepage (guitar), and Eric Sykes were recruited from other great Dallas bands. They are one of the first tribute bands chosen by Live Nation/CBS Radio to tour the House of Blues! They toured major arenas and theaters as part of the Classic Rock Experience in 2008/2009. They Headlined concerts at the Calgary Saddledome and Edmonton Arena.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the third year in a row they will headline the worlds largest Tribute Festival, Jacks Throwback in Dallas. They also performed to over 36,000 people at the Bone Bash in Ft Worth, and have been recruited by Sony Music, AC/DC's new record label, to promote catalog sales. 20th Century Fox have chosen Back in Black over all other tribute bands to record AC/DC's classics "TNT" and "A Long Way to the Top" for two of their movies, Napoleon Dynamite and Garage Days Back in Black has also performed with Cheap Trick, Foghat, Bad Company, Loverboy, Jackyl, Blue Oyster Cult, Grand Funk Railroad, Head East, Seven Mary Three, Cardboard Vampires, Living Colour, Better than Ezra, Ted Nugent, Warrant, April Wine, Great White, Night Ranger, Violent Femmes and Vince Neil of Motley Crue.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rock Out and Meet New Friends in the RESERVED CTPartyClub.com section - LIMITED TICKETS AVAILABLE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We have only 20 seats available in the RESERVED CTPartyClub.com section - Tickets are $20 at the show&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Tickets are $20 at the show&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

ADVANCE TICKET DISCOUNT - $15 While Supplies Last&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTPartyClub.com"&gt;http://www.CTPartyClub.com&lt;/a&gt; * (860) 977-3337&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Pick Up Your Ticket from CTParty Club near the ticket window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365213766000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364132937000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FRIDAY APRIL 5 *Joined Forces with Jimi Bell &amp; Back in Black AC/DC TRIBUTE BAND</name><id>110779562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365202800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/110779562/</event_url></item>