<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Cambridge Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363735</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>588384</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Once again, the Broad Institute is holding their excellent summer lecture series, Midsummer Nights’ Science. This, along with Harvard Medical School's Science in the News lecture series held in the Fall are the best technical lectures in the Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Keeping your brain plastic &amp;quot;, From the site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/outreach/midsummer/schedule.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broadinsti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Your brain is a highly &amp;quot;plastic&amp;quot; organ capable of remarkable feats of adaptation. Intricate processes that allow the brain to adapt are essential for maintaining our mental health. Steve Haggarty will discuss how advances in areas of genetics, chemistry, and neuroscience are providing insights into the molecular nature of brain plasticity, and how this information could be used to develop new ways to treat memory and mood disorders&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Lecturer: Steve Haggarty, Ph.D. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://chemicalbiology.mgh.harvard.edu/labs-haggarty.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://chemicalbiolog...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Stephen J. Haggarty, Ph.D., is an Assistant Professor of Neurology at Harvard Medical School, an Assistant in Neuroscience at Massachusetts General Hospital’s Center for Human Genetic Research, an Affiliate Faculty member of the Harvard Stem Cell Institute, and the Director of Chemical Neurobiology for the Stanley Center for Psychiatric Research at the Broad Institute, a research collaboration of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Harvard University and its affiliated hospitals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dr. Haggarty graduated from The University of British Columbia, Vancouver in 1997 with a degree in genetics and received his Ph.D. from Harvard University in 2003 for his work developing methods for high-throughput chemical screening and the identification of small-molecule probes of the cell cycle and chromatin remodeling. Dr. Haggarty then joined the Broad Institute as a research Fellow in the Chemical Biology Program and became a founding member of the Psychiatric Disease Program and the Stanley Center for Psychiatric Research&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting outside near the entrance where the stone &amp;quot;Broad Institute&amp;quot; sign is located starting at 5:40 pm. We can sit down as a group at 5:45 pm. Everyone and their brother walks in last minute, and by 5:55 pm, the place becomes a full house. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can decide after if we want to go out to eat after, or just hang out in the lobby, where they have cheese plates and veggie trays, and chat with the lecturers. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Register for the event with the Broad Institute:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/outreach/midsummer/register.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broadinsti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Go to the Registration Page at &lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/registration/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broadinsti...&lt;/a&gt; and select the button marked &amp;quot;Attend&amp;quot; under the &amp;quot;Midsummer Nights' Science: July 7th, 2010&amp;quot; category. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* For some odd reason, they want you to specifically create a profile. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Once you log on with your profile, you can select which event you want to go on, July 7th, July 21st, July 28th, or August 4th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* RSVP with Nerd Fun on the individual write up page, just so T.J. knows who to look for so he can wave members of the Nerd Herd into a group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule for Midsummer Nights' Science (On Wednesday Nights):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/outreach/midsummer/schedule.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broadinsti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* July 7th, 6-7pm: &lt;u&gt;Meet your microbes&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* July 21st, 6-7pm: &lt;u&gt;Unlocking the mysteries of diabetes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* July 28th, 6-7pm: &lt;u&gt;The genetic roots of heart disease&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* August 4th, 6-7pm: &lt;u&gt;Keeping your brain plastic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Midsummer Nights' Science:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/outreach/midsummer/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broadinsti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Midsummer Nights' Science will recount the scientific transformation that began more than a century ago with the seminal studies by the Austrian monk Gregor Mendel -- the &amp;quot;father of genetics&amp;quot; -- who observed the ways in which physical traits were passed from one pea plant to another. In honor of the scientific field it helped to launch, the pea plant provides the inspiration for the seminar series, which takes its name from one of William Shakespeare's well-known plays. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Midsummer Nights' Science at the Broad Institute will take place at our research building at 7 Cambridge Center, Cambridge MA, in Kendall Square. The series will run for four weeks on Wednesday evenings, July 7th, 21st, 28th, and August 4th, from 6 - 7 o'clock&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/outreach/midsummer/contact.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broadinsti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Eli and Edythe L. Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard was founded in 2003 to bring the power of genomics to biomedicine. It pursues this mission by empowering creative scientists to construct new and robust tools for genomic medicine, to make them accessible to the global scientific community, and to apply them to the understanding and treatment of disease&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;And what is the Broad Institute?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Watch the Video! &lt;a href="http://www.broadinstitute.org/files/sections/about/video/broadVideo/broadVideo.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broadinsti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions by T:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Get off at Kendall, and head along Main Street to Avery Street &lt;br /&gt;* You will pass Legal Seafood on your right&lt;br /&gt;* Cross Avery Street, continuing down Main Street&lt;br /&gt;* The Broad Institute will be on your right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>26</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282010718000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276574457000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Keeping your brain plastic  @ Midsummer Nights' Science, Broad Institute</name><id>13804272</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280959200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13804272/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/7/global_15739351.jpeg</photo_url></item>