<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Wintonbury Mall</address_2><address_1>863 Park Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06002</zip><lat>41.830796</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>K&amp;G Theatres, Bloomfield 8</name><city>Bloomfield</city><id>1222391</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.737054</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;It's time for another film showing!&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Saviors of the Night&amp;quot; (see below) is part of the Hartford Jewish Film Festival, which has grown from a little festival 14 years ago to a huge success with films all over Greater Hartford&lt;br /&gt;Since this film is in both French and German, I am inviting both Meetup groups to come together to see this 2009 film never before shown in Connecticut!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SAVIORS IN THE NIGHT&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut Premiere&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Germany and France, 2009, 100 minutes, German and French with English subtitles&lt;br /&gt;Director: Ludi Boeken &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Adapted from Marge Spiegel’s stirring memoir, this is the riveting true story of courageous Westphalian German farmers who risked their own lives and sheltered Jewish friends from the Nazis. Genial Jewish horse trader Menne Spiegel (Armin Rohde) won an Iron Cross fighting for Germany in World War I but now he and his family are marked for murder. Desperate, he turns to neighbor Heinrich Aschoff (Martin Horn) who immediately offers to take in Menne's wife Marga (Veronica Ferres) and their young daughter. Hiding for two years and running from nosy SS officers, over-enthusiastic Hitler Youth and frightened citizens, the Spiegels struggle to get by. At film’s end, the appearance of characters whose real life stories are told adds depth to a fine production filled with emotional power and a constant sense of dread.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $10- maybe available at the door &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to see this film, please RSVP as well as possibly purchase your tickete in advance:  www.hjff.org.  Please also say if you would like to meet at the Thai restaurant next to the movie theatre at 5:30 for dinner!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269385483000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French</urlname><id>459167</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Groupe de French</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269026207000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film event this week-end!</name><id>12934677</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269212400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French/events/12934677/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/7/global_1365207.jpeg</photo_url></item>