<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>FYI:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9/11 Truth activists should be present and supportive at this important event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Bugliosi (Author of Prosecution of G.W. Bush for Murder) is appearing and that the conference will consider how to seek indictments and prosecutions in state and local courts. Also included is the topic of planning to &amp;quot;make the question of prosecutions an issue in the fall political campaign.&amp;quot; This means that everyone can be involved in this effort in some way even if you cannot attend the conference. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(Recommended article: &lt;a href="http://www.antiwarleague.com/_mgxroot/page_10687.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.antiwarlea...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please visit the website and learn more about it, and register if you can, and please circulate this message widely.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://war-crimes.info/" target="_blank"&gt;http://war-crimes.inf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Doug Fuda&lt;br /&gt;Antiwarleague.com&lt;br /&gt;14 Fletcher Street&lt;br /&gt;Roslindale, MA 02131&lt;br /&gt;USA&lt;br /&gt;617 331-1491 (cell)&lt;br /&gt;dougfuda@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;********************************************&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The Justice Robert Jackson Conference for Planning the Prosecution of&lt;br /&gt;High Level American War Criminals -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will be held September 13 &amp;amp; 14, 2008 in Andover, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've lined nearly 20 great speakers - law professors, lawyers,&lt;br /&gt;prosecutors, journalists, authors and activists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need your help to get the word out about the event!  Please forward&lt;br /&gt;this email to any interested parties.  The conference website is&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://war-crimes.info" target="_blank"&gt;http://war-crimes.inf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below, you'll find the agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Demers&lt;br /&gt;info@war-crimes.info&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AGENDA FOR THE &amp;quot;JUSTICE ROBERT H. JACKSON CONFERENCE&amp;quot;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLANNING FOR THE PROSECUTION OF HIGH LEVEL AMERICAN WAR CRIMINALS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September 13 - 14, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andover, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration details available at &lt;a href="http://war-crimes.info" target="_blank"&gt;http://war-crimes.inf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The common sense of mankind demands that law shall not stop with the&lt;br /&gt;punishment of petty crimes by little people. It must also reach men who&lt;br /&gt;possess themselves of great power and make deliberate and concerted use of&lt;br /&gt;it to set in motion evils which leave no home in the world untouched.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* * *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Charter of this Tribunal evidences a faith that the law is not only to&lt;br /&gt;govern the conduct of little men, but that even rulers are, as Lord Chief&lt;br /&gt;Justice Coke put it to King James, 'under God and the law.'&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* * *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;And let me make clear that while this law is first applied against German&lt;br /&gt;aggressors, the law includes, and if it is to serve a useful purpose it must&lt;br /&gt;condemn aggression by any other nations, including those which sit here now&lt;br /&gt;in judgment.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;From Opening Statement of The Chief Prosecutor, Supreme Justice Robert H.&lt;br /&gt;Jackson, at Nuremberg.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The same disaster has now happened twice in forty years, in Viet Nam and&lt;br /&gt;Iraq. It must never happen again. As at Nuremberg, we need to take steps&lt;br /&gt;to insure that leaders will never do it again.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday - - 9:00 a.m. Opening Remarks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brief introductory remarks stressing that crimes and misconduct have now&lt;br /&gt;occurred twice in forty years - - in Viet Nam and then again in Iraq - - and&lt;br /&gt;the high level perpetrators need to be punished (as occurred at Nuremberg&lt;br /&gt;and Tokyo in 1945 and 1946) in order to insure that people will not do these&lt;br /&gt;things again (as the Germans and Japanese have not committed their crimes&lt;br /&gt;again).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:30 a.m. Panel Discussion And Subsequent Audience Participation On:&lt;br /&gt;The&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crimes Of Torture And Degrading And Abusive Conduct, And Perpetrators and&lt;br /&gt;Punishments.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:45 a.m. Break&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:00 a.m. Panel Discussion And Subsequent Audience Participation On:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Crimes Against the Peace - - Preemptive War And Aggressive War.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:15 noon Luncheon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00 p.m. Panel Discussion And Subsequent Audience Participation On:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Murder and Other Crimes Under State Laws.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:15 p.m. Break&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:30 p.m. Panel Discussion And Subsequent Audience Participation On:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Torture Team: The Actions of Bush Administration Lawyers, Their&lt;br /&gt;Criminal Liabilities, And Potential Disbarment.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:45 p.m. Break&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:00 p.m. Panel Discussion And Subsequent Audience Participation On:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Existing And Potential Domestic, Foreign and International Court Cases On&lt;br /&gt;Torture, Rendition, and War.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday -- 9:00 a.m. Morning Forum I&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic for Panel and Audience:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What must be done to make the question of prosecutions an issue in the fall&lt;br /&gt;political campaign and to have the question become a significant subject in&lt;br /&gt;the media and on the internet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:30 a.m. Break&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:45 a.m. Morning Forum II&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topics for Panel and Audience:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A. Creating an umbrella coordinating committee with representatives&lt;br /&gt;from various organizations, including those that are already involved in&lt;br /&gt;cases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;B. Creating a Center to keep track of and organize relevant briefs,&lt;br /&gt;articles, books, opinions, facts, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;C. The possibility of having a Chief Prosecutor's office a la&lt;br /&gt;Nuremberg.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00 noon Final Review and Event Summary&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221485943000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216738696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Prosecution of High Level American War Criminals -Mass College of Law</name><id>8388720</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221312600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/8388720/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>