<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;WHEN:&lt;/b&gt; Tuesday, April 28, 2009 6:30 PM-9:00 PM (GMT-05:00) Eastern Time (US &amp;amp; Canada). &amp;#8232;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE:&lt;/b&gt; &amp;#8232;USCG Station New London &amp;#8232;100 Bowditch Street &amp;#8232;New London, CT  06320&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Folks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am co-hosting a SEA KAYAK SAFETY SEMINAR with the Commander of the New London Coast Guard Station.  Lt. Commander Ely is a fellow kayaker and is catering this event to experienced paddlers.  Also presenting is auxilarist Lillian Haines who is the district 1 (Maine to NJ) spokesperson for Operation Paddle Smart.   Their presentation will include an overview of accident statistics, risk assessment and a summary of Coast Guard procedures in the event of an emergency. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Commander Ely and Auxilarist Haines both speak our language and have expressed  interest and enthusiasm for a high level, give and take.  Ample time will be made for open floor style feedback.  There will be a post presentation tour of the facility, which should include a peek at some really cool toys.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a rare opportunity for all involved.  SPACE IS LIMITED so I will need all interested to RESPOND BY E-MAIL so I can keep a head count. If you are going to attend, make sure to BRING A VALID PICTURE ID to enable entrance to the station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for your consideration and hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gerry Polinsky&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sea Sherpa Kayak&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gerry@seasherpakayak.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will not be attending. If you are interested in this, just go.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243694418000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240393304000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coast Guard Sea Kayak Course</name><id>10241063</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241130600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/10241063/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/0/global_6975552.jpeg</photo_url></item>