<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Beginner/moderate, 5-6 miles est.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; Estimated 4-5 hours, with breaks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; The end portion is "exploratory" and may or may not involve minor bush-whacking or a slight detour. Please read the description!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo: Quabbin Reservoir from Enfield Overlook&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/a/a/event_122533482.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DESCRIPTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Park is at the southern end of the Reservoir, with paved roads, long dams, and beautiful viewing spots. Park in the dirt lot on the right, before the Goodnough Dike loop (barely a mile into the park via the East Entrance).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're going to combine a couple shorter hikes/jaunts through the park. We'll start by taking the park road from the Goodnough Dike loop intersection straight to Enfield Overlook, which has stunning views of the Middle and West branches of Quabbin Reservoir, and the long Prescott Peninsula, which divides them. Cameras are highly recommended! The views in Quabbin Park are &lt;strong&gt;stunning&lt;/strong&gt;, and sometimes you see bald eagles, turkey vultures, red-tailed hawks, or deer! We'll do our first picnic here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Enfield Overlook, we'll take a path through the woods and below the overlook to the shoreline. There's a nice beach here with gorgeous views of the peninsula and all the way up Quabbin to Mount Pomeroy, an island up near Baffle Dam, about 2/5 of the way up. Also, just off the path to our right are discarded rails from the Boston-Abany railroad, which were never taken away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo: Middle branch of Quabbin from a "hidden" beach&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/d/c/event_122536092.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This pretty, shady trail follows the rocky shoreline, with an interesting volcanic rock exposed by the glaciers that formed this and other Western Massachusetts valleys, and another small beach. Finally we arrive at a popular spot, huge Hank's Meadow. It's another nice picnic spot! This meadow straddles a long slope from the park road to the water, and has a beautiful beach with rocks and grassy banks to sit on. Later in the year, crab apple trees near the park road attract deer and porcupine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo: Beach at Hank's Meadow (Michele) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/7/2/event_100752402.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start our return trip to the parking near Goodnough Dike. However, we'll only stay on the road part of the way. There is a nice trail that goes through the woods and back down near the water, near lovely white rocks and lookout spots on the shoreline. The trail ends at a tiny meadow from where you can access the park road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the past, I have seen deer east of here, nearer to Goodnough Dike, on a trail through the woods below the road. &lt;strong&gt;Walking the park road today, I think I see where it starts in that meadow...so we will take that as far as we can back towards Goodnough Dike. Note that if it dead-ends, we might have to bush-whack up to the road&lt;/strong&gt;; however, I also noticed today a wood gate very near to the gate that blocks cars from entering the Goodnough Dike loop, so it's possible the trail ends there; then again, that could be another trail; &lt;strong&gt;it could even parallel the loop road, in that case skipping the parking area and dumping us out pretty close to the Dike. This portion of the hike is therefore exploratory, as it's possible we'll do the Dike by default, also, or we may need to backtrack!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our official hike is &lt;strong&gt;planned&lt;/strong&gt; to end where we parked (though I can't guarantee it). If so, you are welcome to join me after for an &lt;strong&gt;additional&lt;/strong&gt; 1.8-mile walk around the loop over Goodnough Dike, or not. I'm doing it before I go home, because I just love it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo: Goodnough Dike, Quabbin Reservoir&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/5/4/event_73249492.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are outhouses on our hike: 1) next to the parking lot at the Goodnough Dike Loop, 2) at Enfield Overlook, and 3) at Hank's Meadow.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water (at least 1 liter)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lunch and/or snacks (we'll stop at 2 lovely picnic spots)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;Deep-woods&lt;/strong&gt;"-type insect repellant, or repellant with Pemethrin. &lt;em&gt;We will try to follow a return path (narrow at points) that deer frequent, where we will brush against vegetation, and &lt;strong&gt;deer ticks&lt;/strong&gt; are prevelant at Quabbin.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera highly recommended. (Lots of pretty views, maybe deer.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quabbin Reservoir Regulations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry-in, carry-out. (Take your trash with you when you go.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove items from the Reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No special clothes or equipment, &lt;strong&gt;but do not wear open footwear, such as sandals&lt;/strong&gt;! Besides deer ticks, on the trails, there could be sticks, sharp stones, or (on the previously unexplored path) wet spots!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please be aware I leave my house by 10am. If you have questions, it's best to comment right here, in case I don't check my email.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE TO ALL:&lt;/strong&gt; Once inside Quabbin park via the &lt;strong&gt;East Entrance&lt;/strong&gt;, go straight one mile. On the &lt;strong&gt;right&lt;/strong&gt; is a small white "Goodnough Dike" sign. The dirt parking lot is immediately before this, on the right.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you accidentally use the Middle Entrance (or prefer it from the west) that's fine. After a curve right and a long uphill, &lt;strong&gt;go straight through the rotary&lt;/strong&gt; (don't turn right/uphill). The road goes downhill, then it's maybe 2 miles to the Goodnough Dike loop, which will be on your &lt;strong&gt;left&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware there are two long, steep hills. Look for a dirt pull-off with a barrier after the second hill. The East Entrance is around a curve, a short distance after the pulloff. (If you pass a marsh on both sides of Route 9, you've gone too far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FYI, if you missed the East Entrance just use the middle one. Eventually, you'll come to a rotary; go straight, not uphill to the right. Goodnough Dike will be on the left, more than a mile after the rotary, maybe closer to two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 31 south to 122 north (it goes diagonally west). If you are closer to Worcester, take Route 56 south to 122 north. Then Route 37A south to Route 9. See the directions from Worcester...pick it up from downtown Ware...it will only be 10 minutes from Route 9 to Quabbin Reservoir's East Entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Or if Route 2 is convenient:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 2 to Route 202 South. After 25 minutes, turn left to go east on Route 9. The East Entrance is the 3rd entrance on your left; it takes 5 minutes to pass all 3 entrances. Before you see the East Entrance, you will pass a marsh on both sides of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the west or southwest:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the most direct road to Route 9, and follow directions as from "Route 2" above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;&lt;em&gt;FYI, if you want to preview portions of this hike, there are many more photos in our albums beyond what I link to here. Event text includes phrases such as "Enfield Overlook" and "Hank's Meadow" and includes hikes this spring (2012). For example, Michele's photo of us picnicing at Hank's Meadow (above) is in one saying "Sunday Hike @ Enfield Overlook" and has Aloyah's picture of a chickadee as the thumbnail.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be parked in the beginning of the Goodnough Dike loop (small sign), where it's shady, or the small, dirt parking lot on the right, immediately before it. I have a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344379223000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344274340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Goodnough Dike to Enfield Overlook and back via shoreline trail to Hank's Meadow</name><id>76572242</id><headcount>4</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344344400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/76572242/</event_url></item>