<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will continue our discussion of &amp;quot;Diamond Sutra Explained&amp;quot; by Master Nan Huai-Chin. published by Primordia, 2004. This paperback is readily available through Barnes &amp;amp; Nobles, Amazon and other booksellers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please read Chapter 17 to the end of the book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Master Nan Huai-Chin’s discourses on the treasured Buddhist Diamond Sutra bring together a lifetime of personal cultivation experience that crosses into several schools of esoteric and spiritual practice. This great contemporary Zen Master uses the Diamond Sutra as a tool to gauge the understanding that we must have when journeying towards understanding our true selves. The various passages from this beautiful Sutra are used to provide the student with a framework that combines understanding with practical cultivation. Master Nan’s teachings are uniquely different compared with interpretations given by other contemporary and past teachers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: &amp;quot;Diamond Sutra Explained&amp;quot; includes a translation of the Diamond Sutra by Master Nan Huai-Chin's translator and editor, Hue En (Pia Giammasi). There are several other translations of the Sutra available in English. Readily available and recommended is our member Alex Johnson's translation. Click on &amp;quot;More&amp;quot; on the Manchester Buddhism Sangha website, then on &amp;quot;Files&amp;quot; to download this PDF document. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297732155000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290975813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Diamond Sutra Explained" by Master Nan Huai-Chin - Part 2</name><id>15575631</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297728000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/15575631/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/d/global_12599517.jpeg</photo_url></item>