<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Members of the SSDOMG and SSFMG for our 2nd Anniversary Celebration Brunch!  You heard it correctly!  The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group and South Shore Fitness Meetup Group are having a 2nd Anniversary Brunch Celebration @ Raffael’s on Nantasket Beach.  Raffael’s has been a family celebration restaurant and now I invite you, my Meetup Family, to my favorite celebration Brunch restaurant.  This will be a great opportunity to meet members of each Group, as well as mingle with friends from your Group.  There will be a short thank-you ceremony as I thank the Current and Former Organizers as well as past and present members and there may be a few surprises as well.  This is a celebration of 2 years of the SSDOMG and SSFMG’s successes, events, friendships and future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brunch costs $18.99pp and includes juices, coffee, and tea.  With 5% sales tax and a 20% gratuity, the total would be approximately $23.73pp w/o soda and alcoholic beverages, etc.  Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, October 26th @ 11:30am-1:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Raffael’s @ Clarion Hotel @ Nantasket Beach&lt;br /&gt;45 Hull Shore Drive&lt;br /&gt;Hull, MA 02045&lt;br /&gt;781-925-4515&lt;br /&gt;www.raffaels.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: None, subject to change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per member.  Current and Former AO’s are invited to bring a Guest Free of Charge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fees: Current and Former AO’s – FREE, All Group Members &amp;amp; their Guests - $2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 3pm on Friday, 10/24!!  We have to get our final count in by Friday afternoon.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page.  All 3rd and 4th time No-Show’s will be assessed the $2 Event Fee due no later than November 15th or your next event, whichever comes first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: We have a room reserved by the bar.  Please meet outside and wait for my arrival before going in to be seated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Info – Please Note!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*PLEASE RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*If you are a member of both Groups, please use the SSDOMG as your RSVP area.  Please RSVP No for the SSFMG (you can enter Comments if you want to let others know you are attending, etc.) and put your true RSVP w/ the SSDOMG.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*1 Guest per member.  (Their No-Show counts towards your No-Shows.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Due to the size of this event, all 3rd and 4th time No-Show’s will be assessed the $2 Event Fee due no later than November 15th or your next event, whichever comes first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please dress nicely.  No jeans, t-shirts, sweats, sneakers or hats.  This is a celebration; let’s look nice for each other!  (I know this may be a a little unusual for members of the SSFMG but I know you can do it.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may click on the restaurant name for door-to-door directions. We will add here at least one week prior to the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>By the front door.  Inside our room by the bar if it's after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227371853000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222216233000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Anniversary Celebration Brunch w/ SSFMG</name><id>8819613</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225035000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8819613/</event_url></item>