<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Somerset Pkwy</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.786249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 886-1200</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Conference Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>692326</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.509536</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's go to a comedy show in Nashua.  The show includes an Italian Buffet and an 1.5 hour show.  Afterward we will go to downtown Nashua for drinks and/or dancing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Comedy Show:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Host Travis Wallace has entertained tens of thousands of people as both a standup comedian and in his one-man show as a North Country Humorist. He has a clean, original take on life in rural New England that has produced three CDs, The Way Life Should Be (Volumes I &amp;amp; II) and Tourist Season, and headlined in 300- to 700-seat theaters around New England, including the Ioka Theater (Exeter, NH), Center Theater (Dover-Foxcroft), Gaslight Theater (Hallowell, ME), and the opera houses in Claremont (NH), Wakefield (NH), Franklin (NY) and Skowhegan (ME). Not merely an accomplished humor writer, but also a talented performer, Travis captures the spirit of small town New England and brings it to life with boundless energy and imagination.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the funniest observational humorists in Boston, Steve Bjork has gone cross-country as a headliner, performing at clubs such as The Improv in Las Vegas, Mohegan Sun in Connecticut, Hilarities in Orlando, Florida, Crackers in Indianapolis, Indiana, and several more. He shared the stage with acts including Dane Cook, Steven Wright, Dom Irrerra, Dave Chappelle, Gilbert Gottfried, Joe Rogan, Dana Gould and Tommy Chong. He also once opened for the legendary musical group The Platters. In recent years, hes focused on spending more time in New England, working clubs, fundraisers and private shows for companies. His PG-13 rated act is a favorite for corporate audiences.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A school teacher by day, Mike Prior has long been one of the top crowd-pleasing comics on the Boston scene. His animated delivery and smart and sometimes silly material has made him a favorite at fundraisers, clubs and theaters, where he’s opened for national headlining comedians and for musical acts such as Weird Al Yankovic, Lori Morgan and Randy Travis. He is a school teacher by day, a comedian by night, and a new husband and father. His humor is often self-deprecating If you can’t laugh at yourself, rewrite the punchline, and audiences frequently find themselves quoting his best lines the next day. A regular performer at the annual Boston Comedy Festival, he has been featured on Comedy Central and MTV.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Comments:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nashua D.O.G. is a 501(c)(3) non-profit organization, dedicated to the task of establishing a permanent dog park in the City of Nashua, New Hampshire. We believe a permanent dog park would be mutually beneficial to residents of the Nashua area—both dog owners and non-dog owners alike.  It is solely up to Nashua D.O.G. and our volunteers to build and maintain this park. Therefore, we are completely dependent upon our volunteers' time and our members' donations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;$25 per person (Includes Italian buffet dinner &amp;amp; 1 1/2 hour comedy show)&lt;br /&gt;Doors Open: 5:30pm Dinner Served: 6:30-7:45 Showtime: 8-9:30 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact Linda Howard to get your ticket and tell her you are with the FAN Alliance.  She will reserve tables (Up to 10 people per table) for the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED TICKET SALES ONLY CALL TODAY! Linda Howard Cell 603-321-8661 E Mail LindaHoward14@comcast.net &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: This show will sell out fast, so please call to get your ticket ASAP.  Please indicate on your RSVP that you've payed.   Since the show is expected to be sold out, I will be expecting only those who RSVP Yes and indicate that they've paid.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert</member_name><member_id>4121028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296180019000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235047093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua D.O.G. Comedy Night </name><id>9775081</id><headcount>49</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241906400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9775081/</event_url></item>