<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Legion Memorial Drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02909</zip><lat>41.813984</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Neutaconkanut Park</name><city>Providence</city><id>6579092</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.465805</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/0/2/event_228791522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join P-Collective member Christopher for Volunteer Service Day at Neutaconkanut Park!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where is this, you say? Is it in Providence? Well yes, and MUCH closer than you might think! Here's your chance to check it out, get outside, help out, and explore one of the city's largest green spaces. We did this last year and it was a lot of fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Neutaconkanut Hill Conservancy (NHC) partners with the City in taking care of a wild but landscaped 88-acre park located at the western edge of Providence. This relatively little-known gem of park has a lot of history, an intact oak-hickory forest, and great views of the city. We'll work on improvement projects for the upcoming summer season that will likely include trail maintenance, brush clearing, invasive plant removal, and/or litter pickup. After the service work, we will go for a guided loop hike/walk along the park's trails with an NHC volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear suitable clothing and shoes for performing outdoor hands-on work. Bringing water and a lunch is recommended, especially if you intend to participate in the walk after the service activity. Tools, supplies, and work gloves will be provided, but you may bring your own if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the yellow park gate at the end of Legion Memorial Drive, Providence, RI, 02909. The service activities will take place from 9 AM -12 PM, followed by a lunch break. The walk will take place after lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: This event is set up as a Yale University Day of Service event in partnership with the Yale Association of Rhode Island, the NHC, and the Providence Department of Parks &amp;amp; Recreation. On May 11, alumni are planning a wide variety of service events around the world. Everyone is welcome to participate! In addition to Meetup, it is requested that you also register on the Yale Day of Service website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://yaledayofservice.org/node/1223" class="linkified"&gt;http://yaledayofservice.org/node/1223&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Christopher is hosting this one, please look at his picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher</member_name><member_id>10240270</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368294548000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366860917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Neutaconkanut Park Volunteer Service Day</name><id>116084562</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368277200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/116084562/</event_url></item>