<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Harvard Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.365641</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greene Rose Heritage Park</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1034326</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094393</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>(We will see if there's room in the Greene Rose Heritage Park. If not, we'll move to Edward J Sennott Park, at 310 broadway street, like 4 blocks away from the original place. Last time there was enough space, and GRH Park turned out to be a really good place to play, you can even do it barefoot!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be an &amp;quot;intermediate and up&amp;quot; level meetup. It will be outdoors on a grass field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intermediate level means: Players with firm understanding of game strategy. Should have a good grasp of skills (passing, setting, hitting) and be able to move around to cover areas of the court.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Access by T: Central Square stop or Kendall square stop. Go to Harvard street or Broadway, and you'll find it quickly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recommendation: bring bottles of water, or you will die by thirst while playing :D (especially the sunny days)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some rules that we usually like to follow (but may change if there is consensus, of course):&lt;br /&gt;- Rally scoring (there's point for your team even if you didn't serve).&lt;br /&gt;- If the ball touches the net while serving, it's a valid point.&lt;br /&gt;- We usually play sets of 25 points. At the end of the set, we exchange fields or mix teams (to try to make them more equivalent).&lt;br /&gt;- Every part of the body is valid to touch the ball.&lt;br /&gt;- Blocks don't count as touches for the touch count (3).&lt;br /&gt;- You cannot do a direct hit (from the net, as in a block) as a reception to the service.&lt;br /&gt;- When it's a set point for the team that serves, it has to be a &amp;quot;jump serve&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;- If there are more than 12 people for a net, up to 14 people can play if 2 of them wait outside of the field for their position to be taken by rotation of the team.&lt;br /&gt;- One of each team is normally selected as the setter (normally the one in the middle-up position, next to the net). Teammates should try to pass the ball to her so as she hits the 2nd touch to set. If no one calls the ball and the setter doesn't request &amp;quot;help&amp;quot;, the setter is supposed to do the 2nd by default (as in, in case of doubt). [This is not a rule, but a good practice.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO LET'S HAVE SOME FUN!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andres G. Aragoneses</member_name><member_id>8249754</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250456962000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250128524000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intermediate Level at Greene Rose Heritage Park</name><id>11100143</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250202600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/11100143/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/3/global_1997523.jpeg</photo_url></item>