<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 JFK St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-0930</phone><name>Wagamama Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802033</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120892</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>To All Puzzle-Lovers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to popular demand, the Boston area Mathematics and Logic Puzzle Lovers and the Theoretical Computer Science Problem-Solving meet-up groups will join forces to conduct their very first puzzle solving contest Friday 10/22/10 at 7PM at Wagamama’s in Harvard Square,  57 JFK Street, Cambridge.  First prize is a $100.00 gift card from Amazon.com, World’s Biggest Bookstore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will hand out 10 math and logic puzzles 1 at a time.  Contestants will have 5 minutes to solve each puzzle and hand in a solution.  The person who solves the most puzzles will win the grand prize: a $100.00 gift card redeemable for puzzle books at Amazon.com, and a place in history as the winner of the 1st Boston area puzzle solving contest.  In case of a tie, additional puzzles will be given out with a 1 minute time limit until the tie is broke.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the contest we will discuss the puzzles, their solutions, and how to improve upon the puzzles or their published solution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All evening we will have the joy and excitement of thinking about, talking about and solving puzzles!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have sent invitations to the Theoretical Computer Science Problem-Solving group and the Mathematics &amp;amp; Logic Puzzle Lovers group for a combined membership of over 100 puzzlists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The people have spoken and we have responded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come and join us for this historic, fun-filled event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Before 7PM we will be outside the door, after 7PM we will be inside at the right end, and at exactly 7PM we will disappear for an instant. and reappear inside.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie</member_name><member_id>2078145</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289000020000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Theoreticians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving</urlname><id>1340773</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Theoretical Computer Science Problem-Solving</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287116657000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Math &amp; Logic Puzzle Solving Contest - 1st. Prize: $100 Amazon.com Gift Card</name><id>15116570</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287788400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving/events/15116570/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_9894127.jpeg</photo_url></item>