<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Middletown</address_2><address_1>85 Miner Hill Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Miner Hill Golf Course</name><city>Middletown</city><id>567976</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674248</lon></venue><fee><label>3 Lessons -$100 Online</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>$140 day of lesson</description><amount>100.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.CTGolfTips.com" target="_blank"&gt;CTGolfTips.com&lt;/a&gt; Invites Us To: Improve Your Game Lessons Play Better Golf &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Improve Your Game Lessons provides the intermediate Golfer playing lessons and experience on the course with a teaching Golf Pro to help you improve your skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Please DO NOT RSVP until after you pay for your spot because space is very limited&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Improving on your Golfing skills, and having a Golf Pro help you improve your technique while playing is vital to making you a competitive Golfer.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A CTGolfTips.com Pro will start out by teaching you about Golf, your swing, and technique. After that, it is on to the Golf Course for additional instruction and coaching, to help you improve your game while you are playing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will teach you to play smart by using course management. Take strokes off your score by learning to make the best playing decisions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This combination of the basics, swing development and practice, and then playing lessons has shown to be extremely effective in developing a good Golfing technique. Playing lessons can help problems that don't appear during regular Golf Lessons.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Improve Your Game lessons are kept small to ensure personal attention.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Video Swing Analysis is included to help you improve your swing and technique.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each lesson starts with 30 minutes of warm-up including stretching, putting &lt;br /&gt;and chipping  -or hitting a bucket at the driving range (optional). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next, it is on to the Golf Course to play Golf with our Golf Pro, as he helps you improve your swing, technique, and course management while you play- -so there is no down-time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Lesson size is limited, and is only $100 for 4.5 Hours ($22/Hour) online or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If any space remains, Improve Your Game Lessons is $140 for 4.5 Hours ($31/Hour) at the Golf course -call ahead for availability (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pay with Credit Card, click on Paypal&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lessons are:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday May 18 at 3:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Sunday May 25 Memorial Day Weekend - no lesson&lt;br /&gt;Sunday. June 1 at 3:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Sunday June 8 at 3:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Minor Hill Golf Course is located on 80 Minor Hill Drive, Middletown, CT 06457&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miner Hills Golf Course and Practice Facility is not only a great place for the beginning Golfer but an excellent spot for anyone to sharpen their skills. Middletown's only Golf course is affordable, comfortable and challenging!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facilities include a practice green, driving range, and a par 30 executive course. &lt;br /&gt;This hidden gem is a relaxed place to take your game to the next level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;George Claffey of the United States Golf Teachers Federation will direct our spring session. George is a certified coach with The First Tee, is employed at TPC River Highlands, and is the teaching professional at Miner Hills Golf Course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call (860) 436-9449 for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.CTGolfTips.com/golf101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golf 101 is available for new Golfers Click Here For Info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;See You On The Course!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us in the white www.CTGolfTips.com hats</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211312079000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209223192000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SOLD OUTImprove Your Golf Game Lessons -Learn From The Pros!</name><id>7816402</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211139000000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/7816402/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/d/d/global_3724573.jpeg</photo_url></item>