<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>67.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested in learning about the permaculture design process but not sure if you want to invest in a full-blown design course?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/7/1/4/event_185542292.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Please join us in &lt;strong&gt;Portland&lt;/strong&gt; for this popular Permaculture Design Seminar Series which we started offering in 2009. &lt;em&gt;If, after taking this Intro Short Course, you are interested in proceeding to the full Permaculture Design Course (PDC), your full fee for this event will be applied toward the PDC fee. This is an affordable and accessible way to get your feet wet and decide if you would like to learn more about the potential for permaculture design.  The instructor for this short course is &lt;a href="http://about.me/lisa.m.fernandes"&gt;Lisa Fernandes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;SPECIAL: We can take two students for time dollars in lieu of US dollars. Inquire with LisaF if you are interested and are an &lt;a href="http://www.hourexchangeportland.org/"&gt;Hour Exchange Portland&lt;/a&gt; member (or member of other local time bank which may have reciprocity with HEP).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three Mondays: April 1, 15 &amp;amp; 29 from 5:00 pm to 8:30 pm each evening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants in this Intro to Permaculture Design Short Course will meet on &lt;strong&gt;three Monday evenings in April&lt;/strong&gt; to work through a real, live design process. With our client (who will have completed a questionnaire in advance) we will co-create a practical permaculture design based on their specific goals and the assets and challenges of their site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will come away with a strong foundation for understanding and applying permaculture ethics and design principles. &lt;strong&gt;You will have a framework and a process for approaching a property from a permaculture perspective.&lt;/strong&gt; You will feel confident about taking strides on your own property, if applicable, and will dispel that feeling of not knowing "where to start."  &lt;em&gt;You will understand much more about permaculture as a design approach.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space is limited to 10 students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some student comments from the last iteration of this seminar:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To my beginner's mind, the challenge elements of this property seemed to be overwhelming and complicated, but in the end Lisa began to bring together aspects of the property's challenges and assets and a design began to synthesize that was manageable and cohesive."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I am impressed with the way Lisa teaches. It is great fun getting together in a small group like that and learning new things."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was excellent!!! I left the gathering thrilled and excited by all I'd learned."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was a great experience to walk through the initial analysis phase of a permaculture design. I came away with a better understanding of how to approach permacluture design and some of the questions to ask. ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was superb. Much more than I could have reasonably expected. I'm very excited. ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;By signing up for this event you are signing up for all three Monday evenings; about 12 contact hours plus brief readings in between each session.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topics Include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permaculture Background, Ethics and Design Principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design Process and Goals Articulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Pattern Literacy (Hands-on)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reading the Landscape and Data Gathering (Hands-on)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real Life Examples / Strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis Techniques and Options (Hands-on)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategies: Energy + Shelter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Synthesis + Site analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of &lt;strong&gt;Draft&lt;/strong&gt; Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please wear weather-appropriate footwear and dress in layers. We won't be outside alot but we will make a couple of short trips around the subject property. Please bring a notebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee/tea provided throughout the sessions. Handouts and copies of all presentations will be provided. Supper will be potluck "appetizer style" - please bring a dish of something to share during our break and also bring your potluck "kit" (plate,bowl,utensils,etc.) A large selection of permaculture-related resources will be on display for reference and inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please use the comments area below ONLY for communicating to the entire attendance list.  Every comment and reply generates a new email and overuse of this feature has caused members to leave the group in the past.  If you have specific questions about this event, please send a message to the event host (right column).  Thanks for you help!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah Bostick</member_name><member_id>6829757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1364897235000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363291546000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intro to Permaculture Design - Short Course (Portland Evening Format)</name><id>109285152</id><duration>12600000</duration><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364850000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/109285152/</event_url></item>