<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>580 Old Homestead Hwy</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03431</zip><lat>42.876114</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Monadnock Regional High School, Swanzey, NH</name><city>Swanzey</city><id>7712972</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.277443</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Discover Why 1700 Technical &amp;amp; Building Professionals are Calling for a New Investigation into the Events of 9/11! Watch "9/11: Explosive Evidence – Experts Speak Out" and Learn Why You Should Too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This powerful new documentary from Architects &amp;amp; Engineers for 9/11 Truth premieres June 15 at the Monadnock Regional Middle/High School in Swanzey, New Hampshire. 580 Old Homestead Hwy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our World Premiere of 9/11: Explosive Evidence - Experts Speak Out tours the US with live appearances by Richard Gage at many venues. Venues are filling up fast. Buy Your Tickets Now to insure available space. $10 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://expertsspeakout.eventbrite.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://expertsspeakout.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event features a live introduction and a Q&amp;amp;A by Richard Gage AIA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't forget to like our Facebook page &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://facebook.com/ae911truth" class="linkified"&gt;http://facebook.com/ae911truth&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

and return here to share this event and invite your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tweet this event - here is a sample: &lt;br /&gt;

9/11: Explosive Evidence - Experts Speak Out; World Premiere coming to your city &lt;a href="http://911expertsspeakout.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://911expertsspeakout.org/&lt;/a&gt; #911expertsspeakout&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a mere utterance of the word, 9/11, or September 11th, or any other various related terms can stir up a cauldron of emotion – and it runs the entire spectrum. From steadfast defenders of the government’s official explanation of what happened on 9/11 to those arguing theories of a deep, dark, evil conspiracy. There is no shortage of passion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of your personal beliefs about what happened on 9/11 we can all agree (as we’ve been told over and over again) that 9/11 has indeed fundamentally changed the world we all live in and experience every day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However the official government reports and the media stories have been proven to be false and have censored critical evidence. In this powerful groundbreaking and graphically rich documentary, 43 highly trained and skilled technical and building professionals who, after having examined the evidence, not only have a reasonable doubt about the official story, they conclude that the three World Trade Center Skyscrapers could not have been destroyed without the use of explosive controlled demolition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The World Premiere Tour featuring AE911Truth’s Richard Gage, AIA, is coming to over 2 dozen cities across the USA from May to June 2012, beginning in Beverly Hills with Ed Asner live. Find the World Premiere stop nearest you and order tickets now! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://expertsspeakout.eventbrite.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://expertsspeakout.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not conspiracy. It’s forensic evidence. You owe to yourself, your children and their children to open your mind, your eyes and your ears and review this information dispassionately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;View our 15 minute video about WTC building 7 here - &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://architects-engineers.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://architects-engineers.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;View a trailer for this movie, 9/11: Explosive Evidence - Experts Speak Out, at this website - &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://911expertsspeakout.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://911expertsspeakout.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out our highly praised and widely disseminated video, 9/11: Blueprint For Truth, at this website - &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://911blueprintfortruth.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://911blueprintfortruth.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit our store to purchase articles, DVDs, t-shirts, and much more at, &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://shop.ae911truth.org/?sourceCode=fbNHevent" class="linkified"&gt;http://shop.ae911truth.org/?sourceCode=fbNHevent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And don't forget to visit our main website, &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://ae911truth.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://ae911truth.org/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

and examine the evidence for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339812911000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339673180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9/11 Explosive Evidence - Experts Speak Out</name><id>69134502</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339801200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/69134502/</event_url></item>