<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We've reserved the Screening room at 360 State Street for another Movie Night! Come see a film for free at this great location!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP's are limited to 18 due to theater size, so please only say "Yes" if you're pretty sure you can make it. (There should be NO Maybe's for this event.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are to attend, I will also need your FULL NAME for the Concierge to let you in to the building, and the same goes for any +1's. So please, when you RSVP, either place it in your comment or contact me (AJ) by meetup e-mail or text message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Events Film Is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Shoot 'Em Up&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; (2007 Action or&amp;nbsp;Comedy/Satire, ~1.5 Hours)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0465602/"&gt;IMDB Description:&lt;/a&gt; A man named Mr. Smith delivers a woman's baby during a shootout, and is then called upon to protect the newborn from the army of gunmen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starring: Clive Owen, Paul Giamatti, Monica Bellucci, Stephen McHattie&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AJ Comments: Summer is often regarded for it's action movies, so here's one from a few years ago that you may have missed.&amp;nbsp; This movie appeals to a wide audience 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;completely depending on your mind set&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; I've known people whom enjoy it because they like to just sit and drool at ridiculous stunts or effects shot that go against Physics.&amp;nbsp; And all the better to them.&amp;nbsp; But I on the other hand as an Engineer like physics, but I still enjoy it on a completely different outlook.&amp;nbsp;(See the Definition of Satire.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event start time is 6:45 for the social portion of the evening, so you can start showing up then. But we will not start the film until 7:30 or shortly there after. Don't plan to be any later than 7:30 though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list. As the date approaches I can add people on the waiting list if someone else backs out, provided you sent me your name for the concierge as a contingency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Snacks:&lt;/span&gt; Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just Please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Getting in:&lt;/span&gt; Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are 
&lt;span&gt;instructions near&lt;/span&gt; the call box and a bell button on it if the door is locked. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call AJ at 315-345-9348.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt; There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 7pm. If you don't mind the longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evening/weekends. (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street.) 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only&amp;nbsp;(Last I checked&amp;nbsp;$5 daily max from 5pm on Friday through Sunday), the entrance is on State Street just to the Right of the building main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the building door, Ring the Bell Button, Concierge will Direct you. If you have more problems, call AJ at 315-345-9348</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313195389000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312510462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie: Shoot 'Em Up</name><id>28334861</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313102700000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/28334861/</event_url></item>