<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meetup to jam, and rehearse for the two weekly open mikes.   Our meetup is playing a half hour time slot at Legends in Waltham this week.  It looks like this will be a weekly gig.   &lt;b&gt;You can also come play at either the Wed or Tuesday Open Mike near Watertown Center, where I am in the house band.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup is also to plan for gigs, form bands, play open mikes, etc. play/arrange your songs, and if ready record.  &lt;b&gt;We are also forming a band.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This meetup is for you and the goal is to enhance your music career/hobby.&lt;/b&gt;  Meetup will be from 2PM until 6PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I play keys in an Open Mike house band that occurs Tuesday Nite at 9PM, near Watertown Center - any competent musician interested can come and play solo or with our backup band, and rehearse at the Sunday meetup if desired.  Let me know if interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is a large turn out at the meetup Sunday we will schedule various interests at various times during the meetup (Jam, work on songs, play various genres, record, etc) and can expand the time to from 1 till 7PM. Generally we start with introductions and goals, and play some simpler group songs (blues, etc), and then go around the group allowing each person to proceed to more detailed agendas. If there is an upcoming gig we will then focus on that, so a main focus now will be for anyone wanting to play at the Tuesday &amp;amp; Wed open mikes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will give exact address to attendees &amp; maybes the day before the meetup</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269373250000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268780503000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jam Rehearsal For Tuesday or Wed Open MIkes</name><id>12895198</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269194400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/12895198/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>