<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Three Cornered Pond Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02366</zip><lat>41.858044</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Myles Standish State Forest fire tower</name><city>South Carver</city><id>7543072</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.697060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Spring into shape with a sometimes challenging hike by MSSF standards while enjoying a part of the forest and trails less hiked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope for mild weather so we can hike an hour or a little more to a sunny picnic spot via trails and roads.  Be prepared to do a little climbing if trees still block some of the roads.  On the way back, we'll enjoy some of the forest's prettier roads and sights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, dress for the weather in layers of preferably breathable material and sturdy footwear.  Bring water and snacks for you and any four-footed friends that may accompany you.  It's always a good idea to have a map of the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I will be attending the morning event at headquarters, there might be a brief lag time in driving up Bare Hill Road but we should be good to set out by 1 pm.  Return time should be two and a half to three hours later unless the group decides to shorten the route.  For those comfortable on their own in the forest, there are several options for returning independently by taking forest roads and watching for signs at posted intersections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Troll</member_name><member_id>11017991</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365383564000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364311447000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April First Sunday Hike</name><id>111131612</id><headcount>11</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365354000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/111131612/</event_url></item>