<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>561 Windsor St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.375324</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 623-0804</phone><name>Taza Chocolate</name><city>Somerville</city><id>257572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.092780</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/f/6/event_118700982.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;If OD'ing on chocolate is your idea of a good time, join us as we tour and taste our way through the Taza Chocolate Factory! We'll learn all about how this award-winning artisanal chocolate company sources and manufactures its products and emerge as newly-minted chocolate snobs. (hey, there are wine snobs and beer snobs, so why not?. . .) I've deliberately chosen the 2 p.m. tour so that we won't be too full from brunch nor too hungry for dinner. The tour takes about 45 minutes so if we are hungry for anything other than chocolate afterwards, we can discuss other options. (Sorry, no Oompa Loompas or guest appearances by Gene Wilder at this event)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: Please note that Taza will supply hair nets and expect us to wear them during the tour, also that they do not permit open-toed shoes inside the factor. This means no sandals, folks. They don't want us wearing perfume/cologne either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 EVEN MORE IMPORTANT NOTE: The attendee limit is quite strict as the weekend tours do not accommodate larger groups. Payment for the tour is required when you R.S.V.P. since I had to pay for it in advance to reserve our spots. If your plans change, I will refund your money only if someone else takes your spot. Please follow this link to learn more about the tour before you sign up: &lt;a href="http://www.tazachocolate.com/Tours/Factory_Tours#expecttour" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.tazachocolate.com/Tours/Factory_Tours#expecttour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in front of the factory at 1:45. Parking is available in the lot diagonally across the street.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341621032000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336849476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Calling all Chocoholics. . .</name><id>64534242</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337536800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/64534242/</event_url></item>