<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>121 Washingston Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-274-2121</phone><name>Local 121</name><city>Providence</city><id>564458</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.414800</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Need a night out downtown? DJ JR (owner of Avery) is a fave spinning 80s** (caveat below) and/or funk every 3rd Saturday at Local 121. A few times in the past this has been super duper fun and crazy, while others more low key. Maybe spring will bring out a crowd that we can mingle with. Dust off your dancin shoes or polish up your people watching spectacles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone wants to meet a bit earlier (around 9pm), we'll find a different spot (without a cover) in walking distance to congregate for a first stop (maybe AS220?). In your rsvp, please make a note that you'd like to meet up earlier and I'll let you know where we are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***JR tends to play old alternative music from the 80s/90s in his bar (avery) when he is there. the times we have been to 121 and 201 when he has played his tunes have not necessarily included this. so don't get your hopes up to hear old Bon Jovi, hair bands, top 40, or completely recognizable songs. If you like it then stick around, if you decide it's not your thing it's okay to mosey somewhere else - you won't hurt our feelings.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274037839000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273533722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Saturday DJ JR @ Local 121</name><id>13443140</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273975200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/13443140/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>