<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>ADDRESS EMAILED 1 WEEK IN ADVANCE</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04049</zip><lat>43.728172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rebecca's House</name><city>Limington</city><id>1040139</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.704552</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP yes only if you are able to attend. It is very important that you play the character you have been assigned for the party to go well. Thank you!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The King of the Leprechauns has had his pot of gold stolen. Who was the devious thief? Was it one of the little people or one of the local Irish lads or lasses? Or was it Laoghaire – the High King? Saint Patrick himself is here to investigate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have just heard that Evan Costello - Laoghaire - the High King's goldsmith has been found dead. It appears that he fell while trying to kiss the Blarney stone at Blarney Castle near Cork. The question is – did he just fall or did someone play a part in his death? And if he was killed, was he killed by the same person who stole the gold, or was it someone else?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Characters:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hendo Barrett (leprechaun)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I’m not a grotesque goblin – I’m more of a mischievous elf. People see me sneaking around but I’m no peeping Tom, I just like to keep an eye on what’s going on. I pop up here, I pop up there – from behind a bush and so on, but I’m harmless. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes such as a green hat and pants with a large brass belt buckle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maeve Barrett (Hendo’s wife)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I never quite know how Hendo comes up with the housekeeping money he gives me as I never sees him doing any work. When I ask he mumbles something about finding a fourleafed clover. I supplement our income by sewing pointy hats for other elves. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes such as a green pointy hat and a skirt with a large brass belt buckle. You can make the pointy hat out of felt or other material or cardboard if these aren’t available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rory O’Hara (leprechaun)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I’m a traditional cobbler. I mainly make shoes and boots for other little people. I am very hardworking and the shoes I make are very hard-wearing and tough. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes. Add a large brass belt buckle to your shoes or boots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Aileen O’Hara (Rory’s wife)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I help Rory by polishing the boots he makes. Rory is the best cobbler in all of Ireland and I am very proud of&lt;br /&gt;the shoes we make together. When I polish them, they shine so much you can see your face in them. I’m a jolly person and I laugh a lot in spite of my worries. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes. Add a&lt;br /&gt;large brass belt buckle to your shoes or boots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Magee MacMahon (Irish lad)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am a blacksmith. My father was a blacksmith and his father before him. I make horseshoes for the little people as well as the normal folk. I am strong and very industrious. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes and a large green apron. Carry a&lt;br /&gt;horseshoe and some billows for the fire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tara Fitzgerald (Irish lass)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I knit sweaters and I sell them at the market. Some people think I always have my nose in the air and that I&lt;br /&gt;act as if I am above everyone. Maybe I am. Or maybe I am just avoiding the bad smells in the gutters around here. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes and a green sweater (also known as a “jumper”).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Malone MacSweeney (Irish lad)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I love to play the fiddle fast and furiously. I am a shepherd by day and a musician by night. When I play, feet start dancing and the sheep if they hear, they start moving too. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes. Carry a fiddle and/or a shepherd’s hook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bridget O’Connor (Irish lass)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I’m a traditional dairy maid. I helps milk my parent’s cows. There’s nothing nicer I think than to rest your&lt;br /&gt;head against a warm jersey cow while squirting milk into a pail. Dress suggestions: Wear green clothes. Carry a metal milk bucket and a little stool to sit on when milking. Or just carry a jug of milk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Desmond Laoghaire (High King)&lt;/b&gt; I’m a powerful leader. Saint Patrick lit a fire just before I was about to light the official fire in order to get my attention. I was impressed with Saint Patrick. Dress suggestions: Wear expensive-looking green clothes such as a velvet cape. Wear a crown on your head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mona Laoghaire (High Queen)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am Laoghaire’s wife. I live the luxurious life of a lady of the royal court. I am always admired for my&lt;br /&gt;elegance, my beauty and my fine dresses and dainty shoes. Dress suggestions: Wear expensive-looking green clothes such as a velvet dress. Wear a crown on your head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saint Patrick (chief investigator)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was born in England but I was taken as a slave to Ireland as a youth. Later I escaped back to Scotland and became a priest. One day I heard Ireland calling to me and so I traveled over and spent&lt;br /&gt;more than 30 years converting the Irish pagans to Christianity. It was I that explained the Holy Trinity (ie the Father, the Son and the Holy Ghost) to King Laoghaire. Dress suggestions: Green clothes &amp;amp; monk’s gown or a white collar or cross.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cassie Maguire (dressmaker)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am Queen Mona’s dressmaker. She’s alwayswanting new dresses which keeps me busy. Dress suggestions: Green clothes. Have a measuring tape around your neck and carry some pins and sewing&lt;br /&gt;thread.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Robbie Gilroy (King of the Leprechauns)&lt;/b&gt; I rule over all the little people and after years of collecting their taxes I have managed to amass quite a big crock of gold. I hid this in the crook of an oak tree in the forest and now someone has stolen it. Dress suggestions: Wear expensive-looking green clothes such&lt;br /&gt;as a velvet cape. Wear a crown on your head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mary Gilroy (Queen of the Leprechauns)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am Robbie Gilroy’s wife. I enjoy being wealthy and I love lying around listening to harp music. I think I was&lt;br /&gt;born to be a queen. I’m sure Robbie will find his gold. He’s probably just forgotten where he hid it. Dress suggestions: Wear expensive-looking green clothes such as a long dress. Wear a crown on your head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hurley Burke (Irish lad)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I work as a servant for King Laoghaire. I like my job but the wages are poor so I don’t have enough money to get a girlfriend. In my spare time I gather wood and peat moss for a bit of extra money. I spend a lot of time in the woods with the birds for company. Dress suggestions: Green clothes. Carry firewood you have collected.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tully O’Byrne (Irish lass)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I work as a maid for Queen Mona. She is so fussy about her clothes. Never wants to wear a dress twice in one month. Dress suggestions: Green clothes. Wear an apron and bonnet.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269038930000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257214740000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Murder Mystery Party - The Luck of the Irish</name><id>11777788</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268521200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/11777788/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/2/7/global_11644135.jpeg</photo_url></item>