<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Warren, NH</address_2><address_1>Ravine Lodge on Ravine Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03279</zip><lat>43.959999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Moosilauke via Gorge Brook Trail</name><city>Warren</city><id>319485</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.879997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TOTAL DISTANCE 7.9 MILES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TOTAL TIME 6.5 HOURS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;﻿Distance Time Elev Change Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude starting at Gorge Brook Trailhead, Al Merrill Loop Trailhead 43° 59' 38" 71° 48' 53" This trail runs form the end of Ravine Lodge Rd. to the summit of Moosilauke. Ravine Lodge Rd. is the access road to the DOC Ravine Lodge and is not plowed in winter. The raod leaves NH 118 on the north, 5.8 mi. east of its northerly junction with NH 25 and 7.2 mi. west of its junction with NH 112. From NH 118, it is 1.6 mi. to the turnaround at the end of the road, where the trail begins. There are two major washouts on the lower section, caution is advised. Asquam Ridge Trail has an impassable washout on its lower section, between junction with Gorge Brook Trail and extension of Ravine Lodge Road. Also, bridge over Baker River reportedly washed away where extension of Ravine Lodge Road meets Asquam Ridge Trail. 0.05 mi 2 min +8 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 0.05 mi 2 min +8 ft This trail runs from the end of Ravine Lodge Rd. to the summit of Moosilauke. The upper part has been completely relocated, making the trail substantially longer but eliminating the steep grades and rough footing of the former route. It is now a relatively easy trail that affords some interesting views as it climbs. Leaving the turnaround at the end of Ravine Lodge Rd., it follows the gravel logging road for 100 yd. to the junction of Al Merrill Loop 43° 59' 40" 71° 48' 51" 0.15 mi 5 min -113 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 0.20 mi 7 min -105 ft Then the trail turns left, descends to Baker River and crosses it on a footbridge, and immediately turns left where the Asquam-Ridge Trail diverges right. to the junction of Asquam Ridge Trail 43° 59' 40" 71° 49' 00" 0.05 mi 2 min +5 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 0.25 mi 9 min -99 ft In a short distance, the Hurricane Trail continues straight ahead, whereas the Gorge Brook Trail turns sharp right uphill and follows Gorge Brook, then crosses it on a bridge. to the junction of Hurricane Trail 43° 59' 39" 71° 49' 03" 0.35 mi 19 min +277 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 0.60 mi 28 min +177 ft The relocated Snapper Trail diverges on the left just past this bridge, while the Gorge Brook Trail continues close to the brook and recrosses it on another bridge. to the junction of Snapper Trail 43° 59' 53" 71° 49' 16" 3.10 mi 2 hr 38 min +2139 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 3.70 mi 3 hr 6 min +2316 ft Then the trail passes the memorial plaque for the Ross McKenney Forest; here the new route begins and swings well to the right of the former route. It turns left onto an old logging road, passes a cleared outlook to the south, then turns left off the road and winds uphill at moderate grades, passing more outlooks to the south and east. It reaches a shoulder covered with low scrub that affords a view to the summit ahead and soon breaks into the open on the grassy ridge crest. It continues to the base of the summit rocks, then clambers up the last rocky 50 yd. to the summit. to Mt Moosilauke 44° 01' 24" 71° 49' 53" 0.90 mi 38 min -344 ft on Moosilauke Carriage Road 4.60 mi 3 hr 44 min +1972 ft This former carriage road climbs to the summit of Moosilauke from Breezy Point, a large clearing with good views, the site of the Moosilauke Inn. Grades are easy to moderate and the footing is in general very good; marking is light in the first part, after which the trail becomes unmistakable. The upper part is above the treeline and greatly exposed to the elements, so it can be dangerous in bad weather. The lower part, up to a barricade, receives heavy snowmobile use in winter. The Moosilauke Carriage Road starts at the summit of Moosilauke and descends the windswept ridge down to treeline. It continues on an old road, now part of the AT, along the ridge, with a narrow fringe of trees on each side. It then reaches the Glencliff Trail which diverges to the right. A few steps along the Glencliff Trail, a spur trail leads left to South Peak, a fine viewpoint. to the junction of Glencliff Trail, South Peak, Mt Moosilauke spur 44° 00' 47" 71° 50' 24" 2 Distance Time Elev Change Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude 0.20 mi 8 min +77 ft on South Peak, Mt Moosilauke spur 4.80 mi 3 hr 52 min +2049 ft 0.20 mi 8 min -77 ft on South Peak, Mt Moosilauke spur 5.00 mi 4 hr 0 min +1972 ft to the junction of Glencliff Trail, Moosilauke Carriage Road 44° 00' 47" 71° 50' 24" 1.20 mi 1 hr 9 min -1091 ft on Moosilauke Carriage Road 6.20 mi 5 hr 9 min +881 ft The Carriage Road descends to the south, soon passing a row of boulders that prevent vehicular use on the upper mountain. As it continues to descend, there are occasional views to the south and east. This section of the road has been widened and improved, eliminating what was formerly a washed-out section with poor footing. to the junction of Snapper Trail 43° 59' 57" 71° 50' 04" 1.10 mi 55 min -704 ft on Snapper Trail 7.30 mi 6 hr 4 min +177 ft This trail was originally cut as a downhill ski trail, but it has been almost completely relocated and now features less steep grades and drier footing than before. It runs from the Gorge Brook Trail to the Moosilauke Carriage Rd., below the summit of Moosilauke. It makes possible a number of loop hikes from Ravine Lodge Rd.; particularly attractive is the circuit over the summit of Moosilauke that combines the Snapper Trail—Moosilauke Carriage Rd. route with the Gorge Brook Trail—these two routes are now approximately equal in distance and difficulty. From its junction with the Moosilauke Carriage Rd., the Snapper Trail crosses the old trail route and angles down the slope in a northeast direction at a moderate grade. It crosses a tributary, swings left, then right, crosses another tributary, then descends along its bank to its junction with the Gorge Brook Trail. to the junction of Gorge Brook Trail 43° 59' 53" 71° 49' 16" 0.35 mi 19 min -277 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 7.65 mi 6 hr 23 min -99 ft The Gorge Brook Trail continues close to the brook. The relocated Snapper Trail diverges on the right, and the Gorge Brook Trail and crosses the Gorge Brook on the bridge. to the junction of Hurricane Trail 43° 59' 39" 71° 49' 03" 0.05 mi 2 min -5 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 7.70 mi 6 hr 25 min -105 ft The Gorge Brook Trail crosses Gorge Brook on a bridge then turns sharp left where the Hurricane Trail diverges to the right. to the junction of Asquam Ridge Trail 43° 59' 40" 71° 49' 00" 0.15 mi 5 min +113 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 7.85 mi 6 hr 30 min +8 ft The trail passes to the left of the Asquam-Ridge Trail, and crosses the Baker River on a footbridge. to the junction of Al Merrill Loop 43° 59' 40" 71° 48' 51" 0.05 mi 2 min -8 ft on Gorge Brook Trail 7.90 mi 6 hr 32 min 0 ft It follows the gravel logging road for 100 yd., arriving at the turnaround at the end of Ravine Lodge Rd. to Gorge Brook Trailhead, Al Merrill Loop Trailhead 43° 59' 38" 71° 48' 53" This trail runs form the end of Ravine Lodge Rd. to the summit of Moosilauke. Ravine Lodge Rd. is the access road to the DOC Ravine Lodge and is not plowed in winter. The raod leaves NH 118 on the north, 5.8 mi. east of its northerly junction with NH 25 and 7.2 mi. west of its junction with NH 112. From NH 118, it is 1.6 mi. to the turnaround at the end of the road, where the trail begins. 7.90 mi 6 hr 32 min 0 ft Totals&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE'LL MEET BEHIND THE RAVINE LODGE.  I'LL BE WEARING A RED BASEBALL CAP AND GREEN PACK</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340616222000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340024187000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOOSILAUKEE VIA GORGE BROOK TRAIL</name><id>69642612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340542800000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/69642612/</event_url></item>