<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Avenue of the Arts</address_2><address_1>465 Huntington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-9300</phone><name>Museum of Fine Arts </name><city>Boston</city><id>500439</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093620</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This a package deal (transportation and Tickets) organized by the Photographer's FORUM camera club. You are welcome to join the trip and spend the day with a great group of people and fellow photographers.  AVEDON is an icon of American photography and the exhibit of his images will inspire you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HERE ARE THE DETAILS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;PHOTOGRAPHERS FORUM FIELD TRIP TO BOSTON-Museum of Fine Arts[/&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;color]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Richard Avedon - The most dynamic photographer of the mid-20th century. His images have become icons of photographic history&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATE:  Sunday, Nov 7&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We’re chartering a bus! The cost is $45/person which includes your admission to the museum and special Avedon exhibit, motorcoach transportation and driver’s gratuity. Deadline for reservations is  Mon, Oct 18  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Itinerary:&lt;br /&gt;~8:40 a.m.—Depart Macy’s, 125 South River Road, Bedford, NH&lt;br /&gt;~9:00 a.m.—second pick-up at Holiday Inn-Nashua, Northeastern Blvd (exit 4) (park in rear lot adjacent to highway—do not wait in hotel lobby)&lt;br /&gt;~10 a.m. to 3 p.m.—time at Museum of Fine Arts on your own. There are 3 restaurants within the museum for lunch. We’ll depart the museum at 3 p.m. and arrive back in NH approx 4 p.m.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Notes:&lt;br /&gt;~Personal, non-commercial photography is permitted without flash or tripods in the permanent collections (not in special exhibits, this includes Avedon)&lt;br /&gt;~Items may be left on the bus for the day such as tote bags, jackets, etc., however, you will not have access to them as the bus must park quite a distance away from the museum&lt;br /&gt;~Please feel free to bring snacks and beverages (no alcohol) aboard the bus &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;To reserve: email colette@newhampshiretours.com or call 603-880-1420 &lt;br /&gt;Please make check payable to Photographers Forum and mail to &lt;br /&gt;Colette Crisp, NH Tours, P.O. Box 3312, Nashua NH 03061&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet the group at bus pick-up location that you select when making your reservation.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289244848000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287514602000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Field trip to Museum of Fine Arts- RICHARD AVEDON exhibit</name><id>15161341</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289135700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/15161341/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/e/global_16414110.jpeg</photo_url></item>