<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>5:30 start to ??? from website info..

If anyone likes good blues music, Black Eyed Sallys is having the annual blues fest in Bushnell Park on Thursday evening, June 7th. It is free and a lot of fun.

8th Annual Hartford Advocate
Black-eyed &amp; Blues Festival

Aetna First Thursday
June 7, 2007
Free

On Aetna First Thursday in June, Hartford?s Bushnell Park is alive with thousands of fans enjoying the sounds of hot blues music at the annual Black-eyed &amp; Blues Fest, featuring renowned national and regional blues artists and outrageous BBQ food from one of Hartford?s hottest restaurants: Black-eyed Sally?s. Produced by the Hartford Advocate, Greater Hartford Arts Council, and Black-eyed Sally?s.


UPDATE:
ROB P.....
 Has a really good idea which i selfishly stole...cuz im lazy..but just think, it is a way to find each other..everyone is coming from different places, different times, and sitting in whereever thay can...
The only thisng i can suggest is to cell phone each other..i dont have one..and might have to work that night also..so.. i might not even get to go..dont know yet...

ANYWAY this is what Rob wrote..check back here or therse or the other group..for info..
Sorry this is just a big event with too many variables..

Announcing a new event for The Central Conn./Hartford Walking Meetup Group!

What: Hartford Advocate "Black-eyed &amp; Blues" Festival

When: Thursday, June 7, 4:45 PM

Where: Click the link below to find out!

Event Description: 8th Annual Hartford Advocate "Black-eyed &amp; Blues" Festival at Bushnell Park (downtown Hartford, at the base of the Capitol Building) - THIS Thursday June 7 @ 5-11PM 
FREE ADMISSION, food and beer for sale, great blues music! 

Hartford's Bushnell Park is alive with thousands of fans enjoying the sounds of hot blues music at the annual Black-eyed &amp; Blues Fest, featuring renowned national and regional blues artists and outrageous BBQ food from one of Hartford's hottest restaurants: Black-eyed Sally's. Produced by the Hartford Advocate, Greater Hartford Arts Council, and Black-eyed Sally's.

&gt;&gt;&gt; NOTE: Coolers and alcohol are not allowed inside the fenced area at the park; however, you can bring coolers and discreetly consume alcoholic beverages outside the fence and still enjoy the music. I encourage you to consolidate coolers and car pool. 

&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Let's plan to congregate outside the fence - about halfway up the hill between the fenced-in area and the Capitol building. &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&gt;&gt; Bring blankets, chairs, coolers, photo ID, glow-in-the-dark necklaces, etc. We can take turns watching each other's belongings when people want to go into the fenced-in area to buy food and get closer to the music. Once organized at our "base", if some people want to set up camp inside the fenced area, that would be a good idea also. 

I will try to be there at approximately 5:30pm, but I'm sure some members who work or live closer to Hartford will be there earlier to stake a claim. It will very loud and hard to communicate by Cell. If in doubt, tell your friends to simply find us half way up the hill between the fenced-in area and Capitol building!

&gt;&gt;&gt; Please check back here on Thursday afternoon for any updates re: if we'll have balloons, flashing lights, a "MeetUp" sign, mosquito-repellant kiki torches, or some sort of flag identifying our location. If you have something along those lines and will be arriving @ 5:00, please contact me ASAP so I can get the word out. Thx. 

- Rob Pudney (aka Rob P.)

FYI: Friends / acquaintances from various MeetUp, etc. groups are invited, so don't worry if there's only a small number of RSVP's on this site - join the growing party!

&lt;a href="http://www.hartfordadvocate.com/bluesfest/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hartfordadvocate.com/bluesfest/&lt;/a&gt;

FYI: For those who stay to the end... they sometimes distribute FREE passes for food, drink, and partying with the performers at Black-Eyed Sally?s private after-party!

Learn more here:
&lt;a href="http://walkers.meetup.com/266/calendar/5853088/" class="linkified"&gt;http://walkers.meetup.com/266/calendar/5853088/&lt;/a&gt;


OK HERE IS THE BEST I CAN DO AS TO GET US TO A GOOD SPOT..
KATHY SUGGESTED WE MEET AT THE CT RIVER AREA IN EAST HARTFORD (PITKIN/OR SIMILAR LOT) AND JUST SIMPLY WALK TO THE PARK....SOUNDS GOOD TO ME..ITS ONLY A MILE WALK..FOR US SEXY AND FIT SINGLES..THATS NOTHING.....

OK I WILL UPDATE AS TO A GOOD TIME  5:30 IS A BIT EARLY TO BEAT THROUGH THE TRAFFIC....
TIME TO MEET ???? IM SAYING ABOUT MORE LIKE 6/6:30 PM

Sorry everyone, I am putting this together from pieces of info and have found in the past these events to be fun but difficut to find each other because of the logistics involved..its the best i can do..
If i cant find you, i wish all of you who did, a good evening..
AL Reigins</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181583306000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179587515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concert at Bushnell Park in Hartford, June 7 2007</name><id>5795363</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181251800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5795363/</event_url></item>