<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Register for our Buying Bank Foreclosures discussion Wed night, Feb. 6th. here &lt;a href="https://www1.gotomeeting.com/register/664014555" target="_blank"&gt;https://www1.gotomeet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buying Bank Owned Property or REO's, is becoming a great way to buy your home or investment property. &lt;br /&gt;As close as 6 months ago this was not the case but, due to the housing crisis that has been seen in the media, along with the mortgage fallout, banks have begun to liquidate their non-performing assets or NPA's.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is a great time to purchase Bank Owned Property. For some it could be the purchase of a lifetime, for others a great investment. Either way if you join us on Wednesday Night the 6th of Feb. We will discuss how you can pick up Bank Owned Properties for .60-.70 cents on the dollar of today's market value. Not based on some market value illusion of a year or two ago. Values are determined by current appraisal, and BPO. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't have money to purchase bank properties? Listen in anyway, we have some options for those of you who are looking for some experience in investing without having to risk any credit or money.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register for the event here at: &lt;a href="https://www1.gotomeeting.com/register/664014555" target="_blank"&gt;https://www1.gotomeet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Garian</member_name><member_id>2553452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202515872000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>I will discuss how to get a great deal on your home or investment property by purchasing a Bank foreclosure.
We will also present a partnering opportunity to those who are interested. 
You can listen in from home</why><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>InvestMetroWest</urlname><id>214680</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Metro West Investors - Boston area Real Estate Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199322256000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metro West Investors - Boston area Real Estate Group Meetup</name><id>7017182</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202342400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InvestMetroWest/events/7017182/</event_url></item>