<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;I will be staying in the area the night before, so be sure to list your contact information so we can fill you in on the details.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;This will be a moderately paced hike - I'm not a fast hiker but I do keep moving. The challenge will be the Owls head slide. The distance and slide make this an advanced level hike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can be a very wet trail. I've also been told it's "boring" because of the lack of views and relatively easy grade (until you reach the Owl's Head Path, which is steep). I happen to enjoy the flat trail in Lincoln Woods. Gives us time to walk and talk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared to come out in the dark. We will have 13 hours from the meeting time until sunset, and the hike will take most of that time. Don't forget that you'll need to eat, not just snack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not a traverse, so we will not have to carpool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet in the lot of the Visitor's Center at Lincoln Woods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for all weather conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a very WET trail, so come prepared to stay dry. You might get your feet wet, water shoes, change of socks recommended. &amp;nbsp;DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This is dangerous especially in cool/wet weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* Sunset on Tuesday will be at 8:33 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* Because this is a LONG hike, headlamps are required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* This hike is not very exposed (except to water)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* There is no hut along this trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* I am not a speedy hiker, but I do try to keep a steady pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;* I will watch the weather carefully and scrub if it looks to be awful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form enjoying the outdoors (Owl's Head does not have fabulous views), SO if the weather looks like it will be miserable, we will do it another time. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - I may delete your 'going' RSVP and/or will not take you from the waiting list if I don't see your answers. If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning/evening of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead. I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Book time is about 12 hrs &amp;amp; 18 miles depending on the route taken. On this trip, we hike at our pace. I love the trail and take breaks if needed. Headlamps &amp;amp; extra batteries are mandatory..This is the darkest night time trail I've ever been on due to the thick tree cover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recommend the AMC Guide and the following websites if you want to research the routes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://hikenh.netfirms.com/XOwlsHTr.htm"&gt;http://hikenh.netfirms.com/XOwlsHTr.htm&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/otherpemi.html#Owl"&gt;http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/otherpemi...&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DISCLAIMER: &amp;nbsp;THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE THESE PEAKS BEFORE BUT EVERY HIKE ON A TRAIL IS A NEW EXPERIENCE. THE WEATHER IS NEVER THE SAME, THE GROUP IS ALWAYS A DIFFERENT BLEND OF PERSONALITIES. &amp;nbsp;DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR HIKE.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the ranger hut. Don't forget to pay $3 for the parking or get an annual pass</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310427896000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309473695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Owl's Head</name><id>24152661</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310292000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/24152661/</event_url></item>