<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Email m@rawyum.com 4 info</address_2><address_1>Baba Yaga's</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364758</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1210196</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103256</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Grand Floating Raw Vegan Brunch&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bring your lovely body and a lovely raw vegan food item to share with other lovely bodies. This rawesome potluck is usually held almost every Sunday; but, please email m@rawyum.com for the address and updated information when available. Please mention &amp;quot;Potluck: Cambridge&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Baba Yaga's&amp;quot;, or &amp;quot;Grand Floating Raw Vegan Brunch&amp;quot; in the subject line. Thank you. Enjoy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;QUESTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;What is this raw food thing? The general argument is that processing food -- specifically, cooking it -- destroys most of the nutritional value. By minimally processing food, avoiding heating it, and using only organic vegan ingredients, you can dramatically increase what you get out of the food you eat. The effect on mood, health, and energy levels is dramatic. There are countless books and websites on the topic, but the best way to learn about it is simply to experience it for yourself.&lt;br /&gt;----&lt;br /&gt;So, you eat a lot of salads? We blend, grind, juice, dehydrate, sprout, and otherwise massage raw nuts, fruits, and vegetables into delicious creations.&lt;br /&gt;----&lt;br /&gt;Can I make food there? Absolutely! Feel free to arrive at 10am to prep or come the night before if you need to dehydrate something overnight (please email to confirm). Dehydrator/juicers/vitamix/food processor/grinder/ice cream maker all available for use.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;What can I bring? If you don't feel up to preparing a raw recipe, it's easy to contribute: you can help clean the kitchen, everybody loves ripe organic avacados and young coconuts, fresh vegetables to juice are always a big hit (my recommendations -- kale, chard, spinach, celery, beets, carrots, broccoli, cauliflower, cilantro, cucumber, lettuce). A jar of raw almond butter (be sure it says 'raw' on the label) can often be found at whole foods or harvest.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;Can I bring my amazing vegan hummus/pancakes/cupcakes/chocolates/other cooked/commercially prepared dish? Please don't. Some participants are strict raw vegan and I want everybody to be able to be comfortable with the food set out. I make an exception for 'best effort' ingredients that cannot be reasonably obtained in true raw form (e.g. the FDA requirement that all almonds sold in the US be steamed for 30 seconds). Store-bought juices are pasteurized and sugar-loaded, please avoid those and just bring the source fruits instead and juice here!&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;Is this a kid-friendly event? Yes!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280709736000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268570342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck: Cambridge (Sundays)</name><id>vtkhnyngbgb</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270396800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/12871961/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/1/global_14098401.jpeg</photo_url></item>