<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Harrison Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Encuentro5 (fifth floor)</name><city>Boston</city><id>610414</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>SEPTEMBER 25TH BOSTON MAY DAY COMMITTEE (BMDC) CONFERENCE ON IMMIGRATION POLITICS &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;IMMIGRANT RIGHTS ARE WORKERS RIGHTS&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;SATURDAY, SEPTEMBER 25 - 1PM - 5PM&lt;br /&gt;33 HARRISON AVE 5TH FL. -- ENCUENTRO5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that we will start promptly at 1 PM. With a packed schedule we cannot afford to waste any time. All presentations will be limited to 10 minutes to allow ample time for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BLOCK 1:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;0. WELCOME&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. WE STRUGGLE FOR MIGRANT WORKERS RIGHTS AND RIGHTS FOR THEIR FAMILIES &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by: GEOFF CARENS, Harvard Union of Clerical and Technical Workers&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Statement of working class solidarity. While the victims of repression play an important role in their own liberation, this act of victimization and exploitation of immigrant labor is responsibility of all workers and of all people with a sense of justice. We also make the connections with historical struggles for workers rights such as the struggle typified by May 1st. remembering the Martyrs of Chicago of 1886.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;2. INTERNATIONAL NATURE OF THE CLASS CONFLICT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by: DOROTEA MANUELA AND SERGIO REYES, Boston May Day Committee Members&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Internationalism indicates that we assume the fight of all workers in the world and of workers from anywhere in the world. While 12 millions people without documentation and subject to documentation in the U.S. is an amazing number, hundreds of millions of workers move from their countries to other countries in search of jobs. Since we live in the U.S. it is our responsibility to denounce the injustices committed by the government the and demand change. Brief presentation of our experience at different World Social Forums. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;3. CHARACTERIZATION OF THE STRUGGLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by: AVIVA CHOMSKY, Professor of History and Coordinator of Latin American, Latino and Caribbean Studies, Salem State College &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Globalization of capitalist exploitation is responsible for the displacement of workers from their native countries towards the dominant economies, either globally or regionally. All the rulings classes of all countries involved are responsible for the injust situation workers confront today, not just the countries that workers gravitate towards. Therefore an international solution is necessary. This solution should include the concept of no borders for labor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OPEN DISCUSSION AND CONCLUSIONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BLOCK 2&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;4. STRATEGIES AND TACTICS &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Here we should listen with the intent to learn and to adopt proposals that contribute to our struggle from the organizations that work within the committee, mainly Socialist Alternative, Socialist Party USA, Socialist Workers Party, ANSWER (Act Now to Stop War and End Racism), Mass. Global Action, the anarchist collectives and other grassroots organizations. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After a consciencious debate on the merits of diferent proposals we should come up with a common denominator proposal that will be our standing working document and position. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;------------------------------ &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The outcomes of the conference are: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;1.- A summary BMDC position paper and strategy and tactics for our future work &lt;br /&gt;2.- A deeper theoretical paper and proposal to overcome immigrant labor persecution and exploitation &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign the on-line petitions demanding that the U.S. sign the UN Convention on Migrant Workers Rights&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonmayday.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonmayd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285612568000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284756816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Immigrant Rights Strategy Conference with the Boston May Day Committee</name><id>14807012</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285434000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/14807012/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/2/global_18019762.jpeg</photo_url></item>