<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 1A</address_2><address_1>Ocean Blvd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03874</zip><lat>42.893494</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Seabrook Harbor</name><city>Seabrook</city><id>1073054</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.817248</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Date: 24-May 11 ends 23-August 11  (Recurring Event)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TUESDAY NIGHTS 6:00 PM    &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; This is a free form skill session to practice surfing with sea kayaks.   If there are no waves, we will work on self and assisted rescues,  towing, and other basic kayak skills. Most weeks we will paddle under  the bridge towards Hampton Beach. (to the north) A note to all, there  can and will be strong currents when paddling out to the ocean or  returning to the harbor. For your safety, if you're not a strong  paddler, come on a day where the tides are outgoing when we leave, and  incoming when we return to make it easier. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Put in is at Seabrook Harbor (NH), on the Seabrook side of the  Hampton Bridge Rte 1A in the large parking lot (Bay Side). There is a  restroom which is open from Memorial Day to Labor Day. The parking area  is FREE with easy access to a sandy beach launch. As days become  shorter, launch times may be earlier. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; All people attending must be wearing a pfd and sprayskirt.  Other safety  items to consider bringing are a bilge pump, helmet, and paddle float.    Check the water temps before leaving and dress appropriately.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; See you on the water, &lt;br /&gt; Bill Harter&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Harter</member_name><member_id>7618241</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308093297000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305942776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seabrook Harbor Surf Sessions</name><id>cmhvrypjbsb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308088800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/19757101/</event_url></item>