<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Children are dying in religious families&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Seth M. Asser does not like to see children die. He gets especially mad if children die when proper treatment could have saved their lives.&lt;br /&gt;In his 17 years as head of the children's intensive care unit at the University of California in San Diego, Dr. Asser, a board-certified pediatrician (or children's doctor), took care of many critically ill children whose parents had taken them to Tijuana for the latest miracle cure like Laetrile or coffee enemas. &amp;quot;Their illness generally got worse because they weren't being properly treated or they got complications from the crazy treatments they received in Tijuana, and they ended up in my ICU,&amp;quot; he says. So Dr. Asser began to research the problem of why people would reject modern scientific medical care for Third World voodoo or miracle cures.&lt;br /&gt;In the course of studying this phenomenon, Dr. Asser came across some former Christian Scientists who had organized a group called Children's Health Care Is a Legal Duty, or Child. &amp;quot;It was founded by a couple who had lost their own child when he had an illness and instead of getting medical care, they called a Christian Science practitioner to come and pray over the child,&amp;quot; Dr. Asser says. &amp;quot;They were eventually told that the baby wasn't getting better because they didn't have enough faith. Actually, the child had bacterial meningitis and needed antibiotics.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dying of Treatable Causes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the baby died, the parents formed the organization call Child. Dr. Asser learned that the founders of Child had become aware of some 300 similar cases over the years of children who had died when they could have been saved by simple medical treatment.&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Asser turned this information into a medical study that was published in the medical journal, Pediatrics, in 1998, in which he documented that these children died slow, horrible, painful deaths from easily preventable or treatable conditions like appendicitis, pneumonia or measles, or just not having a trained nurse or doctor at a delivery.&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Asser has written and published and spoken out about this problem to try to help change still-in-existence laws in most states that allow religious parents to be exempt from child neglect or child abuse charges when they let their children die from lack of medical treatment. &amp;quot;Only a small handful of these parents have been prosecuted, and of those, only three that we are aware of ever served any jail time.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Come and hear the good doctor tell Rhode Island Atheist Society about which religions perpetrate this kind of child neglect, what happens to the sick children and their parents, and what can be done to prevent these unnecessary deaths of innocents who cannot speak for themselves.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We meet in the private function room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan DaRocha</member_name><member_id>3370189</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232412785000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Atheist</urlname><id>12929</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225848939000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society December Meetup and Presentation by Dr. Seth Asser</name><id>9095740</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228782600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Atheist/events/9095740/</event_url></item>