<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our January BizSpark Meetup will be held on Tuesday, January 12th at Microsoft Research Center located at One Memorial Drive in Cambridge. The security officer will direct attendees to the correct floor. There is also parking available at a cheap evening rate in the building. Parking is also free on the street in front of the building at 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn out this will also be on the same day as Tech Tuesday sponsored by the Masssachusetts Technology Leadership Council also at Microsoft NERD.  Between the two groups it's going to be a BIG TECH PARTY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 6:30 PM Jon Frisch of &lt;a href="http://t3advisors.com" target="_blank"&gt;T3 Advisors &lt;/a&gt;will present on the basics considering leasing office space for tech startups.  T3 Advisors is the premier tech startup commercial real estate buyer agency in the Cambridge area.  You can learn more about T3 Advisors at &lt;a href="http://t3advisors.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://t3advisors.com...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 7:30 PM Chris Hurley of &lt;a href="http://revolutionaryangels.com" target="_blank"&gt;Revolutionary Angels&lt;/a&gt; will present on the current state of angel investing given the current economic conditions and the Revolutionary Angels alternative to the traditional model.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation | demonstration, we will go around the room introducing ourselves and asking the group for advice | opinions on any startup-related issues members are facing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Microsoft will provide pizza. What a generous organization! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP and bring guests.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marsh Sutherland</member_name><member_id>3795141</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263510387000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>BOSSparkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-BizSpark-Meetup</urlname><id>1535927</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston BizSpark Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258760600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>State of Angel Funding &amp; Office Leasing Basics for Tech Startups Presentations</name><id>11922618</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263337200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-BizSpark-Meetup/events/11922618/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/5/7/global_11095623.jpeg</photo_url></item>