<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;You've gotten along just fine as you are, so why bother to regenerate the rest of your original  DNA template NOW?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And what does this have to do with cosmic energetic changes occuring in 2012?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ancient records containing our true history have recently been translated.  Scientific details of the multi-dimensional nature of the cosmos, as well as our original DNA encoding as multi-dimensional beings are included.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These records were cloistered for eons to preserve their integrity so we would have them NOW, when we need to understand the implications of what will happen in 2012. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This topic has EVERYTHING to do with ADVANCED ENERGY HEALING, since these translations also include the most powerful healing system ever on planet, and it's all about SELF-HELP!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more, attend our FREE monthly Meetups,  just 3 mi. from I-93 exit 22.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This information was not channelled and it is not to  be confused with various New Age metaphysical belief systems.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can get the gist of it by viewing all 3 video presentations on the link below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.krystalspi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The diagrams are complex and may be difficult to understand.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So make a list of questions to bring to one of our FREE Meetups!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't make it this time, bring your questions the next time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt; ****** &lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The records indicate that Earth's grids contain reversals, which are automatically transferred to the encoding of all life forms as they incarnate here.  Furthermore, forced genetic hybridizing with inter-galactic visitors from fallen systems created VERY serious consequences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Does any of this make sense to you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fallen beings still masquerade as angels of light, duping well-intended New Age practitioners to create more reversals by doing their harmful techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may have seen ads such as &amp;quot;22-Strand DNA Activation&amp;quot;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our original organic DNA template had either 12, 24, 36, or 48 strands. Each strand should have 12 functioning sub frequency bands with fire-letter codes which have NOT been reversed. If a different number of strands is advertised, this reveals a fallen source.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The term &amp;quot;fallen&amp;quot; will be defined at the Meetup, along with some of the agendas of fallen beings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's important to know all the facts. Take the time to study Keylontic Science and our true history. The time is NOW to &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;RESTORE  YOUR  COMPLETE  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ORIGINAL  ORGANIC   DNA  TEMPLATE!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/center&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The details of how to do this SAFELY appear in recently translated MCEO Keylontic Science technologies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(MCEO stands for Melchizedek Cloister Emerald Order.)&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Numerous FREE techniques to restore your original organic DNA template and all portions of your multi-dimensional bio-spiritual anatomy can be viewed at &lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.AzuritePress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is also an e-group you can join by clicking on a link at that site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Individual appointments for facilitation by a MCEO Level IV Ordinate Consummate can be scheduled via&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt; www.ulcsclinic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you wish that type of an appointment, just say so in the comments box.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But it's important to understand that &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;YOU  CAN  LEARN  TO  DO  THIS  BY  YOURSELF!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join this Meetup group, click &amp;quot;Join Us&amp;quot; in the upper right corner of this screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each monthly topic is related to a different aspect of the process of regenerating your original organic DNA template and other portions of your multi-dimensional bio-spiritual anatomy, as necessary to &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;RECLAIM YOUR BIRTHRIGHT &lt;br /&gt;BEFORE DECEMBER 2012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since space is limited, it would be best to RSVP to reserve a seat after the details for each month's Meetup are posted. This is usually done the day after the previous meetup was conducted.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also reserve extra seats for guests, but please change your RSVP if you or your guests can't make it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;******&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will learn how Keylontic Science technologies included in the Kathara(TM) Bio-Spiritual Healing System, can be used to heal yourself energetically, mentally, physically, emotionally and spiritually!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With your COMPLETE original organic DNA template regenerated, you will &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;BECOME  ALL  THAT  YOU  WERE  CREATED  TO  BE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These MCEO translations are still on-going, and essential for self-preservation because our current planetary energetic crisis is known to be getting worse.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of irreversable energetic changes occuring in 2012, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME  IS  OF  THE  ESSENCE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sometimes the TRUTH can seem stranger than science fiction, because we were all raised in a very limited and incomplete paradigm, with most of our perceptual capabilities switched off.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But the fact is that we live in a multi-dimensional cosmos, the structure of which will be explained in detail at these meetups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;******&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That is just the beginning, since if you decide to continue studyng Keylontic Science you will become aware of much more.  For example:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that the condition of your DNA encoding is what will determine your destiny? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that the most important part of your original organic DNA encoding has been deactivated and turned into &amp;quot;junk DNA&amp;quot;? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that the fire letter sequences of numerous remaining portions are currently reversed?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that these functioning portions (now believed to be the human genome) are actually a mutated subset of of all you were created to be?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that even the remaining strands, which are now functional, still  contain harmful miasmic blockages?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that you were created as a beautiful talented spiritual multi-dimensional being, with capabilities that would be perceived  as &amp;quot;super powers&amp;quot; by contemporary society?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that at one time, humans had perpetual wellness and did not &amp;quot;age&amp;quot; beyond the condition of a totally healthy body at age 33?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that instead of getting sick, ageing and dying, we once ascended naturally, with all memories in tact?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that getting your DNA activated before it has been restored to it's original template by MCEO technologies causes serious consequences?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that once one's DNA gets activated, what will manifest is determned by the encoding in the DNA? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that numerous unknown medical conditions with no known remedy (perceived as plagues) are likely to result from activation of existing miasms?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that there is a black hole in the center of our Milky Way galaxy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that when our solar system gets sucked into it, all  inhabitants who have not been assisted by the MCEO technologies by December 21, 2012 will ultimately suffer the same fate?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that black hole fall includes those residing in all density levels, including so-called &amp;quot;spiritual planes&amp;quot; (Density Levels include: Physical in Density 1, Soul in Density 2, OverSoul in Density 3, Avatar in Density 4, Rishi in Density 5.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you  know that the original organic encoding in one's DNA template also contains keys to specific ascension gates? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that humanity's current state of DNA code-convolution leads to ultimate deterioration on all levels, including DESCENSION instead of ASCENSION?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that descension into black-hole fall implies ultimate &amp;quot;space-dust return&amp;quot; to God-Source in a state of fragmented consciousness with no memory (ie,   undifferentiated units of Partiki), to be recycled into new creations?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that regeneration of your original DNA encoding restores your ancient ascension capabilities, allowing return to God-Source in a state of wholeness, with all your memories in-tact as an eternal life being?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that Indigoes have incarnated here in large numbers from another Time Matrix as a team, on a mission to anchor the Krystal Spiral Host on planet, so everyone will have the option to catch this WAVE OF ASCENSION and ride it out of our falling galaxy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Did you know that regular use of Kathara(tm) Healing Keylontic Science technologies progressively clears and resets DNA mutations back to their original organic imprint, as necessary to energetically ride the Krystal Spiral?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt; ******  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;   &lt;b&gt;What manifests anywhere (whether individually or cosmically) is always governed by scientific laws of multi-dimensional bio-spiritual cosmic physics, as explained by Keylontic Science.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's why the MCEO technologies are VITAL!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since it takes time to regenerate your original organic encoding, please don't delay if you wish to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RECLAIM  YOUR  SACRED  BIRTHRIGHT! &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ****** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Meetup adjourns at 9:00 PM.  Please bring your own refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:  Get on I-93 from wherever you are.  We are approx. half an hour north of Concord, NH.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get off on exit 22.  At the end of the ramp go North on Rt. 127 (toward Gaza).  In approx. 1.5 miles you will come to a stop sign.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn left, going North on Rt 132.  Watch for mailbox number 298 on the right side of the road, approx. 1.5 mi. up.  A tan building with semi-circular window  is across the street, on the left side. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go up the first driveway into the property, which has a Meetup sign at the end.  Do NOT go up the second driveway which has a sign &amp;quot;ULCS Clinic&amp;quot;.  No parking is allowed there, so if you get that far, turn around in that driveway and go back and up the first driveway.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enter through the front door, where you will see another Meetup sign.  No need to knock.  Just go on in and down the stairs and have a seat in the classroom.  If you are arriving early for a private appointment, have a seat in the waiting room instead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup sign at end of first driveway and on front door. No need to knock.  Meeting is in downstairs classroom.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349856596000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280936052000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Energy Healing Emergency: Self-Help Techniques  to Complete Before Dec. 2012 </name><id>jdtqnynnbzb</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287525600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/14316931/</event_url></item>