<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Federal Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01102</zip><lat>42.108025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>SEC at STCC</name><city>Springfield</city><id>499074</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.577020</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Feb 1, 2012 Public Meeting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Featuring Jim Mumm of Sandler Sales and Management Training!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Speaking on the topic "&amp;ldquo;Why Entrepreneurs Fail It the Sales Role and What to Do About It&amp;rdquo;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Dear IRN community, &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This is Big News. Our Feb 1 public meeting features an experienced sales trainer from a well respected national firm! All enterprenuers, innovators and inventors will benefit from this presentation. Jim's firm, Sandler Training, has had the #1 ranking for training programs in Entrepreneur Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Franchise 500 nine times since 1994, the most recent being for 2010. With over 250 training centers worldwide, this firm has trained business leaders in every field. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please note that this is a PUBLIC meeting, so you are welcome to bring your friends and collegues. Seminars such as this are normally quite costly, but the cost in this case is zero. Both members and non-members are invited. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

NOTE THAT FOR THIS ONE MEETING THE ROOM HAS CHANGED! &lt;br /&gt;

We will be using the TELECLASSROOM, &lt;strong&gt;3rd&lt;/strong&gt; floor east (on the&amp;nbsp;right)&amp;nbsp;for the Feb. IRN meeting. &lt;br /&gt;

A sign will be placed in the lobby and outside the door of the usual room with this change. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

New - LOWER Member Dues for 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We are pleased to annouce that members dues for 2012 will be reduced to $25.00. Our job is to foster innovators and we have found that we have a surplus in the existing account, so are lowering the dues to closer match our actual yearly expenses! Dues payment entitles you to the mailed newsletter, attendance at members only meetings as well as special events that we are planning! In addition, of course, it supports the mission of the club! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We also have a new "family/office/corporate" membership available for $40, the same as the old individual member price. This allows you to enroll up to 2 additional family members, corporate collegues or friends along with your membership. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Membership notices will be sent out in the near future. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We hope to see you at the Feb 1, 2012 Public Meeting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also ask members to spread the word about this event. Please tell your friends, spread the word on your social network, and put up flyers if you attend college. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Sincerely, &lt;br /&gt;

The IRN Organizer Team&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Scibelli Enterprise Center, Across from STCC, 3rd floor Teleclassroom</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Kat.</member_name><member_id>8999115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331167270000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326912307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>(NEW LOCATION) February Public Meeting with Speaker</name><id>48627982</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328140800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/48627982/</event_url></item>