<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>94 Derby Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.180252</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-749-1007</phone><name>Burton's Grill</name><city>Hingham</city><id>894700</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.907761</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Members [and Guests] of the SSDOMG for a late lunch as we spring into Burton’s Grill @ The Derby Street Shoppes in Hingham.  This was one of the top-voted 2007 Restaurants on our Restaurant Suggestions and Recommendations – 2007 Discussion Thread.  We are turning over a new leaf and springing into something old (2007 restaurant suggestion) in addition to something new this month (Potluck and K Restaurant).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the appetizers include Grilled Stuffed Zucchini, Philly Spring Rolls, and Thai Shrimp Lettuce Wraps.  Soups and Salads include classics such as Caesar Salad, as well as Clam Chowder and Poached Pear Salad.  Reuben Sandwich, Steak Sandwich and a Classic Cheeseburger are among the burgers and sandwiches that includes a Burton’s Burger that may be worth checking out.  Rounding out the main courses are entrees such as Crabcakes, Ribeye, Salmon Picatta, Pan Seared Chicken and Wild Mushroom Ravioli, and Filet Mignon and Lobster and Shrimp Pasta.  Is your mouth watering yet?  Mine sure is and I haven’t even mentioned dessert or adult beverages, both of which abound.  Two of my favorite desserts are on the menu – Chocolate Chip Bread Pudding and Vanilla Bean Crème Brulee.  With so much to choose from you may want to consider sharing and splitting.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did I mention Burton’s Grill offers monthly specials?  A couple of February’s specials were Vegetable Lasagna, Seafood Stew and Lobster Mac and Cheese, and a Mediterranean Chicken Sandwich.  Expect to find some equally delicious specials in March.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a delicious Saturday afternoon lunch as the SSDOMG continues to sample your restaurant suggestions and recommendations – regardless of whether they were recommended two months ago or two years ago!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Afternoon Luncheon&lt;br /&gt;Burton’s Grill&lt;br /&gt;Derby Street Shoppes&lt;br /&gt;94 Derby Street&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043&lt;br /&gt;781-749-1007&lt;br /&gt;www.burtonsgrill.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/b&gt;: Near the Host Station or outside the Front Door if it’s nice out.  We may have to wait a few minutes for our table as we are dining towards the end of the lunch rush.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer(s)&lt;/b&gt;: Donnamarie and Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max&lt;/b&gt;: Max of 16 attendees.  Please add yourself to the WaitList if you would like to attend but the event is full.  Those on the WL will be changed to Yes as space opens up in the order in which you were added to the WL.  If you are no longer able to attend please change your RSVP to No so we can accurately fill the seats.  (Please see our No-Show Policy on the About Us page.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests&lt;/b&gt;: Sorry, this event is for members only due to the high number of RSVPs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee&lt;/b&gt;: Org Team and Annual Members - Free, Members and Guests - $2pp.  Please bring exact change.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range&lt;/b&gt;: Appetizers, Soups and Salads range from $6-14; Entrees range from $10-34; Desserts range from $5.95-7.95.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/b&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps us to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/b&gt;: Friday, March 27th @ 4pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview: Located in the Derby Street Shoppes off Route 3 at Exit 15.  Burton’s is in the back left quadrant at the end of the row of shops next to the Apple Store and across from Barnes and Noble.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 3 to Exit 15/Derby Street, Hingham.  Driving Northbound, take a left at the end of the ramp; Southbound, take a right at the end of the ramp.  Take a right at the next light into the Derby Street Shoppes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Near the Host Station or outside the front door if it's nice out.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245212311000</updated><rating><average>4.57999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236211180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Afternoon Luncheon</name><id>9882991</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238261400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/9882991/</event_url></item>