<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Due to some unexpected circumstances, we have to change the location of the party.  The party will not be held Boston, but will be in Acton, MA which is about five miles west of Concord at the intersection of Rt 2 and I-495.  I will be sending out an e-mail with more specifics for the location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to due pretty much the same party: bring a dish from the country that you represent or would like to represent, and wine, beer or what ever you like to drink.  There will be a TV with the game on for anyone who wants to watch the game.  There will also be a small grill, if anyone wants to bring something to grill.  This is going to be mainly an outside event, (I'll bring insect repellent) so if the weather is bad and its raining a lot, we'll probably have to cancel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let us know a little bit about what you are bringing so no one brings the same thing.  The game starts at 2:45 and we will go till the last person leaves. Please come even if your not in to soccer the game is not the only thing going on at this party. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are also adding a $2.00 fee for each guest to cover the cost of the party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215042228000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Were not just going to have the soccer finals, there will be music, and the deck</why><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>51</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212975782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EURO Soccer Final </name><id>8105837</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214755200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/8105837/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/f/global_4585039.jpeg</photo_url></item>