<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update&lt;/b&gt;: Care to join us at Pizzeria Uno's beforehand? Sign up here: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/12067264/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I made reservations for twenty. I was thinking we would be leaving the restaurant at 7:30 or 7:40 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Brattle Website&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/091218.html#a"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(1985) dir Terry Gilliam , w/ Olivia Hussey, Margot Kidder, Keir Dullea, John Saxon, Jonathan Pryce, Kim Greist, Robert DeNiro, Katherine Helmond, Ian Holm, Bob Hoskins, Michael Palin [142 min] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Considered by many to be the pinnacle of Gilliam’s career, BRAZIL weaves a contorted, modern nightmare as poor, disheveled Sam Lowry (Pryce) is mistaken for a dangerous radical in a future dystopia choked by skyscrapers, pollution and bureaucratic red tape. Now recognized as one of the best films of the 1980s, BRAZIL is not to be missed on the big screen!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I've always described &amp;quot;Brazil&amp;quot; to my friends as a bleak &amp;quot;Blade Runner&amp;quot; setting mashed up with &amp;quot;Walter Mitty&amp;quot; with a Monty Python twist to the bleakness. Care to watch it at the Brattle? We can grab dinner before. Where, I am not sure. I always seem to pick John Harvard's Brew House as a fall back. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be in front of the lobby of the Brattle Theater at 7:40 pm. We can grab seats then. T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Terry Gillam film series this December&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/091218.html#a"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Tilting At Windmills: The Films Of Terry Gilliam&lt;/u&gt;: Despite the fact that his career includes as many infamously unfinished films as completed masterpieces, the visionary director Terry Gilliam continues to prevail as a vital voice in contemporary film. Surely one of the most determined filmmakers ever, Gilliam cobbles together budgets from multitudes of international sources and consistently draws from a pool of amazing actors for his idiosyncratic projects. In celebration of his newest feature, the phantasmagoric Imaginarium Of Doctor Parnassus – which had it’s own series of disasters including the untimely death of its star – the Brattle has put together a tribute to Gilliam that includes all of his best-known films&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Brattle&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/about.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle shows the best in classic, cutting-edge, foreign, and art-house films. We also show first-run films and new releases of classic films, but our specialty is a repertory programming format consisting of films from a particular director, genre, or subject shown over the course of a week, or on the same weekday throughout the month. Visit our Series Archive to learn more about past repertory programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Movies have been shown at the Brattle Theatre since 1953, when Bryant Haliday and Cyrus Harvey Jr. started things off with a screening of the German film, Der Hauptmann von Köpenick (The Captain from Köpenick). Haliday and Harvey later founded Janus Films for the purpose of distributing foreign films nationwide. Learn more about Janus Films and the Brattle Theatre on the Timeline page, or read this essay about the first 100 years of the Brattle&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Terry Gilliam, from his website&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.terrygilliam.com/bio.html"&gt;http://www.terrygilli...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;For most of Terry Gilliam's early career, fans of the popular comedy show Monty Python's Flying Circus assumed that he was British, since Python's other five members were natives of Britain. But the innovative animator and future director, who spent more time behind the scenes than in front of the camera, was actually the troupe's only American member. Born in Minneapolis, Minnesota, on November 22, 1940, Gilliam was briefly employed by Mad Magazine as a writer/illustrator before he emigrated to England in 1967. Soon after he arrived in the U.K., he began working on Do Not Adjust Your Set, a popular children's TV show, developing his eccentric animated cartoons, which put into motion a hodgepodge of images, including photographs, cutouts from magazines, and famous works of art. Gilliam's contributions to the show were geared more toward adults, as his surrealistic stream-of-consciousness segments, drenched in black humor, were beyond the grasp of most children.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In 1969, Gilliam was asked to join the absurdist comedy troupe Monty Python. In addition to writing for Monty Python's Flying Circus, Gilliam also contributed his animated interludes, for which he was pretty much left to his own devices; the other Pythons just told him how much time he needed to fill and never gave him any narrative direction. Gilliam began offering his iconoclastic vision to moviegoers with the comedy troupe's first original film, Monty Python and the Holy Grail (1975), which he co-directed with fellow Python Terry Jones [...]&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The story of Brazil&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.terrygilliam.com/bio.html"&gt;http://www.terrygilli...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] After co-directing with Terry Jones the third and final Python film, Monty Python's the Meaning of Life (1983), Gilliam made what many people consider his masterpiece, the dystopian satire Brazil (1985). Instead of journeying back to the Middle Ages, Gilliam boldly predicted a retro-1930s future of anonymous office drones commanded by an all-powerful computer. Blindingly imaginative, the film starred Jonathan Pryce as Sam Lowery, who attempts to escape the stifling bureaucratic system by fantasizing about being a superhero, and later by actually battling the powers-that-be in his own cowardly fashion. Consistently blurring the line between fantasy and reality and uncompromising in its surreal eccentricity, Gilliam's masterwork has been called Orwellian, Kafkaesque, and Luddite. A failure at the box office, Brazil has made up for that disappointment with its cult status. In addition to critical praise and a Los Angeles Film Critics award for Best Film, Gilliam received an Oscar nomination for Best Original Screenplay&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The theatre entrance is on the left side of the building - look for our sidewalk poster case&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Take the MBTA Red Line to the Harvard Square stop. Use the Brattle Street exit through the bus way. When you reach the top of the stairs you will see Brattle Street ahead to the right. The Brattle Theatre is the second building on the left side of the street, next to Wainwright Bank and Eastern Mountain Sports&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261589822000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257282250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Terry Gilliams's "Brazil" @ Brattle Theater</name><id>11785569</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261184400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11785569/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/6/global_11631654.jpeg</photo_url></item>