<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I have updated the amount of people to 12.  If you would like to attend, please RSVP ASAP.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, our &amp;quot;E&amp;quot; restaurant choice takes us south, not geographically, but in terms of cuisine!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in Weymouth Landing, the bustling business district at the Weymouth-Braintree line on Route 53, El Sarape has been serving food widely aclaimed as some of the best Mexican around since 1988. Posters online seem pretty uniform in their advice: Skip the stereotypical Tex-Mex fare like tacos and enchiladas and go for something more authentic, like Mole poblano or one of the dishes incorporating cilantro.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are looking forward to the chance to share with our members a venue and a cuisine that are definitely out of the ordinary for SSDOMG's region. Please join us at this small but significant piece of the South Shore dining mosaic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link to place: &lt;a href="http://elsarape.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://elsarape.com/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;El Sarape Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;5 Commercial Street &lt;br /&gt;Weymouth Landing &lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184 &lt;br /&gt;(781) 843-8005&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FROM ROUTE 3 NORTH (COMING FROM CAPE COD):&lt;/b&gt; El Sarape is located on Commercial St. in Weymouth Landing. This section of Commercial St. is part of Route 53.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 16 onto Rt 18 North. Go straight through the first light (Dairy Queen is on your right).&lt;br /&gt;Next light is the end of Rt 18. You will be facing one of the large chain drugstores: turn left onto Rt 53.&lt;br /&gt;Follow Rt 53 straight through one light (Broad St.), then straight through the next light (Sacred Heart Church on the near right corner, note do not turn right even though the sign says Commercial St).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;El Sarape is on your right in the row of buildings between this light and the next. Parking is mostly on either side of the street but should be fairly easy in the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FROM ROUTE 3 SOUTH (COMING FROM BOSTON):&lt;/b&gt; El Sarape is located on Commercial St. in Weymouth Landing. This section of Commercial St. is part of Route 53. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 17 (Union St.), which lets off onto a rotary. Get off the rotary onto Union St.(third exit you'll come to), passing the Braintree Police Station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through two traffic lights. The third traffic light is at Weymouth Landing (7-Eleven convenience store on left), don't go straight through the light but bear right onto the intersecting road (Rt 53).&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the light that comes up immediately - El Sarape is in the row of buildings on your left between this light and the next one (intersection of Front and Commercial St., Sacred Heart Church on far left corner). Parking is mostly on either side of the street but should be fairly easy in the evening.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a small place but I will be caring the Pinata!!  Ha, ha</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathy</member_name><member_id>339609</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213972536000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Because we always have fun!</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212603095000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>El Sarape!</name><id>8078062</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213741800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8078062/</event_url></item>