<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>There was a time when programming and visual design lived on opposite sides of the brain, however, in today's web 2.0 environment it's wishful thinking that coders and artists can exist in isolation. Although it's always good practice to separate business logic from presentation (can you say MVC) it is equally important (for your career) to at least become conversant in the elements of design and style? and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) is the lingua franca to which you should aspire to speak.  Neither fish nor fowl, CSS straddles the brain hemispheres to provide the tools of elegant design/web-apps while promoting the separation of presentation and business logic that we all strive for. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is CSS a mystery to you?  Do you find yourself editing your styles over and over just to get them to display correctly in IE and Firefox?  Have you created a powerful application, and want it to look nice and clean?  Do you want to take your knowledge of CSS and Design to the next level?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Michael Bourque, Director Parametric Technology Inc. (PTC), when he shows us how to make a powerful impact on end users by applying style and design through the construct of CSS.  In this session you will learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Basics of CSS&lt;br /&gt;    * Design &amp;amp; Layout&lt;br /&gt;    * Web Standards&lt;br /&gt;    * Usability Testing&lt;br /&gt;    * Tips &amp;amp; Tricks&lt;br /&gt;    * Rich Visual Behaviors&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208645326000</updated><rating><average>4.55999994278</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207592224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rescheduled April User Group:: The mystery of CSS and Design</name><id>7692458</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208385000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/7692458/</event_url></item>