<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Cathedral of the Pines is a natural sanctuary, literally a &amp;quot;cathedral without walls&amp;quot;, where all people may worship and seak spiritual renewal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dream of a Cathedral of the Pines began more than sixty years ago as a loving tribute to a son lost in battle. It is now this nation's only memorial dedicated to the honor of all men and women, military and civilian, who have given thier lives to protect our freedom and who have served to promote the cause of peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to all faiths, Cathedral of the Pines is an enduring monument to patriotic sacrifice It is also an abiding testament to the universal kinship of mankind and , above all, it is a haven for all who find peace, inspiration, and spiritual nourishment in the beauty and serenity of nature.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The memorial is located in the rolling hills of southwestern New Hampshire. It is over 200 acres of stately pine forests and formal gardens give way to panoramic views of neighboring mountains, including the most climbed mountain in the world, Grand Monadnock. This nearby 3,165 ft. peak offers extensive hiking trails and spectacular vistas that include all six New England states. Such American literary notables as Henry David Thoreau, Ralph Waldo Emerson and Mark Twain have written of the innate spirituality of these mountains and the surrounding countryside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Along with the natural, pastoral beauty of the Cathedral grounds, visitors find inspiration in its many unique stone shrines, altars, and gardens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among these is the Altar of the Nation, officially recognized by a unanimous vote of the United States Congress as a national memorial to all American war dead. All of the stones that make up the altar were donated. They come from every state and territory of the United States, and from various battlefields around the world. The Altar also includes stone tributes from every U.S. President, beginning with Harry Truman, as well as from the five-star commanders of the Army, Navy, and Air Force.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Women's Memorial Bell Tower, the only monument in the nation to specifically recognize the countless numbers of patriotic women who have sacrificed thier lves in the service to our country, is another of the Cathedral's awe-inspiring shrines. The impressive 55 foot stone tower stands atop an expansive knoll at the Cathedral's entrance. Artist Norman Rockwell created the drawings of the women who make up the bas-relief bronze tablets located over the Tower's four arches, and his son, Peter, sculpted the figures!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other shrines throughout  the Cathedral grounds include the bronze Fountain and Tree of Life, and unique stone appointments like the Mother's Chapel, the Baptismal Font, the Lecturn, the Pulpit, the Ten Commandments Monolith, and the Altar of St. Francis. All lend themselves to reflection and reverence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beautifully mainicured gardens also enhance the Cathedral's natural landscape and add to its overall sense of inner peace and tranquility. The Cathedral's cemetery, located on a hillside below the Altar or the Nation and within view of Grand Monadnock, is considered by many to be one of the loveliest spots to choose as a final resting place. The cemetery's size, however, limits it to cremated remains only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cathedral holds public services each Easter, Memorial Day, and Veteran's Day, and is open to the public daily from May through October for tours and for those who seek individual private meditation. Its facilities are available for weddings, memorial services, religious services for all faiths, and other rites, ceremonies, and special events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At various times, visitors can enjoy outdoor musical recitals that include organ meditations, church choirs, and small instrumental ensembles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cathedral's museum houses artifacts from all over the world, and the gift shop offers post cards, souveniers, and other memorabilia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yankee Magazine's &amp;quot;Travel Guide to New England&amp;quot; has included the Cathedral of the Pines as one of its top choices among the many exciting places, special attractions, and shops that are in the picturesque and historic Monadnock area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of the Pines is an all-denominational, not for profit, charitable foundation. It receives no government funding, and relies solely upon tax deductible donations and bequests for which we are deeply grateful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of the Pines is located at 10 Grassy Pond Road, Rindge, NH. 03461. Telephone number in case you get lost is 603-899-3300.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The information does not note a entrance price on this Cathedral of the Pines, however it is probably just a nominal amount to be sure to bring about $20 per person for parking, entrance and something to eat. That would be my guess.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing  a FAN sign at the entrance.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222095993000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216844683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cathedral of the Pines</name><id>8398055</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221922800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8398055/</event_url></item>