<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>121 Washington St .         </address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.823136</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.421.6969</phone><name>Local 121</name><city>Providence</city><id>835888</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415156</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Local 121 on Washington St. in downtown Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its the end of February, and what better way to begin toasting the end of the long cold winter (which can't end soon enough) and look towards spring then at Local 121?!&amp;nbsp; Amazing dark wood paneling with incredible detail grace the entire bar area, coupled with the old-world charm of herald painted stained glass windows. It is truly a feast for the eyes!  Plus the restaurant side is very trendy and known for their locally grown eclectic mix of gourmet fare and house-created drink concoctions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can it be true!!!??? We haven't been to Local 121 for an MNM since September!? Well, its high time we go!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.   &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf, but we're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299028990000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><why>This is possibly one of the most beautiful bars in Providence - its definitely worth knowing about!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298606261000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Local 121!</name><id>16697916</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298934000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/16697916/</event_url></item>