<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>475 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.367938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 894-8755</phone><name>Little India</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739937</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.237468</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lunch location: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=475%20Moody%20St%2C%20Waltham%2C%20MA" target="_blank"&gt;Little India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;475 Moody St, Waltham, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximate cost:&amp;nbsp; $18&amp;nbsp; (includes lunch, tax, tip, and $1 to support the meetup).&amp;nbsp; May be a little less depending on location.&amp;nbsp; Additional cost for anything you add from the menu (breads, beverages, chai).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the book: "In a remote town in the Himalaya, Maya tries to put behind her a time of great sorrow. By day she teaches in a school and at night she types up drafts of a magnum opus by her landlord, a relic of princely India known to all as Diwan Sahib. Her bond with this eccentric, and her friendship with a peasant girl, Charu, give her the sense that she might be able to forge a new existence away from the devastation of her past. As Maya finds out, no place is remote enough or small enough. The world she has come to love, where people are connected with nature, is endangered by the town's new administration. The impending elections are hijacked by powerful outsiders who divide people and threaten the future of her school. Charu begins to behave strangely, and soon Maya understands that a new boy in the neighbourhood may be responsible. When Diwan Sahib's nephew arrives to set up his trekking company on their estate, she is drawn to him despite herself, and finally she is forced to confront bitter and terrible truths. A many-layered and powerful narrative, by turns poetic, elegiac and comic, by the author of An Atlas of Impossible Longing."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>books on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>6571667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335135612000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326658105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April 2012 -- The Folded Earth, by Anuradha Roy</name><id>48208362</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335024000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/48208362/</event_url></item>