<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Howdy folks, I'm back.  I haven't hosted a single event in 2013 yet so while it has been nice to take some time off, it is time to get some gaming on.  And I have a new plan of attack for Mini-Meetups hopefully allowing people busy with jobs, kids, whatever get some entertainment in during their normal weekly grind so get ready.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Speaking of hosting, have YOU hosted an event lately?  It is really easy and rewarding and gives you an excuse to play the games you enjoy with awesome people.  Please check out the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/pages/Event_Hosting_Guide/"&gt;Event Hosting guide&lt;/a&gt;.  We really hope you consider giving it a try as it helps the group and the organizers out tremendously!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Now on with the show...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7 Wonders&lt;/strong&gt;, 6 players and 3 hours will be tonight's theme.  Let's meet and enjoy as many games as we can in this timeframe.  Perfect for fans of the game to scratch their itch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I am happy to include brand new players of this game at tonight's event, keep in mind, the rules can be pretty heavy and there are a lot of options you have to weigh each turn so I would advise, if you are brand new to this game, that you familiarize yourself with the &lt;a href="http://www.headlesshollow.com/downloads/games/7Wonders_v1.2.pdf"&gt;rules&lt;/a&gt; first and/or be okay with playing strategy games with a lot going on.  The game itself is pretty quick provided you know what you are doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drinks will be provided.  Please consider bringing a lite refreshment to share, and/or eating dinner prior to joining us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the location:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This event will be hosted at a private residence, conveniently located at the intersections of Route 1 and Route 95.  If you need directions, just ask.  This is a housing complex, so please do &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; park in any numbered spaces.  There are no animals on the premises and the property should be child-friendly.  Look for Unit 901 since Meetup doesn't display addresses correctly! :-(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365127324000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364767050000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: 7 Wonders</name><id>111974262</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365116400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/111974262/</event_url></item>