<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Colby Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.405510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Outside the Lines</name><city>Medford</city><id>2549401</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114464</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This is a joint event with Social Fun and several other groups.&lt;/span&gt; I will send out more detail closer to the date on what time and where we can meet.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;FREE and to the open public Art N Music event from 2PM to 10PM for Outside the Lines Studios, a nonprofit (charity) that help adults with learning disabilities to experience and create Art.. Outside the Lines Studios website is 
  &lt;a href="http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/%20"&gt;http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Located at 70 Colby Street Medford MA, inside their 10,000 Sq Feet Art warehouse, on the edge of the Tuffs Campus in Medford, a 12 -14 minute walk from Davis SQ, but still close to RT 93. There are 2 parking lots and parking for 80 cars Next door is an open ball field so we can plan outdoor games here too, like kickball and volleyball. We are expecting over 300 people to attend over the 8 hour period.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Musician/ Band Schedule&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Acts performing for 30 to 45 minutes each, times may vary. organized by Bill Brockmeyer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;2:30 PM TBD&amp;ndash; music
 &lt;br /&gt; 3:00 PM Kelly &amp;ndash; solo musician
 &lt;br /&gt; 4:00 PM Barbershop Quartet trying to get New England B-shop Quartet Social
 &lt;br /&gt; 5:00 PM John Sage &amp;ndash; solo musician - 
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/johnsagemusic"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/johnsagemusic&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 6:00 PM Musjammer Blues band &amp;amp; Stds
 &lt;br /&gt; 7:00 PM Jazz band - standards etc
 &lt;br /&gt; 8:00 PM Juro Mukai from Medford and his new Rock Band
 &lt;br /&gt; 9:00 PM Brock &amp;amp; Roll Revival
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;List of showcasing Artiest:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;1. 
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Biagio&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt; 
  &lt;strong&gt;Occhino&lt;/strong&gt; Engineer and budding Contemporary Artist from Belmont, MA now living in Burlington, MA. Displaying his Art Project called 
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Art in Every Day Objects&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/strong&gt; Which is Art from an Engineer&amp;rsquo;s viewpoint. Engineers tend to look at the world differently. They see how things work internally and the secrets behind everyday objects. Biagio decided it was time to show this hidden world to others around him and let them reflect on the complexity and Artistic side of what Engineers work on. Link to Art in Every Day objects art statement: 
  &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/950281/ART_Statement_for_Biagio.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.com/950281/ART_Statement_for_Biagio.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;2. 
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;David Barnes&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt; Photographer. His photography takes a tradition - photographing the fine art nude figure, and branches out to explore new ground. Using a variety of studio lighting techniques, his work has revolved around combining multiple figures to create one form. Over the last 10 years he has incorporated increasing levels of abstraction to a point where his current images only hint at the curves of the human body, with overlapping silhouettes against brightly colored backgrounds. Website: 
  &lt;a href="http://www.fineartfine.com/"&gt;www.fineartfine.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;3. 
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Jay Pendexter&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt; Professional artist/painter from Jamaica Plain. specializing in representational nature scenes (landscapes, seascapes, and wildlife) executed in watercolor with pencil, oil pastels, or soft pastels. His watercolors are known as &amp;ldquo;hard edged&amp;rdquo; and are usually done on cold pressed paper.( nature scenes executed in watercolors Paints and pastels) Web site: 
  &lt;a href="http://www.jayzart.com/"&gt;http://www.jayzart.com/&lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;4. 
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Jeff York&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt; Professional artist/painter Salem, MA specializing in acrylic as the media for his commercial endeavors. Acrylic paint dries fairly quickly, allows him to repaint as he works, and he finds the colors to be extraordinarily vibrant; The bulk of his paintings are cityscapes of some well-known areas in New England. I have come to use a style that he likes to simply call "bent" in which he distorts the contents of the painting. This is sort of like looking through a glass brick. It is a base of realism mixed with object distortion and sharp, eye-catching bright colors. Website: 
  &lt;a href="http://www.art-york.com/Artist.html"&gt;http://www.art-york.com/Artist.html&lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;5. 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Lelia Asher&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; Photographer from Jamacia Plain, MA 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Photography Form:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; Jewelry, Landscape, Marketing, Freelance, Graduation, Food, Fine Art, Family Portrait , Female / Women, Digital, Event, Commercial , Candid, Advertising, Architectural, Outdoor, Photo Finishing, Baby / Child, Stock, Wedding Photographers, Photo Retouching &amp;amp; Restoration, Nature 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Photography Type&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Commercial Photography, Digital Photography, Color Photography, Black &amp;amp; White Photography.&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Website: 
&lt;a href="http://www.asher-photo.com/"&gt;http://www.asher-photo.com/&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 6. 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Tania Brisson&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; a Photographer from Quincy, MA 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Photography Form:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; Nature, Places, Outdoor and People 
&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Photography Type&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Digital Photography,Color,Black+White Website: 
&lt;a href="http://www.wix.com/tania73/taniarose-photography" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wix.com/tania73/taniarose-photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;7. 
&lt;strong&gt;James &amp;ldquo;JB&amp;rdquo; Finnerty&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Colorful Outside the Lines Artist who tends to look on the bright side, although his life&amp;rsquo;s been miserable in the past.&amp;rdquo; Creates whimsical drawings - fun little drawn characters or watercolors that exude a happy spirit. As a child he was inspired to draw, in part, by the Muppets, and his artwork often references his love of Jim Henson and comics such as &amp;ldquo;Get Fuzzy.&amp;rdquo; His artwork has developed into a more abstract and symbolic style and is exploring a graffiti-like style that is uniquely his own. He associates/connects things to each other in ways that are often unexpected and unusual, and these surprising connections often require some thinking about to understand. He has a novel way of viewing the world, which is an asset for him as a visual artist. Outside the Lines Web site: 
&lt;a href="http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theartists.html"&gt;http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theartists.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;8. Tony Lake:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Outside the Lines Artist who is the creator of ovoid abstractions, often referencing self-portraits that incorporate facial features.&lt;/span&gt; His ovals are rich with layers of color that he observes in his surroundings, and the colors often reach out and interact with the surrounding space. Lake&amp;rsquo;s work has qualities that many abstract expressionist painters aspire to. His choice of color is deliberate, his language of mark making is varied and sensitive, and his pieces hold a balance, like a delicate, liquid ecosystem. Outside the Lines Artist Web site: 
&lt;a href="http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theartists.html"&gt;http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theartists.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;9. Denise Tupper&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Outside the Lines Artist whose drawings and paintings are difficult to categorize.&lt;/span&gt; They are often crude and colorfully reproduced interpretations of objects and characters with a presupposed significance or meaning &amp;ndash; from hearts and flowers to pop cultural icons from children&amp;rsquo;s books, usually Disney characters. Humor is a huge part of her personality and it comes across in most of her work. Denise makes use of an aesthetic that develops the image of its subject without the desire for realistic representation, instead using mangled, gestural lines that give a playful and sometimes subversive flavor to her work. Outside the Lines Artist Web site: 
&lt;a href="http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theartists.html"&gt;http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theartists.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;P&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;articipating Non Outside the Lines Artist&lt;/span&gt; are donating 20% of their proceeds from any Art sales to Outside the Lines Studios a Non Profit since they are letting us use their space. We plan on putting out like a donation jar / box too to collect money for Outside the Lines Studios as well.
 &lt;br /&gt;Thanks
 &lt;br /&gt;Biagio Occhino&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;From the MBTA Davis Square T Stop:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Turn right out of the station and walk up College Avenue. When you arrive at Powderhouse Square, continue straight across the Square (use the sidewalks to avoid getting struck by traffic!!) onto Warner St., Warner St. becomes Harvard St. at Boston Ave. Continue on Harvard, passing under the railroad bridge. Colby St. is the next street on your left, just after the Tufts University Science Building. Continue on Colby St, take a quick left and a quick right (this is still Colby St.)&lt;/span&gt; and walk to the very end to the big parking lot and you're here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;From the North:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Take 93 South to Exit 31 (Mystic Valley Parkway/RT.16-E) toward Revere. Turn Right at the Mystic Valley Parkway and continue on this road which becomes Harvard St. Continue on Harvard St. Take a right onto Main St. and take your 2nd left onto Bowdoin St. (just before the little market on your right) Go to the end of Bowdoin and turn righton to Colby St. Got to the end arriving at the big parking lot andyou're here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;From the South:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Take 93 North to Exit 31 (Mystic Valley Parkway/RT.16-E) Take the exit and keep to the right. You'll come to the intersection of RT. 16 and Main St.(RT.38) Take a left on to Main St. and keep to the right to continue on Main St. Continue on Main St. for about a 1/2 mile and take a right on to Bowdoin St. (just after the little market on the left) Go to the end of Bowdoin and turn right on to Colby St. Got to the end arriving at the big parking lot and you're here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Its just us inside this warehouse at 70 Colby Street Medford, MA</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313868455000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313025871000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art, Music and Games event at Outside the Lines Studios</name><id>29061101</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313863200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/29061101/</event_url></item>