<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for our regular monthly meeting where Dr. Kate Miller of Charlie's Playhouse (www.charliesplayhouse.com), joins us for an evening to discuss &amp;quot;Humanism in the Playroom: Where are the Evolution Toys?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We humanists sometimes have it rough in the toy store. Three questions about the last time you were in one: 1) How many Noah’s Ark toys did you see? 2) How many dinosaur toys did you see? 3) How many evolution- themed toys did you see?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your answers are probably something like, “1) A bunch. 2) A gazillion. 3) Zero.”  In other words, the toy industry is very happy to present history stories to kids, including religious stories and stories that include real creatures from the fossil record. And that is all good for the consumers of America. But the industry won’t – no way, not ever, not until pigs fly -- tell children the story of biological evolution. And that is not good for we humanist consumers of America, and especially not good for the next generation of humanists coming up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lack of toys is just one part of a larger cupping-of-hands over childrens’ ears when the topic turns to evolution. We are by now used to the battles over evolution in the biology classroom, but the silence extends further, to the book publishing industry, our national science standards, and even how Darwin’s bicentennial is being celebrated this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate is a mom and scientist based in Providence, RI who discovered all this a few years ago when her two young boys got interested in dinosaurs. Leaving her field of social science research on women’s reproductive health, she decided to produce and market the evolution-themed toys and games that she and her kids had made up for themselves in the playroom. She launched Charlie’s Playhouse in late 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her talk will include a discussion of the politics around evolution education, what she’s learned about the toy industry and the dinosaur-industrial-complex, how Charlie’s Playhouse got started and how it is faring, and a hands-on demonstration of her products. Bring the kids!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Through the double doors on the right.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266692629000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232585137000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Meeting - Humanism in the Playroom</name><id>9573891</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236724200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/9573891/</event_url></item>