<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In closing his 
&lt;em&gt;Tractatus Logico-Philosophicus&lt;/em&gt; Wittgenstein remarks that 
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;em&gt;"&lt;/em&gt;Wh&lt;/span&gt;ereof one cannot speak, thereof one must be silent."&amp;nbsp; Yet, as has often been remarked one suspects that, very unlike the Logical Positivists who were spawned by the publication of the 
&lt;em&gt;Tractatus&lt;/em&gt;, Wittgenstein may have harbored some mystical inclinations.&amp;nbsp; After all, being unable to speak about something does not necessarily imply a lack of substance; it may simply mean that we are unable to speak meaningfully about it, and one should not say that a dog&amp;rsquo;s barks at an intruder are without substance because it is unable to put its barks into words.&amp;nbsp; We do a lot of barking too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Perhaps Wittgenstein just didn&amp;rsquo;t want to encourage mystical barks?&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; As with everything Wittgensteinian I&amp;rsquo;m sure it is not that simple (his philosophy is far more complex than it appears; well his later philosophy anyway because the 
&lt;em&gt;Tractatus&lt;/em&gt; is overtly complex).&amp;nbsp; But the subject of this discussion concerns the barks that many of us including myself cannot resist.&amp;nbsp; Physicists will tell you that the fractional moments just after the Big Bang occurred can be conceptualized and quantified, but 
&lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; the bang...well on that subject science must consign itself to silence.&amp;nbsp; Our universe may have been spawned by other universes or by other dimensions but whatever argument is taken it seems to descend into an infinite regress that begs the question of &amp;ldquo;How did it all begin?&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;The &amp;ldquo;before the big bang&amp;rdquo; conjectures are only one example of what I am playfully calling metaphysical &amp;ldquo;barks.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; We love to bark, as much as wolves love to howl at the moon.&amp;nbsp; And, sorry dear positivists, a philosopher who is true to his questioning and angst driven core will always question the basis of those questions that defy answers.&amp;nbsp; Evolution and the questions concerning the origins of life are more fodder for probing the outer limits of thought. 
&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; As the saying goes, &amp;ldquo;What came first, the chicken or the egg?&amp;rdquo; but of course as every good evolutionist knows there is no paradox here: the 
&lt;em&gt;evolving&lt;/em&gt; chicken came first until finally (as an emergent property?) an egg emerged that would spawn a clucking chicken that we would recognize today.&amp;nbsp; But, dear Darwinians, not so fast!&amp;nbsp; Much like the Big Bangers you too cavalierly dismiss the question of First Cause, i.e. the thing that caused the Big Bang in the first place or the thing that spontaneously or non-spontaneously created the first wave or subatomic particle, the first atom, the first molecule, the first gas, liquid, solid, galaxy, sun, planet, DNA. The first cause of the universe?&amp;nbsp; The first cause of life?&amp;nbsp; Let's call these casual dismissals examples of a &amp;ldquo;Big Begging of the Question.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp; So let&amp;rsquo;s start barking.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;One of the philosophic accomplishments of Immanuel Kant was the formulation of his antinomies of pure reason.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The questions about 1) space and time, 2) atomism, 3) freedom and 4) God are, Kant argued, impossible to resolve because in each case opposite conclusions can be deductively proved, but since the thesis and the antithesis cannot both be correct certain knowledge regarding these basic questions is impossible (I make no claims here of precisely stating Kant&amp;rsquo;s argument).&amp;nbsp; So, is the philosophical contemplation of these questions meaningless and/or fruitless?&amp;nbsp; I think not.&amp;nbsp; In fact, the second antinomy shows why contemplating the inconceivable is well worth the effort.&amp;nbsp; Modern physics may not have solved the problem of whether or not all matter is ultimately composed of simple atomistic parts as, for example, quantum physics allows quanta to be both a particle and a wave, but the fact of the matter is that knowledge of the basic building blocks or non-blocks of matter are vastly more understood today than in Kant&amp;rsquo;s day.&amp;nbsp; The unrelenting research and query into these fundamental questions expands both knowledge and wisdom.&amp;nbsp; In the matter of atomism, I think that the answers to this particular question may ultimately be attainable.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Do we need to resort to Platonic forms to impose categories on our deepest contemplations?&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Again, I don&amp;rsquo;t believe so.&amp;nbsp; Rather, I would like to submit that absolute categories such as the Forms or Ideas of Plato are often counterproductive in the most metaphysical and mystical of speculations.&amp;nbsp; What we need when entertaining these realms is not the rigidity of frozen categories but the freedom of thought or free thinking that join together the philosopher, the artist and the mystic.&amp;nbsp; Yes, dear Naturalists, you too should join us!&amp;nbsp; Be unafraid of losing your terrestrial tethers and your positions will be stronger for welcoming the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;The Big Bang in its own terms may be interpreted as a temptation to engage immateriality.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;In this discussion, might we not broach a whole new method?&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Can we not ask each participant for his or her spontaneous, free thinking, creative response and thinking-outside-the-box to a question relating to the origin of life, the origin of the universe, to one of Kant&amp;rsquo;s antinomies, or to immaterial existence.&amp;nbsp; Not to worry, if we go that route, as always, it would be purely optional for each participant. Please chime in with your feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;I can already hear the barking of Mystics and Skeptics off in the distance...
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt; (Green Tea Restaurant)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the big round tables in the rear of the dining room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317657260000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314554630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Outer Limits of Thought:  Contemplating the Inconceivable</name><id>31277502</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317423600000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/31277502/</event_url></item>