<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Worcester Rd. (Rt 9 East)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.296829</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Big Papi's Grill</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1030320</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408667</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for dinner and DVD swap at the new Big Papi's Grill (partially owned by David Ortiz) on Rt. 9 in Framingham (former home of Metro 9 Steakhouse). We will be having dinner at  this new restaurant, then swapping dvd's. This is a perfect way to get a new movie without spending any money! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Big Papi's Grill has a wide menu selection including hamburgers, salads, steaks, pasta dishes and more. It is always fun to check out a new restaurant! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please no adult movies or exercise DVDs.  DVDs may be either new or used, but must be in excellent condition. Please be aware that once you swap DVDs, your original ones will not be returned to you. You can bring a few movies with you, if you would like. DVD swap is optional, you can always join us for dinner. Everyone is responsible for their own dinner/drink cost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there. If you have trouble finding our group, please call Catherine at 774 232 0000.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside ent. If need to, please call 774 232 0000</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250996138000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249537205000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and DVD Swap at new Big Papi's Grill in Framingham</name><id>11048351</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250722800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/11048351/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/global_9282182.jpeg</photo_url></item>