<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 West Main Street </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06001</zip><lat>41.810083</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-674-1561</phone><name>The Inner Space</name><city>Avon </city><id>1384886</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.831693</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Energy Healing class with Erik Harris.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class utilizes Tong Ren Therapy, Reiki, TSR, Aromatherapy, Qi Gong healing, and Tui Na Technique. We gather with the collective unconscious and use the bioelectric rhythms of the body to open up blockages allowing for healing to occur. Format of the class includes group healing, long distance healing, and individual energy work. All are welcome. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tong Ren Therapy overview &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are Guinea Pig Healing Classes?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guinea Pig classes are group-healing sessions using Tong Ren therapy. The classes typically serve sixty or more patients each session and take an average of one minute per patient. The patients are seated facing the group leader and often a group of assistants. The group leader has an interactive dialog with each patient to determine the patient's diagnosis and condition. They then determine the treatment points to be addressed for the patient and they direct their activity to accessing the collective unconscious and applying energy to the treatment points. Patient contact and even close proximity to the patient are not required. During each patient's therapy, we will typically ask the patient for his or her current condition and any sensations he or she may feel. We determine the length of time that treatment is required for each patient and then move on to the next patient.&lt;br /&gt;The Guinea Pig classes utilize Tom Tam's Healing System. The basis of energy healing is that energy removes blockages in the body that cause illness. Removal of these blockages restores the natural flow of 'Chi' energy so that the body naturally corrects itself and therefore functions properly and heals.&lt;br /&gt;In the &amp;quot;Guinea Pig&amp;quot; class, Tong Ren energy healing does not come from the practitioners alone. Master Tam believes that &amp;quot;Chi is energy, which is created in the universe and can be used to create healing.&amp;quot; This universal Chi is accessed through the collective unconscious, and our experience shows that the practitioner's belief in the effectiveness of Tong Ren healing is a key element enabling access by the practitioner to the collective unconscious.&lt;br /&gt;Based on the people who have attended class during the last three years, more then 90 percent of these people are alive and remain hopeful. Many of the patients that were considered seriously ill and hopeless have returned to living a normal life, and many patients have been able to resume their employment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What will I do in the Class?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Patients are only asked to do nothing in the class - just sit, relax and quietly receive the healing energy. There is no special diet, exercise or religious beliefs required to practice Tong Ren.&lt;br /&gt;During the class, participants are completely free to do what they want as long as they are not interfering with others. This is not a support group, however many people like to share their stories. Many people arrive early to class and talk to others or stay longer to share their experiences.&lt;br /&gt;Some people attend the class to support a friend or family member. They sit in the room, watch and listen. During the class, everyone has the right to receive or refuse the energy treatment. Several family members have taken Tong Ren training so they can continue treatment of their loved ones at home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What should I feel during the healing section of the Class?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of the patients report that they feel warmth or heat, first in their face. This warmth or heat is, according to Chinese belief, the Chi moving through the body. The Chi typically moves down from the head to the arm to the palm of the hand. Some may feel tingling in the hands or in their feet. Some people report feeling their body becoming lighter and some may feel their body becoming heavy and cannot move. All of these feelings are the Chi movement. Some times people cry in an emotional release. After they cry, most of these people can feel how much has been released.&lt;br /&gt;In the class, some of the breast cancer patients have felt their tumor shrink, soften or disappear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>erik  harris</member_name><member_id>10967674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289420273000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287083072000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tong Ren Healing Class</name><id>qvvqpynpbmb</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289347200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/15110710/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/2/b/global_12747883.jpeg</photo_url></item>