<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet at 8am at the Dunkin Donuts accross the street from the Park Street station.  The address of the DD is 127 Tremont St, corner of Park St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will participate as a team in Project Bread's 39th Walk for Hunger.  The Walk for Hunger is the oldest continual pledge walk in the country and one of the few walks dedicated to social justice. This is a 20 mile walk, but not all of us will finish it.  There are shuttle buses to bring you back to the starting point.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have registered our team on the Project Bread website.  We have a team webpage where we can make our donations (below).  There is no fee for the event, but I am suggesting a $20 donation for each participant.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must register for the walk on our page on the Project Bread site.  Here you can register for the walk, make a donation, and see how much our team has raised.  You can give the link to anyone that you are asking to make a donation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.projectbread.org/goto/meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can check out the genaral Project Bread website on the following link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.projectbread.org/site/PageServer?pagename=walk_main" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.projectbre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.projectbread.org/site/PageServer?pagename=walk_info" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plans are already in the works for the 39th Walk for Hunger! At this year's event, you will enjoy:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music at many locations along the route.&lt;br /&gt;Free snacks and juice at the halfway point. &lt;br /&gt;Health and wellness centers along the route. &lt;br /&gt;Refreshing water at all checkpoints. &lt;br /&gt;Ice cream at the end of the day. &lt;br /&gt;First aid and shuttle buses along the route. &lt;br /&gt;Facilities for your convenience. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178668839000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172631403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk for Hunger</name><id>5520826</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178452800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5520826/</event_url></item>