<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>1 Bennett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-5000</phone><name>Charles Hotel </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>744847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Social Determinants of Global Population Health&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Please read the next paragraph. Thanks. S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The morning session on the 15th (9-12:30 PM) is free and open to the public. If you would like to attend the morning session, please RSVP to Emily O'Donnell at eodonnel@hsph.harvard.edu. Seating is limited, so you must have a confirmation from us in order to attend.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The remainder of the conference is by invitation only. Invited guests should complete and submit the required registration form.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Center for Population and Development Studies&lt;br /&gt;Special Event&lt;br /&gt;Social Determinants of Global Population Health Conference&lt;br /&gt;January 15 &amp;amp; 16, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Charles Hotel, One Bennett Street Cambridge , MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Harvard Center for Population and Development Studies is pleased to host a conference entitled &amp;quot;Social Determinants of Global Population Health,&amp;quot; co-sponsored by the Harvard Center on the Developing Child, the Harvard Initiative for Global Health and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Commission to Build a Healthier America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join government officials and academic and foundation leaders from Brazil, China, India, Japan, Mexico, Uganda, United Kingdom, and the U.S. in developing tangible next steps to reducing health inequalities around the globe. This event will seek to translate public health and social science research into effective practice and policy, and represents a unique and timely opportunity to build on the recommendations in the 2008 WHO Commission on Social Determinants of Health Final Report and the 2009 Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Commission to Build a Healthier America Report. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The morning of the 15th (9:00 AM - 12:30 PM) is free and open to the public and will feature the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introduction by:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa Berkman, Director, Harvard Center for Population and Development Studies and the Thomas D. Cabot Professor of Public Policy and of Epidemiology at the Harvard School of Public Health. She is an internationally-recognized social epidemiologist whose work focuses extensively on social and policy influences on health outcomes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special address by:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julio Frenk, Dean of the Faculty and T &amp;amp; G Angelopoulos Professor of Public Health and International Development at the Harvard School of Public Health. Dr. Frenk is an eminent authority on global health who served as the Minister of Health of Mexico from 2000 to 2006. He pursued an ambitious agenda to reform the nation’s health system, with an emphasis on redressing social inequality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keynote address by:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sir Michael Marmot, Director of the International Institute for Society and Health, and MRC Research Professor of Epidemiology and Public Health, University College, London. Dr. Marmot was Chair of the WHO Commission on Social Determinants of Health from 2005 to 2008. He has led a research group on health inequalities for the past 30 years. He is Principal Investigator of the Whitehall Studies of British civil servants, investigating explanations for the striking inverse social gradient in morbidity and mortality. He leads the English Longitudinal Study of Ageing (ELSA) and is engaged in several international research efforts on the social determinants of health. He chairs the Department of Health Scientific Reference Group on tackling health inequalities. He was a member of the Royal Commission on Environmental Pollution for six years and is an honorary fellow of the British Academy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is made possible by generous gifts from Seth and Sarah Glickenhaus; Ambika Collins and Phyllis Collins; The Dillon Fund; and The Clarence and Anne Dillon Dunwalke Trust&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No organizer will be present. See message below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316506446000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262897424000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Global Health Conference</name><id>12253943</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263564000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12253943/</event_url></item>