<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>MetroWest</address_2><address_1>13 Port Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01749</zip><lat>42.386047</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 568 0561</phone><name>Riverview Restaurant at the Hudson Portuguese Club</name><city>Hudson</city><id>1124056</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.578629</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Fellow foodie, Joana, wanted to share a special luncheon deal with us. For just $23 per person, appetizers, an entree and dessert samples will be available. They will be prepared from recipes collected for the Hudson Portuguese Club cookbook, which will be on sale for an additional $20. So, purchase one if you want to try whipping up Portuguese dishes at home or buy a book or two as holiday gifts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hudsonportugueseclub.org/cookbook.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;A Taste of Hudson Luncheon Flyer&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All Yes RSVPs will be included with the reservation Joana makes with the &lt;a href="http://www.riverviewhpc.com/restaurant/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Riverview Restaurant&lt;/a&gt; located at the &lt;a href="http://www.hudsonportugueseclub.org/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Hudson Portuguese Club&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;b&gt;you will be able to pay on the day of the luncheon to the restaurant.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joana, visited the Hudson Portuguese Club earlier this year and was impressed by its beautiful view and landscaped grounds. She discovered in addition to the Riverview Restaurant the club is comprised of several function halls, a bar, a gym, outdoor patio, and even a shrine with a waterfall/river dedicated to the Lady of Fatima. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your route &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;For those who RSVP YES, please write a comment stating either:&lt;br /&gt;if you're able to offer a ride and from where&lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;if you need a ride and from where&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: &lt;br /&gt;You should find ample free parking  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough money to pay for what you consume and or purchase as well as tip and tax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If lunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant staffing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call Tonya's cell (617) 445-7549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to me, &lt;a href="http://brunchclub.meetup.com/107/members/3389565/"&gt;Tonya&lt;/a&gt; explaining your absence is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Joana will arrange for our seating which you will be directed to by the Riverview staff</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260292120000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258975409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portuguese Cookbook Luncheon</name><id>11937505</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260118800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/11937505/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/b/8/global_11953208.jpeg</photo_url></item>