<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1245 Worcester Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.299291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Limited (inside the Natick Collection, near Crate &amp; Barrel)</name><city>Natick</city><id>1119578</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.384213</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Join for a fun evening as we check out Nicole Williams appearance at The Limited. Nicole is a career expert and best selling author, Nicole Williams (appearing on The Today Show and MSN- among others). Nicole has written an ingenious book, Girl on Top, that turns dating rules into career strategies and now it's time to celebrate its arrival on bookshelves. For more info on Nicole and her book, check out: &lt;a href="http://www.nicolewilliams.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nicolewill...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As part of her nationwide Girl on Top book tour sponsored by The Limited and Elle Magazine, Nicole is hosting networking parties/runway shows in 15 cities across the United States including Natick!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s what those who RSVP for the event will receive:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - networking with professional women&lt;br /&gt;- An amazing gift bag (first come first serve, so get there on time!)&lt;br /&gt;- An exclusive 40% discount on The Limited's brand new business-chic attire (perfect for that next big meeting or interview)&lt;br /&gt;- Free-flowing Girl On Top Cocktails&lt;br /&gt;- Career advice from Nicole Williams (who couldn’t use that at a time like this?) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited, so be sure to RSVP on their site asap. Visit &lt;a href="http://girlontopbook.com/tour" target="_blank"&gt;http://girlontopbook....&lt;/a&gt; to sign up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet outside the entrance to The Limited. If you can't make it for 6pm, please look for us inside. Please come as early as you can for the gift bag! If you have trouble finding us, please call Catherine at 774 232 0000. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) at The Limited entr.  If need to, please call 774 232 0000</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259348858000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258143927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Cocktails, Free Gift Bag, Networking and Fun from "Girl on Top" author</name><id>11868408</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258498800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/11868408/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/global_9282182.jpeg</photo_url></item>