<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Roy Scott will bring his band to Pellegrini Park in Nonantum (part of Newton) for a free outdoor concert. Bring a beach blanket or lawn chair,  a box dinner/beverage if you want, insect repellent, and most of all your dancing shoes! We will meet at the site of the concert. It is sometimes also known as Pellegrini Playground.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the west: From I-95 take exit 21, Route 16. &lt;br /&gt;From east or west, follow Route 16 eastbound to the light just before the Charles River, not quite in Watertown Square. Turn left onto Watertown St.** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the east: &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 20 or 16 or take Western Ave./Arsenal St. to Watertown Square. (This is the intersection of Main St./North Beacon St./Route 20, Mt. Auburn St., Galen St., and Charles River Road. Two of these roads change names at the square. Check a map!)  From Watertown Square head west up Galen St. one block. An MBTA bus yard will be on your right. At end of bridge over the Charles River, turn right onto Watertown St. **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Soon there is a fork. Go left at the fork and follow Watertown St. until you reach Hawthorn St. Turn left onto Hawthorn St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mass Turnpike: Take exit 17. Proceed around rotary, following signs for Washington St. Follow to Adams St. Turn right onto Adams St. Follow Adams 6-7 blocks until you reach Watertown St. Turn left onto Watertown St., and in 1 block turn left onto Hawthorn.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you RSVP "yes", Sylvia will send you her cell phone number.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sylvia</member_name><member_id>4519074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marie A</member_name><member_id>4623326</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280965697000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280801802000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dancing to the Roy Scott Big Band</name><id>14299517</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280961000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/14299517/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/b/global_3153499.jpeg</photo_url></item>