<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 State St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076996</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-9715</phone><name>The Rosa Restaurant</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>260717</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.754150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our September pick for this month is The Year of the Flood by Margaret Atwood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We picked this in part b/c Ms. Atwood is coming to speak and read from this book at The Music Hall on September 21st.  Details for that event can be found here: &lt;a href="http://www.themusichall.org/calendar/event_detail.asp?eventID=970" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.themusicha...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a synopsis of the book from Barnes and Noble: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Synopsis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The long-awaited new novel from Margaret Atwood. The Year of the Flood is a dystopic masterpiece and a testament to her visionary power. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The times and species have been changing at a rapid rate, and the social compact is wearing as thin as environmental stability. Adam One, the kindly leader of the God's Gardeners a religion devoted to the melding of science and religion, as well as the preservation of all plant and animal life has long predicted a natural disaster that will alter Earth as we know it. Now it has occurred, obliterating most human life. Two women have survived: Ren, a young trapeze dancer locked inside the high-end sex club Scales and Tails, and Toby, a God's Gardener barricaded inside a luxurious spa where many of the treatments are edible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have others survived? Ren's bioartist friend Amanda? Zeb, her eco-fighter stepfather? Her onetime lover, Jimmy? Or the murderous Painballers, survivors of the mutual-elimination Painball...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More Reviews and Recommendations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The New York Times - Michiko Kakutani&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ms. Atwood has loosened up in this volume and given her imagination free rein…By focusing on her characters and their perilous journeys through a nightmare world, she has succeeded in writing a gripping and visceral book that showcases the pure storytelling talents she displayed with such verve in her 2000 novel, The Blind Assassin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Barnes &amp;amp; Noble&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Margaret Atwood's novel somehow manages to be both futuristic and primordial. Set in a post-apocalyptic age when most of humanity has been obliterated, The Year of the Flood tracks its two rare, perhaps unique female survivors. Ren, a supple young trapeze dancer who is imprisoned inside a sex, club and Toby, an ex-counter clerk who has become a follower of Adam One, the religious leader who predicted the catastrophic natural disaster. Beyond this mismatched trio are a host of bizarre walk-ons and sideshow characters, not to mention an ominous police state waiting in the wings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Publisher&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set in the visionary future of Atwood’s acclaimed Oryx and Crake, The Year of the Flood is at once a moving tale of lasting friendship and a landmark work of speculative fiction. In this second book of the MaddAddam trilogy, the long-feared waterless flood has occurred, altering Earth as we know it and obliterating most human life. Among the survivors are Ren, a young trapeze dancer locked inside the high-end sex club Scales and Tails, and Toby, who is barricaded inside a luxurious spa. Amid shadowy, corrupt ruling powers and new, gene-spliced life forms, Ren and Toby will have to decide on their next move, but they can't stay locked away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Biography&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Accomplished in equal measure as a poet, novelist, and essayist, Margaret Atwood is as much a dazzling storyteller as she is a committed feminist. Her novels and stories educate as much as they entertain, but without ever veering into dogmatism.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287009292000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280231709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup - The Year of the Flood</name><id>dphrnynmbsb</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284505200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/14226604/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/2/global_17130642.jpeg</photo_url></item>