<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Pequotsepos Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06355</zip><lat>41.363023</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Denison Homestead Museum</name><city>Mystic</city><id>1353232</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.945986</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mystic, CT – Our very own Red hosts the first Family Day will be held at the Denison Farm Market on Sunday, August 22, from 12:00 to 3:00 pm. Sponsored by the Denison Homestead and Denison Pequotsepos Nature Center (DPNC), the afternoon will be filled with fun activities focused on history, the environment, and local agriculture. From craft projects, live music and family nature hikes, to an inside look at the world of bee keeping, there will be a little fun for everyone. &lt;br /&gt;Drawing on the rich history of the Homestead, planned activities include a play area with old fashioned toys  and games, a scavenger hunt for children, and a display of herbs used during colonial times, and &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;cooking with herbs today by our cooking club members&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.  Educators from the Denison Pequotsepos Nature Center will also lead hikes of the land surrounding the Homestead.   &lt;br /&gt;The farm market is located just beyond the Denison Homestead Museum at 120 Pequotsepos Road in Mystic, CT. Parking is available adjacent to the market.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Denison Farm Market&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Denison Farm Market is host to over 18 local farmers offering local products such as jams, cheeses, homegrown USDA inspected beef, free-range eggs, heirloom herbs, local honey, a wide variety of breads and pastries, and of course an abundance of fruits and vegetables. The market is held on the fields of the Denison Homestead, surrounded by meadows and woodlands with over 8 miles of nature trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Denison Homestead&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.denisonsociety.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.denisonsoc...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Denison Homestead encompasses 200 acres of open land that was part of the original 1654 land grant to Captain George Denison, making him one of the first settlers in the Mystic area.  The 18th century farmhouse, built by Captain George’s grandson in 1717, continued as home to six generations of Denisons. In 1930, the last Denison descendant to live in the home, created a non-profit family organization, the Denison Society, and charged its members with the stewardship of the house, its contents, and the land. The house opened as a museum in 1948. Each room represents a different period of American history and tells the history of Mystic through the stories of one family. In 1946, the Denison Society also established a wildlife sanctuary on the land, still in existence today and run by the Denison Pequotsepos Nature Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Denison Pequotsepos Nature Center&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Since 1946, the Denison Pequotsepos Nature Center has provided visitors and the community with experiential science programs that further the Center’s mission:  to inspire and nurture appreciation and scientific understanding of the natural world and foster a personal environmental ethic.  DPNC serves 50,000 people each year with environmental science programs. Originally made possible through the long-term support and commitment of the Denison Society, the Nature Center is a private, not-for-profit organization funded by admission fees, memberships and contributions.  The Nature Center provides many rewarding recreational and educational opportunities on site and at nature preserves and parks throughout the region. More information about the DPNC and its programs can be found at: www.dpnc.org. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>at the herb station</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer</member_name><member_id>3917688</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282570957000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282329277000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Family Fun at the Denison Farm Market in Mystic - cooking demos by us!</name><id>14486747</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282492800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/14486747/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/8/global_17324792.jpeg</photo_url></item>