<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please read the full description from top to bottom, before you RSVP Yes.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GPS coordinates&lt;/b&gt;: 44.30222, -71.22083&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/?q=44.30222, -71.22083" target="_blank"&gt;Map of 44.30222, -71.22083&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Distance&lt;/b&gt;: 11.54 miles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation gain&lt;/b&gt;: 4836 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time&lt;/b&gt;: 8 hours and 15 minutes  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trails&lt;/b&gt;: Nineteen Mile Brook, Wildcat Ridge, Carter-Moriah, Carter Dome&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am planning on hiking these two peaks on Monday. Others are welcome to join me for both or either. The plan is to go up Nineteen Mile Brook Trail to The Wildcat Ridge Trail which takes me to Wildcat A. At this junction anyone looking for an easier hike can continue the 2/10ths of a mile on Nineteen Mile Brook Trail to Carter Notch Hut, which is open, and hang out there.  After Wildcat A I will go to the Hut, regroup with any that waited there, then we all head for Carter Dome. Anyone opting for just Wildcat A can return by Nineteen Mile Brook at this point. From Carter Dome a decison will be made to either descend by carter Dome Trail or take a slight detour to Mt. Hight, which has the best views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These trails are all reportedly broken out, except the Mt. Hight detour. Several of these trails are quite steep. Namely the Wildcat Ridge Trail to Wildcat A climbs over 1000 ft in .7 miles. Carter-Moriah Trail from hut to Carter Dome climbs 1500 feet in 1.2 miles. The Carter-Moriah Trail from Mt. Hight to Carter Dome Trail loses 600 feet in .4 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that you're late or lost.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/What_to_wear_on_a_hike/"&gt;What to wear on a hike&lt;/a&gt; and pack water and food.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy F</member_name><member_id>3324456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230826182000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230470881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Late Notice: Carter Dome with Wildcat A</name><id>9396366</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230555600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9396366/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/a/1/global_6755281.jpeg</photo_url></item>