<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-325</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>447074</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Boston Investors Main Meeting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;ROB HANNA ON TRADING EDGES FOR THE CURRENT MARKET DYNAMICS PLUS HARLAN RIEUR ON THE MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Feature Talk: Trading Edges for the Current Market Dynamics by Rob Hanna&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last November Rob gave us a tremendous, deeply researched talk. He discussed in some detail the concept of Trend vs. Chop in the market.  In this talk Rob will provide a short review of that concept.  He will also cover some new research related to Trend vs. Chop and discuss what kind of adjustments would be appropriate should the market character change back from “choppy” to “trendy”.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob will also discuss two models which can be used to help time the market.  The first is based on weekly data and looks at the lead/lag relationship between the Nasdaq and S&amp;amp;P 500.  Rob will review the Excel spreadsheet that was used to study this model and attendees can later download the spreadsheet for free from his website.  The 2nd model looks at rapid changes in the yield curve and what that has historically meant for the stock market.  With all the recent movement in the bond market it is a model that has been active lately and has produced steady opportunities for nearly 50 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Rob Hanna is a full-time market professional. He has served as president of Hanna Capital Management, LLC since 2001. From 2003 to 2007 his column “Rob Hanna’s Putting It All Together” could be found twice a week on TradingMarkets.com. In January of 2008 Rob began Quantifiable Edges. The blog and subscriber letters focus on assessing market action through indicators and history. Rob looks at price, volume, breadth and sentiment indicators. Some are well known and publicly available and others are proprietary. The frequent market studies he publishes in both his blog and newsletters help to provide a foundation for his market analysis and trading bias. &lt;a href="http://www.quantifiableedges.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for Rob's blog Quantifiable Edges.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Market Talk by Harlan Rieur&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is our regular forum for market discussion. The talk starts with a market prediction by the speaker. The speaker then makes a short case for the prediction - about 10 minutes.  The audience participation of this 30 minute talk should be 20 minutes. The discussion is lively; insights come from around the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda:&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls and Open Discussion by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;7:20 Stock Picks by Chris&lt;br /&gt;7:50 Market Talk by Harlan&lt;br /&gt;8:20 Break&lt;br /&gt;8:30 Feature Talk: Trading Edges for the Current Market Dynamics by Rob Hanna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to join our online discussion!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own decisions about investing your money. Investment ideas and recommendations made in our meetings and our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are open to the public, there is no admission fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247009012000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>76</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244691272000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors Main Meeting</name><id>10627009</id><headcount>101</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245884400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/10627009/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/5/global_9090389.jpeg</photo_url></item>