<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our venue is a few minutes' walk from the JFK/UMass stop in Dorchester on the Red Line.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Happy New Year!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This&amp;nbsp;meeting&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;(rescheduled&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;because our presenter was expressing cold-like symptoms two days before the meeting scheduled in early January) features a SPECIAL HYPNOSIS SESSION on&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;goal attainment&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;(which could be, for many of us,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;organization&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp; decluttering), utilizing the special skills of our meeting host,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Kevin Merry&lt;/strong&gt;.* We will meet in Kevin's home for about an hour and a half, until 2 pm, during which time people will be asked to remove their shoes in the event of inclement weather to protect the floors&amp;nbsp;(so bring house slippers if you wish).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin encourages each of us to &lt;em&gt;bring something&amp;nbsp;to work on&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;related to our particular goal,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;which can serve as an "anchor" for us to experience -and then recall and &lt;em&gt;re-&lt;/em&gt;experience on our own, later- the &lt;em&gt;physical sensations, cognitive experience, and emotional satisfaction&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;of &lt;em&gt;productively working toward our goal&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;following the group hypnosis&amp;nbsp;(e.g., bring "portable stuff" if your goal relates to decluttering...perhaps a pile of papers that has defied your best intentions to sort, for weeks...small enough&amp;nbsp;to fit on your lap and the floor in front of your seat, please.&amp;nbsp;If you do bring stuff to declutter,&amp;nbsp;PLEASE ALSO BRING TWO BAGS of suitable size and weight to sort your stuff into a "KEEP" and a "DISCARD" bag to take back home with you after our meeting. Nothing is to be left at the host's home, please.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the help of our host's hypnosis skills, let's focus on achieving our respective goals, share our dreams--and put our hearts, minds, and energies into realizing them in this new year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Refreshments will be provided (or bring a snack if anyone in your party has special dietary considerations). The $10 required contribution helps pay for event coordination and the organizer's monthly Meetup.com maintenance fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Kevin Merry&lt;/strong&gt;, a practicing hypnotherapist, will introduce us to a potentially powerful way to "reprogram" our lives to relatively quickly and effectively&amp;nbsp;conquer cluttered thinking for more successful, satisfying living, generally characterized by greater relaxation and better well-being. Kevin&amp;nbsp;has been practicing hypnotherapy for 15 years, having studied with renowned teacher and author Julie Griffin from The Hypnotherapy Training Company. His main focus is smoking cessation (having been a former smoker himself) and weight loss, and he has integrated relaxation hypnosis into his massage and reiki practice as well. He recently completed a course in mental coaching for golfers--and its basic principles can be applied to a broader audience. Kevin is a member of the National Guild of Hypnotists in Merrimack, New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;YOUR IDEAS for meeting topics, formats, and venues&amp;nbsp;are requested. I&lt;/em&gt;f you know others who could&amp;nbsp;benefit from our group focus, please bring them along to scheduled meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the "Suggest a New Meetup" tab here on our group's website to offer your ideas for others' consideration. (Fyi: &lt;em&gt;three registrants are required&lt;/em&gt; for any suggested meeting to be scheduled on our group's official&amp;nbsp;calendar, so invite interested friends and others to sign up for meetings that you&amp;nbsp;suggest!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since some group members have noted that they declutter most actively&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;right before expected visits,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;do consider hosting one of our future Meetups in&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;home (or work place) as an impetus&amp;nbsp;to clean and clear your space. Let me know if you could host a meetup event and we will arrange a suitable date-and&amp;nbsp;topic of special interest to you...perhaps even a subject matter expert of your choice!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Judy&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Contact the meeting's co-host to learn more</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>kevin</member_name><member_id>10254324</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328069980000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317501932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hypnosis Session for Goal Attainment</name><id>35749852</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327771800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/35749852/</event_url></item>