<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Long Sands Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>03909</zip><lat>43.144133</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207-363-2818</phone><name>York Public Library</name><city>York</city><id>807781</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.649861</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us as Isabeau Esby, internationally known psychic medium, and Dr. Joel Glenn Wixson, clinical psychologist, speak on the ideals and the realities of enlightenment.  While there have been numerous books written on the topic, what are some of the details that many are not sharing with you?  Discover the realities of the concept of enlightenment and learn of the possibilities in your own future in this nonsectarian discussion. While Isabeau brings to the table an understanding that stems from spiritual experience and visionary living, Joel brings to the table a viewpoint of enlightenment that was developed through the witnessing of countless, amazing life stories.  A question and answer session will follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Isabeau Esby resides in Portsmouth, New Hampshire.  She received a Bachelor’s Degree from the University of Minnesota with a major in Mathematics and minors in Biology and Teaching.  In addition to psychic readings, she works as a spiritual counselor and volunteers her time working with patients who are being cared for by their families in their last days of life as well as helping people to understand their own psychic abilities.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joel Glenn Wixson holds a doctorate in clinical psychology, a masters in substance abuse counseling and is a certified addiction specialist.  He is the co-founder of The Living Way, center for organic learning, has a private practice in Portsmouth, New Hampshire and is on the faculty of Leslie University’s Division of Counseling and Psychology.  He has presented and published numerous papers on various topics including substance dependance and narrative therapy.  &lt;br /&gt;Cost - Free&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lecture hall is on the lower level</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234393760000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230865232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Lecture - Psychic and Psychological Perspectives on Enlightenment</name><id>9422775</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232755200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/9422775/</event_url></item>