<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A leaf peeper's delight, the tower atop Mt Carrigain's summit provides stunning 360 degree views of the Pemi and Sandwich wilderness and beyond.  If you choose to join me, I plan on waiting a little longer and working a little harder for those views (ie we will not be having lunch on the summit).  The loop begins 2.1mi down the Sawyer River Road, a dirt road maintained by the WMNF and closed in the winter (so driving it is slower going so PLEASE plan accordingly--add an extra 10min to your drive time).   The loop begins with the Signal Ridge trail; at the fork we will go to the RIGHT on the Carrigain Notch trail. We will pass the exposed ledges of Vose Spur and the junction of the Nancy Pond trail, and wrap around to the Desolation trail.  The Desolation trail is steep and rough so more time will be taken here.  We will reach to the summit of Mt Carrigain by mid-afternoon, where we will have a well deserved break/photo opp as we have just hiked 8.5mi.  Then we continue out along the Signal Ridge trail for the remaining 5mi back to the cars.  There are several excellent vantage points along the entire loop, including hiking through a few sections of birch.  Appropriate gear for water crossings (poles, trash bags, waterproof boots etc) is recommended as there will be a few, and headlamps are recommended.  Please read the description in your guide book for more detailed trail info.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to later start time and roughness of the Desolation trail, this is an &lt;i&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/i&gt; hike, where I expect you to sign up ONLY if you are:&lt;br /&gt;(1) in great physical shape&lt;br /&gt;(2) have been consistently hiking 4000 footers&lt;br /&gt;(3) can hike the 13.5mi/3,000'+ gain while maintaining book time (8hrs 35min)&lt;br /&gt;(4) own your own White Mtn Guide or know how to research this trip on your own&lt;br /&gt;(5) assume all responsibility for your own safety (&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is hard to predict weather this far out.  This meetup is scheduled for Saturday, with Sunday as a rain date.  If the weather is foul, I will contact all 'yes' RSVP's to confirm your availability for the following day, offline.  Also, I will never start my meetups earlier than what is posted but if the group is on time and you are not, we will not wait.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DISCLAIMER: This is a social hike and I am NOT trained in wilderness safety. I merely want to hike in the company of other strong hikers for safety and fun, while getting some great exercise and enjoying the views.  &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286227024000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284242482000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Carrigain foliage hike: the longer way via the counterclockwise loop</name><id>14737003</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286024400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14737003/</event_url></item>