<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>boston</address_2><address_1>charles river</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02466</zip><lat>42.352798</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>charles river kayak</name><city>Auburndale</city><id>309616</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095833</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Our most recent outing, kayaking, was so much fun, let's do it again.  Weather permitting let's get together at Charles River Canoe and Kayak .  Friday July 6, 2007 is the date.  7:00 pm would be a good time to meet.  It's very reasonably priced, $14-16 per hour for a single kayak.  If there are more than 8 people we can get a 20% discount. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations are available for groups renting eight or more boats. Discounted rates for groups renting eight or more boats are available during off-peak hours, and peak-hour group reservations are available with a reservation fee. Examine our policy below, and please call or e-mail us to request a quote or ask questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations are Required&lt;br /&gt;Call (617) 965-5110, Monday-Friday 10am-5pm, to Reserve&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounted Group Rates (not valid noon-5pm on weekends &amp;amp; holidays)&lt;br /&gt;For groups renting eight or more boats, we offer a 20% discount off our regular rental rates. No discounts are offered on kids kayaks. &lt;br /&gt;Customized instruction is available for $120/hour or $500/day per instructor. &lt;br /&gt;One person must pay for all boats and instruction at the same time. &lt;br /&gt;A $50 deposit is required for groups renting 10 or more boats. &lt;br /&gt;No discounts are offered during our peak hours of noon to 5pm on weekends and holidays, though you can still reserve boats. See our Peak Hour policy below. &lt;br /&gt;special rates for school groups (K-12) and camps:&lt;br /&gt;when renting 8-9 boats: 20% off regular rates (except kids kayaks) &lt;br /&gt;when renting 10-14 boats: 40% off regular rates (except kids kayaks) &lt;br /&gt;when renting 15 or more boats: 50% off regular rates (except kids kayaks) &lt;br /&gt;customized instruction is available for $75/hour or $400/day per instructor &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peak-Hour Reservation Fee (noon-5pm on weekends &amp;amp; holidays)&lt;br /&gt;Peak-hour reservations are available for groups renting eight or more boats. We require pre-payment of a reservation fee of $10/boat plus a deposit equal to one hour of rental for each reserved boat. &lt;br /&gt;No discounts are available during peak hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation Policy&lt;br /&gt;Group reservations cancelled with at least 24 hours notice will receive a refund of their deposit less a $15 registration fee. &lt;br /&gt;For cancellations with less than 24 hours notice, no refunds or credits will be issued. &lt;br /&gt;Cancellations made due to weather must be made before 5pm the night before the event; customers will receive a refund of their deposit less a $15 registration fee. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;©2006 Charles River Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak&lt;br /&gt;2401 Commonwealth Avenue; Newton, Massachusetts 02466; (617) 965-5110&lt;br /&gt;paddling store - rentals - paddling school - trips &amp;amp; tours - group outings - for kids - rowing - contact - resources&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541660000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182807753000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHARLES RIVER KAYAK</name><id>5934863</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183762800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/5934863/</event_url></item>