<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:20, so let's meet inside the doors (or outside if it's nice out) of the theater BY 6:50. Please call me with any last-minute RSVPs, if you can't make it, if you're going to be late, or if you get lost: 508/308-4897. We'll head to Friday's after the movie to chat and hang out and grab some drinks and eats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Thursday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Kinda creepy, kinda actiony -- I think &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810034384/info" target="_blank"&gt;Knowing&lt;/a&gt; will be buckets of fun. Besides, I love Nic Cage. Who wants to come play?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;In 1958, as part of the dedication ceremony for a new elementary school, a group of students is asked to draw pictures to be stored in a time capsule. But one mysterious girl fills her sheet of paper with rows of apparently random numbers instead. Fifty years later, a new generation of students examines the capsule's contents and the girl's cryptic message ends up in the hands of young Caleb Koestler. But it is Caleb's father, professor John Koestler, who makes the startling discovery that the encoded message predicts with pinpoint accuracy the dates, death tolls and coordinates of every major disaster of the past 50 years. As John further unravels the document's chilling secrets, he realizes the document foretells three additional events -- the last of which hints at destruction on a global scale and seems to somehow involve John and his son. When John's attempts to alert the authorities fall on deaf ears, he takes it upon himself to try to prevent more destruction from taking place. With the reluctant help of Diana Wayland and Abby Wayland, the daughter and granddaughter of the now-deceased author of the prophecies, John's increasingly desperate efforts take him on a heart-pounding race against time until he finds himself facing the ultimate disaster -- and the ultimate sacrifice.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The usual stuff:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet inside the theater doors (or outside if it's nice out) and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.50 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers eacg for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are always welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Knowing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239748709000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238439566000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Knowing</name><id>10071626</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239318000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10071626/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>