<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ok---Ok-- SO I worked a little bit harder on this for you guys and guess what? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WE ARE IN!!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go to the web site listed below and click on the red sign up button in the upper right corner. Fill out the information and wait for your confirmation email to be sent to you- then confirm - you are signed up and  ready to participate in the event and be signed up for the prizes....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.photoshopuser.com/photowalk/city/worcester.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.photoshopu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link to see the video about this event and to see all the prizes...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE also had to create a flickr account just for this events for you to upload photos too. I will be sure you get that link too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE get your friends to join us for the day!!! Up to 50 people can join in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is some info:&lt;br /&gt;The best photo from the day (as chosen by your local walk leader) will win a copy of Scott's &amp;quot;Lightroom 2 Book for Digital Photographers&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Grand Prize&lt;br /&gt;Check out this mega prize package awarded by Scott Kelby to the single best overall photo taken from all the Photo Walk locations around the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New additions to the top prize package:&lt;br /&gt;B&amp;amp;H - A $500 Gift Card for Purchases Online or in Store&lt;br /&gt;Mpix - Two 20&amp;quot;x30&amp;quot; Color Prints/Kodak Professional Portra Endura Paper&lt;br /&gt;Peachpit - A $250 book bundle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Honorable Mentions:&lt;br /&gt;Ten Honorable Mentions chosen by Scott Kelby will receive a copy of Adobe® Lightroom® 2 (full version), provided by Adobe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. What is a Photo Walk?&lt;br /&gt;A. It's a social photography event where photographers get together, usually in a downtown area or trendy section of town, to walk around, shoot photos, and generally have fun with other photographers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. What day is this special Worldwide Photo Walk?&lt;br /&gt;A. Saturday, August 23rd, 2008- 4-6pm Two hours, from start to finish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Is the number of people in each city limited?&lt;br /&gt;A. Yup. It's limited to just 50 people per city (If groups get much bigger, it gets really hard to manage; hard to find a restaurant to hold more people, it creates crowd control problems, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Do I have to sign up in advance?&lt;br /&gt;A. Yeah, you have to let us know you're going to a part of a particular city's event by using the registration form (found right here). Don't forget to choose your city from the pop-up menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Do we have to stick together as one big group?&lt;br /&gt;A. Nope. Once the walk starts, you kind of move at your own pace, and we try to make the routes short enough so you have plenty of time for shooting and exploring along the way, and still get to the ending point on time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Are there any prizes involved?&lt;br /&gt;A. You betcha! Since this Worldwide Photo Walk is to celebrate the release of the update of the world's bestselling Lightroom book (Scott Kelby's &amp;quot;Lightroom Book for Digital Photographers&amp;quot;), the best photo from the day (as chosen by your local walk leader) will win a copy of Scott's new book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Where will these photos be posted for judging?&lt;br /&gt;A. We've asked approved leaders to set up their own flickr group, a link will be posted on each individual photo walk page to this group (by the leaders, when they set it up), so you can see the best shots from the other photo walkers in your area (and around the world).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Is there a Grand Prize?&lt;br /&gt;A. Oh man is there a grand prize!!!! Check out this mega prize package (awarded by Scott to the single best overall photo taken that day, from all the Photo Walk locations around the world. They are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Adobe CS3 Creative Suite Premium Package&lt;br /&gt;The New Adobe Lightroom 2&lt;br /&gt;Two full conference passes to the Photoshop World Conference &amp;amp; Expo&lt;br /&gt;The new Wacom 6x11 Widescreen Tablet&lt;br /&gt;A $500 Gift Card for Purchases Online or in Store at B&amp;amp;H&lt;br /&gt;From Mpix - Two 20&amp;quot;x30&amp;quot; Color Prints/Kodak Professional Portra Endura Paper&lt;br /&gt;From Peachpit - A $250 book bundle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. How should I dress?&lt;br /&gt;A. Casual, and wear comfortable shoes because you'll be walking (Hey, it's a photo &amp;quot;walk,&amp;quot; right?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Anything else?&lt;br /&gt;A. Nope, just go and spend a great day, with some great people, who love making images just like you do. :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing an orange shirt and straw cowboy hat!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219694875000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218039283000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>You're invited to join us "Worldwide Photo Walk" Worcester MA</name><id>8489583</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219521600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/8489583/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/a/global_5133674.jpeg</photo_url></item>