<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>The Pease Greeters </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03033</zip><lat>42.750433</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pease International Airport.</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1267098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.679201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome the Troops return home from overseas.&lt;br /&gt;    Friday Oct. 1ST, 1:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;    Flight arrives at 2:20 pm. &lt;br /&gt;But we need to be there, before they land.&lt;br /&gt;This is because the Pease Greeters will want to give you a tour and explain what happens.&lt;br /&gt;Also, because flights are early or late some times.&lt;br /&gt;    Pease International Airport.&lt;br /&gt;    Portsmouth / Newington NH.&lt;br /&gt;    Host: Steve O1b.   603-491-1962    ob@tds.net&lt;br /&gt;    Carpooling from Nashua and Manchester NH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Please sign up online for the Pease Greeters emails.&lt;br /&gt;   Flights are  subject to change or delay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Welcome To The Pease Greeters&lt;br /&gt;    Flight Alert Channel&lt;br /&gt;    Your source for the latest flight information updated daily.&lt;br /&gt;    Hotline (603) 766 0502&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Schedule - Flights Added, Deleted &amp;amp; Time Changes&lt;br /&gt;The schedule has been updated to include the addition of flights, the deletion of one flight and times changes to two flights.  The schedule is as follows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 10-01-10 Friday  2:20 PM  Coming Home  flight #59  # of troops returning 386 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Please join and meet Steve Obermiller and friends for an hour or two at the Pease Air Terminal. We  will welcome home about 386 returning troops, from their latest overseas tour of duty. The troops have no idea anyone is there waiting to welcome them. They are expecting just another empty airport where maybe they can get something to eat out of a machine. Flights land here for only an hour or so to refuel and change crews. Before they tack off again to return to their homes and bases throughout our country. Most of the the troops landing in NH. are not from New England. This will be their the first time they have set foot in the USA.. Most of the troops feel they are not sure yet. If they are coming home in a seat or a box until they land back in the USA.. When Steve O. returned from his oversea tours. He was welcome home the first time. The second and third times, he was given the cold treatment, and no one was there at all. So, now that we have learned to support our troops, and not to blame them for a bad war.  Steve O. would like your help in giving these brave men and women a warm New england thanks and welcome them home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Please sign up online for the Pease Greeters emails. Flights are  subject to change or delay. They will let you know where and when the flights are arriving. They will also let you know, if the flights are late or early. Most of the flights are usually on weekday nights or early morning. So, Steve O. has been reluctant to ask people to join him to welcome past flights. But, this is a weekday and not too late or too early. So, join us. Steve O. has attended this event before, and found it more than worth the time.&lt;br /&gt;    More info. below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Directions from Boston:&lt;br /&gt;    Take Interstate 95 North into New Hampshire, continuing through the Hampton Toll Booth towards Portsmouth. Take Exit 3 Portsmouth/Greenland to the stoplight. Take left onto Rt 33, at the next light you will see a sign for Pease International Tradeport, take a right at the light onto Grafton Drive.&lt;br /&gt;    Not the Air National Guard air terminal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Copyright © Pease Greeters Fund, Inc. 2010. All rights reserved&lt;br /&gt;    Contact the Postmaster at Pease.Greeters@hotmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;    To make a tax deductible donation contact Ed Johnson at (603) 964-5929 or e-mail at captedmun@aol.com. You may also mail your contributions to Pease Greeters, P O box 178, Rye Beach, NH 03871&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call us at anytime 603-491-1962 and look for the Meetup sign I will be holding.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285959330000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285874904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Welcome the Troops Home!</name><id>14954013</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285954200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/14954013/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/f/d/global_18370349.jpeg</photo_url></item>