<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for an alternative economy? Need a ride to the airport, help with your garden or a massage? &lt;strong&gt;Join Socializing for Justice for a&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;Skillshare on Time Banking in the Time Trade Circle on June 6, 6:00 - 8:30 PM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SoJust hosts events that draw progressives of all stripes that share common values but may work on different issues. We create social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections and run a Skillshare Series, hosted by The NonProfit Center*, which builds our individual capacity to make a difference in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this is a TTC Orientation, we're waiving our regular skillshare fee. &lt;br /&gt;Please donate $2 at the door to cover group expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE  &lt;br /&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing - &lt;strong&gt;bring your own dinner &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;6:30-8:30 Orientation and Q &amp;amp; A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time banking in the Time Trade Circle (&lt;span&gt;TTC&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This workshop will talk about time banking - exchanging services based on time - and tell you all about the Time Trade Circle (&lt;span&gt;TTC&lt;/span&gt;), a local time bank with 800+ members all over the greater metro-Boston and Eastern-Mass area. The workshop will explain how to join if you are interested, and forms will be available. I'll explain how time banking is different from bartering, how our local Time Trade Circle time bank works, what kinds of services people &lt;br /&gt; trade, and how members participate through their online account. &lt;a href="http://www.timetradecircle.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.TimeTradeCircle.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT OUR PRESENTER  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol Moses&lt;/strong&gt; is one of the 3 Coordinators for the Time Trade Circle.  For several years she has been running Time Trade Circle Orientations for new members and is a  huge fan of the philosophy of time banking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*&lt;a href="http://www.nonprofitcenterboston.org/site/c.ddKGIQNuEmG/b.1363373/k.5381/About_Us__Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt; - The NonProfit Center&lt;/strong&gt; is located one block from South Station at 89 South Street. The Center is accessible through the main lobby to people who have restricted physical abilities.   &lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this "Movement Moment". Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With 1750 members and 4 1/2 years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston (95+ events!), Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309018249000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304910831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Time Banking in the Time Trade Circle</name><id>17664391</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307397600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/17664391/</event_url></item>