<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This meet up is for both people new and experienced to the Boston area to discover new and interesting places to eat while meeting new people interested in American or Japanese culture.  A new restaurant will be picked every week, so please make sure to check the location.  Also please only respond to this event with a yes if you are sure you can go.  Also do to the fact that I have to make a reservation for this event, if the meet up que is full, and you decide to show up to the event, please keep in mind that we did not anticipate you and might not be able to accommodate you if the restaurant is busy.  To avoid any issues like this, please email me if you cannot sign up and I will add you to the list on my end and also contact the restaurant to make sure they can accommodate more people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also if anyone has suggestions for places they would like to go in future events please either email me, or write your suggestions down and bring them with you to the  event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week we will be starting this event off by going to an Indian restaurant in Harvard Square called Cafe of India.  I really like the Indian food here, and while the prices are higher than some restaurants, I think the atmosphere and the food make up for the cost.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will bring a sign that will be on our table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brent</member_name><member_id>6258711</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244846542000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243915996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Restaurant Sampling</name><id>10552431</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244673000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/10552431/</event_url></item>