<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We did this last year and it was the best lobster I've ever had!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afternoon kayaking in Portsmouth followed by lobster feast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 12:30 at Portsmouth Kayak and kayak for a few hours in a sheltered, low current area. You must have kayaked at least once before to rent from them, the cost is $35 for a half day ($49 for double kayaks, prices may have changed since last year). Afterwards we will go nearby for lobstah!  Chauncey Creek Lobster Pier allows you to bring your own beer of wine, so we will take advantage of that! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of the distance carpooling is encouraged.  Please offer gas$ to your driver. If you need a ride, please ask for one in the rsvp comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be renting most of their kayaks, so you should call and make a reservation. A 50% deposit is required to make reservations and there is a 48 hour cancelation policy.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Please let me know if you are coming with your own kayak.  You can park and put in there for $5.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayak info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.portsmouthkayak.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.portsmouth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;185 Wentworth Road&lt;br /&gt;Portsmouth, NH 03801&lt;br /&gt;(Located within the Witch Cove Marina)&lt;br /&gt;603-559-1000&lt;br /&gt;From Rt 95 north: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 3. At end of ramp take right onto rt 33. At second set of lights take a right. Go approx. 2mi. to the intersection of Rt 1 and go across. Proceed approx. 2mi. to the end. Take left onto rt 1A, go 1/4 mi. Take right on 1B and then 40 yards on your left, you'll find Portsmouth Kayak Adventures in Witch Cove Marina. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lobster Info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chaunceycreek.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chaunceycr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;16 Chauncey Creek Road&lt;br /&gt;Kittery Point, ME 03905&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 207-439-1030&lt;br /&gt;Chauncey's began as a working lobster pier, and in the early 1950's started selling boiled lobsters and lobster rolls to local patrons. With gradual expansion and word of mouth, Chauncey Creek Lobster Pier has become what it is today--the best and most accessible of the countless lobster pounds that dot the coast of Maine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in Kittery Point, barely an hour north of Boston, Chauncey's sits on a large deck perched on the bank above Chauncey Creek offering 42 brightly painted picnic tables, an enclosed area for inclement weather, and a postcard-perfect view across the water to the pines and back down toward Pepperrell Cove, sails and spires gleaming in the sun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Picnic hampers and ice chests are definitely part of the scene at Chauncey's as you are welcome to bring any food from home that is not offered on our menu including beer or a bottle of your favorite wine.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1248536252000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237895214000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking &amp; Lobstah!</name><id>10023105</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247934600000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10023105/</event_url></item>