<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1741 S Willow St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.953915</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-668-5557</phone><name>Barnes and Noble</name><city>Manchester</city><id>759357</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.436569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In this meeting we will take a break from deep study of texts to read a &amp;quot;short,&amp;quot; interpretative and personal book that give us the voice of a contemporary teacher. The book is &amp;quot;It's Up to You - The Practice of Self-Reflection on the Buddhist Path&amp;quot; by Dzigar Kongtrul  (2005, paperback, 129 pages, published by Shambhala - available in audio). The book has a Foreword by Pema Chodron and a Preface by Matthieu Ricard. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Its Up to You&amp;quot; is based on a series of talks by the author. According to Kongtrul, &amp;quot;These teachings are inspired by the needs and questions of my students as they work to integrate genuine practice with their lives. Although the teachings are rooted in the traditionals teachings I received from my teachers (in Tibetan Buddhism), I do not consider them traditional teachings as such. Rather, they are my own contemplations and insights. They are also intended to encourage the students to engage in joyful and honest self-reflection as a way to deepen their understanding of the spiritual path. In the end, all teachings -- traditional or informal -- have one aim: to help reduce self-importance and make room for the truth.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dzigar Kongtrul is a highly trained Tibetan Lama who became a professor of Buddhist philosophy at Naropa University in Boulder, Colorado, in 1990. He has since founded his own teaching organization Mangala Shri  Bhuti, and has established a mountain retreat center in southern Colorado, as well as a retreat center in Vermont. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284423242000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263226610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"It's Up to You - The Practice of Self-Reflection on the Buddhist Path"</name><id>12286773</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284418800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/12286773/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/5/global_1946069.jpeg</photo_url></item>