<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Harrington Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.263920</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-929-2700</phone><name>Ecotarium</name><city>Worcester</city><id>669440</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.769241</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>If it's Friday, it's Jazz at Sunset at the Eco Tarium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jazz at Sunset is one of Central Massachusetts' best ideas for kicking off your weekend! For six weeks each summer, the EcoTarium is transformed into a concert venue unlike any other. Jazz enthusiasts, young families, retirees and couples sharing a romantic picnic all rave about the unique and relaxing experience of the Jazz at Sunset series produced by the EcoTarium and WICN Public Radio. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2007 Schedule&lt;br /&gt;Concerts are on Fridays from 6:30 to 8:30 p.m. on the museum's Sundial Plaza. In case of rain or the threat of rain, concerts are held in the tent pavilion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evening Snacks&lt;br /&gt;As always, EcoTarium offers an array of delicious light dinners, snacks and beverages at all Jazz at Sunset concerts, catered by Apple Spice Junction. Beer and wine are available by the glass. Guests are welcome to pack a picnic; however, state law prohibits guests from bringing alcoholic beverages on site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Pets Policy&lt;br /&gt;Pets are prohibited at the EcoTarium. EcoTarium has many animals on exhibit and also living on the museum grounds. For their safety, we ask that you please leave your pets at home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185143764000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181173504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Larry Harlow's Latin Jazz Encounter</name><id>5862548</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184970600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/5862548/</event_url></item>