<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2500 N. River Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>43.037675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Southern New Hampshire University</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1119845</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.454030</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's enjoy a fabulous night of Far East food at the Southern NH University Culinary Institute's restaurant, the Quill.  It's run entirely by students with a once a week themed dinner on Thursday nights.  For this evening the menu will include dim sum, soups, and a variety of special dishes from the China and Southeast Asia areas.  The full menu can be viewed at &lt;a href="http://www.snhu.edu/7927.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.snhu.edu/7...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost of the dinner is $25.  A service charge of 15 percent will be added to the bill's total. The money that is generated from this service charge is directed to fund scholarships for the culinary students. Any additional gratuity goes directly to the student.  Guests are unable to place this additional gratuity on a credit card, however.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations are limited and must be made in advance.  Because seats fill up fast and a waiting list is created, I will call and make the reservations when they first open as long as I do not have to pay in advance.  If reservations must be made with a credit card, I will post an update.  Restaurant personnel cannot guarantee that parties of seven or more will be seated together. It may be necessary to divide parties of this size into separate tables.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270334101000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266548222000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at SNHU Culinary School</name><id>12644329</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270161000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/12644329/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/b/global_13187979.jpeg</photo_url></item>