<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03442</zip><lat>43.000154</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Pinkham Notch Camp</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>832702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.922233</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;If you plan to begin winter hiking or need to brush up on your skills I would strongly recommend the Winter Hiking Workshop being offered by the New Hampshire Chapter of the AMC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;This program is designed for experienced three-season hikers who are looking to extend their hiking into the winter months. They’ll teach you the basics of safe winter travel and give you informed choices for winter gear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;While you can use this event listing to get together with other randomites who are going and to coordinate car pooling, you need to officially register for this program on the AMC NH Chapter's website by clicking &lt;a href="http://amc-nh.org/committee/excursions/index-winterhikingseries.php"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This program runs on Saturday October 20 and Sunday October 21, 2012 and then there are hikes scheduled on weekends through December 22. It consists of a series of training hikes always finishes to rave reviews and great friendships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;The first Saturday session is lectures and discussions as we get to know each other and show you the necessary equipment for later in the course. Sunday we will have our first hike, rain, snow, or shine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;The first weekend is based at Pinkham Notch where lodging and food is available. It will be much more convenient if you arrange to stay at Pinkham for the first weekend. We have special reservations set up, but you must apply early to get them. We will send you the reservation information once we have quickly evaluated your application.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;It is taught by enthusiastic and knowledgeable hikers whose main goal is to have you thoroughly enjoy the winter wonderland of the high peaks while being safe and comfortable. You simply can't find a better group of instructors ... and they all volunteer their time for the love of the sport.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Along the way you'll pick up hundreds of tips and techniques garnered from thousands of hikes in New Hampshire and around the world. Normally we have to select from scores of candidates for only 20 spots, but due to a late start advertising the course, there are better chances on being accepted ... so apply quickly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;This Course gives you the training and experience to successfully and safely hike in Winter.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Topics include body heat management, footwear (boots, crampons, &amp;amp; snowshoes), energy management, nutrition, winter apparel, group dynamics, and other topics.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Starting in the mid-Fall, before you need full winter gear, it shows you what to buy and why with discussions of the advantages of various types of equipment.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;It is not necessary to buy specialized winter gear before the start of the sessions ... other than Micro Spikes or Stabilicers which are mandatory for the start of the series.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;The program costs $75 for AMC members/$85 non-members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;You must register online (&lt;a href="http://amc-nh.org/committee/excursions/index-winterhikingseries.php"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;) to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;For information and application information call or (preferably) email:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Bob Humphrey&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;(603) 456-3708 (7:00 PM – 9:00 PM ONLY)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;bobh@mcttelecom.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kaitrin</member_name><member_id>11139555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350861137000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348543245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC NH's Winter Hiking Workshop</name><id>83960602</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>129600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350730800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/83960602/</event_url></item>