<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Dance Club Singles Dances&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are a 30's plus singles dance held every Saturday &lt;br /&gt;Night @ S.A.C. Park 438 Lake St., Shrewsbury, MA &lt;br /&gt;01545.   The dance lessons begin at 7 pm and the &lt;br /&gt;dance begins at 8pm closing at 1 am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       Most nights we will have a DJ, playing top 40's from the &lt;br /&gt;70's to today. Our collection includes everything from Motown &lt;br /&gt;and the Blues to modern pop. Occasionally we will hire live &lt;br /&gt;bands, give away door prizes, and offer other special events &lt;br /&gt;that promote socializing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       We offer a complimentary, beginner friendly dance &lt;br /&gt;lesson from 7 to 8pm before the dance begins each Sat. Night.&lt;br /&gt;We will be teaching Swing, Salsa, Tango, The Cha Cha, etc... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each week will be different.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  COMPLIMENTARY DANCE LESSONS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  SPOT LIGHT DANCE COMPETITIONS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  DOOR PRIZES&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  MEET AND MAKE NEW FRIENDS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  DANCE THE NIGHTS AWAY ON THE  &lt;br /&gt;  AREAS LARGEST DANCE FLOOR&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We offer a unique environment for singles to meet, &lt;br /&gt;dance and just have fun. Our dances offer a certain &lt;br /&gt;level of class and socializing you won't find in a night &lt;br /&gt;club/meet market. Our customers dress to impress &lt;br /&gt;and are out for a casual evening of dancing and &lt;br /&gt;socializing, yet open to the possibility of finding &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;THE ONE&amp;quot;. We offer a safe and friendly atmosphere &lt;br /&gt;for singles to meet. Most of all, we have all the &lt;br /&gt;ingredients for a fun night out of the house. We &lt;br /&gt;encourage everyone to dance any way they like and &lt;br /&gt;enjoy themselves.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;THE DANCE CLUB&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 495 take the route 9 west exit and follow to Shrewsbury. Go &lt;br /&gt;left onto Lake St. (@BORDERS BOOKS). Travel 1.4 miles and we &lt;br /&gt;are on the right. Watch for the yellow  sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 290 take the route 9 east exit (Shrewsbury St.) and follow to &lt;br /&gt;Shrewsbury. Go right onto Lake St. (@ BORDERS BOOKS.) Travel &lt;br /&gt;1.4 miles and we are on the right. Watch for the yellow sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 20 turn onto Lake St. and travel .5 miles and take &lt;br /&gt;your second street on the right which is the continuation of Lake &lt;br /&gt;St. and travel .4 miles and we are on the left right.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174349337000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173700459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Dance Club Singles Dances</name><id>5561350</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174176000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/5561350/</event_url></item>