<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This walk is the most enjoyable way to visit the Great Meadows National Wildlife Refuge, which stretches more than 10 miles along the Concord River. A loop that can typically be done in one hour (but more if you stop frequently to watch wildlife, as will likely be the case), it starts on a large dike across open wetlands, and returns through a path in the woods. An observation tower will give you unobstructed views over the entire area, and a board at the trail head will indicate recent sightings to help you identify birds and other animals on your way. &lt;br /&gt;With abundant wildlife and flat terrain, this walk is also an ideal destination for visitors with children and younger kids in strollers (a 3-wheeled stroller is preferable). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the detailed directions: &lt;br /&gt;From the parking lot, you can first climb up the observation tower; then, walk past the gate and onto the main trail across the wetlands. In winter and spring, sections of the trail can be submerged, making it impassable if you have regular walking or hiking shoes; calf-high rubber boots are generally enough to cross in these conditions &lt;br /&gt;Walk down the trail until you reach the river; then turn right on the trail (the trail on the left allows you a short walk on the other side but it ends on private land) &lt;br /&gt;Follow the trail along the wetlands and turn right to enter the woods &lt;br /&gt;You soon reach a large unpaved road; take it to the right to walk back to the Refuge entrance&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210041501000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204328119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Meadows National Refuge</name><id>7435789</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209304800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/7435789/</event_url></item>