<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 6</address_2><address_1>163 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02053</zip><lat>42.147101</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 533-0669</phone><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name><city>Medway</city><id>911296</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.427202</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Power of Neutrality &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

June 5th&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30PM-8:30PM &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Cost: $10 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Presented by: Stephen Dupre &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Stephen is the Solstice Healer Share organizer and a Yuen Method practitioner. Come join Stephen and learn how the principles of neutrality can quickly improve your life condition. This will be a discussion and live demo format. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Get Neutral + No reacting = No Symptoms &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Come join Stephen and learn how the principles of neutrality can quickly improve your life condition. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This will be a discussion and live demo format. There will be time set aside for participants to pair off and work with these concepts immediately to shift themselves and others. Useful worksheets and handouts to take home will be provided. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 *Stop reacting to your own thoughts, experiences and also the energy of others around you &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 *Learn how neutrality can eliminate pains and discomfort and allow you to increase your physical potential. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * Improve your relationships, finances, career or purpose, aging worries or stresses caused by fears/phobias. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * Strengthen yourself to be neutral to any negative energy outside of you without having to use grounding or blocking techniques.&amp;gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * Use neutrality tools with any other modality to quickly identify blocks and areas to focus on &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 *Stress/Symptom elimination - not management &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Why is neutrality powerful? Neutrality means not having any reaction or emotional charge on an experience, thought or event. Neutrality is where the power is - not suppressing or avoiding our negatives or being overly positive or passionate. For example, passion often triggers negative expectations of the future, weakens our energy, and sub-consciously and non-consciously keeps us from realizing and manifesting our wants / needs and desires in our life. It is our focus on what bothers us that continues to re-create the imbalance of energy and struggle that keeps us stuck. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 RSVP if you have a meetup.com account or email Stephen at info@nowenergetics.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Solstice Healing</member_name><member_id>9244342</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370482373000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center</urlname><id>1422661</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359321430000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Power of Neutrality</name><id>qvsxgfyrgbgc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370471400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center/events/101660292/</event_url></item>