<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1360 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373419</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Au Bon Pain Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>703897</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119422</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This was so much fun last year, we're doing it again. This is a not to be missed event. Day-to-Night Block Party on Holyoke Street Music, Lights, Children&amp;rsquo;s Events, French Food, Beer Garden, And Dancing in the Street from 3:00 pm until 10:00 pm. The region&amp;rsquo;s largest Bastille Day celebration, free and open to the public, takes place on Holyoke Street There is a Summery beer garden and french food all day long Traditional waiter&amp;rsquo;s race along Holyoke Street at 5 PM (Grand Prize is Free Round Trip Jet Blue Ticket.) 8:00 pm &amp;ndash; 10 pm - Dance under twinkling lights to what the kids are listening to in the streets of Paris with DJ&amp;rsquo;s from the Boston French Party. Sandrine&amp;rsquo;s Bistro is the culinary and cultural co-host for this event and Chez Henri and Rialto will be joining them in providing traditional French Food outside on Holyoke Street for the evening! Hopefully the weather will be nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be out front of Au Bon Pain (1360 Mass Ave, Cambridge) at 6:30 pm. We'll go to a local pub and get something to eat or drink.&amp;nbsp; Then we can head over to the festival for music and dancing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link for parking at Harvard Square: &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in front of Au Bon Pain at Harvard Square</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311042300000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>48</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309828296000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bastille Day at Harvard Square</name><id>24558661</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310941800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/24558661/</event_url></item>