<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Today: A slight chance of showers between 9am and noon. Cloudy, then gradually becoming mostly sunny, with a high near 68. Northwest wind between 6 and 8 mph. Chance of precipitation is 20%.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOOKS GOOD ENOUGH...to keep the event..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK ITS NOT LOOKING GREAT OUT..BUT THIS IS NOT A long TRIP, ITS JUST PLAY IN THE LAKE, CHECK OUT THE EQUIPMENT AND CAN BE MODIFIED AT ANY TIME TO HEAD TO THE AFTER PARTY EVENT  NEARBY INCLUDING A WALK TO THE TOP OF PAINT LOOKOUT HILL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE WEAR SOME FLEECE JACKET AND POLY STUFF TO KEEP WARM IN CASE SOME WATER SPLASHES ON YOU..NO COTTON OR JEANS..IF THEY GET WET IS COLD ON YOU..OR HAVE SOME CLOTHES READY TO CHANGE INTO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is event is especially made for the Recreational and Beginner Paddlers. Experienced paddlers are welcomed and would inspire the beginners..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; All we are going to do is introduce paddling to the beginners, we can demonstrate a few rescue routines, paddle float entry, a T rescue, and maybe something else..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we paddle around the lake and see whats new on the lake.. a pretty simple ..a Get in shape thing for the next one. (most likely Eaglevill dam upstream portion, just like last year.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The other thing is to socialize on the beach and water, try out each others kayaks to see what might be a better fit to us..etc... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;There is a easy to reach boat launch right off of rte 44 in Bolton that has plenty of parking and PortoPotties at the parking lot (they should be there by then if not , Pee in the water..LOL). Further to the east on the lake is a beach area that would be an excellent place to sit in the sun eat some snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: to the boat launch.&lt;br /&gt;Rte 384 heading East to Bolton Notch &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (left part of fork) ...rte 6 is to the right &lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next light has the boat launch to the left and a church to the right. (South street intersection)&lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then its a BARBIE-Q NEARBY,&lt;br /&gt;I chose the Bolton Notch Pond area since its nice and secluded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the boat launch area , take a right and go to the tarffic light at the intersection of Quarry road and across from the Post Office and Bug Juice store ?..&lt;br /&gt;From this intersection its exactly 0.4 miles to the entrance to the rails to trails parking lot. There are no signs.. (i will most likely put a orange stryped tarffic cone there if i can)&lt;br /&gt;its really easy to miss this entrance and its angled in a hard to see way..so be on the lookout for it. its before you see the pond..&lt;br /&gt;enter the drive way, bear left past the parking area and go down the dirt road around the pond..i will be easy to spot..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;use apx between 398 and 400 Boston Turnpike, Bolton  to get you close..this isnt really a good GPS address place but for a general graphic reference for a map.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look at the picture:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/DEP/cwp/view.asp?a=2686&amp;amp;q=383780&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1620" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/DEP...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update the event details as the time gets closer.. rain ..exact time etc.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RENTAL Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;NOTE: SOME OF THE FOLLOWING KAYAKS ARE BEING REPAIRED AND MAY NEED FURTHER REPAIRS BUT SHOULD BE OK ENOUGH FOR THIS EVENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Homless Persons Bathtub= Pungo 12' with F/R floataion bags installed=  Reserved by Durelle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper &amp;amp; Dipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= BIGG BUTT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna Snake= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = Reserved by Evan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Wild Dancer= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= (bottom sealed needs testing)=?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Flat Boat= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= Alex&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 5 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used UTILL THEY ARE SEA READY, THEN ITS 15 - 20 BUCKS...LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case of any rain wind or cool cloudy weather, It might be best to wait till a better weekend.&lt;br /&gt;but i will update the last time at 10 am the day of..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be safe and bring your Personal Flotation Devices if you have some,  a whistle will let us hear you if ya fall in.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayak trailer and Stryped Orange Cones</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243274632000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240017638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking Event @  Bolton Lake With WALK &amp; Barbie-Q after at Bolton Notch </name><id>10210089</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241283600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10210089/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/6/global_3541542.jpeg</photo_url></item>