<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>So for those who have scavenger hunted with me in the past, Watson Adventures is offering us the chance to do it again, but this time, for FREE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Yep, that's right, a FREE event, but it does involve some &amp;quot;work&amp;quot; and attentiveness on your part.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who haven't hunted, Watson Adventures offers Scavenger Hunts in a variety of locations in and around Boston, that differ from the hunts of our youth in that we are gathering facts, not items (please do not uproot any statues!! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Copied directly from their newsletter, check out the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Watson Adventures will celebrate its 10th anniversary and 100,000th hunter with a day of free scavenger hunts for the general public in New York, Boston, Chicago, Los Angeles, Philadelphia, Princeton, N.J., Washington, DC, and, for the first time, San Francisco, on Saturday, April 18, 2009. On each hunt, teams of up to six people will follow clues and answer tricky, humorous questions about the objects and places they discover.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Conquer Cambridge Scavenger Hunt&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, April 18, 3 to 5:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;See the best of Cambridge and the Harvard campus while uncovering the secrets of John Harvard himself, the spot where Washington took charge of the revolution, an L-shaped bullet hole, fowl play in Radcliffe Yard, a blacksmith made famous by a poem, the pranksters of the Harvard Lampoon headquarters, the oldest poetry bookstore in the U.S., a building an artist tried to eat and more. (Please note, if you’ve already done our Munch Around Cambridge Hunt or plan to, that the Conquer Cambridge hunt has many questions in common.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET TICKETS FOR FREE HUNT DAY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;• You must have a ticket to participate in any hunt on April 18. You will receive meeting place information on your e-ticket.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;• Individuals can reserve a maximum of two tickets. Unlike on our other public hunts, participants on Free Hunt Day must agree to combining with people they don’t know to form a larger team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;• Tickets will be available from WatsonAdventures.com only. No tickets will be available by phone. Please do not call us regarding Free Hunt Day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;• First come, first served. Tickets will become available within one week of April 18. If you’d like us to alert you by e-mail when the tickets are available, sign-up via our event page on Facebook or you can sign up for our free e-mail newsletter. (Please note that signing up for the e-mail alerts or selecting “Attending” on Facebook will not guarantee you a ticket!)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May I reiterate, that tickets are required, and, unfortunately, we may not be able to sweep the Hunt Meetup style as in years past as teams may be mixed (but Meetup's all about meeting new folks, right?)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, it is up to you to stay alert and reserve tickets on your own. &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt; Tickets will be available for reserving at 10 am on April 17th off this website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://watsonadventures.com/anniversary.html#tix" target="_blank"&gt;http://watsonadventur...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm not sure where they'll be meeting but I'm guessing, based on hunts past, fairly close to our meeting spot at the Harvard Co-Op.  Although there are a ton of entrances, we'll be at the one facing Harvard Square, on Mass Ave, across from the Out-of-Town news.  If this confuses anyone, I'll be sending out my cell phone number a day or so prior so you'll be able to &amp;quot;Hunt&amp;quot; me down.  Please note we are meeting a half-hour prior to the start of the hunt so we can find each other and take the hunt by storm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to RSVP yes or maybe for now, but please plan to alter your RSVP based upon having acquired your ticket.  I'll be changing any maybe's to no's a few days prior to the event as, per Watson Adventures, tickets must be reserved in advance.  You can always change your RSVP back when you have tickets in hand.  Tickets can be reserved in pairs, so feel free to stake out a buddy from the RSVP's&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is co-posted with Social Fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email Lisa with any questions!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the alcove at the entrance facing Mass Ave and Harvard Square,</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240617413000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238084298000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Watson Adventures: Conquer Cambridge Scavenger Hunt</name><id>10041438</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240078500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10041438/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>