<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Jul 20 New York City - Teleclass - DIY Publicity and PR (8:00-9:30pm)  &lt;br /&gt;Your Home Ages:21-60 &lt;br /&gt;PAYMENT POLICY:&lt;br /&gt;$30 if pre-paid&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER AND PAY HERE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://moxiepr.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://moxiepr.eventb...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;How do you come up with an effective message for your product, yourself or you brand?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let PR Pro Jennifer Kronstain of KMG Worldwide Public Relations take you through the most effective ways to write and distribute press releases and copy as well as how to get the word out about your product or service (even if that product is YOU!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT YOU`LL DISCUSS: &lt;br /&gt;1. Why do PR? &lt;br /&gt;2. Identifying realistic goals and connecting those to your business &lt;br /&gt;3. Key tactical elements / materials needed for PR (press release, pitch, &lt;br /&gt;bios, photography, etc.) &lt;br /&gt;4. Tips on dealing with reporters and editors &lt;br /&gt;5. Social media as part of your overall PR strategy &lt;br /&gt;6. Leveraging the coverage you earn to build your business &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“KMG Worldwide Public Relations provides strategic media relations services that balance traditional and interactive tactics, keeping in mind the ever-present influence of the Internet. KMG’s senior-level associates go beyond simply communicating a story – they become an integral part of clients` overall business strategies. Our offices in New York, London and New Jersey support the following areas: Advertising, Technology (b-to-b and b-to-c), Consumer Electronics, Environmental Issues, Health and Wellness, Non-Profit. For more information, visit &lt;a href="http://www.kronstainmediagroup.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kronstainm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248394176000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialnetworking</urlname><id>251346</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246460772000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DIY (Do It Yourself) Publicty &amp; PR Writing - Teleclass</name><id>10778689</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248134400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialnetworking/events/10778689/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/a/global_9448842.jpeg</photo_url></item>