<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One First Stamford Place</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06905</zip><lat>41.062529</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 918-6910</phone><name>Hilton Stamford</name><city>Stamford</city><id>954298</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.542136</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here's a link from the Stamford Hilton website for directions &amp;amp; parking info...  Kay&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hiltonstamfordhotel.com/location_and_directions/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hiltonstam...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Mon, Oct 19, 2009 at 1:01 PM, joe markley wrote:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Folks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I spoke with the Stamford Police this morning and their plan is to put us on Greenwich Avenue at 1 Stamford Place, closing down one lane of the road to accomodate us.  It's firm enough that they were comfortable with me putting out the word.  They understand that we'll be setting up a platform and a sound system.  I'm meeting with the officer in charge at the site on Wednesday morning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Our next step may be to identify parking space for attendees.  According to the officer, the location for the rally is only a block or two from the train station, so riding in that way might be ideal for many of our people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    An update on this situation will clearly be our first priority on tomorrow night's call--also a review of the excellent Liberty Forum on Saturday, and a word on the upcoming Halloween party.  Let me know what else we need to cover.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Joe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Phone number is 605 990-0015; enter 771858638&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President Obama will be at a dinner fundraiser for Chris Dodd on Friday, October 23.  Details are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:  5 PM Friday October 23rd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:  Hilton Stamford Plaza&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;#1 First Stamford Place ( 240 Fairfield Ave , between Greenwich and Fairfield Aves.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I block west of the Stamford train station&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Protest:  Right now it is scheduled for 5pm on Friday, Oct. 23rd.  We are currently in discussions with the police to obtain a site within close proximity to the hotel.  Details on our protest site will follow as soon as they become available.  There will be a sound system and several speakers will address the gathering (including yours truly).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, everyone who can, please plan to be there and bring your signs protesting Dodd, Obama or the entire socialist agenda.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please circulate this to all those who may be interested.  More to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In liberty,&lt;br /&gt;Bob MacGuffie &lt;br /&gt;Right Principles&lt;br /&gt;www.RightPrinciples.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256504627000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255363935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Obama and Dodd in Stamford!</name><id>11608152</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256331600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/11608152/</event_url></item>