<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>297-2053</phone><name>Trinity College Life Sciences Center Auditorium</name><city>Hartford</city><id>440540</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join international film buffs as well as Spanish language speakers and learners at Trinity College's free weekly showings of Iberian and Latin American films.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's film is EL VIOLIN, Directed by Francisco Vargas (Mexico, 2004)&lt;br /&gt;Filmmaker Francisco Vargas makes his feature film debut with this expansion of his well received short film detailing the struggle between the peasants and military in 1970s-era Mexico. Don Plautarco is a dignified elder who, along with his son Genaro and grandson Lucio makes his living as a traveling musician. On the side, the trio secretly smuggles weapons and supplies to the freedom fighters who are bravely attempting to overthrow the oppressive regime. When the trio returns to their hometown to find that it has been occupied by the army in their absence and the villagers have been forced to flee, Genaro departs in hopes of salvaging their supplies while Plutarco boldly approaches the squad captain with the intention of personally recovering the ammunition on the sly. An outwardly harmless old man who convinces the captain to allow him access to the cornfields in exchange for playing music, Plutarco slowly but surely begins smuggling the ammunition back into the village on his violin case as the unsuspecting military man ravenously gorges himself into oblivion. &lt;a href="http://www.spout.com/films/282099/default.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.spout.com/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Luis Figueroa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film starts at 7:00 in the Life Sciences Building. &lt;br /&gt;For directions to Trinity, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.e.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;Or call (860) 297-2053.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For campus map, see: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.e.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can come earlier than 6:45, please join us for supper in the Cave cafeteria (basement of Mather Hall, no id required). Prices are reasonable and the food is quite good. I usually get there by 5:15.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll display a Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret Vincent</member_name><member_id>1777042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239226344000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233945031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film: El Violin</name><id>9688216</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238626800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/9688216/</event_url></item>