<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Littles Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.759810</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Spencer Perice Little Farm</name><city>Newbury</city><id>1366382</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938717</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;IPSWICH ALE FALL FEST&lt;br /&gt;Spencer Perice Little Farm&lt;br /&gt;Newbury, MA ~ 1-6pm&lt;br /&gt;Rain Date: September 19th&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let’s go join in the fun with Ipswich Ale at Spencer Peirce Little Farm some of the events going on will be a Vintage Base Ball games, beer, live music by The Orville Giddings Band, food from Ipswich Clam bake and Tennessee BBQ.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever seen a Vintage Baseball Game? Let's all go check it out together! We will learn about teams such as the cloud-hunters, stingers, daisy cutters and all there is to know about playing baseball according to 1861 rules.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be plenty of parking around the farm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is FREE, not sure if there will be a charge for the beer or any of the food, so this will be a pay as you go event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event starts at 1:00 let’s meet there at 2:00, catch a game grab a beer and listen to some music and have some fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meetup Phone:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are running late or get lost please call and we will help you. The phone number is: 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rain:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it rains this event will be cancelled, please check back for details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 to Route 113, Newburyport. Route 113 turns into Route 1A (High Road). Follow Route 1A for 3.7 miles. Turn left onto Little's Lane.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little history about Spencer Perice Little Farm:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1635-1651: Spencer Ownership: First Settlement&lt;br /&gt;John Spencer was granted a 400-acre parcel, the lion’s share of which now makes up the Spencer-Peirce-Little Farm, in 1635 as part of the first allocation of land to new settlers. He was an investor in the cattle venture that drove settlement in Newbury, and was a man of means. The town also granted him a house lot of four acres near the landing site in the Parker River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Spencer played a prominent role in the early years of the fledgling settlement, representing the town to the General Court in Boston, acting as a captain in the militia, and involving himself in a mill-building venture with friend and fellow wealthy settler Richard Dummer. In 1637, however, both Spencer and Dummer were disarmed for being supporters of Anne Hutchinson and part of a heretical sect. He left Newbury, likely intending to return, and left his property to his nephew. John Spencer died in England in 1648, and his nephew sold the property, now smaller by 100 acres, to Daniel Peirce. For more information about the Farm go to: &lt;a href="http://www.historicne.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.historicne...&lt;/a&gt;. .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in front of the Ipswich Ale booth.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284900230000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283610712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ipswich Ale Fall Fest.</name><id>14655229</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284832800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/14655229/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/f/global_17686847.jpeg</photo_url></item>