<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>91 Hampshire Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.368736</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Art &amp; Soul</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1549881</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;MBSR is an intensive training in mindfulness meditation, based on ancient healing practices, which meets on a weekly basis. Mindfulness practice is ideal for cultivating greater awareness of the unity of mind and body, as well as of the ways the unconscious thoughts, feelings, and behaviors can undermine emotional, physical, and spiritual health. The mind is known to be a factor in stress and stress-related disorders, and meditation has been shown to positively effect a range of autonomic physiological processes, such as lowering blood pressure and reducing overall arousal and emotional reactivity. The program brings meditation and yoga together so that the virtues of both can be experienced simultaneously. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The MBSR program started in the Stress Reduction Clinic at the University of Massachusetts Medical Center in 1979 and is now offered in over 200 medical centers, hospitals, and clinics around the world. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group will meet on 5 consecutive Mondays, starting April 4th at 8- 9:45pm at the Art &amp;amp; Soul Yoga: &lt;a href="http://www.artsoulyoga.com/Art_%26_Soul/Home.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.artsoulyoga.com/Art_%26_Soul/Home.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will also be a 3 hour retreat in the fourth week of the program. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please email me at 8weekmbsr@gmail.com if you have any questions about this program or visit: &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://8weekmbsr.vpweb.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://8weekmbsr.vpweb.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To register, go to: &lt;a href="http://mbsrapril2011.eventbrite.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://mbsrapril2011.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;. Your spot will not be guaranteed untill you register there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilia</member_name><member_id>1728643</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302018365000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>This class presents mindfulness meditation, breath work and yoga as critical skills for managing life’s challenges. For more information about the program, please visit: http://www.umassmed.edu/cfm/stress/index.aspx</why><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>whole-living-center</urlname><id>1384267</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Whole Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299439392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A taste of Mindfulness Based Stress Reduction ( 5 weeks)</name><id>gzwpqypgbgb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301961600000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/whole-living-center/events/16819831/</event_url></item>