<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1307 Seabright Ave</address_1><state>CA</state><zip>95062</zip><lat>36.975482</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(831) 426-8893</phone><name>Pacific Cultural Center</name><city>Santa Cruz</city><id>734615</id><country>us</country><lon>-122.008907</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join us for an Enlightening conversation and a heart opening Tantra Ritual!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt; Friday, March 27, 2009&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;7:30 pm - 10:00 pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Pacific Cultural Center&lt;br /&gt;1307 Seabright Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Santa Cruz, CA 95062&lt;br /&gt;831-426-8893&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This special Puja is designed to heal, awaken, and open your entire energy system, especially the heart Chakra of your body. This ritual is profound, educational, and a great deal of fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a Puja you will stand in a circle with other people and practice many different meditations with those in the group. Through these exercises you will gain a deep understanding of Tantric principles and practices in a safe atmosphere to assist you in going deeper in your private relationships.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Charles Muir&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt; will be speaking about Tantra Yoga, an ancient spiritual system in which sexual love is considered a sacrament and the body the temple of the spirit. Of the hundreds of Yogic paths, it is the only one that gives an alternative to celibacy. It is a path for householders, where two partners become One in an extended meditation wherein the entire body becomes an instrument of Love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The goal of Tantric practice is not just about better sex, it is about Union. It increases intimacy and connection, honoring the divine goddess in every woman, awakening and releasing female and male sexual energy to move up through you, not out of you. It is about aligning and awakening all of the Chakras.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;As our gift to you, we will be presenting each participant with their own copy of &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&amp;quot;Intro to Tantra Practices and Principles&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;, an audio CD that will get you started on your way. Plus, you can enter our drawing to win one of many educational Tantra products.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact Kerry Churchill for more information about this Puja and We would love for you to invite your friends and family!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Beginners Weekend Seminars in the Santa Cruz Mountains of California happen on a regular basis and we want you there! Visit our website, call or email Kerry for everything you need to know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Suggested Donation:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;$5-$15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Phone: 831.566.2113&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.sourcetantra.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sourcetant...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have the big smile and the blue eyes!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah Alchin, ACTE</member_name><member_id>7260814</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>YogiJamie</member_name><member_id>8132480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240022024000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Tantric Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tantrausa</urlname><id>1157501</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Tantra USA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232824360000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra Puja Intro and Mixer! </name><id>9592533</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-25200000</utc_offset><time>1238207400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tantrausa/events/9592533/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/1/global_4199313.jpeg</photo_url></item>