<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.347622</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-357-7387</phone><name>DoggieDay Playcenter</name><city>Boston</city><id>668961</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068500</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>DoggieDay has created a summer-long event to help non-profits, to raise money in order to provide services to their communities. I am currently fundraising for my American Lung Association Bike Trek, which is a 160 mile ride from Plymouth to Provincetown on Oct 4th 2009. Doggie Day is assisting me in my fundraising efforts on Sunday, September 20th for the &amp;quot;Sunday Sudz&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday Sudz is a self-bathing program for pet-owners to bring their dirty pets to the Spa @ DoggieDay and give them a bath, FREE OF CHARGE, every Sunday beginning Sunday, July 12th and continuing through Sunday, September 20th and beyond every other Sunday from 10am until 3pm.  DoggieDay has dedicated Sept. 20th to the ALA so I'm hoping you can make it. No need for reservations-just show up between 10 until 3PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DoggieDay will provide all the shampoo, brushes, towels, shammies, dryers, etc.  Participants are encouraged to make a donation to the non-profit for that day-I am asking a $10 donation or anything you can afford (I know money is tight these days).  Anyone making a donation of $10 or more will be entered into a daily drawing to win a photo-session with Dana Berenson of LaMuse Photography (valued at $250) Dana has been kind enough to donate a sitting for each week; a total of 9 weeks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;100% of the donations raised that day go directly to the American Lung Association.  I will have details on the foundation and the ride as well as door prizes and a raffle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me in this effort while giving your dog a spa treatment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't make the event and care to donate or want to join our team (it's not as difficult as it sounds-many people last year had only done 10 miles at any given time on a bike), the Boston Angels, please visit my online donation site: &lt;a href="http://www.mrsnv.com/evt/e01/part.jsp?id=2210&amp;amp;acct=8013393647&amp;amp;rid=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mrsnv.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THANKS and hope you can make it! Louie and I will be there to welcome you and your dog(s)!&lt;br /&gt;Terri&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255626528000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248319468000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Sudz at DoggieDay-to raise money for the American Lung Association</name><id>10938555</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253455200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/10938555/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/7/global_9816295.jpeg</photo_url></item>