<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This New Year is filled with hope, promise, and possibility! We are offering our support for your intentions and resolutions with this clarifying, energizing and inspiring workshop. Sally Fiore will begin the day with a healthy and realistic stretching routine , followed by a guided meditation. Rain Phillips will impart her infinite wisdom on cleansing and juicing, and share some of her sought-after secrets (not secrets any more!) on holistic health and nutrition. Then, we will stir up our &amp;quot;creative juices&amp;quot; by embarking together on a soulful and insightful writing journey. A short walking meditation on the very sacred, peaceful grounds of The Larches Inn will refresh us, then we will conclude the day by creating our own  inspiring and affirming Intention Sticks. We will finish up at about 3 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intention sticks can be embellished with sentimental treasures that represent your resolutions and goals for the coming year.  You can bring your own sentimental items, but we will have some beautiful, symbolic, treasures found in nature, along with lovely beads and shells to add to your own ornaments. Between now and the workshop date, we encourage you, (in fact, make it a quest!) to be on the lookout for interesting and meaningful finds when you are out walking. Perhaps take a trip to the beach, where you would be surprised what is thrown into your path when you are planning to create something like this! Often Mother Nature and Source give you all kinds of help to set up an Intention Stick with interesting artifacts, so much so,  that you will want to keep this one prominently displayed as a constant reminder of your goals and intentions that you have set for this New Year of growth and prosperity!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your own lunch if you require more than fruit or juice. We will also have some healthy snacks such as nuts, seeds and berries - great high energy, spirit-connecting nourishment! Looking forward to seeing you here and helping you to fulfill your visions and dreams for 2010 and beyond!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll assemble in the kitchen! </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sally Fiore</member_name><member_id>8203589</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264431860000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262802626000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Year Cleansing and Intention Workshop</name><id>12241926</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264258800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/12241926/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/7/global_10366711.jpeg</photo_url></item>