<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you ever wanted to invest in Real Estate? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now's your chance! &lt;br /&gt;The Metro West Real Estate Investors group is the best way to learn how to invest in real estate. With our hands on approach we will take you, step by step through the process of buying real estate. From how to find properties to making offers, to how to get financing. There is no obligation to attend and you do NOT have to buy Real estate to join the group. We hope that you do make the decision to invest in real estate, but that part's up to you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every Month we will look for properties and Analyze their potential.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many ways to invest in Real Estate. And while we will cover many topics in detail, it is the main focus of the Metro West Real Estate Investors group to assist investors and people looking to become investors, in finding good solid real estate investments from start to finish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn how to Invest in Real Estate by signing up today. It's fun, it's free, and could be extremely valuable!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Search for Homes that are for sale using the MLS property search.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Find investment properties that you would like to see analyzed during  the next Meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just click the link to www.ListRightRealEstate.com and go to the Property Search tab.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No registration is required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see [url=http://www.ListRightRealEstate.com]&lt;a href="http://ListRight" target="_blank"&gt;http://ListRight...&lt;/a&gt; Real Estate&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Garian</member_name><member_id>2553452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1170979886000</updated><rating><average>3.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>InvestMetroWest</urlname><id>214680</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Metro West Investors - Boston area Real Estate Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1168391455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metro West Investors. Real Estate Group February Meetup</name><id>5380017</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1170806400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InvestMetroWest/events/5380017/</event_url></item>