<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Only non-native-speakers should RSVP on this list.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Native speakers use this list:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://esl.meetup.com/76/calendar/12213178/"&gt;http://esl.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I had a conversation with a friend of mine about learning English. His first language isn't English, but he speaks it well. He'd like to speak it better, but he's found that after he reached a certain level, people stopped correcting him. He feels like he's reached a plateau and he'd like to go beyond it. After we had the conversation, I corrected him on some small things - things that I wouldn't normally mention, but he specifically said that he wanted to know where to improve. This made him happy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I'm trying an experiment.  This event is for other people like my friend - people who manage well-enough in English but would like to improve - and people like me who are happy to help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;There will be equal numbers of people who are native speakers of English and people who are non-native speakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;People will talk about whatever they want to talk about, same as at any other event, except that in addition to whatever is the topic of conversation the native speakers are also supposed to give feedback about English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;In order to ensure that there is an equal number of native speakers and non-native speakers, there are two separate RSVP lists. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I'll give people little stickers to wear, one kind of sticker for native-speakers, another kind of sticker for non-native speakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The event is at a hotel bar that typically has only a few people in it, so it should be quiet enough to have a conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a joint event with the Euro Social Meetup Group.  If you're a member of both groups, please only register with one of them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, use the link above next to &amp;quot;Who's hosting?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I sent an email to everyone in the group when I posted this event to the website.  If you want me to send it to you again, use the link above next to &amp;quot;Who's hosting?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Only non-native-speakers should RSVP on this list.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Native speakers use this list:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://esl.meetup.com/76/calendar/12213178/"&gt;http://esl.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the Cafe/Lounge. Look for the small EU flag (about 4"x6"), or ask anyone already wearing a sticker. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>A</member_name><member_id>8074607</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>13</waitlist_count><updated>1264428726000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>English Students &amp; Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>esl-76</urlname><id>55264</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston English as a Second Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262573487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drinks and English</name><id>12212129</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263690000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/esl-76/events/12212129/</event_url></item>