<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.311540</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919685</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;This weekend we are hosting events led by Father Peter Bowes, a national speaker, author, musician, priest, and mystic. On Saturday there will be a seminar entitled: You've Heard It All Before. What on earth does that mean? If you have ever thought, 'There must be more to life, to God, to spirituality, than what I've heard or seen so far', then this seminar may have some answers for you. Father Peter is a mystic and a Christian Master Teacher. His aim is to teach people how to have a real experience of God inside themselves, beyond the borders of religion. If this sounds appealing or intriguing to you, we invite you to come and see what it is about. You might go home with a new and brighter perspective.&lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna and Rev. David&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a vast difference between theory and evidence, knowledge and wisdom, concept and experience. If you have read many books about the ocean, for example, that certainly does not mean that you have been to the ocean and that you know what the ocean is like. You can not really know the ocean until you have been there and experienced it for yourself. The same holds for God. Books, concepts and theories about God can only bring you so far. They are helpful in that they can pave the way for an actual experience. But why stop there? Why stop at the temporary inspiration gleaned from other peoples experiences? Why stop at the shallow well of belief and theory? Why not learn how to dive deeply into an actual experience of God's peace and presence? This is certainly possible for everyone. This seminar will introduce you to powerful ways in which you can move steadily and smoothly into the reality of God's love, joy and acceptance that awaits you within.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A $35 donation is suggested. A light lunch will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298396089000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208838200000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: You've Heard It All Before</name><id>7787215</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209218400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/7787215/</event_url></item>