<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Many of you know that I've been doing personal growth work with the Human Awareness Institute for almost 8 years now and it has substantially changed my life. &amp;nbsp;When I began in 2003, I was in a relationship that was stifling my creativity -- my vital life force energy. &amp;nbsp;I didn't know the difference between intimacy and sex. &amp;nbsp;And although I wanted to express myself deeply and authentically, I didn't know how without fear of hurting someone. I wanted people to like me and did whatever I could to make sure they did! &amp;nbsp;Ouch!! I was living in a small box on overdrive not really knowing where to turn. &amp;nbsp;I saw a flyer on a bulletin board about a workshop that was happening the weekend of my birthday. &amp;nbsp;And I decided that was a sign....and I signed up! My life has never been the same. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a daily basis, I experience a deep satisfaction and happiness about my life, my work and my relationships with others. &amp;nbsp;I have the tools I need to create what I want in my life. I feel empowered to make changes, ease in my connections, and creative in my work and life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to feel any of these, and do not, please join me at this &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt; workshop, led by a colleague of mine, Glenn Bigonet. I will be there and will be available to support you. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover how your beliefs about love, intimacy and sexuality affect your life every day: your friendships, relationships, sexual satisfaction, health, body image, ability to find love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Human Awareness Institute workshops are about:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

* Letting go of the obstacles that are in the way of a joyful, blissful life &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;* Discovering greater depths with those you love &lt;br /&gt;

* Finding love, being honest and creating intimacy &lt;br /&gt;

* Creating the relationships you&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;* Healing from the inside out&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In this&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;mini-workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll have the opportunity to discover what it is you are missing in your life and whether a HAI workshop will support you in getting what you want in your life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;You'll have the opportunity to connect with others through verbal sharing and exercises designed to open your heart. Come and get a taste of what you&amp;rsquo;ve been craving, in a totally safe, non-sexual environment. The event is free, and the people are wonderful. All that&amp;rsquo;s missing is YOU!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The Human Awareness Institute (HAI) welcomes singles, couples, traditional and non-traditional relationships, without regard to sexual choices or preferences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;(btw, there's no hard sell at these free workshops -- you'll know if signing up is right for you and we can support you in doing that; if not, we hope that you leave with some very specific tools that will support you in moving your life forward in the way that you want it to.) &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316789611000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Tantra Practitioners/Teachers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>new-england-tantric-meetup</urlname><id>804252</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>New England Tantric Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315922081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Deepening Intimacy: Learning and Implementing the Tools</name><id>33359362</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316732400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/new-england-tantric-meetup/events/33359362/</event_url></item>