<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We've reserved the Screening room at 360 State Street for another Movie Night! Come see a film for free at this great location!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP's are limited to 18 due to theater size, so please only say "Yes" if you're pretty sure you can make it. (There should be NO Maybe's for this event.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees: I will also need your 
&lt;strong&gt;FULL NAME (and that of any +1) for the Concierge&lt;/strong&gt; to let you in to the building.&amp;nbsp; So please, when you RSVP, either place it in your comment or contact me (AJ) by meetup e-mail or text message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, enough light/fluffy/goofy stuff for now, this Events Film Is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Kingdom of Heaven - Director's Cut&lt;/strong&gt; (2005 - Historical Fiction - Rated R - 190 min.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a Ridley Scott film&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starring: Orlando Bloom, Eva Green, Marton Csokas, Liam Neeson, Ed Norton, David Thewlis, Jeremy Irons (Note: Primarily Orlando Bloom.&amp;nbsp; Those last 4 names appear in roughly 1/3-1/2 the movie each.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0320661/"&gt;IMDB Description:&lt;/a&gt; Balian of Ibelin travels to Jerusalem during the crusades of the 12th century, and there he finds himself as the defender of the city and its people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AJ's Comments:&amp;nbsp; This is one of my favorite historical fiction films.&amp;nbsp; I liked the normal version, but the directors cut is much better. (Normal DVD actually has a preface with Ridley Scott where he complains about how much FOX 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;made&lt;/span&gt; him cut.)&amp;nbsp; The film discusses themes of Religion, Morality, and Honor and how they intertwine with life decisions.&amp;nbsp; It actually takes place between the 2nd and 3rd Crusades, and while it is Fiction many of the Characters and Major Events are heavily based on Historical Record.&amp;nbsp; (Chose this film as I felt some of the themes and settings relevant to the day after the screening.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event start time is 6:45 for the social portion of the evening, so you can start showing up then. But we will not start the film until 7:30 or shortly there after. Don't plan to be any later than 7:30 though.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;Due to it's length I plan to leave little if any grace period and take a short intermission (~5-10 min.) in the middle to allow for Bio-breaks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list. As the date approaches I can add people on the waiting list if someone else backs out, provided you sent me your name for the concierge as a contingency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Snacks:&lt;/span&gt; Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just Please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Getting in:&lt;/span&gt; Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are 
&lt;span&gt;instructions near&lt;/span&gt; the call box and a bell button on it if the door is locked. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call AJ at 315-345-9348&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt; There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 7pm. (For now, this will be changing)&amp;nbsp;If you don't mind the longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evening/weekends. (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street.) 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only (Last I checked $5 daily max from 5pm on Friday through Sunday), the entrance is on State Street just to the Right of the building main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the building door, Ring the Bell Button, Concierge will Direct you. If you have more problems, call AJ at 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1315760028000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314109515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie: Kingdom of Heaven - Directors Cut</name><id>30560041</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315694700000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/30560041/</event_url></item>