<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>US-1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.579218</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chili's</name><city>Danvers</city><id>812558</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.969260</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Been a long week?  Ready to get out and have dinner with friends?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come on down to Chili's for a relaxing dinner and socialize with a great group of people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the lobby at 6:15 and be seated for a 6:30pm dinner.  We will have a relaxing dinner and find out how everyone's week has been, what's up for the long weekend and find out how hectic everyone's holiday season was.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement weather will cancel this event, if the weather is questionable, please check back on the site for any updates.  The organizers find it necessary to cancel this event due to inclement weather, we will attempt to do so at least 1 hour prior to the start time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at Chili's&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295193522000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294545153000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Dinner &amp; Conversation</name><id>15976648</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295046900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15976648/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/e/global_20678014.jpeg</photo_url></item>