<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>407 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396122</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comicazi</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1498136</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121231</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Good news Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In anticipation for the Hunger Games coming out to theaters, we are going to read the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hunger_Games"&gt;first book&lt;/a&gt; of the series by &lt;span&gt;Suzanne Collins.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Amazon synopsis: "In the ruins of a place once known as North America lies the nation of Panem, a shining Capitol surrounded by twelve outlying districts. Long ago the districts waged war on the Capitol and were defeated. As part of the surrender terms, each district agreed to send one boy and one girl to appear in an annual televised event called, "The Hunger Games," a fight to the death on live TV. Sixteen-year-old Katniss Everdeen, who lives alone with her mother and younger sister, regards it as a death sentence when she is forced to represent her district in the Games. The terrain, rules, and level of audience participation may change but one thing is constant: kill or be killed."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be meeting at Comicazi on Highland Ave in Davis Square. There is metered parking all along Highland as well as a public lot on Day Street near Redbones. There is also T access and bus connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 -Josh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edit: I talked to Comicazi and they were able to accommodate us! Hopefully people can still make the new date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: Sorry about moving the date again! There was a mix-up with myself and Comicazi as to what date was available to meet. Hope you can all still make it :-/&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the back of the store.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Josh</member_name><member_id>9704391</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329497805000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323307773000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Book Club Meeting</name><id>43770272</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329438600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/43770272/</event_url></item>