<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Haverhill Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03079</zip><lat>42.842712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-893-8300</phone><name>America's Stonehenge</name><city>North Salem</city><id>801018</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.204262</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NOTE - YOU MUST ALSO MAKE YOUR RESERVATION WITH STONEHENGE - INSTRUCTIONS ARE BELOW  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****IF THE EVENT IS FULL BUT YOU HAVE YOUR OWN SNOWSHOES AND WANT TO ATTEND, JUST COME ALONG! THE LIMIT IS ONLY BECAUSE STONEHENGE HAS A LIMITED NUMBER OF SHOES******  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just be sure to also register with Stonehenge - Please don''t wait to register. This will sell out!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Torches softly glow throughout the trail as you meander under a blanket of stars. Warm up in our toasty log cabin with complimentary hot chocolate and cookies. Reservations are Required. Snowshoe Rental is included. Trail conditions permitting.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The trail is on a gradual incline with some uneven rocky terrain. The length of the trail is 1/2 mile. Most visitors spend roughly 1 hour touring the site.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are some snow shoes available for rental on a first-to-reserve-and-show-up basis. Otherwise, you can try renting from a local place like EMS in Salem. Also, remember to dress warmly and in layers (they recommend not to wear jeans)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the tricky part: There is a fee for this event, but paid directly to Stonehenge. There is also a two step registration process.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; here.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. To Reserve a spot and snow shoes Go to: &lt;a href="http://stonehengeusa.com/CandlelightSnowshoeReservations.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://stonehengeusa....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;l... (Stonehenge's site) to reserve your spot and/or snowshoes with Stonehenge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2a. You will be asked for your name, number, and email. Then you will have to pick a date from a drop-down menu. Please be sure to pick January ...., 2011. Then you will have the opportunity to choose snowshoe rentals for each member of your party. Lastly and very importantly, there is a text box at the bottom of the screen. Enter the number of people you are making reservations for and tell them that you are part of the South Shore Hike &amp;amp; Bike Meetup Group.  Press &amp;quot;Submit Form&amp;quot; and wait for your email confirmation. That's all! We pay when we get there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fee is $15 with shoes and $10 if you bring your own.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a NO DOG policy at Stonehenge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After party - Merrill's Tavern at the Atkinson Country Club (2.5 miles from Stonehenge) Food served till 10pm. Bar open till midnight.   &lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************   &lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From their site:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Physical Address: 105 Haverhill Road Salem, NH 03079  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93   &lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 to exit 3. in NH Follow Rt. 111 east for approximately 5 miles. Watch for the American Stonehenge sign just past the North Salem Village Shops. Turn right at the Traffic lights the Gulf gas station should be on your left side at the intersection. Follow this road for 1 mile. Entrance is on the right.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM 495   &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 50 (Route 97) and follow Route 97 North. Turn right at Hampstead Road (97 Shoppes Plaza is located on right). Follow approximately 4 miles. Hampstead Road changes to Shannon Road and then to Haverhill Road. America's Stonehenge is located on the left.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate Drive Times:   &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 35 Minutes   &lt;br /&gt;Providence, RI 90 Minutes   &lt;br /&gt;Wareham, MA 105 Minutes&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295835389000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291554917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Candlelight Snowshoeing in Salem NH</name><id>15646024</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295737200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/15646024/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/5/global_20935701.jpeg</photo_url></item>