<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Séraphine&lt;/b&gt; Belgium/France 2008 121 min. Directed by Martin Provost&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Seraphine starts at 4:05&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Séraphine&lt;/b&gt; is the story of Séraphine Louis aka Séraphine de Senlis (Yolande Moreau), a simple and profoundly devout housekeeper who in 1905 at age 41, self-taught and with the instigation of her guardian angel began painting brilliantly colorful canvases. In 1912 Wilhelm Uhde (Ulrich Tukur), a German art critic and collector - he was one of the first collectors of Picasso and champion of naïve primitive painter Le Douanier Rousseau - discovered her paintings while she worked for him as a maid in his house in Senlis outside Paris. A moving and unexpected relationship develops between the avant-garde art dealer and the visionary cleaning lady leading to Séraphine’s work being grouped with other naïve painters – the so-called “Sacred Heart Painters” - with acclaimed shows in France, elsewhere in Europe and eventually at New York’s MOMA .  Martin Provost’s poignant portrait of this now largely forgotten painter is a testament to the mysteries of creativity and the resilience of one woman’s spirit.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A sleeper hit in France in the fall of 2008, &lt;b&gt;Séraphine&lt;/b&gt; went on to a surprise win of the Best Picture and Best Actress for Yolande Moreau along with five other awards at the Cesars - the French Academy Awards.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Séraphine&lt;/b&gt; is one of the most evocative films about an artist I've ever seen--and in its treatment of madness one of the least condescending. New York Magazine  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Provost and cowriter Marc Abdelnour explore the mutable boundaries between spirituality, naivete, genius, and madness, showing how the two outsiders and polar opposites cultivated a mutual understanding. Chicago Reader  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The story of Séraphine de Senlis perhaps deserves a finer film, but there is no finer actress. Moreau plays Séraphine with an understated complexity that only a truly great performer can convey—particularly with little speech to assist her. Moreau’s Séraphine is whimsical, naïve, audacious, gentle, obsessive, sincere, moody, perhaps a little slow, and deeply devout, with a child-like sense of wonder and awe and an equally child-like petulance, lack of responsibility, and secret craving for attention. &lt;b&gt;Séraphine&lt;/b&gt; is not made out to be a beatific figure of divine inspiration and disposition; she is flawed, humble, and ordinary, just as every other “extraordinary” artist, despite their massive talents, is still just ordinary. The Detroiter  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully the weather will cooperate and we will be able to discuss this film al fresco on a glorious August evening at one of the nearby restaurants -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249002885000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seraphine at Kendall</name><id>10998229</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249848000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10998229/</event_url></item>