<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In this informal hands-on craft workshop, we&amp;rsquo;ll experiment with combining text and art.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIME:&lt;/strong&gt; 1-3 p.m. (rescheduled from 2/29 due to weather).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE'LL DO:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss some principles and view examples of works ranging from illuminated manuscripts to vintage French posters to collages based on &amp;ldquo;found&amp;rdquo; text to contemporary urban graffiti.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we&amp;rsquo;ll play with different ways of merging text--including words, letters or characters , punctuation and numbers--with images and backgrounds. Feel free to bring a journal to practice in, but I'll have a selection of ATCs, 5 x 5 squares, postcard-size cards and sheets that will fit in the Sketchbook journals available as well. Or you may make ATCs on the workshop theme instead. No previous experience needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; $15.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Required&lt;/span&gt;: Scissors, a glue stick, a metal ruler if you have one (but if not, don't worry).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Recommended&lt;/span&gt;: One or more ultra-fine-point Sharpies or similar markers; a black rubber-stamp pad.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Optional&lt;/span&gt;: Paper with interesting text, such as pages from magazines, vintage books, dictionaries, textbooks; copies of old handwritten letters; foreign-language publications; sheet music. Also favorite rubber stamps of words, letters or numbers. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;If you don't have these items, don't worry: We have plenty to share&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll also supply as many backgrounds as you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LUNCH:&lt;/strong&gt; If you'd like to bring lunch or a snack to share, please feel free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to a fridge, spring water, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND&lt;/strong&gt;: Anyone--but participants must be 18+.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt; Reserve a place for yourself and any guests by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; If we need to cancel due to bad weather or other reasons, we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter through door off parking lot or front door; go up stairs to ArtStudio (unfortunately, no elevator)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331662119000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321556118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ArtStudio 360 Workshop: Text + Art (Rescheduled from 2/29)</name><id>41530702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331402400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/41530702/</event_url></item>