<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Valentine's Day is coming &amp;ndash; love is in the air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will create a sacred place to support you in opening up, feeling relaxed, and moving towards friendship and unconditional love. We hold the space for you to discover more about yourself and what you really want in life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme of this Meetup on Valentine's Day is Love, Love, Love---especially the experience of being at once the lover and the beloved. Far from being narcissistic, a deliberate practice of regular self love helps us ground, feel secure, and nourished in exhilarating ways that give us confidence, joy, extra energy, and love to share. When we take care of ourselves we are quite attractive to others.  &lt;br /&gt;If your current method of manifesting an ideal mate is not working then this workshop may be ideal for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this meeting we will dig deep to find our eternal luminous essence, the well-spring inside us that provides a never-ending source of love. We may encounter some roots, buried rocks and stones and much dirt in our search, but we will learn how to clear those away to find jewels and release the spring of love inside us.  &lt;br /&gt;We will learn how to activate and feel our chi (life force) stirring and flowing within.  &lt;br /&gt;We will notice that part of us that is totally unique and celebrate how special we are. There is no one like us! Another reason to like us! ;-)  &lt;br /&gt;We will become conscious of what contributes to a feeling of love in our bodies.  &lt;br /&gt;We will attempt to notice barriers against loving that we have built within ourselves.  &lt;br /&gt;We will taste the power of witnessing, accepting, owning, and expressing our individual truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will learn how to attract the ideal mate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." --- Anais Nin  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;"Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness, that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous? Actually, who are you not to be? Your playing small doesn't serve the world. There's nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we're liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others."  &lt;br /&gt;- Marianne Williamson  &lt;br /&gt;"Love is innocent when there is no motive in it. Love is innocent when it is nothing but a sharing of your energy. You have too much, so you share... you want to share. And whosoever shares with you, you feel grateful to him or her, because you were like a cloud - too full of rainwater - and somebody helped you to unburden. Or you were like a flower, full of fragrance, and the wind came and unloaded you. Or you had a song to sing, and somebody listened attentively... so attentively that he allowed you space to sing it. So to whomsoever helps you to overflow in love, feel grateful. Imbibe that spirit of sharing, let that become your very style of life: to be capable of giving without any idea of getting, to be capable of giving without any conditions attached to it, to be capable of giving just out of your abundance." Osho  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;Dwelling deep within our own hearts, and within the hearts of all beings without exception, is an inexhaustible source of love and wisdom. And the ultimate purpose of all spiritual practices, whether they are called Buddhist or not, is to uncover and contact with this essentially pure nature. When we have developed our own inner purity, inner compassion, and inner love, we can then see the reflection of this purity and loving kindness in others. But if we have not contacted these qualities within ourselves, we will see everyone as ugly and limited. For whatever we see everyday in outer reality is actually nothing more than a projection of our own inner reality.The existence of this deep, essentially pure nature of mind is not a matter of belief or dogma. It is a matter of experience. Countless people throughout history have discovered this great treasure of peace, love and wisdom inside themselves.&amp;rdquo; - Lama Yeshe, Introduction to Tantra&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meet up is facilitated by Bob J&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$25&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297733993000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Come together with other single people.  Have fun, learn about yourself and discover new ways to relate and connect.</why><group><who>Goddess</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>goddess-327</urlname><id>1289522</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Goddess Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294625179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Awakening the Lover Within " - Valentine's Day Event w/ Boston Tantra Meetup</name><id>15987260</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297729800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/goddess-327/events/15987260/</event_url></item>