<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Market Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.812378</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-462-7336</phone><name>Firehouse Center for the Arts</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>287736</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.874626</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;TIME:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; Meetup at 6:45&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Concert runs from 7:30 pm - 9:00pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; Free&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;LOCATION:&lt;/strong&gt; The Firehouse Center For The Arts, 1 Market St, Newburyport MA ( the concert is held Waterfront Park directly behind the Firehouse Center)
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHERE TO MEETUP:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; We are all meeting up in front of the
 &lt;br /&gt;Firehouse Center for the Arts at the bench closest to the
 &lt;br /&gt;street. As the date gets closer, I will remit my contact info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This concert is a part of Newburyport's " YANKEE HOMECOMING" series. If you haven't been, the concerts are great and VERY well-attended! If you decide to go,good spots (and parking) fill quickly! So, it's best to get there as early as possible. This&amp;nbsp; year in Newburyport, they have introduced paid parking in most areas. Let me stress that events for Yankee Homecoming are VERY well- attended. That means if you opt to go, to please keep&amp;nbsp;this&amp;nbsp;in mind. THIS IS A SHARED EVENT WITH SEVERAL OTHER MEETUP GROUPS I'VE INVITED. It's going to be a FUN night!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;**************************************************
 &lt;br /&gt;Make sure to bring a blanket or chair to sit on, insect repellent if needed and whatever else you'd like. Depending on how things go after the concert, we all may go out somewhere for drinks and food - However there is not set plan. I'm going to leave that up for decision at the time. It usually works best that way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;JAMES MONTGOMERY BLUES BAND:&lt;/strong&gt; When&amp;nbsp;blues legend James Montgomery plays the harmonica, he "brings it on home." Whether it's recording with Kid Rock, sitting in with Greg Allman, or fronting his hot band for 30 years - Montgomery plays with authority. While growing up in 
&lt;span&gt;Detroit&lt;/span&gt; he learned first-hand from the masters, James Cotton, John Lee Hooker, and Jr. Wells. - at the legendary "Chessmate." Over the years, he's carried on in the tradition and continues to be a vital presence in Blues as one of the most dynamic performers on the scene. 
&lt;a href="http://www.jamesmontgomery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;www.jamesmontgomery.com&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are all meeting up in front of the Firehouse Center for the Arts at the bench closest to the street.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312588896000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310663103000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waterfront Concert in Newburyport - James Montgomery Blues Band - multigroup</name><id>25737881</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312584300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/25737881/</event_url></item>