<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;Ian and I thought it was time to explore the mountains in Vermont for a change.  Join us for a weekend of fun in southern Vermont.  On Saturday we will hike around Griffith Lake and summit Baker Peak.  Sunday is leaders' choice, so we will decide based on how everyone feels after Saturday, but it will be a less strenuous and shorter hike. We hope you can join us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Facts:&lt;br /&gt;Length: 6.6 miles round trip to Griffith Lake&lt;br /&gt;5.6 miles round trip to Baker Peak&lt;br /&gt;Feature: Mountain, Lake&lt;br /&gt;Max elevation change: 1910 feet to Griffith Lake&lt;br /&gt;2100 feet to Baker Peak &lt;br /&gt;USGS maps: Danby Quad&lt;br /&gt;Amount of use: Moderate &lt;br /&gt;Hiking level: Moderate - Difficult&lt;br /&gt;Average hike time: 4 ½ - 5 hrs round trip    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Description:&lt;br /&gt;The Lake Trail climbs out of the Otter Creek lowlands and enters Big Branch Wilderness Area on a long switchback that eventually brings one to McGinn Brook. This brook flows out of the spectacular ravine cutting the mountain flank that can be seen from Route 7. At the McGinn Brook crossing, the Baker Peak Trail branches off to the north (left). In just short of a mile, the Baker Peak Trail meets the Appalachian/ Long Trail and ascends over bare ledges, affording fine views of the Otter Creek Valley, Dorset Mountain, and other peaks in the Taconic Mountain Range. The Lake Trail continues east, to Griffith Lake over gradual grades on an old woods road, crossed with small streams. The trail leaves the road, then crests a small hill and reaches the AT/LT junction. Head south (right) to Griffith Lake. A $5 per person/night fee, paid to the Green Mountain Club caretaker, helps maintain the shelter and trails, monitor impacts, and protect vulnerable soil, water, and vegetation. Please practice Leave No Trace ethics, such as carry out what you carry in. Trail blazing, maintenance, and signage will be minimal in Wilderness Areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Route 11/30 in Manchester, travel approximately 10 miles north on Route 7. Turn east (right) on South End Road (Forest Road 259). Follow FR 259 for about a ½ mile, past a sharp right to the trailhead parking on the left. &lt;br /&gt;From the center of Danby, travel 2.0 miles south on Rte 7, turn east (left) on South End Road (Forest Road 259). Follow FR 259 for about a ½ mile, past a sharp right to the trailhead parking on the left. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the trail head.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paula</member_name><member_id>5505578</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ian Robinson</member_name><member_id>10403736</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284423175000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281960615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Vermont You Say!</name><id>14436084</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284211800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/14436084/</event_url></item>