<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&amp;nbsp; Come join me for an easy six(six miles according to northquabbinwoods)(we think it's 8 miles) mile hike around Long Pond in Royalston, MA. We'll stop for a nice lunch break at the half-way point. This is a gorgeous trail with more hiking opportunities after if anyone is up for a bigger challenge. There are local water falls to explore as well as many other trails including the 22 mile Tully Trail which can be explored in parts or the 4 1/2 mile trail around Tully Lake which leads up to Doane's Falls.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please note: Below, this is described as a strenuous hike but it is relatively easy with some small hills. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Also if anyone wants to pack a cooler and stay for the day, there is a cookout area at the lake. Please bring your own charcoal or wood if you plan to cook. Alcohol is allowed. Please drink responsibly.....little wink goes here;-)...thanks. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; There are horseshoe pits, a volley ball area, not sure if net is set up yet and even disk golf course near the dam. BYO horseshoes, volley ball or disks. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&amp;nbsp; Please also note: This is a dog friendly hike so please feel free to bring your wonderful people friendly buddies with you(please bring a leash just in case you need one but if your dog is well behaved, I think it's okay to let them be free;-). Many dogs on the trails are free. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/130"&gt;http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/130&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A challenging 22-mile loop trail(yellow blazes)incorporating the most scenic features of the beautiful Tully area. Camping at a shelter near Royalston Falls and at Tully Lake Campground. &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;A 6-mile mountain bike loop also accessible from the campground.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 22-mile loop of the Tully Trail is the result of impressive cooperation among government agencies, private organizations (in particular, Mount Grace Land Conservation Trust), individual landowners, and volunteers. It showcases various types of land conservation - state and commercial forests, wildlife management areas, and land conserved by organizations such as The Trustees of Reservations. In addition to forests, hikers also discover wonderful wetlands - lakes, ponds, rivers, streams, waterfalls, swamps, marshes, and bogs. Ridgelines and hilltops afford spectacular views of North Quabbin valleys and further hills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail makes a broad loop around Tully Mountain, and the major trailhead is at Tully Lake Campground, where parking, restrooms, and tent sites are available. Parts of the trail allow easy or moderate hiking, but others require strenuous effort; spring and storm overflows can close parts of the trail. The trail is marked by rectangular yellow blazes and the blue-and-white Tully Trail logo. For those seeking additional challenge, the Tully Trail connects in the north to the white-blazed Metacomet-Monadnock Trail. A trail shelter at the eastern junction of the two trails is available on a first-come basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Part of the Tully Trail doubles as one arc of a strenuous six-mile mountain bike loop around Long Pond; access is also from the Tully Lake Campground.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To campground trailhead: From Athol Center take Rte 32 north. Go about 4 miles, past Tully Dam. Turn right onto Doane Hill Rd. and go about 1 mile to parking lot on right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to a website for Tully Lake:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/168"&gt;http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/168&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a maroon Monte Carlo. Parking area at Campground</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332690065000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332427477000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Long Pond(easy six mile loop)(Dog friendly)</name><id>57407352</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332599400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/57407352/</event_url></item>