<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>~~&gt;Pull way in on grass, almost to water</address_2><address_1>50 River Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.902084</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Strawberry"s  Park (Kayak Put In)</name><city>Windsor</city><id>626791</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.675758</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the last run on this section of river for the year, other sections are still going to be listed but not many.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather: ????? too soon to really believe but here is whats predicted from fryday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Sunny, with a high near 63. North wind at 7 mph becoming south. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Night: wear your cool cloths..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a simple fun trip down a river we have often paddled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For most of us, its local, its only a few hours, and we are close to Barts..&lt;br /&gt;A few of us will be at Rob&amp;quot;s Volenteer event 5 minutes away in the morning, so i chose this as an event for the day to finish  off the day with a Potluck Barbie-q and fire pit ending..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will git something to cook from the PR Store on the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Strawberry Park is our meeting spot, and we have to move cars to the take out spot for a one way paddling trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone unloads at Strawberry, Everyone drives to Barts, then a few drive us back to Strawberry,&lt;br /&gt;once paddling ends back at Barts,  some drive the people that drove us back to Strawberry, , then the PotLuck Lunch/Dinner and Barbie -q can start.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i will have the fire pit also loaded to set the environment..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok getting to Strawberry Park, the put in and meeting place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;take I 91 North to exit # 38,&lt;br /&gt;This is the exit for rte 75.&lt;br /&gt;Take a right off of the exit and go North on rte 75 toward Bradley Airport Direction,&lt;br /&gt;go 2.25 miles, cross the river bridge and the first right is RIVER STREET, go apx 1,000 feet and the Park entrance is on the right..go into the drive way around the little circle, we will be unloading in the grass a bit further into the park nearer the river..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our take out point is behind BARTS Drive In restaurant in the boat ramp area.&lt;br /&gt;This is where we can do a simple Barbie-Q and also get stuff to eat from BARTS if they are open but i want to be a bit more on the lawn area away from the ramp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok getting from Strawberry Park to Barts, &lt;br /&gt;Leave Strawberry Park, take a left onto River Street, a left onto rte 75, head toward 91, go under 91 stay on 75 for another 1.25 miles and take a left onto Pleasant Street,  (Barts is on the corner of Pleasant and Palisado)&lt;br /&gt;Barts is on the left a short ways after you go under the rail bridge underpass, pull into the boat ramp lot and we will go back to Strawberry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember and PRINT these directions....LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok bring some food, and other stuff for a short boat trip and get together after..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the grill and other acessories ready to light up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;available Kayaks are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a few kayaks available but would like a rental doughnation of 15 bucks for each one on this closer local shorter trip. It buys new paddle stuff like carbon paddles, jelly seats, and an occcasional new kayak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have enough safety equipment and paddles for the above boats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK if you know which kayak fits your paddling style and know its characteristics say so in your comments..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can only rent kayaks to full yes RSVP's..(limited carry capacity and none can be left on the trailer)..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;BACK UP PLAN ~~&amp;gt;IF THERE IS NO DAM RELEASE WE GO TO RAINBOW RES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Release is planned for 1:00 pm or before, but depends on stored capacity and rain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blonde Necky Eliza, Short sea kayak 16' with one of the paddles in the bucket= SUSANNE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub Pungo 12' with flotation bags installed, Recreational Kayak with Carbon Kalista 230 strait w/ small shaft dia Paddle= =DEBBIE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper Riot Tourlite 15', Short Sea Kayak , w/JUNK  Paddle= AL-R&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bananna Yellow Cobra Expidition SOT 18' , Long SOT Sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista 230 bent &amp;amp; small shaft dia Paddle= = ALEX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyline Wind Dancer 18', Long sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista 220 bent w/ small shaft dia Paddle= JACKIE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red NDK Greenlander Pro 18' , Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Camano 220 Fiberglass or Wood Greenland Paddle= KIM O&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya all there,&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the ORANGE HUNTING HAT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255193462000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250710195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>- KAYAK EVENT-- STRAWBERRY Park &amp; BARTS @ Farmington River, &amp; POTLUCK BARBIE-Q</name><id>11150361</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253984400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/11150361/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/3/global_2851763.jpeg</photo_url></item>