<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festival sounds like a lot of fun. My family and I will be there. &lt;br /&gt;Katya Taradai&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is the info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Website: Edaville USA National Cranberry Festival&lt;br /&gt;Occurs at: Edaville USA&lt;br /&gt;Location: 7 Eda Avenue, Carver, MA, 02336 directions&lt;br /&gt;Phone:(877) EDAVILLE&lt;br /&gt;Date: Saturday, October 10, 2009 - Monday, October 12, 2009&lt;br /&gt;In/Outdoor: Outdoor&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $$ see below&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the colorful fall foliage and annual cranberry harvest during the National Cranberry Festival™at Edaville USA. The Festival features vendors selling cranberry-related items, entertainment, craft fairs, plus all the exciting attractions Edaville USA has to offer. A perfect outing for the entire family. Fireworks on October 10th at 8:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cranberry Festival has been a family tradition for more than 40 years. Take a trip on the 5 1/2 mile Edaville Railroad through the 1300 acre cranberry plantation. Enjoy narrated bog tours during the height of the cranberry harvest season. Learn about the growing, harvesting and processing while riding alongside a bog as it is harvested. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit Cranberry World Museum sponsored by Ocean Spray and taste different types of Ocean Spray products. Enjoy plentiful cranberry-related foods, crafts and recipes throughout the family fun park. Take in the live entertainment and activities that will be featured every day of the festival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Train Departure Times:&lt;br /&gt;First train leaves at 11:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;Last train leaves at 4:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Katya</member_name><member_id>7009032</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256247618000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Russian Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>expatrussian-64</urlname><id>1112191</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Families with Russian Kids, Moms Club, Playgroups</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254246716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cranberry festival, Carver, MA - October 10, 2009. </name><id>11499306</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255183200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/expatrussian-64/events/11499306/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/1/global_3820625.jpeg</photo_url></item>