<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>About 6 miles north of Jackson &amp; south of Glen Boulder trail</address_2><address_1>Rte 16 south of Pinkham Notch</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03846</zip><lat>44.205025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rocky Branch Trailhead Parking Lot</name><city>Jackson</city><id>292583</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.226112</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I really enjoyed doing this as an overnight backpack  and staying in the shelter vs a long daytrip.  I work Saturday moring, but there is enough daylight hours to hike in the afternoon, camp and hike out the next day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a Sunday dayhike has been posted separately for those who want a dayhike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAMPOUT: There is a 3 sided shelter at Rocky Branch #2 and tent spaces.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP and list if you want to camp Saturday night. communcations are very important for campouts, so make sure your phone # is listed so we can talk to you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Fair weather only, Rocky branch trail isn't nice when wet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having fun is mandatory, the summit is optional.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The AMC lists the following for Mt Isolation.  Rocky Branch Trailhead Parking Lot&lt;br /&gt;Rte 16 south of Pinkham Notch About 6 miles north of Jackson &amp;amp; south of Glen Boulder trail&lt;br /&gt;Jackson, NH 03846&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;@ 14.6 miles via Rocky Branch Trail, Isolation Trail, Davis Path &lt;br /&gt;@ 3,400 feet elevation gain&lt;br /&gt;AMC 9:00 book time excluding stops and water challenges.  My pace is slower than this so add time and enjoy the trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;3:30 pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  starting at Rocky Branch Trailhead - northeast&lt;br /&gt;entering wilderness area hike 3.70 mi/2 hr 51 min/+1557 ft on the Rocky Branch Trail&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;At the northeast terminus, on NH 16 below Pinkham Notch, the trail leaves the north end of the parking lot (avoid a gravel road that branches left just below the parking lot) and climbs moderately by switchbacks on an old logging road. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Avalanche Brook Ski Trail enters from the left and leaves on the right. Then the trail swings left, away from the bank of a small brook, and continues to ascend, then turns sharp left and follows an old, very straight road on a slight downhill grade. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After about 0.5 mi. on this road, it swings gradually right and climbs moderately, following a brook part of the way, and reaches the Presidential Range–Dry River Wilderness boundary just east of the ridge top. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Passing the almost imperceptible height-of-land, the trail follows a short bypass to the left of a very wet area and runs almost level, then descends easily, with small brooks running in and out of the trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail begins to swing left, descends gradually to the Rocky Branch and follows it downstream for a short distance, then crosses it. &lt;b&gt;This crossing may be very difficult, and the trail can be difficult to follow from this crossing for travelers going toward NH 16 because it is poorly marked and there are well-beaten side paths to campsites&lt;/b&gt;—heading for NH 16, the main trail first parallels the river going upstream and then swings gradually away from the river on a well-defined old road&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;camp at shelter #2  7PM&lt;/b&gt; the Rocky Branch Shelter #2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday morning 9AM &lt;/b&gt;  to the junction of Isolation Trail  hike 2.60 mi/1 hr 49 min/+1023 ft on the Isolation Trail&lt;br /&gt;The Isolation Trail starts from the Rocky Branch Trail, about 60 yd. from the Rocky Branch Shelter #2.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It ascends easily, along the east bed of the Rocky Branch. The trail swings right, crossing to the west bank, then away from the bed, and continues at a moderate climb until it meets the Rocky Branch again, and climbs more rapidly. The path swings to the left, climbing moderately, and joins the Davis Path.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Davis Path hike 0.90 mi/31 min/+88 ft on the Davis Path&lt;br /&gt; The east branch of the Isolation trail leaves on the left. The Davis Path leads past the site of the former Isolation Shelter, and then ascends south on easy grades.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mt Isolation spur hike 0.07 mi/5 min/+86 ft on the Mt Isolation spur to Mt Isolation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 pm  retrace to trailhead&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>contact by phone and look for me at the trailhead</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274747270000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273869721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Isolation  Overnight  Camp and Hike</name><id>13486219</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274556600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13486219/</event_url></item>