<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1667 Massachusetts ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.351513</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Lizard Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>505987</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089810</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What no plans for this Friday night?&lt;br /&gt;If not join me and the Cello Chix for their CD release party!&lt;br /&gt;They are playing from 9pm till 12pm at the Lizard lounge in Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $7 in advance $8 at the door. Good idea to show up alittle early,&lt;br /&gt;The Lizard Lounge is a small venue and could be packed for this show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lizardloungeclub.com/main.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lizard Lounge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I just found out about this last night when I was at the Lizard Lounge enjoying some live music, It sounded too good to pass up. I hope some of you might be able to join me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cello Chix: Tearing and Sawing Through Classic Rock Since 2002&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of the Cello Chix hail from the Boston area. Becca and Susanna, classically-trained cellists, both went to the Oberlin Conservatory, but only really got to know each other a decade later at the party of a mutual friend in Watertown. A fan of hiking and cool acoustics, the friend suggested that the two bring their cellos on a hike and then play some tunes in a ravine. The prospect of turning antiques into kindling didn't thrill the cellists, so instead they decided to start playing duos at friends' parties, getting paid in chocolate and compliments. It was the usual string stuff: Bach, Handel, Mozart. But they also tried out a couple of Beatles arrangements that Susanna had been working on. The audience loved them. Emboldened, the Cello Chix started showing up at Open Mic Night at the Burren, replaced their antique cellos with electric ones, ditched the Mozart, and soon got gigs playing oldies and newbies at bars around town. It was there--at Toad, specifically--where they met Nancy, a drummer and FOAF. Nancy brings over twenty years of playing and gigging experience--plus a certain je ne sais quois--to the band. The Cello Chix now have a repertoire of over 40 classic rock, jazz, pop and Latin tunes, a loyal and sizeable following, and a CD coming out on 2/8/08. Check them out at cellochix.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/thecellochix" target="_blank"&gt;Listen to the Cello Chix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I could meet for a bite to eat close by before the show, that is if anyone can attend on such short notice.&lt;br /&gt;Let me know, I hope some of you can Meetup with me &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a small venue I shouldn't be hard to spot. I can provide my cell phone number to the few members that might show up on such short notice.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg D</member_name><member_id>4879355</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202737130000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Because you probably have never seen anyone perform rock, Jazz, Pop and Latin tunes with Electric Cellos!</why><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202426601000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cello Chix @ Lizard Lounge</name><id>7286368</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202522400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/7286368/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/d/global_3165069.jpeg</photo_url></item>