<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197-203 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.743869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 246-5700</phone><name>The Alchemy Juice Bar &amp; Growing Green Co-op</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1035078</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689453</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>350.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;High Vibe Tribe Transformational Workshop Intensive with Internationally Renowned Master Healer &amp;amp; Teacher Don Hanson &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Come explore what is getting in the way of you living your life from the place of your most authentic &amp;amp; abundant self! A unique opportunity to gather and practice the skills of community living while focusing on our own process! Change Your Programming ~ Change Your Life! A 4 Day Transformational Workshop! www.donhanson.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During a Transforming Cellular Memory workshop divine energy flows through the body on a regular and continuous basis. This energy is so powerful it targets all limitations in your body, mind and emotions that have to do with old fear based realities, belief systems and conditioning you inherited from your ancestors and cultures that are not in alignment with the universal laws of love, gratitude and abundance. This energy is brought through Don's body on request and will enter the individual or group he is working with and start to undo the cloak of world mind that your soul takes on when you come into this world. Layer by layer this cloak is unraveled and dissolved. A cellular, molecular shift takes place in your body at the most profound levels. Over time, as you are guided by the divine light flowing through, your body makes a complete metamorphosis. Those behavior patterns, mind sets and energy blockages that are at the foundation of physical, mental and emotional illness start to disappear and a new structure of excitement, passion, and self-love begin to emerge. Don Hanson was given the gift of clairvoyance and the ability to bring through a profound, healing, transformational energy to assist and teach a process of self-realization and enlightenment. The divine energy that flows through comes directly from the heart of God and is some of the most powerful, transformational energy available on the planet at this time. The process of life taught at these workshops, retreats and private sessions has a way of completely transforming how you think and the way you see reality, providing a structure that connects you directly with the intelligence and healing power of the Great Spirit. You will experience shifts in your body, mind, emotions and life that years of therapy could not achieve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don has been called a mystic, healer and highly evolved soul. He is an international teacher who initiates students to become powerful channels of wisdom, clarity, power, truth, and vehicles of immense transformational energies. He orchestrates and guides the Kundalini Awakening process, teaching each of his students to become masters and teachers of Light. People Attend Don&amp;rsquo;s Workshops to - heal, transform and realize their full-potential - accelerate their spiritual transformation - gain vision, insight and clarity - develop gifts and healing abilities- dissolve physical, emotional &amp;amp; mental pain - understand the Tantric way of life - And to learn structures for thinking and living in alignment with how the Universe works. This is a very powerful Self-Realization &amp;amp; Enlightenment Process that walks you into full liberation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information or to register: Contact Marc Chiaramonte 862.228.3030 mcmonte@me.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investment: $350&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commuter Package: Overnite Accommodations &amp;amp; Meals available ~ please email Imani@themamalution.com for pricing &amp;amp; details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323998048000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317868770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Transforming Cellular Memory Intensive with Don Hanson</name><id>36342152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323993600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/36342152/</event_url></item>