<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cabins</address_2><address_1>67 Island Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01516</zip><lat>42.063730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wallace Cove Cottages</name><city>Douglas</city><id>353497</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.766594</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Michelle wanted us to make this an offical meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She is opening the offer up to 4 more folks to join them on the Free Camping weekend... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there are a few of you who would like to reserve one of the FREE cabins for the weekend, let me know ASAP! Details below!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographers Retreat VERY special Offer!&lt;br /&gt;Wallace Cove Cottages, Douglas, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laurie Church, owner of Wallace Cove Cottages, is offering photographers in the area an amazing offer. Wallace Cove is located on 100 acres of forest land that abuts Douglas State Forest and is right ON beautiful Whitin Reservoir. There are 4 cabins and one guest house. Each sleeps 4-6 depending on sleeping arrangements. Each has a bathroom with shower, a wood stove for heat and kitchen facilities. There?s a fire pit for bonfires, Adirondack chairs to relax on, grills and even a canoe or two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The four cabins are nestled together on a private beach. Did I mention this is in a 100 acre forested private piece of land..seclusion and nature!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laurie has graciously offered her cottages basically FREE-of-CHARGE* to photographers to serve as a weekend retreat. She is gathering market research to officially offer retreats next year and this will give her valuable input. So, in return for the free use of her cottages for a weekend or two, she asks for detailed input from the group as to how she can make her retreat packages work best.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September 14/15/16 is available for us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* There will be a small stipend for the wood we?ll use in the cabins and we?ll also figure out what the food will cost for community breakfasts and dinners, etc.&lt;br /&gt;Details and picture can be seen at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfontainephotography.com/Retreat.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mfontainep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tentative agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrival on Friday afternoon/early evening &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday dinner Burgers and hot dogs on the grill or cook in your cabins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday evening sitting around the campfire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday morning sunrise photo excursions, wandering around, hiking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 a.m. Saturday morning breakfast on your own&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;noon - burgers and dogs on the grill at the main house&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m. Saturday glare time critique during 1 ? 3 p.m. we?ll have a critique session using projected images taken earlier or images you bring with you. This is a group opportunity to learn and all are expected to participate with images and comments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:00 p.m. Saturday dinner ? community dinner looking for volunteer to coordinate and cook. All are expected to pitch in any way they can to help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday evening sitting around the campfire, talking ?shop?.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday morning sunrise photo excursions, wandering around, hiking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 a.m. Sunday morning breakfast on your own &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m. lunch and brainstorm about the retreat for next year!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542009000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187896804000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photographers Retreat</name><id>6231978</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189789200000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/6231978/</event_url></item>