<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1228 Riverdale St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.137860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>On The Border Mexican Grill</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>669419</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.625950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/a/9/e/event_95419102.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Remarkable Creatures - Tracy Chevalier &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 A voyage of discoveries, a meeting of two remarkable women, and extraordinary time and place enrich bestselling author Tracy Chevalier's enthralling new novel. From the moment she's struck by lightening as a baby, it is clear that Mary Anning is marked for greatness. On the windswept, fossil-strewn beaches of the English coast, she learns that she has "the eye"-and finds what no one else can see. When Mary uncovers an unusual fossilized skeleton in the cliffs near her home, she sets the religious fathers on edge, the townspeople to vicious gossip, and the scientific world alight. In an arena dominated by men, however, Mary is barred from the academic community; as a young woman with unusual interests she is suspected of sinful behavior. Nature is a threat, throwing bitter, cold storms and landslips at her. And when she falls in love, it is with an impossible man. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Luckily, Mary finds an unlikely champion in prickly Elizabeth Philpot, a recent exile from London, who also loves scouring the beaches. Their relationship strikes a delicate balance between fierce loyalty, mutual appreciation, and barely suppressed envy. Ultimately, in the struggle to be recognized in the wider world, Mary and Elizabeth discover that friendship is their greatest ally. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Remarkable Creatures is a stunning novel of how one woman's gift transcends class and social prejudice to lead to some of the most important discoveries of the nineteenth century. Above all, is it a revealing portrait of the intricate and resilient nature of female friendship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book chosen by: Alyce &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power of Myth by Joseph Campbell&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Among his many gifts, Joseph Campbell's most impressive was the unique ability to take a contemporary situation, such as the murder and funeral of President John F. Kennedy, and help us understand its impact in the context of ancient mythology. Herein lies the power of The Power of Myth, showing how humans are apt to create and live out the themes of mythology. Based on a six-part PBS television series hosted by Bill Moyers, this classic is especially compelling because of its engaging question-and-answer format, creating an easy, conversational approach to complicated and esoteric topics. For example, when discussing the mythology of heroes, Campbell and Moyers smoothly segue from the Sumerian sky goddess Inanna to Star Wars' mercenary-turned-hero, Han Solo. Most impressive is Campbell's encyclopedic knowledge of myths, demonstrated in his ability to recall the details and archetypes of almost any story, from any point and history, and translate it into a lesson for spiritual living in the here and now. --Gail Hudson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book chosen by: Jeanne&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alyce</member_name><member_id>3445975</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>3778047</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335376270000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329791355000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April's Discussion: Remarkable &amp; The Power</name><id>53131202</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335306600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/53131202/</event_url></item>