<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>670 Legacy Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02026</zip><lat>42.230778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Showcase Cinema De Lux</name><city>Dedham</city><id>2809191</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.177940</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's catch the newest James Bond flick and hang out afterward. This is the opening weekend of the movie, which has received strong reviews, so expect a packed house. Showtime is at &lt;strong&gt;7:10pm&lt;/strong&gt; and you may want to purchase your tickets in advance if you are able. The aim is to be in our seats at least 20min in advance so we can get the best seats possible. We have a big group so even going in early, we may not all sit together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Lux Level seating is sold out. I highly recommend buying the general tix in advance. You can pre-purchase on Movietickets.com($1 surcharge). If the theater is not showing up, a workaround is to go to&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.showcasecinemas.com/showtimes/15589/1352505600"&gt;http://www.showcasecinemas.com/showtimes/15589/1352505600&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;first, then click on the 7:10 show link that will take you to movietickets.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few bars inside of the Dedham complex so we'll do a small bar crawl afterward or just post up at one spot depending on the weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finding Us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet and greet by the Studio 3 lounge inside the theater beginning at 6pm. Again, we'll be heading to our seats around 6:45 so if you are late, we'll regroup in the lobby after the movie before heading out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traveling:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a free parking garage that leads into the theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always check the event page the day of the meetup to see if any details change. Last minute changes will be posted to the site and sent via email to those that RSVPed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cabral Thomas</member_name><member_id>9824758</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352599355000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345945188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Night Out: Skyfall + Loungin'</name><id>79372012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352588400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/79372012/</event_url></item>