<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Back Bay</address_2><address_1>279A Newbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349358</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 536-2233</phone><name>Cafeteria</name><city>Boston</city><id>882326</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083969</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Someone posted, 'Anyone interested to check out the brunch at CAFETERIA on Newbury? Sounds good.'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since there is a bit of interest, let's return to Cafeteria for another brunch. The last time we dined here, there was a major snow storm. However despite the inclement weather, six hearty soles showed up. It was&amp;nbsp;good company, good food and good times. Let's do it again but with better weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cafeteria offers a modern interpretation of classic soul-satisfying American dishes prepared with organic grass-fed beef and lamb, free-range chicken, the freshest seafood and organic, local produce. These properly raised ingredients behave perfectly with a new world of herbs, spices and culinary techniques to create deeply satisfying comfort food for the new millennium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cafeteriaboston.com/menu-brunch.php"&gt;Cafeteria Brunch Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cafeteriaboston.com/menu.php"&gt;Cafeteria Lunch/Dinner Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cafeteriaboston.com/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;MBTA:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://mbta.com"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;five (5) minute walk from Green Line Copley Square or Green Line Arlington&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ten (10) minute walk from Orange Line Back Bay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to plan your route&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://boston.bestparking.com/index.php#1"&gt;Best Parking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I list the Reservation Rules, please understand the NO-SHOW policy was established to ensure everyone who wants to join can and it will be fairly and strictly enforced. I want to assure you I do understand if you've RSVPd YES and you have a sudden change of plans because you're lost, you don't feel well, you have transportation issues, you don't have the money, or you just don't want to be around people. My only request is for you to let me know as soon as possible so we don't worry about you and our reservation is adjusted. As long as you contact me you will not be considered a NO-SHOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rules for Events with Reservations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it is less than an hour from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at (617) 445-7549&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All RSVPs are on a first reply, first reserved basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO and WAIT LIST if meal is full. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you RSVP YES or WAIT LIST, you MUST answer the question which appears after your RSVP. If you don't your RSVP will be changed to NO.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the brunch and you have not attended nor contacted me, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I change your RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update brunch confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW, each will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within an hour of the brunch, it is counted as a NO-SHOW if you do not contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events with reservations you are removed from the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing the survey afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be arrive at 1:45 to welcome you from Cafeteria's bar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>3332443</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331004657000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313548617000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cafeteria on Newbury Street for Brunch</name><id>29792031</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317578400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/29792031/</event_url></item>