<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This will be a What’s Your Philosophy of Life Party (sort of). The New Year will be upon us, and so I thought that this year we can have a free flowing discussion of&lt;/span&gt; our different philosophies of life or, what is often also called, “the meaning of life.” For this meeting, folks will be given the opportunity to stand in the Speakers Corner and use up to five minutes to give a monologue about his or her philosophy of life. Afterwards, the speaker can remain for another few minutes to answer questions. When there is no speaker who has volunteered then, of course, the normal roundtable discussion will proceed at the two round tables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not to worry&lt;/strong&gt;: There will be no pressure on anyone to get up and speak; it's just an opportunity that, time permitting, all&lt;/span&gt; will be afforded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What are some philosophies of life?&lt;/span&gt; Here are a few ideas:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;The quest for knowledge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;The quest for pleasure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Creative expression. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meditation and spiritual unity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;A life of action. Jogging? Bungee jumping? Skydiving? Russian roulette? (LOL)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Chiding people who use the term 'LOL'?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Helping others?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Helping oneself?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;To live philosophically; always pondering the big and small questions. Hmm, why did I say that? (Very deep) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you have a favored philosopher whose philosophy largely comprises your philosophy of life? Go existentialism!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Or:&lt;/span&gt; Is your philosophy of life the philosophy that there is no philosophy of life?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HAPPY HOLIDAYS!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people).   After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.  It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.  And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house! The basic cost is $20 (this covers your entree, 3 or 4 shared appetizers per table, tax and gratuity but &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; drinks). If you order drinks please pay the cost of the drink times 125% to cover additional tax and tip (e.g. if you order one drink that costs $6.00 then your total cost for food and drink would be $27.50). If on a &lt;em&gt;rare&lt;/em&gt; occasion you only order a drink or an appetizer, or if you do not order anything, then you will owe a minimum charge of $12 to compensate the restaurant for their service.  If there should be a shortfall, which is unlikely, then the group agrees to chip in to cover the difference. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.  However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*****************************&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP for one of our events it is expected that you have every intention of attending. Please refrain from impulse reservations and impulse cancellations!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1360983011000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355255058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Philosophy of Life Party!</name><id>94972652</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356739200000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/94972652/</event_url></item>