<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>210 Howe Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.755830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 683-7771</phone><name>BOXWOOD GRILL </name><city>Methuen</city><id>1017422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.173902</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The purpose of our presentation is to transmit how a self-confident women entrepreneur can make the right, positive, convincing and energetic impression on clients and in business. Women need to feel good about themselves to radiate certainty, happiness and success!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Ahva Desment:&lt;/b&gt;  Ahva is a mom from Hampstead, NH, she has three small boys under the age of four. Ahva has been with Arbonne for three years and loves to help women understand their skin and how to keep it looking and feeling its best. You can contact her personally at ahvanicday@aol.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Maria Murphy:&lt;/b&gt;  I began my career as a Computer Systems Analyst.  I left the corporate world to raise 3 children.  I returned, to be a florist for 10 years.  Now, I have my dream job.  Helping people shine, in Silpada Jewlery!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Sylvia Sasso:&lt;/b&gt;  I am a certified nutritionist and personal trainer and specialize in working through the mind to achieve a healthy body and lifestyle. I have been in the field of counseling, health and wellness for over 20 years and am very passionate about my mission to help women of all ages, shapes and health goals to look great, feel fantastic and radiate self confidence and happiness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen Campaiola</member_name><member_id>6037081</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281755298000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Daring Women!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup</urlname><id>1412014</id><group_lat>42.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Dare To Be Phenomenal's Success Minded Women's Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277702506000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DARE Networking Luncheon</name><id>rwlgnynlbpb</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281540600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup/events/13932372/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/4/0/global_12349600.jpeg</photo_url></item>