<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are still working out the how to get there info but I need a head count! Who's with us for this fun night! You'll never see anything like this anywhere else... Please RSVP so I know if you are coming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween is not celebrated any place else in the world with such fun and&lt;br /&gt;magic as in Salem, Massachusetts. With the changing colors of the leaves, New&lt;br /&gt;England autumn brings out the ghosts and goblins that Halloween is known&lt;br /&gt;for; you will find it all in Salem this October.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Salem is a fine walking city and you won't want to miss a beat during Salem&lt;br /&gt;Haunted Happenings 2008, so bring good walking shoes. If walking is not&lt;br /&gt;your style, then hop on and off a local trolley. From events at the numerous&lt;br /&gt;museums to fabulous annual costume balls all over the city to psychic readings&lt;br /&gt;to playing on the Common, October is chocked full of events to for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Destination Salem’s website at www.salem.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting to Salem could not be easier! Just leave your broom behind and&lt;br /&gt;hop on board public transportation. Whether by land or sea you will find&lt;br /&gt;lots of ease and magic getting here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is easier during Haunted Happenings to park and come in to town on&lt;br /&gt;public transportation. No need to worry about parking! On Halloween&lt;br /&gt;night, it is the only way to get in and out without issues. Many streets in the&lt;br /&gt;downtown area are closed on Opening Night and on Halloween evening.&lt;br /&gt;Beat the traffic and take the T! The MBTA has a fleet of buses, as well as&lt;br /&gt;commuter trains that leave from Boston and come to Salem if you prefer&lt;br /&gt;land transportation. If you come from Boston or Rockport, Newburyport or&lt;br /&gt;Ipswich, the MBTA has you covered! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By sea, you can hop on The Salem&lt;br /&gt;Ferry at Long Wharf near the Aquarium in Boston for a 45 minute ride on&lt;br /&gt;the ocean along the coastline to Salem’s Blaney Wharf.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether by land or sea, once you get in to Salem it is a quick 2-5 minute&lt;br /&gt;walk to all of the sites, sounds and activities of Haunted Happenings. From&lt;br /&gt;world class museums, delicious restaurants or uniqie shopping opportunities,&lt;br /&gt;you will find yourself all of a sudden there from all of the transportation outlets&lt;br /&gt;to and in town.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once at Blaney Wharf you can hop on and off Salem’s two trolley companies.&lt;br /&gt;CityView Trolley and The Salem Trolley continuously loop through the&lt;br /&gt;city with easy on and off places to stop, stroll and hop back on board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are also other sweet and unique ways to view the city. Horse drawn carriages, bicycle cabs, and of course our city taxis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For information please go to www.hauntedhappenings.org for a list of our&lt;br /&gt;transportation sponsors. For the MBTA schedule go to www.mbta.com.&lt;br /&gt;No matter how you get here though, you can leave your car home and find&lt;br /&gt;it easy to get around the city!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HauntedHappenings.org&lt;br /&gt;The City of Salem’s official website for Haunted Happenings sponsored by&lt;br /&gt;Destination Salem.&lt;br /&gt;Destination Salem, City of Salem’s Office for Travel and Tourism&lt;br /&gt;www.salem.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226365412000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220365377000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot: Halloween Night - Salem MA- Scary!! or not...</name><id>8669771</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225483200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/8669771/</event_url></item>