<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list. A yes list will be provided as soon as possible. All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All attenddees must have foot traction. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website. starting at Falling Waters Trailhead and Old Bridle Path (Franconia Range) Back to here There are 5 blowdowns but the trail is passable. The lower section (below Falling Waters junction) is heavily eroded but passable. hike 0.20 mi/8 min/+62 ft on the Old Bridle Path The trail leaves the parking lot (which is a stop for the AMC&amp;rsquo;s Hiker Shuttle) on the east side of the parkway (reached from the west side by a paved path 0.1 mi. long) near the hiker information kiosk, in common with the Falling Waters Trail, and passes through a clearing into the woods. to the junction of Falling Waters Trail hike 2.70 mi/2 hr 34 min/+2337 ft on the Old Bridle Path The Falling Waters Trail turns sharp right and immediately crosses Walker Brook on a bridge, while the Old Bridle Path continues along the brook for 50 yd., then swings left away from the brook and starts to climb at a moderate grade. Old Bridle Path swings back to the right, enters the WMNF (sign), and soon comes to the edge of the bank high above Walker Brook, then swings away again. Then it makes a sharp left turn with rock steps at the edge of the ravine, where there is a glimpse of Mt. Lincoln through the trees, then turns right and soon gains the ridge. The first of the spectacular outlooks from the brink of the ravine is reached, and several more are passed. The trail then begins to ascend the steep part of the ridge, sometimes called Agony Ridge (a name that originated with hut people who had to pack heavy loads up this steep section). In one pitch, the trail struggles up a steep basalt dike with somewhat slippery footing. Then an unmarked side path diverges right, passes two fine outlooks, and rejoins the main trail 40 yd. above the lower junction. Still climbing, the main trail passes a view to Cannon Mountain, Kinsman Mountain, and Mt. Moosilauke from a grassy spot, then crosses a small sag through a patch of dead trees and soon reaches Greenleaf Hut. to AMC Greenleaf Hut entering alpine zone hike 1.10 mi/1 hr 5 min/+1026 ft on the Greenleaf Trail The Greenleaf Trail heads toward Lafayette, enters the scrub, and dips slightly, passing south of the Eagle Lakes, two picturesque shallow tarns (though the upper lake is rapidly becoming a bog). The trail rises, passing over several minor knobs, and swings left after passing an open, sandy area on the right. The trail soon climbs above the scrub into the open and ascends at a moderate grade, sometimes on rock steps between stone walls. The trail bears left around a ledge on the right side of the trail from which a remarkable spring issues, very small but fairly reliable. Now the trail turns right and soon reaches the summit of Mt. Lafayette. Here the Garfield Ridge Trail leads north and then northeast to Mt. Garfield, Garfield Ridge Campsite, Galehead Hut, and the Twin Range. To the south, the Franconia Ridge Trail leads to Liberty Spring Campsite and the Franconia Notch Parkway via the Liberty Spring Trail, or to the Kancamagus Highway via the Osseo Trail. to Mt Lafayette Totals Distance 4.00 mi Time 3 hr 47 min Elev Gain +3589 ft Elev Loss -164 ft Elev Change +3425 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 1.00 mi/39 min/-162 ft on the Franconia Ridge Trail Leaving the summit of Mt. Lafayette, the trail descends at a moderate grade to the first sag, where it passes through a small scrub patch that might provide some shelter in bad weather. It then climbs across a prominent hump, descends to another sag, and climbs again to the summit of Mt. Lincoln. From there, it descends sharply, keeping mostly just to the east of the crest of the knife-edged ridge between Mt. Lincoln and Little Haystack Mountain, which has steep slopes on both sides. At the base of this knife-edged section, the ridge becomes nearly level and much broader, and the trail continues on the ridge crest in the open to the junction with the Falling Waters Trail on the right, just under the summit rock of Little Haystack Mountain to Mt Lincoln hike 0.70 mi/25 min/-324 ft on the Franconia Ridge Trail The Franconia Ridge Trail continues to the south end of the Little Haystack summit ridge, enters the scrub and descends steeply over ledges for a short distance, then moderates and follows the long, fairly gradual ridge to a junction with the Liberty Spring Trail on the right. There is water at Liberty Spring Campsite. to Little Haystack Mtn Totals Distance 5.70 mi Time 4 hr 51 min Elev Gain +4014 ft Elev Loss -1074 ft Elev Change +2939 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.40 mi/30 min/-590 ft on the Falling Waters Trail The Falling Waters Trail leaves the Franconia Ridge Trail at the summit of Little Haystack. It descends straight down the summit until it turns left and continues south to a spur which leads left about 100 yd. to Shining Rock where there are fine views south and west over Franconia Notch. This steep granite ledge, more than 200 ft. tall and nearly 800 ft. long, is usually covered with water from springs in the woods above and, seen from the mountains across the notch, shines like a mirror in the sunlight. Caution: Climbing Shining Rock without rock-climbing equipment and training is extremely dangerous. This steep ledge is wet and very slippery; several accidents involving serious injuries have occurred here to hikers who tried to scramble up the rock. to Shining Rock hike 1.20 mi/1 hr 16 min/-1306 ft on the Falling Waters Trail The Falling Waters Trail descends the ridge via a series of switchbacks. It then meets up with and continues on an old logging road. The trail approaches the south bank of the Mt. Lincoln Branch. The trail swings to the left, and crosses to the north bank of the brook. leaving alpine zone hike 1.40 mi/1 hr 55 min/-982 ft on the Falling Waters Trail It continues on the old logging road and crosses the same brook back to the south side and then back to the north side. It continues to descend steeply, following the north bank of the Mt. Lincoln Branch. At the head of Cloudland Falls (80 feet) are two small (25 ft.) falls practically facing each other. The one to the south, which emerges from the woods, is on the branch of Dry Brook that runs down from Little Haystack, while the other is on the Mt. Lincoln branch. Here, at the top of the falls, is a viewpoint looking out over the valley toward Mt. Moosilauke on the skyline. The trail leaves the falls and descends steeply down the steep bank of the brook with a ledgy scramble to the bottom of the falls. It then descends roughly down an embankment until it joins an old road which descends gradually in the narrow gorge of Dry Brook. It then leaves the old road and follows a steep rock staircase to a shady glen beneath Swiftwater falls which descends 60 ft. The trail passes beneath Sawteeth Ledges and arrives at the top of Stairs Falls. It follows along the south bank of the beautiful cascades, turns right, and crosses Dry Brook (use care if the water is high). Heading north, then west, the trail crosses Walker Brook on a bridge and turns sharply left onto the Old Bridle Path. to the junction of Old Bridle Path hike 0.20 mi/8 min/-62 ft on the Falling Waters Trail The Falling Waters Trail joins the Old Bridle Path through the woods and into a clearing. It passes the hiker information kiosk and terminates at the parking lot on the east side of the parkway (reached from the east side by a paved path 0.1 mi. long) The parking lot is also a stop on the AMC's Hiker Shuttle route. to Falling Waters Trailhead and Old Bridle Path (Franconia Range) Totals Distance 8.90 mi Time 8 hr 40 min Elev Gain +4154 ft Elev Loss -4154 ft Elev Change 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL MEET IN THE NORTHBOUND PARKING LOT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1333058208000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331553459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT LAFAYETTE &amp; LINCOLN LOOP</name><id>55998772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332595800000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/55998772/</event_url></item>