<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>81 Mirror Lake Dr</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06451</zip><lat>41.549408</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>West Peak &amp; Castle Craig</name><city>Meriden</city><id>745527</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.832081</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>West Peak has an excellent view.  As you stand on the bald, rocky ridge, you can see Sleeping Giant to the south, and Castle Craig a short distance away on the same ridgeline.  It's a nice place to take a break, especially after humping it up the mountain.  That'll be the main destination for the hike, but the ridge extends north along a lesser-trod trail, and we'll continue along that way for a while before doing an about face and turning back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike should take 3 to 4 hours walking at a normal pace, and has enough up that we'll be resting a few times before reaching the peak.  Our ascent will start at the footbridge crossing I-691, and our descent will differ in that we'll come down the non-steep way near the pavillion under Castle Craig.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group will meet at 10am on Saturday in the parking lot by the playground, and leave when everyone has arrived (or when 10:15am has come).  We should be back at the parking lot by 2pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bing.com/maps/OneClickDirections.aspx?mkt=en-us&amp;amp;rtp=~pos.qxrdxb8xxm1p&amp;amp;FORM=LLMP" target="_blank"&gt;Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring water,  a snack, and appropriate footwear.  Sunscreen and/or a hat might be appropriate as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250203856000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249301705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>[Meriden, CT] West Peak</name><id>11021060</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249740000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11021060/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/global_6186111.jpeg</photo_url></item>