<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>First Ever Pub Crawl Cambridge to Boston. People have been asking for a pub crawl and a walking tour. This one is for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll begin somewhere in Cambridge and then walk across the river to Boston and end up in Beacon Hill.  Along the way, we'll be checking out Cambridge and Boston urbanscapes while stopping off for drinks, food and good conversation. We'll be walking across the river and up the Commonwealth Mall and through the parks, as well.  Have you walked across the river yet? This is your chance! You'd be amazed at how many people who live here have not done this.  Walking is also a great way to see the city.  And in a group it will be a lot of fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While living in NYC... I got so use to having many friends around that enjoyed exploring the city at the ground level - by walking every inch of its neighborhoods, parks, main streets, and even many of the more obscure nooks and quiet side streets. I miss those times and experiences of trekking about a city and seeing and noticing everything, and discovering and learning all kinds of new things that I wouldn't have seen otherwise. And there was always so much to see. I miss knowing a city on that level.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Need to RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240314738000</updated><rating><average>4.94999980927</average><count>21</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236167782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Co-Event w/Girls with Moxie - First Pub Crawl Cambridge to Boston  </name><id>9877908</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240070400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9877908/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/c/global_7605004.jpeg</photo_url></item>