<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03846</zip><lat>44.190338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Square Ledge</name><city>Jackson</city><id>712016</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.226990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This cliff is located across from the Pinkham Notch visitor center, in fact that is where you should park!  If we have already left the parking lot here is how to find the crag:  Carefully cross rt 16 walk south about 100 yards, and hike up the Lost Pond Trail. Go over a wooden bridge, turn left on the Square Ledge Trail at a signpost, head directly across a country ski trail and continue up to the base of the cliff, all in roughly 15-20 min from Pinkham notch.  Cliff description can be found in Ed Websters Rock climbing in the White Mountains of New Hampshire book.   Open to all climbers! These are shorter climbs, so toprope is possible, children welcome.   If you don't have gear and would like to attend please let me know by Fri. as I will be heading up early on Sat. morning and camping Sat. night.  I won't have access to this site after Sat morning, so if your plans change please call my cell #  603-312-3924 ***** BEAUTIFUL VIEWS OF MT WASHINGTON!!!  &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you up there&lt;br /&gt;Kellie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>large green van look for meetup signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kellie Barr-Foster</member_name><member_id>6992283</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217344296000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Rock Climbers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>rockclimbing-134</urlname><id>1120342</id><group_lat>43.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>The NH Rock Climbing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216139712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Square Ledge</name><id>8345300</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217170800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rockclimbing-134/events/8345300/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/1/global_3885009.jpeg</photo_url></item>