<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you ever been aware you were dreaming? Have you ever flown through the air in your dreams? Have you ever been weightless and floated up into the air, like a balloon? Have you ever traveled to other places and times in your dreams? In this workshop we will explore these and other topics, including astral travel and out of body experiences. In addition we will learn techniques to intentionally dream lucidly, how to fly, and how to travel through time and space. Through guided meditation we will practice the art of lucid dreaming. There will also be time to share our dreams. Welcome aboard bold dream travelers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Meetup workshop is facilitated by Deerheart, who is a professional dream guide. An experienced explorer of the dream realms, he has been studying dreams for over thirty years. He has had many teachers of dreamwork, shamanism, psychology, empowerment, and healing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, April 26&lt;br /&gt;2-5 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is a sliding scale - $10-$30, depending on ability to pay. Anyone who cannot afford to pay should contact Deerheart, to arrange alternatives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited. Only those who have RSVPed will be admitted. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. Blessings, Deerheart&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244584664000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236215532000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lucid Dreaming, Flying, &amp; Dream Travel</name><id>9883831</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240768800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/9883831/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/f/global_7377007.jpeg</photo_url></item>