<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to meet at the McDonald's on 98 Weston Street, Hartford, CT&amp;#8206; before the event at 1:30pm.  We'll be outside our cars so just find the people hanging out.  After we gather we'll head in together; of course after we tailgate at the event some. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wingmen and Wingwomen, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Korn and Rob Zombie should be leading the show and I'll definitely be there when I come home in July. I am actually thinking about making this the best event ever! I can't stress enough how much fun concerts like these are! Even if you don't like rock music just come and hang out with everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every time I go it's like a giant party because you see so many people you know from throughout the state. Great place to bring your friends and network with people as well. Your not gonna want to miss this! It's a blast I wouldn't steer you all wrong so come and have a good time. Details on where we're going to meet up and such will be coming in another email in the near future. I need to get a head count for now and I hope to see all of you there! :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                                    Cheers, &lt;br /&gt;                                                                    Red Man &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the link for more info on tickets and such: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.metalinsider.net/touring/rockstar-mayhem-fest-announces-2010-lineup-dates" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metalinsid...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Email Me For Info. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John </member_name><member_id>6728192</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280086528000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275841652000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rockstar Energy Drink Presents Mayhem 2010 in Hartford!</name><id>13714626</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279992600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/13714626/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/8/global_15533800.jpeg</photo_url></item>