<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>288 Plymouth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02721</zip><lat>41.696030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Trader Jan's Archery Pro Shop</name><city>Fall River</city><id>1651931</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150902</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Archery is here! All of those who have asked me about it for months and months, even a year... it's finally happening! So come out and learn to shoot with me at Trader Jans :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost is $12/hr (group rate) for the event with all necessary equipment provided. The event will most likely be 1.5 to 2 hours ($24 max) and you will receive basic instructions on how to shoot. Payment is made at the end of the event, the day of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a limited event with a maximum of 10-12 participants from this group. I am making it a joint meetup with another group so we have a good turnout. I do have to state that this is for those who are serious only. Trader Jans has agreed to close down their shop for the couple hours just for us! So, I would appreciate only those serious about attending the event. I understand that life happens, things come up all of a sudden. Please find the time to let me know if you cancel, so that I have enough time to fill your spot if anyone is waiting to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*** Please serious attendees only, this is a paid event, paid on the day ***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And lastly, I know I know liability... we just want to make sure you don't blame us if you get hurt. So please read the liability waiver below and accept it if you plan to attend. In all honesty, I doubt anything will happen, as long as you are aware of your surroundings and follow the instructions they give you.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Trader Jans, &lt;a href="http://www.traderjans.com"&gt;Visit their website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*** LIABILITY WAIVER ***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration of being allowed to participate in any way in with the &lt;strong&gt;Providence Bicycling, Walking, etc.&lt;/strong&gt; events and activities, the undersigned acknowledges, appreciates, and agrees that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The risk of injury from archery and other known and unknown events and activities and/or the use of the related buildings, structures, equipment, and personal property whether owned by archery facility or others is significant, including the potential for permanent paralysis and death, and while particular rules, equipment, and personal discipline may reduce this risk, the risk of serious injury does exist; and, I acknowledge and agree that the use of archery equipment by myself or others on premises or otherwise are inherently dangerous and high risk activities whether such archery equipment are discharged by myself or others; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I KNOWINGLY AND FREELY ASSUME ALL SUCH RISKS, both known and unknown, EVEN IF ARISING FROM THE NEGLIGENCE OF THE RELEASEES or others, and assume full responsibility for my participation; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I HEREBY RELEASE AND HOLD HARMLESS &lt;strong&gt;Providence Bicycling, Walking, etc.&lt;/strong&gt; its organizers, assistant organizers, members, and other participants, owners and lessors of real property and personal property used to conduct the events and activities (&amp;ldquo;RELEASEES&amp;rdquo;), WITH RESPECT TO ANY AND ALL INJURY, DISABILITY, DEATH, or loss or damage to person or property, WHETHER ARISING FROM THE NEGLIGENCE OF THE RELEASEES OR OTHERWISE, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BY RSVP YES, I HAVE READ THIS RELEASE OF LIABILITY AND ASSUMPTION OF RISK AGREEMENT, FULLY UNDERSTAND ITS TERMS, UNDERSTAND THAT I HAVE GIVEN UP SUBSTANTIAL RIGHTS BY SIGNING IT, AND SIGN IT FREELY AND VOLUNTARILY WITHOUT ANY INDUCEMENT.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's located on the second floor of the building. Find the entrance and elevator at the back of the building.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309175892000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305904583000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Archery @ Trader Jans</name><id>19093621</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309014000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/19093621/</event_url></item>