<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>559 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353722</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Paramount Center Mainstage, ArtsEmerson</name><city>Boston</city><id>5656472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062416</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1944, U.S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This adaptation of Vera Caspary's suspense novel was begun by director Rouben Mamoulien and cinematographer Lucien Ballard, but thanks to a complex series of backstage intrigues and hostilities, the film was ultimately credited to director Otto Preminger and cameraman Joseph LaShelle (who won an Oscar for his efforts). At the outset of the film, it is established that the title character, Laura Hunt (Gene Tierney), has been murdered. Tough New York detective Mark McPherson (Dana Andrews)&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;investigates the killing, methodically questioning the chief suspects: Waspish columnist Waldo Lydecker (Clifton Webb), wastrel socialite Shelby Carpenter (Vincent Price), and Carpenter's wealthy "patroness" Ann Treadwell (Judith Anderson). The deeper he gets into the case, the more fascinated he becomes by the enigmatic Laura, literally falling in love with the girl's painted portrait. As he sits in Laura's apartment, ruminating over the case and his own obsessions, the door opens, the lights switch on, and in walks Laura Hunt, very much alive! To tell any more would rob the reader of the sheer enjoyment of watching this stylish film noir unfold on screen. Everything clicks in Laura, from the superbly bitchy peformance of Clifton Webb (a veteran Broadway star who became an overnight movie favorite with this film) to the haunting musical score by David Raskin. Long available only in the 85-minute TV version Laura has since been restored to its original 88-minute running time. ~ Hal Erickson, Rovi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;ROTTEN TOMATOES: &amp;nbsp;100%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;"Not just another noir classic of '44,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Laura&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;almost succeeds in pulling the screen apart at the seams... Less investigative thriller than an investigation of that genre's conventions &amp;#150; voyeurism (looking at, and for, Laura), a search for solutions (not just whodunit but whodunwhat), and the race against time (clues and clocks, fantasies and flashbacks) &amp;#150; the plot is deliberately perfunctory, the people deliciously perverse, and the&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;mise-en-sc&amp;egrave;ne&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;radical."&amp;#8232;&amp;#150;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Time Out (London).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After, we'll go to PENANG (685 Washington Street) for a bite and light-hearted Review,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See You at the Movie,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Caroline will be sitting in the theater with the group that is the only attendees of the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caroline </member_name><member_id>10711981</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333243528000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330994346000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LAURA</name><id>55131842</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333146600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/55131842/</event_url></item>