<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;There are some great discounts and free lessons set up for the the Jan 6 to 8 weekend. Stay at the Wedeln Ski House and meet other beginners and snowboarders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want free lessons/rental/lift ticket?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SkiNH.com has designated Jan 7th to 13th as "Learn to ski/ride NH week". &amp;nbsp;Many NH ski resorts will offer free learn to ride deals. &amp;nbsp;Just got to their web site now and download the coupon then early on Jan 2nd sign up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skiNH.com/deals/learntoskiandsnowboardmonth.aspx"&gt;http://www.skiNH.com/deals/learntoskiandsno...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sign up (on SkiNH) is first come first serve so get the coupon and be ready on Jan 2nd to claim your spot. &amp;nbsp;We will plan to go to Bretton Woods on Saturday and Attitash on Sunday. &amp;nbsp;If this locations fill up please note that the ski club is close to Cranmore, Black and Wildcat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you experienced and want a ticket deal?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately signing up for the free deal will not work for experienced riders, terrain/lifts may be limited but we do have a few deals. &amp;nbsp;Friday is only $9 at Cranmore. &amp;nbsp;Saturday our race team will be at Bretton Woods so anyone staying at our club pays the same as our racers, usually about $45 (reg price is $78). &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am looking for experienced snowboarders that can do a few runs with the beginners. The plan is to have beginners take official lesson in the morning, all meet for lunch then the experienced people will take the new people for a few runs in the afternoon. &amp;nbsp;Any help providing the beginners with pointers is appreciated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- (optional) meet us Friday morning at Cranmore for $9 lift ticket day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or at the ski house after 7pm for a meet and greet. &amp;nbsp;Please pay all guest fees, and meal fees friday night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- Breakfast option at the club for $5 then off to Bretton Woods. &amp;nbsp;I will try to find a spot for us to meet for lunch at 12:30pm. &amp;nbsp;Hangout apres ski for an event (more details later). &amp;nbsp;We may have a dinner option at the house if we get enough people up. &amp;nbsp;Cost is usually $15&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- $5 breakfast at club then off to Attitash. &amp;nbsp;Same free lesson deal if you sign up on skiNH.com on Jan 2nd. &amp;nbsp;I don't have discount tix for Attitash, for the more experienced check liftopia.com, they currently have tickets at $48.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Details&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Check the lodge out at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.wedeln.com/"&gt;www.wedeln.com&lt;/a&gt;. The lodge is located on the North Conway, NH / Bartlett NH town line and is less then 3 hours from Boston. Directions given to those who RSVP Yes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Guests bring their own sheets/pillow/sleeping bag, as well as their own towels, toiletries, and flip flops for the showers. Rooms are separated by gender and are dorm style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Regular guest fees are $25 per night.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- To RSVP - a $25 deposit is required. Please use the link above to make a payment through Amazon Payments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions.&amp;nbsp;The Wedeln Ski House is always age 21+ only, no pets. Most bedrooms have 2 bunk-beds, rooms segregated by gender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ps The beginner lesson deals are between you and the mountain, not sure what rules may apply (limited lifts or time period) and they may sell out. &amp;nbsp;If you are unable to reserve a spot on Jan 2nd please let me know by Jan 3rd and I can return your room deposit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>directions will be sent</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325898782000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Snowboarders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>snowboard-46</urlname><id>389975</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Somerville Snowboarding Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324421986000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Learn to Ride Weekend (FREE lessons)</name><id>45069122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325894400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/snowboard-46/events/45069122/</event_url></item>