<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Market St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02885</zip><lat>41.730804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>40`-247-4200</phone><name>2nd Story Theater</name><city>Warren</city><id>777424</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.281755</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For this Meet-up we will return to the 2nd Story Theater in Warren, RI for "Sabrina Fair." Here is the description of the play:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Sabrina Fair is the daughter of a chauffeur to the wealthy Larrabee family, who live in a mansion on the North Shore of Long Island. Returning from a stay in Paris after working as the private secretary to the 'Assistant Economic Commissioner Office of Special Representative for Europe Economic Cooperation Administration', she presents herself as a young woman of beauty, charm, incredible sophistication and zest for living, so different from the domestic's daughter the family had largely ignored. She proclaims her desire 'to do everything and see everything, sense everything; to know that life is an enormous experience and must be used. To be in the world, and of the world, and never stand aside and watch.' Although she once had a crush on David Larrabee, the young playboy of the family, and returns to America with a wealthy French suitor in tow, she finds herself drawn to Linus Larrabee, whose intelligence, lack of sentimentality, and knowledge of the world stimulates her."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $25. Seating is General Admission. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Each person is responsible for purchasing their own ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For reservations, please call the 2nd Story Theater at 401-247-4200.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note that Saturday nights at 2nd Story do sell out early. Please do not wait to order your tickets! I strongly recommend that you order your tickets now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;When you order your ticket, please tell them you are a member of this group.  They will then reserve our seats together.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a fairly large parking lot located next to the theater between Market Street and Route 114 in Warren. A sign for Second Story Theater is on Route 114, although it's somewhat hidden. Identify yourself as a member of this group when you arrive at the theater and they will show you to our seats.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tell the usher you are with our group when you arrive.  He will show you to our seats.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345344712000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333475045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sabrina Fair</name><id>59084322</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345332600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/59084322/</event_url></item>