<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Driving directions come with your reservation</address_2><address_1>2056 Mohawk Trail</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01339</zip><lat>42.620644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crabappel White Water Rafting</name><city>Charlemont</city><id>339389</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.844720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE MAR 18...&lt;br /&gt;i JUST CALLED CRABAPPEL TO GET A NUMBER FIGURE OF WHAT AMOUNT OF SEATS WERE AVAILABLE..&lt;br /&gt;THEY INDICATED ONLY 46 AS OF TODAY..&lt;br /&gt;They WILL CLOSE THE EVENT IN A FEW DAYS..&lt;br /&gt;CALL AND RESERVE IF YOU ARE GOING&lt;br /&gt;AL-R&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RESERVATIONS: AL REIGINS PARTY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Millers River trip is only offered in the spring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You resreve for yourself, say AL REIGINS PARTY so you will be in our raft.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im going whether or not any of you go.This river is new to me and i want to be able to see it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The other trip we will see listed later..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We run the Millers River on special dam releases and natural flows from the Spring thaw. Early April flows yield non-stop Class (3)* action punctuated by &amp;quot;The Funnel&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Tsunami&amp;quot; bumps. Later in April and early in May, the Millers often runs for a Class (2)* intermediate trip. This trip has action from beginning to end with long, continuous bumps and only short breaks as we float behind active and historic mill sites. This trip is tough to beat for continuous action! Check out the Photo Gallery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Provision for this free flowing river: If conditions force us to cancel a Miller's trip, all rafters will switch to another Class (3)* trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip Overview:&lt;br /&gt;Miles: 9&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rapid Classification: Class II, III, (IV) DURING THE SPECIAL DAM RELEASE APR 12/13&lt;br /&gt;Trip time: Full day&lt;br /&gt;Minimum Age: 12&lt;br /&gt;Food: Hamburger and Hot Dog cookout after trip at base camp (on other trips its a full dinner but it sounds good anyway)&lt;br /&gt;No. of people per boat: 6 - 8&lt;br /&gt;Digital Slide Presentation from &amp;quot;The Funnel&amp;quot; rapid&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Thank you so much for our experience on the Millers River...Our students continue to talk about the intensity of the experience and the exciting day they had...Experiences like this make better kids!...You made our group feel extremely special and treated each one of us with respect and care. Though many students were nervous before the trip, not one has expressed a moment where they felt insecure or unsafe. That is purely a credit to the ability of your guides to care for children and make them feel that they are in good hands.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greg W - Hingham, Mass. Middle School Adventure Club&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miller's River Rafting Prices and Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;Rafting Price: $79 pp (wetsuits included) see info below also&lt;br /&gt;YOU MUST RESERVE WITH THEM ( 1 800 553 7238 ) AND PAY THEM ..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;website: www.crabapplewhitewater.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;rsvp's here is only for our purposes, if you didn't pay/reserve with them, ya wont be able to go..&lt;br /&gt;im not responsible if it fills up and ya didnt get to go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group Rates for 16 or more rafters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Includes:&lt;br /&gt;Pre-trip safety instruction, professional guide, PFD and helmet, full wet suit Rental or bring your own, transportation to and from river, hamburger and hotdog cookout, photo presentation of your adventure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM HARTFORD:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate Time 1 1/2 hours?Take I-91 north to Exit 26 in Greenfield, Ma. Go around the rotary and pick up Rte 2 west. Our base is about 11 miles west of Greenfield on the left side of Rte 2.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Day on the Miller's River&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crab Apple on the Deerfield - Charlemont, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;Time:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trip meets at different times - check your confirmation for your trip time. Please consult a map along with our directions. It is your responsibility to arrive on time. The trip cannot wait for latecomers.&lt;br /&gt;Trip Itinerary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Meet at appropriate trip time&lt;br /&gt;* Lifejacket and helmet fitting&lt;br /&gt;* Safety lecture and paddling instruction&lt;br /&gt;* Bus ride to put-in&lt;br /&gt;* Raft 3 miles in Class II-III whitewater&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;The Funnel&amp;quot; rapid - Class III/IV&lt;br /&gt;* Riverside snack&lt;br /&gt;* Continue 4 miles in Class II-III whitewater&lt;br /&gt;* Take out and ride back to Crab Apple&lt;br /&gt;* Hearty picnic lunch&lt;br /&gt;* Slide presentation of trip&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Bring:&lt;br /&gt;For every trip you need:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Bathing suit or shorts...(POLY is best)&lt;br /&gt;* Warm wool/fleece socks&lt;br /&gt;* Warm hat&lt;br /&gt;* Warm, layered clothing... (POLY is best)&lt;br /&gt;* For torso and legs: wool, fleece, capilene, polypropylene&lt;br /&gt;* Outer layer: wind jacket and pants are great for shedding water and can be worn over a wetsuit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wetsuits&lt;br /&gt;Clean, comfortable wetsuits and wetsuit boots will always be available for rent. (This time its included)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fleece and synthetics are extra warm under wetsuits and wetsuit boots. Wind jackets and pants can be worn over wetsuits to shed water and add warmth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crab Apple on the Deerfield houses a fun store where you may purchase photos of your trip, a fine selection of apparel and souvenirs. A snack bar is also available with ice cream, snacks, soda, beer and wine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medications:&lt;br /&gt;Always bring medications which you may need on the river i.e. asthma inhaler, bee sting kit, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* class of river rated by Al-r..&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;The actual rating listed is HIGHER by (Crabapple White Water)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the parking lot of the Crabappel In Shelburne Falls MA at 9:15, or at our chosen point for carpooling on the way up apx 7:30-8:00,
then we are on our way...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208497367000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>If you enjoy excitement..this is it...LOL</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203362794000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special COLDEST &amp; Meanest GOD DAM release of water on Earth ICE Rafting Trip</name><id>7356237</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208006100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/7356237/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/c/global_3264476.jpeg</photo_url></item>