<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday February 12th  at City Bar inside the Lenox Hotel located at Copley Square!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's Back Bay neighborhood 6:30-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Afterwork mixer returns this Thursday February 12th. This time we are taking the party to City Bar, a stylish lounge located inside Copley Square's Lenox Hotel. City Bar is known for having the best martinis Boston has to offer! With Presidents day weekend approaching, this will be a great way to end the week  while enjoying cocktails with friends as we gear up for the holiday weekend! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also if you are a new member or have not yet been to an afterwork mixer, I encourage you to come out and see why this is one of the best meetups in Boston.  festive weekend in the city! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: We will meet at the front bar , please look for me upon entering, my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section. I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, with winter time in Boston this place will fill up fast!!&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Line to Copley&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to Backbay&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1235177149000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>65</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233892592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Afterwork Mixer This Thursday!!!</name><id>9685049</id><headcount>67</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234481400000</time><rsvp_limit>66</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/9685049/</event_url></item>