<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>3rd Floor</address_2><address_1>44 Portland Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.259712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-533-2847</phone><name>The Davis Art Gallery</name><city>Worcester</city><id>773622</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.801953</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Haven’t you ever wanted to see the inner workings of an artist studio? Are you curious about what it looks like behind the doors of the imaginative and inventive artist? Through his editorial style photography, Scott Erb captured of some of the most talented artists in Worcester County in their creative environments. Join us for an entertaining and revealing evening looking at the artist’s work and where they created it. What you find may surprise you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Join Us on &lt;b&gt;November 14, 2008 at the Davis Gallery at 44 Portland Street, Worcester MA&lt;/b&gt; 5-7:30PM for an enjoyable evening of fun, food, and art. You’ll meet and greet not only the photographer and writer of the book “The 20 Artists of Worcester,” - but also the artists themselves at this exhibition. We will be unveiling the book and Scott Erb &amp;amp; Julie Grady – will be there to sign them just for you. Plus - The gallery show of photographs by Scott Erb and artwork from each of the 20 Artists will be on display. An event not to be missed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wine and Hors D'oeuvres will be served. Yum…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can’t make the show? – Check out a preview of the book and portraits of the artists at our web site. (These are just portraits and not the studio images of the artists. Yup, it’s a teaser!) The 20 Artists of Worcester and their Work Spaces exhibition will run until Jan 23, 2009. So you can make an appointment to see the work or stop by during regular business hours to see the show, M-F 10AM-4PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Web Site for Book: &lt;a href="http://20artists.wordpress.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://20artists.word...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Erb – Erb Photography web site: &lt;a href="http://www.erbphoto.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.erbphoto.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please find us and say hello!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227230169000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222436197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scott Erb Book Signing and Gallery Show 20 Artists of Worcester</name><id>8837925</id><headcount>37</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226700000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/8837925/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/5/global_5650101.jpeg</photo_url></item>