<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>92 Derby St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.180264</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-740-2550</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Hingham</city><id>702244</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.907600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us at Panera Bread in Derry St Shopping Mall at 7pm for coffee and conversation about business and how to build our businesses.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My favorite tip of the bunch came from coach and speaker Gilda Bonanno:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Use a positive mantra. Rather than thinking negative thoughts before I begin to speak, like don’t screw up or what if I forget what I want to say?, I repeat my positive mantra as a means of boosting my confidence and focusing on the audience (because my speech should be about them, not me). I encourage people to find a mantra that is personally meaningful and believable. It could be a song title - Aretha Franklin’s 'Respect' comes to mind - a line from a poem, or anything that makes you feel powerful and confident. And it has to be strong enough to drown out the negative, 'joy-sucker' voice in your head that undermines your confidence and makes you less able to convey your knowledge and experience to the audience. My personal mantra is You go, girl! (accompanied by a mental fist in the air).&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take a minute to develop your personal pre-speech mantra - and share it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathleen A Bowman </member_name><member_id>7213289</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269990848000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-784</urlname><id>1149510</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9300003052</group_lon><name>Business networking and social meeting</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268153432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connecting thinking outside ourselves </name><id>12828713</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269817200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-784/events/12828713/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/7/3/global_13558979.jpeg</photo_url></item>