<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;An Evening with Lenny A musical tribute to Leonard Bernstein Doors open at 6:30 pm to begin Silent Auction. &amp;nbsp;Show begins at 7:30 pm The Lyric Stage Company of Boston 140 Clarendon Street, Boston Tickets: $40, $100, $250, $500 Order Tickets Now Who is the man the New York Times recognized as "one of the most prodigiously talented and successful musicians in American history," that&amp;rsquo;s Leonard Bernstein, Lenny to his friends. Tonight we honor the man who through his music, passion and inexhaustible zest for life became a household name and icon. He was an innovative, award-winning composer, conductor and multi-talented pianist. He was equally respected by Broadway Theater lovers, jazz aficionados and the classical music community. His Broadway musicals are legendary, and include &amp;lsquo;On the Town&amp;rsquo;, Wonderful Town, &amp;lsquo;Candide&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;West Side Story&amp;rsquo;. He packed many lives into his 72 years until his untimely death from lung cancer in 1990. On October 25th, you are in for a treat. Boston theatre celebrities Leigh Barrett, Brian De Lorenzo, Hildy Grossman, and Scott Wahle electrify the theatre performing Bernstein&amp;rsquo;s extraordinary songs of life, love and the human condition. Under the musical direction of Timothy Evans together with the visionary direction and choreography of Ilyse Robbins, you are in for a wonderful evening. Award-winning Arts and Entertainment Critic, Joyce Kulhawik, returns to weave her magic as the evening&amp;rsquo;s emcee. There will also be additional special guests, a silent auction and raffle (rumor has it there is a Bruins&amp;rsquo; hockey puck in the house).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please go to &lt;a href="http://www.UpstageLungCancer.org"&gt;www.UpstageLungCancer.org&lt;/a&gt; for more information, to purchase&amp;nbsp;a ticket, become a patron or a benefactor, or to be a volunteer for this event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>www.upstagelungcancer.org</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dale</member_name><member_id>3901963</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320405688000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>425314</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Jewish Singles 55+  of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315741437000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Upstage Lung Cancer</name><id>33082552</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319585400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston/events/33082552/</event_url></item>