<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The first Boston Atheist camping trip of the year! The reservation is for a group site from Friday June 11, 2010, 1pm (check-in) until Sunday June 13, 2010, 11am (check-out). Campers can show up on Saturday if you wish (just let us know in your RSVP). The campground is at Harold Parker State Park in North Andover Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a gorgeous park and not too far from Boston. There are trails and many other activities including swimming. Dogs can be brought as long as their vaccinations are current. Parking is limited so we hope to organize carpooling and the commuter rail is not too far! Pickups can be made from the Andover station. Bathrooms and showers are available! And there will definitely be S’mores! Maybe a few campfire tales from the camping vets will be told as well!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This park only has one group site location so we should have lots of room. If you can’t stay the night, you can come and spend the day Saturday. There is a commuter rail that comes to Andover and pickups are available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Supplies, food, camp activity items, and donations are greatly appreciated. Carpooling is available. Please message Jennifer Markowitz if you would like to participate and let her know where you live; you can contact her through her profile page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can donate a ride please message Jen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plans are underway to arrange a tent-sharing system; at least three extra tents will be available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're having a group dinner Saturday; other possible activities include a community service project; swimming; hiking; campfire S’mores fun; and board and ball games. And more! This is your camping trip; please don't be shy about letting the organizers know what you'd like to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are requiring $10.00 per-person fee to cover the cost of the reservation, food for Saturday's dinner, and part of the cost of firewood. You can Paypal the amount by following the link below, or you can pay Jennifer Markowitz in person when you arrive for the weekend. &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276637652000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266898467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Atheist Camping Weekend!</name><id>12680986</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276275600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/12680986/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>