<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>yes it's still the same old Pajama party but it's also Carol's birthday. So I had to change the name. Feel free to bring her some kind of silly gift. Not mandatory but make it something fun. She's turning 30 so we want it to be special for her. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back by popular demand - I'm not kidding. No less than 8 people have asked me to have another one of these. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;post-Holiday Party  for Gentiles, Jews, Muslims, Hindus, buddhists, Agnostics and Even athiests - Presbyterian's require special permission !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We strongly encourage flannels with cozy slippers.  Those not in festive garb will be required to sing for the rest of us.  After they clean the dishes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know what you plan on bringing so we don't get duplicates. Every guest doesn't have to bring a dish. We don't need that much food. So you can either bring a dish or BYOB as long as we share whatever arrives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK in the spirit of a Healthy new year. All food must be healthy... or at least not all sugar or fat. Let's make it a healthy lean new year.  Please ??? I need your help. Stop bringing yummy fattening food cuz I eat it when you leave. I have no willpower... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;gifts not necessary !&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy with the Santa Outfit</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295717213000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292844618000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Post Holiday Pajama Party – Carol's Birthday Party @ Roger's House </name><id>15778798</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295478000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/15778798/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/7/global_6044183.jpeg</photo_url></item>