<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;#9830; Do you often put others' needs before your own?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you find it challenging to assert yourself?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you agree to things you don't actually want out of guilt, obligation, or a fear of losing connection?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually think of boundaries as putting a wall of separation between us and others.&lt;br /&gt;What if there was a way to set clear boundaries that created more connection rather than less?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Learn why saying “no” is essential to getting what you want.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Learn a win-win negotiation technique to empower both parties.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Discover how staying in integrity with yourself can bring you closer to others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this playful, experiential workshop you will practice asking for what you want, staying true to yourself, and finding mutually enjoyable alternative outcomes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to beginners. Wear loose, comfortable clothing. Bring a journal, pen and water bottle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finding parking can be tricky in Harvard Square. Plan extra time or take the T.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; June 8, 7:30-9:30pm &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Across from 105 Brattle St Historic Longfellow House, on inbound side of circle. (Harvard Sq T) "Friends Room"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277089080000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273862687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healthy Boundaries: The Key to Having What You Want!</name><id>13485055</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276039800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/13485055/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/9/global_9117145.jpeg</photo_url></item>