<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Where: &lt;br /&gt;Lake waramaug&lt;br /&gt;New Preston &lt;br /&gt;New Preston Marble Dale , CT 06777&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;Join us for a day of kayaking at beautiful Lake Waramaug in New Preston Ct.!!! A large,GORGEOUS lake that has something for everyone!!! &lt;br /&gt;Kayaks are available for rent at a decent price, so even if you don't own one you can still join the fun!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALr's comment:&lt;br /&gt;These are the stable kind and another chance for those who didnt really fit well with mine to have a relaxing fit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or there is a small beach there for sunning...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I will bring all of my kayaks, but you have to reserve the one you know you can paddle...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok back to AnnMaries listing;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those with yaks, the launch facility is along side the road (not a great one) and then you have to move your vehicle to the parking lot across the street. We will meet up near the rent a kayak area! &lt;br /&gt;There is an entrance fee to the park if you don't have a state park pass! Please be there and ready to paddle by 11:00. I will be wearing a pink Yankee hat and you can reach my cell #860-309-3933 if there are any problems! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:From Litchfield- follow rt.118 to Litchfield. At the intersections of rts. 118 and 202 in Litchfield bear left onto rt.202. Follow rt.202 to New Preston. Take a right onto rt.45 and than a left onto North Shore road. Continue around lake to the park, taking Lake Warmamaug road to the lake Waramaug State  park entrance, its just past the campground . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;another way in is off of rte 45 you can take North Shore road to Lake Warmaug Rd..&lt;br /&gt;BUT as ALWAY LOOK AT YOUR MAPS FIRST..its a long way and ya dont want to waste the trip...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It may be a drive for some...but its soooo worth it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For mapquest/gps or others, use 300 Lake Waramaug Road, New Preston, CT to get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182869492000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182092497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak Event on Lake Warmaug</name><id>5901271</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182696300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5901271/</event_url></item>