<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skillful, Successful, Safe: Self Defense for Women Entrepreneurs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;$20 (WBOA Members receive $5 cash back at check-in)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP by Sunday, January 13, 2013 at Midnight.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever felt anxious about pitching a new client? Have you ever felt scared walking on a dark street? Would you be surprised to know that the skills to ace that presentation can also protect you from danger?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lynne Marie Wanamaker is a nationally recognized expert in empowerment-based self defense. Since 1991, she has taught hundreds of women and girls skills to avoid, neutralize, and respond to interpersonal violence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The self defense tool kit includes awareness, communication, fighting, and healing strategies. “These tools aren’t only important in worst-case scenarios,” says Lynne Marie. “Self defense training gives women the confidence to succeed in whatever they put their minds to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants should anticipate an accessible, dynamic presentation that will reinforce their expertise at keeping themselves safe and introduce new information and skills. By the conclusion of the workshop, participants will be able to assess personal safety risks, identify action steps to increase their security, and practice verbal assertiveness in everyday scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lynne Marie Wanamaker is a confident and dynamic anti-violence educator with over twenty years of experience developing and delivering training on topics of interpersonal violence. She is an engaging and sought-after public speaker, expert spokesperson, and author consulted by local media, including WHMP, WGBY, The Daily Hampshire Gazette, and The Springfield Republican.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lynne Marie holds a degree in Women’s Studies from the City University of New York. She was trained in empowerment-based self defense by the Center for Anti-Violence Education (CAE, Brooklyn, NY) and is certified by the National Women’s Martial Arts Federation (NWMAF). Lynne Marie has provided professional leadership to the NWMAF by mentoring emerging instructors, chairing the 2010 professional development conference, and co-authoring professional standards for self defense instructors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lynne Marie is an accomplished martial artist holding black belt rank in two styles of Okinawan karate. She earned certificates in group exercise instruction and personal fitness training from Holyoke Community College and also holds industry certification. She teaches self-protection skills for interrupting, neutralizing, and defending against interpersonal violence. As a personal trainer, Lynne Marie creates custom exercise programs for adults who want to be stronger and live longer. Find out more about upcoming programs at www.compassionateconditioning.com.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Parizo</member_name><member_id>5035</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361455188000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357010537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January Breakfast Meeting: Self Defense for Women Entrepreneurs</name><id>97273952</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>6300000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358426700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/97273952/</event_url></item>