<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>277-311 Boston Post Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06461</zip><lat>41.224731</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Topside Cafe</name><city>Milford</city><id>10953152</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.071640</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/8/8/event_192673192.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;During the last drive, J-Cuts, along with Topside Café in Milford, Eileen Henri’s Keith Urban “Monkeyville” members and Facebook fans and Joshua Sussan’s Troop 1 Milford Boy Scouts helped spread monkey love to children in need, abused &amp;amp; neglected children, impoverished, adopted and sick children, and frightened children involved in police calls, as well as children who may feel a little left out when a younger sibling is born. Children of Connecticut Army National Guard soldiers deployed during the Valentine holiday also received stuffed monkeys.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 6th Annnual Monkey Love Valentine Drive, held in 2012, collected and distributed 907 stuffed monkeys to the A.C.T./Spooner House Homeless Shelter, Department of Family &amp;amp; Children’s Aid Shelton &amp;amp; Danbury Safe Homes, the Shelton Police Department, Bridgeport Hospital, Griffin Hospital, Yale New Haven Children’s Hospital, Casey Family Services, Covenant to Care for Children and the Lower Naugatuck Valley Boys &amp;amp; Girls Club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year, in addition to collecting for children in need serviced by local organizations, the coordinators would like to offer some monkey love to the children of Sandy Hook Elementary School in Newtown. They are hoping for a very successful collection this year so they can continue to spread the monkey love to as many children in need as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topside Café in Milford holds an annual “Monkey Love Sunday” on the Sunday before Superbowl. For 2013, the celebration will take place on Sunday, January 27th from 1 pm to 5 pm. Topside Cafe is located at 333 Boston Post Road. Everyone is invited to attend for food, fun and raffles. The "cover charge" is at least one new stuffed monkey. Local Milford and Shelton Pubs are also encouraged to join in by holding a "Monkey Love Sunday" event of their own. &lt;br /&gt;

TO ALL MY MEETUP FRIENDS PLEASE STOP DOWN AND DROP OFF A STUFFED MONKEY FOR THESE KIDS THAT DON'T FEEL THE LOVE AT VALENTINE'S DAY--ALSO KIDS ARE WELCOME AT THIS MEETUP. &lt;br /&gt;

THANKS LENNY M.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359373965000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357234331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MONKEY LOVE SUNDAY</name><id>97699332</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359309600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/97699332/</event_url></item>