<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Updated on 8/22/2010:&lt;br /&gt;Here is &lt;a href="http://www.baxterstateparkauthority.com/hiking/hikingParking.html" target="_blank"&gt;Baxter State Park web page to make a reservation for your car's Parking Lot&lt;/a&gt; if you visit state park on the day of the hike without camping.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm planning to visit Maine for multiple day hikes.  Let's hike to several High Peaks in Maine together!!    &lt;br /&gt;The mountains which I highlighted in &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;red&lt;/span&gt; are listed in NE 4K footers and in &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;blue&lt;/span&gt; are listed as NE HH (New England 100 Highest).   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is cross posted event from my own hiking meetup - &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hiking-490"&gt;Hike/Snowshoe Vermont Meetup&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Day-4 hiking event description to peakbag 4 particular High Peaks: &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;North Brother  (4151 ft)&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;South Brother (3970 ft), Mount Coe (3795 ft) and Fort Mountain (3867 ft)&lt;/span&gt; in Baxter State Park.  North and South Brother are open peaks that offer splendid views in several directions.  Mount Coe is located Southeast from South Brother and it has excellent views into the Klondike and is well worth the challenging of the climb.  Fort Mountain requires bushwhacking from North Brother for approx. less than 2 miles RT.  This is another strenuous and challenging hike!  &lt;br /&gt;You can join us only one of my Maine hiking events or all which is up to you.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Hiking Plan:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) This is loop trip hike which doesn't require car spot. &lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the parking lot of Marston Tr trailhead in Baxter State Park &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;at 7:00AM.&lt;/span&gt;  and start hiking at &lt;u&gt;7:15AM sharp&lt;/u&gt;.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Here is my brief plan to take multiple trails to grab 4 mountain peaks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Marston Trail to the trail junction of Mt Coe Tr, 1.3 mi (50 min) &lt;br /&gt;* Continue on Marston Tr to the 2nd trail junction of Mt Coe Tr. &lt;br /&gt;* North Brother summit, 3.7 mi (3 hr) &lt;br /&gt;* Fort Mtn northwestern summit, 4.7 mi (4 hr) &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;- bushwhacking!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Return to North Brother, 5.7 mi (5 Hr) &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;- bushwhacking!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* South Brother summit via Mt Coe Tr, 7.5 mi (6 Hr 20 min) &lt;br /&gt;* Mt Coe summit via Mt Coe Tr, 9 mi (7 Hr 30 min) &lt;br /&gt;* Return to the parking lot of Marston Tr trailhead, 11 mi (9 Hr 30 min) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: distance is cumulative mileage and inside parenthesis is cumulative book time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Hiking Level:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Moderate  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking Distance:  Approx. 11 miles  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking Pace:  Slow to Moderate &lt;br /&gt;Hiking Hours: 9.5 hours + Lunch 30min + Break Time (Of course, hiking hours varies depending on your hiking pace) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;One of my hiking mates told me this would be very challenging hike and she recommends I split this hiking plan into 2 separate hiking plan because it includes bushwhacking.  I'm going to do more research on this hike to determine which is better.  Depending on my searching result, I may split this hike into 2 days hike.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Suggested Meetup Locations:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) We'll meet at the parking lot of Marston Trail trailhead &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;at 7AM&lt;/span&gt; on Park Tote Road in Baxter State Park.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2)  I booked motel for 9/11 night stay at Kathadin Inn &amp;amp; Suites in Millinocket, ME.  We can possibly meet at this Motel's Parking Lot &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;at 5:30AM&lt;/span&gt; before entering the State Park for carpool if anyone preferred.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kathadin Inn &amp;amp; Suites&lt;br /&gt;740 Central Street&lt;br /&gt;Millinocket, ME 04462&lt;br /&gt;Toll Free: 877-902-4555&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 207-723-4555&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 207-723-6480&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://katahdininnandsuites.com/"&gt;http://katahdininnand...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=740+Central+St,+Millinocket,+Maine&amp;amp;daddr=45.939094,-69.041176&amp;amp;geocode=FeWsuAIdV9Tn-ynh2AocWbO6TDFgX0yxVt4iqA%3B&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=dme&amp;amp;mrcr=0&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=14&amp;amp;sll=45.924588,-69.037485&amp;amp;sspn=0.050689,0.057249&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=14"&gt;the google map from Kathadin Inn &amp;amp; Suites, in Millinocket, Maine to The trailhead of Marston Trail in Baxter State Park.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is obvious if you've done enough research regarding day hike in Baxter State Park, but, here are some useful information for you just in case: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) In Baxter State Park, you'll get water from brook or river only.  It means you'll need water filter or something in order to drink it.   I recommend you bring enough water before you get into the park if you don't have water filter or some other treatment stuff. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) The nearest campground to get to Marston Trail trailhead is Kathadin Stream Campground (5.9 mi South from the trailhead).  If you'd like to stay there, please book sites by yourself ASAP.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, please feel free to drop me an email.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer,     &lt;br /&gt;Tomoko Nakajima&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Updated on 08/10/2010:  Updated the Motel Information.  Also, google map is updated from Kathadin Inn &amp;amp; Suites to the trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My Car is Honda CR-V (Blue)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284377886000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281324944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Multiple Day-Hiking Events in Maine - Day 4: The Brothers, Mt Coe and Fort Mtn</name><id>14362494</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284289200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14362494/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/1/0/global_17056368.jpeg</photo_url></item>