<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 School Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.567486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Custom Heat LLC</name><city>Danvers</city><id>9792522</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.936180</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you heard of 3D printing?  It's a technology and movement whereby special machines can create actual objects in 3 dimensions.  Real life objects such as hooks you can hang your coat on, utensils you can use to eat with and a variety of other things that you probably encounter on a day to day basis and could get from Walmart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But did you also know that 3D printing is part of a larger democratic movement to empower people to make their own stuff, reduce energy needs and strengthen community through openness and sharing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-sponsored by the North Shore T.E.C.H. group this afternoon's presentation and discussion will explore what 3D printing is and how it can empower you and your community.  We'll touch upon how the technology's ecological effects, how it can be used to create sustainability, resiliency, bring back local manufacturing, etc.  We'll also show the printer in action, show off some things that can be made and talk about how this movement is coming to Danvers, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope you can join us for this unique look into a special technology that can be used in community development and reinvention. :-)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>look for the North Shore TECH sign in the alley next to the building</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358080953000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357703115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creating Sustainability and Community through 3D Printing: a Discussion</name><id>98678512</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358017200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/98678512/</event_url></item>