<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Tour of the Property: Nathaniel Hawthorne's Birthplace &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GENERAL TOUR (before the program - recommended start time no later than 5pm) $12 ($11 for Seniors and AAA members) - no advance purchase or reservation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nathaniel Hawthorne YEAR BUILT: 1750&lt;br /&gt;STYLE: Georgian&lt;br /&gt;BUILT FOR: Unknown&lt;br /&gt;MOVED TO ITS CURRENT SITE: 1958&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This house was originally located a few blocks from here on Union Street. It was moved to this location in 1958 with the assistance of architectural historian and conservator, Abbott Lowell Cummings. While not a particularly fine example of Georgian architecture, this house is best known for one famous inhabitant. It was here, in this modest home, that Nathaniel Hawthorne was born on July 4th 1804 to Elizabeth and Nathaniel Hathorne. Tragically, Nathaniel's father, a sea captain, died while on a voyage when Nathaniel was only five years old. This left Elizabeth with three small children and little wealth. She and her children were left no alternative but to move out of this house and accept the charity of her family, the Mannings. Elizabeth Hathorne was not alone in losing her husband on an ocean voyage. In the late 1700's upwards of one in four women were widows who had lost their men to the sea. As an adult, Nathaniel Hawthorne found a literary outlet for this early childhood trauma. Many of the characters in his novels have suffered the loss of one or both parents, and are dependant on the goodwill of others for support. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RECOMMENDED PROGRAMS - these sound like good spooky fun:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Legacy of the Hanging Judge - Named one of the 2005 Top 100 Group Events by the American Bus Association at 7:15pm $14 or $25 if combined with Spirits below - ADVANCED RESERVATION REQUIRED DIRECTLY WITH THE SITE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1692 the Salem Witch Trials wrought havoc on a small New England Community. Relive these events - in their own words! This show takes place in the Nathaniel Hawthorne House, where you will be interrogated by magistrate, John Hathorne, Hawthorne's great-great grandfather, who is infamous for his role in the condemnation and deaths of so many people. From there, encounter the tormented, the accused and their accusers in this interactive theatrical experience. Beware, you may find yourself being accused of &amp;quot;writing in the devil's book!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spirits of the Gables at 8:15pm $14 or $25 if combined with Legacy above - ADVANCED RESERVATION REQUIRED DIRECTLY WITH THE SITE&lt;br /&gt;Guilt! Greed! Revenge! Enter the world of Nathaniel Hawthorne's burdened characters from his classic The House of the Seven Gables, as they haunt the hallways of their eerie mansion. Witness two families entangled in a curse as Matthew Maule condemns Colonel Pyncheon with the very words destined to become his fate and follow his family for nearly 150 years; &amp;quot;God will give you blood to drink!&amp;quot; Travel through this house at your own risk, for as long as there is a Pyncheon descendant inside, only darkness and death will fill its walls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND...since it's a Saturday, we could go a bit earlier, stroll the town and have an early bite to eat.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I may be a witch that day/evening,  but I'm tall and have strawberry blonde hair</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen</member_name><member_id>3330386</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy </member_name><member_id>3699089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225493670000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>travel-575</urlname><id>418980</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Old and Not so Old Ladies Travel</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219166641000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>House of the Seven Gables in Salem!</name><id>8577268</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224352800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/travel-575/events/8577268/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/8/global_5217096.jpeg</photo_url></item>