<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;So you'd like to teach a class or a workshop--on art or writing or another topic, at ArtStudio 360 or somewhere else. Or perhaps you'd like to run a demo at one of our group's regular Meetups or lead a workshop at our annual retreat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Workshops 101 will provide you with some basic guidelines on the best way to develop and run a one-session class. You'll learn how to:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose the right focus and craft a great workshop name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decide what to include and what to leave out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a great workshop description&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare for and kick off your workshop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage participants individually and as a group&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid or address common challenges during class&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send participants home fired up to continue on their own&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If interest warrants it, we'll also discuss how to promote your workshop. I'll invite participants to share their workshop-teaching tips and experiences, too. You'll go home with handouts filled with tips and more resources to explore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;ArtStudio members: Free (this is a benefit for Studio members). Non-members: $15--cash or local check made to "ArtStudio 360."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; Note-taking materials, if you're so inclined. Dinner, if you won't have time to eat before class.&amp;nbsp;(Please note: We won't order out during this session, so please do make arrangements to either dine beforehand or bring your own food.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND&lt;/strong&gt;: Anyone (18+ only, please). No previous teaching experience necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt; Reserve a place for yourself and any guests by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; If we need to cancel due to bad weather or other reasons, we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOUR INSTRUCTOR:&lt;/strong&gt; I am a part-time communications professor at Lasell College in Newton and have also taught at Boston University, Northeastern University and Emerson College. I've been a faculty member at the Cambridge Center for Adult Education for more than 20 years and have taught 100+ writing and art workshops there, in other adult-ed programs and at conferences and retreats. I've also run training workshops for various employers over the past 25 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my workshop-teaching career, I've had many successes and a few flops. I hope my experiences from both ends of the spectrum will help you as you develop your own workshops.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter through front door or door off parking lot; proceed up stairs to ArtStudio 360 (unfortunately, no elevator)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327512602000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321560455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshops 101: An introduction to creating and running a great class</name><id>41542632</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327447800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/41542632/</event_url></item>