<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Amazing System That Compels Members Of The Opposite Sex to Approach You &lt;br /&gt;First For a Date No Matter Your Looks, Age, Race or Income.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus Where to Meet Them, What to Say, and How to Never Be Rejected Ever Again...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sick of having to face rejection, not knowing exactly what to say?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dating can be very difficult and stressful and its not your fault.&amp;nbsp; I stumbled on a simple system that I am going to teach you that compels strangers to want to meet you so you have to do almost no work to get fantastic dates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine   being the center of attention where you don't have to approach strangers.&amp;nbsp; The person you want approaches you. You will surprise yourself with how easy and   effortless it  is to strike up conversations with total strangers and   get to know  them once they approach you.  Once you have this skill, you'll be able to make   friends and  attract lovers anywhere you go, anytime you want.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to create situations where &lt;strong&gt;people will&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;throw themselves at you, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;without you having to approach them or face rejection.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The simple steps to create a special event that will &lt;strong&gt;feed you hot dates &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;and make you the &amp;ldquo;popular and in demand&amp;rdquo; person everyone wants a piece of&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The simple secrets of becoming approachable so member of the opposite sex want to talk to you. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to develop an almost &lt;strong&gt;Celebrity-Like Reputation&lt;/strong&gt; for yourself so you get approached and asked out on dates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A simple system that compels members of the opposite sex to approach you and strike up conversations so you never have to worry about rejection again. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The    meeting is limited to 35 people due to the size limitations of the    classroom (we'll be moving around a lot).  Our meetings usually sell out    quickly, so here's what I recommend.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your   calendar right now, and see if you have &lt;strong&gt;Sunday, May 29th&lt;/strong&gt; available.    The meeting runs from &lt;strong&gt;3:30pm to 5:30pm&lt;/strong&gt; and is conveniently located in   Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.    &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#2    - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this  workshop   right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They  always do.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#3   - Write it in your calendar so you remember to  attend, and please   arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal  networking.   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The   cost of the event is only $20, which is a  bargain for a professional   training that includes these skill-building  drills + personality   feedback.  Please remember to bring:  &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20 cash &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Eric &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;P.S.    - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the    event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you    should have no problems.  My cell is: 617-903-7371. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door. The signs will point you to the room. Its the big lecture room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Edgemont</member_name><member_id>12651136</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nick Richards</member_name><member_id>12716842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311727506000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306183217000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Get Them to Approach YOU</name><id>19434581</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306697400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/19434581/</event_url></item>