<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ciao! Bonjour! Hola! Hallo! Witaj! Salut! Hello!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who want to enjoy a walk outdoors with good friends, followed by a drink or two, then this is a meetup for you. The starting point of the walk will be outside La Luna Cafe which is across the fire station and half a block from McDonalds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start our walk at Central Square and head towards MIT and Kendall Square. Then we will head back to Central Square and continue on to Harvard Square. We will rest and buy drinks/food at Harvard Square. Then we will head back to Central Square. This walk will be longer than our first walk this summer. We will take a few minutes to walk around the MIT campus and the Harvard campus. Harvard and MIT grads/profs should come and give us a quick tour of their campuses!! [please mention if you are a grad/prof of these schools in your rsvp]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it rains that day, 07/20th, then the event will be rescheduled for the next Sunday 07/27th. &lt;br /&gt;Please join us!! There is no limit to the number of members who can join us on the walk. Great opportunity to meet members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to take this moment to thank Noelle and Maia for hosting great summer parties at their residences. Also much thanks to those who attended and made our summer parties a real blast. We have an eclectic group and we encourage all to come out and meet other members of the Euro Social meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is easy to find in Central square and inexpensive. The Green Street Garage is located at the corner of Green St. and Pearl St. Enter the garage by going down Pearl St. for one block (Pearl St. is parallel to Prospect St., one block east of Prospect St.) and then taking a right onto Green St. The entrance to the garage is on your left. This garage is only $1 per hour to a maximum of $8. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 3 municipal lots along Bishop Allen Drive that are free after 6:00 pm on weekdays and they are free on weekends. There is also a very large private lot on Prospect Street that is free and open to the public after 5:00 pm. There is an open-air city parking lot across Mass Ave behind Blockbuster Video (Bishop Allen Drive and Norfolk Street), and another open-air lot across Mass Ave behind Quest Diagnostics/McDonalds (Bishop Allen Drive and Douglass Street). In both of these lots, the meters go off at 6pm so parking is FREE in the weekday evenings. Public parking is free at the meters and Public parking lots all day Sundays.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be sitting outside La Luna Cafe. My cell is 508 498 1651 if you are late.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216753561000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215457940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Walk &amp; Drinks</name><id>8292963</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216580400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/8292963/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/3/global_1218899.jpeg</photo_url></item>