<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I've had some communication with Larry about his interest in facilitating or optimizing the flow of ideas during our topical meetings, and I agree that it is sometimes difficult for participants to get a word in edgewise. We've exchanged a few ideas on how we can improve the experience and, perhaps, create a new format that, like the Impromptu Philosophizer, might recur periodically. This particular Impromptu will seek feedback, brainstorm ideas and perhaps reach some consensus, but discussion format need not be the sole topic of the meeting.&amp;nbsp; Should the &lt;em&gt;Group Will&lt;/em&gt; desire&amp;nbsp; more philosophical philosophizing it will not (cannot) be denied!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The regular Impromptu Philosophizer introduction follows&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An  Impromptu Philosophizer is a casual meeting at a cafe or pub that may  or may not have a specific topic, and may even be scheduled &amp;ldquo;on the spur  of the moment!"  It's great to know that there is now a way for  philosophically minded people to meet but with no particular agenda  other than that of satisfying the need to talk about what's on your  mind.  Whether the interest or concern involves current events or  politics, cultural or intellectual issues, personal stuff, pure  philosophy or whatever else is on your mind we can all benefit from  sharing philosophical perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Therapy for the sane," a term used by Gerd Achenbach (founder of the modern &lt;a href="http://www.integralhypnosis.com/philosophical_counseling.htm" target="_blank"&gt;philosophical counseling&lt;/a&gt; movement), may partially suggest the Impromptu Philosophizer concept  but it is more multifaceted than, say, an occasional "therapy" session  after a trying day.  IPs are designed to be fun, engaging and unique  opportunities for creating a near spontaneous venue to meet other group  members for the purpose of sharing thoughts, ideas and concerns from a  philosophical perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Impromptu Philosophizers are  spontaneous, existentially driven meetings and discussions.  Of course,  continue to check back often for the scheduling of the somewhat more  structured, topical meetings  that are regularly scheduled by Boston  Area Philosophy Discussions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIAL NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; By its  very nature, an Impromptu Philosophizer may often have a small turnout.  Accordingly, in order to prevent situations in which the event host  arrives and there is no one else who shows up, in some cases those who  'Yes" RSVP may be asked to email a further confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture (Look for the Meetup sign.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304726399000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301415022000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Impromptu Philosophizer</name><id>17101647</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302562800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/17101647/</event_url></item>