<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1227 Burnside Avenue Suite 1</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.783787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-888-4314</phone><name>The Conduit Center</name><city>East Hartford</city><id>1228246</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.585075</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Harmonic Meditation Concert&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Vibrations of Breath, Sound &amp;amp; Voice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cultivate a spirit of Harmony - in the world, in oneself and for all beings – at the Harmonic Meditation Concert in Wickham Park, Saturday May 8, 2010 in East Hartford CT. This event is a blend of sacred chant, breath meditation, and sound healing for harmony, peace and understanding. By creating an awareness and attunement to essential nature of Harmony, we can &amp;quot;listen in&amp;quot; to the deeper nature of self and reality.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Held in the open spaces of beautiful Wickham Park, participants will attune to three aspects of harmonics: contemplative practices of sitting and walking; sound healing using ancient gongs and Tibetan bowls; and sacred voice, or kirtan, a participatory mantra singing experience. The concert, sponsored by The Conduit Sound Mind Sound Body Center, seeks to develop mindfulness, compassion, and greater potential through universal vibrations with the cosmos.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two special guests will join The Conduit. For 15 years, Bret Duback has organized concerts and retreats in Kundalini yoga and sacred chant. He is the organizer of the annual 700 Voices Yoga &amp;amp; Music Festival (700voices.com) which is an outdoor weekend camping event happening June 12, 2010. Christine Ucich, a Taoist Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation instructor, leads workshops on Taoist meditation and transformational breathwork. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$8 donation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Conduit Sound Mind Sound Body Center,  &lt;br /&gt;1227 Burnside Avenue, East Hartford CT 06108&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Participants will meet at The Conduit Center at 9:30 am.  &lt;br /&gt;Questions? Please contact owen@gongtheplanet.com or call 860.888.4314 &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273610700000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271265960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harmonic Meditation Concert</name><id>13181902</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273325400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/13181902/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/a/global_14374058.jpeg</photo_url></item>