<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187114</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>Richard Tosti Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>826225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236877</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>5 high integrity men wanted. We achieved women's quota. No more women.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE BEST OF BOTH WORLDS – If you’d like to talk quietly, privately with the new friends you meet at this Singles Dinner/Dance Party, there’s a cozy, warm, newly-redecorated, separate, private room measuring 30' x 20' available that’s quiet and isolated from the dance floor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DANCE THIS HOLIDAY WEEKEND - A member suggested I schedule this Singles Dinner/Dance Party this holiday weekend. He said, “Many people don’t go away.&amp;quot; So, since I'm one of them, let's see if there’s interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR ENERGY WILL SOAR AGAIN - We’ll live our dream this one special night. For we know that accomplishments start with a dream. So, dare to dream!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INVITE SOMEONE YOU KNOW - I’d be especially pleased if you’d invite a wonderful male friend. Our objective is always to achieve a 50-50 ratio of men and women. So let’s redouble our efforts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LARRY, OUR DYNAMIC DJ - Will be back again at this Singles Dinner/Dance Party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Theme - Tropical Dreams&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This weekend’s Singles Dinner/Dance Party will have a Tropical Theme. Imagine the Caribbean. We’re strolling along, mesmerized by the warm blue waters. There is a hot sultry breeze, and you’re holding the Love of your Life in your arms. You’re passionate, and your bodies are beating against each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you feel it? There’s not a molecule of oxygen between you and your Partner. You feel an intoxicating connection. Do you feel the embrace, the laughter, the joy, the carefree spirit of being in love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s that feeling of having total trust in someone, believing in them and sharing each other’s deepest feelings and thoughts. Nothing else matters except gazing into each other’s eyes with the expectation of embracing the entire night and into the morning, being one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allow yourself to trust and dream the dream. Do you feel it? Do you see it? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;What is she wearing, what are you wearing? Her colored blouse and white shorts. Your white slacks and colored flowered shirt. Do you see it?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please wear it September 4th. Please dress just the way you would when you’re with the Love of your Life on a wonderful tropical Caribbean island paradise. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WOMEN - When a man sees you, he’ll be so dazzled that he’ll stumble on his words or forget what to say.  Please have patience, he’ll recover and make sense in a moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVERYONE - Be yourself, don’t be a cliché.  Be honest about your age, marital status, job, and education. If you lie, you’ll just attract dishonest people.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;LEARN TO “DO WITHIN WHEN WE ARE DOING WITHOUT” - Imagine this wonderful person. Where are you with them? It might not be the Caribbean, but it could be Cape Cod. Perhaps it’s going to a movie, dining out, walking in the park, having coffee at Starbucks, or just having a new friend visit you at home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See it, feel it, and we’ll achieve it!&lt;br /&gt;__________________________________&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Our Values&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE ARE PRINCIPLE-CENTERED - We are high integrity, are honesty, reliable, positive, non-judgmental, gentle, kind, cheerful, friendly, and respectful toward everyone. We use private Singles Dinner/Dance Parties as a vehicle to meet other singles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our purpose is to socialize with other principle-centered people in our age range (30-65) who are also searching for a lifetime partner.  Let’s have fun meeting old and new friends. Circulate, and talk to everyone. If someone is alone, introduce yourself and say hi!  Please be Friendly, Positive, and Optimistic to everyone.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• THE YES DANCE - Please be respectful and dance at least one time with anyone who asks you.  This is our No. 1 value.  If you’re willing and able to say yes, then this will be a great event for you to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•  INVITE OTHER FRIENDS, PARTICULARLY MEN - Our objective is to have an equal amount of men and women.  Our Singles Dinner/Dance Parties are always close to equal numbers of men and women. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it a truly memorable dance party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fees &amp;amp; Food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ENTRY FEE - $15 (pay at door), plus wine or food assignment as listed below.&lt;br /&gt;Your option, if you’re unable to bring anything, is to pay a $30 entry fee.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DRESS CODE - Summer Casual&lt;br /&gt;DATE - Saturday - Sept. 4th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;TIME - 7:30PM - 11:00pm&lt;br /&gt;PLACE - Temple Shalom Emeth - 16 Lexington St. - Burlington, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MAXIMUM ATTENDEES – 80 People&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MUSIC - Dance music by DJ&lt;br /&gt;APPETIZERS - 7:45PM&lt;br /&gt;PIZZA BUFFET - 8:15PM&lt;br /&gt;FOOD RESTRICTION - No pork or shellfish&lt;br /&gt;OPEN BAR - Wine &amp;amp; Beer &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food assignments will be given two days prior to event. If your last name begins with the following letter please bring the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;APPETIZER, WINE/SODA, DESSERT - Food requests are altered every month. Next time you’ll be assigned other selections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A THROUGH C - Wine (Minimum of $10)&lt;br /&gt;D THROUGH N - Pizza (large size)&lt;br /&gt;O THROUGH T - Desserts (pies, apple, blueberry, lemon meringue), your favorite, cakes, (no cookies)&lt;br /&gt;U THROUGH Z - Healthy appetizers (Salad) or 4 bottles of soda/One gallon water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location &amp;amp; Directions&lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth, 16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;1. Go 128-North, take Exit 32B (Middlesex Turnpike - Burlington/Arlington).&lt;br /&gt;2. At the end of the ramp, turn right onto Middlesex Turnpike - see Barnes/Noble on your left.&lt;br /&gt;3. Drive along the Burlington Mall.&lt;br /&gt;4. Turn right at the lights onto Burlington Mall Rd. - see Longs Jewelers on left.&lt;br /&gt;5. Pass Kohl’s on your left, and take an immediate left onto Lexington Street&lt;br /&gt;6. Temple Shalom Emeth is on your left at16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: There are two parking lots on the right side of building.  Enter through the side entrance at the end of the building.  There’s a third parking lot is across the street - McGinnis Ave. - Mt Hope Church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you soon. The best is yet to be!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;Your Organizer/Host/Coach&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;President&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti Associates&lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road&lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA 02090&lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286063057000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>74</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280638067000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Private Singles Dance Party 30-65</name><id>14277611</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283643000000</time><rsvp_limit>80</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/14277611/</event_url></item>