<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biopharmaceutical Summit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;When: March 9, 2012&lt;/span&gt;  Where: Inn &amp;amp; Conference Center, Lowell MA (Univ. of Massachusetts Lowell)  &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Registration: email&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="mailto:bpqc@uml.edu" target="_blank" style="color : #704525"&gt;bpqc@uml.edu&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;The main theme of the biopharmaceutical summit is to address how to overcome hurdles and challenges, and drive innovation in biopharmaceutical manufacturing. The covered topics will include:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;* Challenges in biopharmaceutical development and manufacturing&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;* Innovative technologies for overcoming challenges and hurdles&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;* Implementation of innovative technology for advanced manufacturing&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;* Next generation biopharmaceutical process&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Who will be participating?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;This one-day workshop will mark the very first annual event of the Biopharmaceutical Process and Quality Consortium, which kicked off in October, 2011. Expected summit participants are scientists and engineers from biopharmaceutical manufacturers, technology/system providers, raw material suppliers and agencies in the area of development, manufacturing, and engineering. Via this workshop, we hope professionals and leaders of biopharmaceutical industry get together and talk about challenges in manufacturing and development, new breakthrough, and share success stories. It will be also a great chance to network with professionals from major biopharmaceutical manufacturers and various technology providers such as Biogen Idec, Genzyme, Pfizer, Momenta, Millipore, GE, SAFC and more!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Featured Speakers and talks&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Jorg Thommes, Vice President of Global Engineering at Biogen Idec and Robert Steininger, head of manufacturing and operations at Acceleron Pharmaceutical will give featured presentations on "Challenges of Biopharmaceutical Manufacturing and Development". Learn about the case studies of what challenges these great companies were facing and how successfully they are managing. In addition, Prof. Betenbaugh of John Hopkins University will talk about groundbreaking Genomics research of CHO cells. This will provide significant advances in biopharmaceutical research and development&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Registration&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;This event provides a unique venue for attendees to learn about biopharmaceutical challenges and novel technologies that shape the industry. For registration, please send an email to&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a style="color : #704525"&gt;bpqc@uml.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;with "registration" in the subject. Registration fee is $200 per person. Payment options for the fee will be arranged soon.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-----------------------&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Featured Speakers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style="color : #704525"&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Jorg Thommes, PhD, Vice President of Global Engineering, Biogen Idec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Dr. William E. Bentley, Robert E. Fischell Distinguished Professor and Chair, Fischell Department of Bioengineering of the University of Maryland, college Park&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Bob Steininger, Head of Manufacturing and Operations, Accerolon Pharmaceuticals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Dr. Michael J. Betenbaugh, Professor of Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering at Johns Hopkins University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distinguished Speakers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style="color : #704525"&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Rajesh Beri, PhD, Director of Manufacturing Sciences and Technology Department, Lonza Biologics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Alex Fotopoulos, Sr. Director of Manufacturing Technology, Momenta Pharmaceutical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Cenk Undey, PhD, Director of Process Development, Amgen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Brian Lee, PhD, President and CEO of PBS biotech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Tom Fletcher, Director of Cell Culture R&amp;amp;D, Irvine Scientific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Rahul Godawat, PhD, Process Scientist of Downstream Development, Genzyme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Tim Johnson, PhD, Manager of Process Development, Genzyme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Magdalena Leszczyniecka, PhD, CEO, STC BIOLOGICS,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Mark Plavsic, PhD, Corporate Bio-Safety Advisor Genzyme Biopharmaceutical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;Consortium faculties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #704525"&gt;20~30 Posters by graduate students and researchers of Biopharmaceutical consortium.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;For questions, email&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="mailto:bpqc@uml.edu" target="_blank" style="color : #704525"&gt;bpqc@uml.edu&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;For detailed information,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #704525"&gt;http://seongkyu-yoon.wiki.uml.edu/Biopharmaceutical+Summit&lt;/a&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331302977000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329278267000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Biopharmaceutical Summit</name><id>52399062</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331298000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/52399062/</event_url></item>