<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>RAW LUCK Event: Raw pot luck and raw chef presentations!&lt;br /&gt;November 13, Tuesday. Arrive at 5:30 PM. Eat at 6:00. Presentations at 7:00. Ends 9 PM.&lt;br /&gt;Raw Chefs teach how to Plan a Healthy Thanksgiving Dinner.  &lt;br /&gt;At Presbyterian Church, downstairs dining room, at 34 Alder St, one block off Moody Street, in Waltham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All those attending are requested to bring a raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal based (vegan with no honey) ready- to-serve dish for 6 - 8 people.  Please bring serving utensils labeled with your name and a typed or neatly printed recipe to display next to your dish.  The fee is $5 to cover Meetup site cost and paperware/plasticware costs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP necessary to Betsy Bragg at bbski@stanfordalumni.org or call 781-899-6664.&lt;br /&gt;Note: there is also a November 10, Tuesday event so please specify which you are going to attend. Please be sure to give your postal address, phone number &amp;amp; email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presenters of the Tuesday, November 13th RAW-LUCK event:&lt;br /&gt;Adrienne Martin of Abundant Living (main speaker) and other chefs including Sparkle Richardson of Veggie Mundo Caterers, Susan Bowen of Life-Giving Raw Foods,  Marie-Alice Johnson of Alice's Cuisine and Rosana Gijsen, private raw food chef, will teach us their favorite holiday recipes. Samples will be available with handouts to help replicate these wonderful taste sensations in your own home.  Each chef is providing recipes for a complete holiday menu (5 menus of recipes in all).  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278886791000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192818699000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Raw Luck Meetup November 13 Tuesday</name><id>6580817</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194993000000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/6580817/</event_url></item>