<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>486 Chandler Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.268673</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester State University</name><city>Worcester</city><id>3350762</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.841370</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Brian Skerry is one of the BEST photography speakers I have ever seen. If you can make this lecture - do it. You won't regret it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;National Geographic Underwater Photographer Brian Skerry presents Ocean Soul&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Thursday, September 20, 2012, 4 – 5pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Location&lt;/span&gt; Helen G. Shaughnessy Administration Building – Fuller Theater (2nd Floor) 
&lt;p&gt;Ocean Soul is a love story. It is a story of discovery. It is a story of hope. The story begins when a boy who loves the sea attends an event with underwater photographers and has an epiphany: “I had always wanted to explore the oceans, but I now understood how I would do this. I would do it with a camera.” With sheer deter­mination, hard work, and a little bit of luck the boy, named Brian Skerry, realized his dream with more than 20 awe-inspiring articles for National Geographic magazine. Now, with Ocean Soul, he showcases his stunning photography and describes his adventurous life in a gripping portrait of the ocean as a place of beauty and mystery, a place in trouble, and ultimately, a place of hope that will rebound with the proper attention and care. Free and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brian Skerry is a photojournalist specializing in marine wildlife and underwater environments. Since 1998 he has been a contract photographer for National Geographic Magazine covering a wide range of subjects and stories. Skerry was born and raised in Central Massachusetts. He graduated with a Bachelor of Arts in media and communications from Worcester State College in 1984.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An award-winning photographer, Brian is praised worldwide for his aesthetic sense as well as his journalistic drive for relevance. His uniquely-creative images tell stories that not only celebrate the mystery and beauty of the sea, but also help bring attention to the large number of issues that endanger our oceans and its inhabitants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.worcester.edu/newsnmedia/calendar.htm?trumbaEmbed=view%3Devent%26eventid%3D101438589" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.worcester.edu/newsnmedia/calendar.htm?trumbaEmbed=view%3Devent%26eventid%3D101438589&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Location: Helen G. Shaughnessy Administration Building – Fuller Theater (2nd Floor)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348409174000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347910319000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Geographic Underwater Photographer Brian Skerry presents Ocean Soul</name><id>82821372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348171200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/82821372/</event_url></item>