<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I've completely failed to keep track of the specific start time for this film.  Thanks to Bruce D. for the heads up.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tokyo Sonata starts at &lt;b&gt;1:20 pm&lt;/b&gt;.  Please note the earlier start time.  I apologize for the mess I've made of this meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can stilll make it, and join us for conversation after the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tokyosonatamovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Tokyo Sonata Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;KIYOSHI KUROSAWA DIRECTOR/WRITER&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Born on July 19, 1955 in Kobe, Hyogo Prefecture, Japan, Kurosawa started directing 8mm independent films while studying Sociology at Rikkyo University. In 1980, his first work SHIGARAMI GAKUEN screened at PIA Film Festival. Kurosawa then spent the next few years studying with directors Kazuhiko Hasegawa and Shinji Somai. In 1983, he made his commercial debut with the feature film, KANDAGAWA WARS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1999, LICENSE TO LIVE screened in the Berlin Film Festival Forum, and CHARISMA was highly acclaimed at the Cannes Film Festival Directors’ Fortnight. Later that same year BARREN ILLUSION was screened at the Venice International Film Festival. In 2001 PULSE screened at the Cannes Film Festival in Un Certain Regard, where it won the Critics’ Prize. Later that year, the film also garnered the Critics’ Prize at the Sitges Film Festival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two years later, Kurosawa returned with BRIGHT FUTURE, screening In Competition at the 2003 Cannes International Film Festival. That same year DOPPELGANGER, about a man who faces his alter-ego, was selected as the opening film for the Pusan International Film Festival. RETRIBUTION, finished in 2006, was officially selected for the Venice Film Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time Approximate.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film, we'll discuss the film and hopefully other works of a director whose works look compelling.  Thanks, Tim T, for the heads up!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John Will be Holding a Meetup Sign as the Credits say Sayonara</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240912960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tokyo Sonata</name><id>10283933</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241975700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10283933/</event_url></item>