<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Piper Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02421</zip><lat>42.420914</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-643-7468</phone><name>Temple Emunah</name><city>Lexington</city><address_3>Lexington, MA 02421</address_3><id>409761</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.229607</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sounds of Concord will again be offering free* group voice classes for men who sing and who wish to become better singers. If you are a guy or know a guy who enjoys singing, this is a great program!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The classes are sponsored by Sounds of Concord, an award winning men's a cappella chorus, and will consist of 4 classes on Thursday nights beginning Janury 13, and continuing on January 20, 27 and February 3.   Class meets at Temple Emunah, 9 Piper Rd in Lexington, MA, just off Route 2.  Please come at 7:15 to get signed up.  The class will run from 7:30 to 8:30.  Then from 8:30 on you will have the opportunity to practice what you just learned by singing along with the full chorus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Classes will be taught by Steve Tramack, former director of the Nashua Granite Statesmen, and baritone of Breakaway, a Top 5 quartet in the Northeastern District of the Barbershop Harmony Society. Topics will include breath support, improving resonance, vowel matching, and other techniques to improve vocal production. Music will be taught using voice part learning CDs, so you don't have to read music!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what some guests have said about these classes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Thank you SO much for this wonderful experience. You all have given me renewed hope and enthusiasm for improving my singing. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I was truly impressed by the musicality and comraderie of Sounds of Concord. Singing with the group after the lessons each week was an unexpected treat. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I want to thank you and the rest of Sounds of Concord for a fabulous experience, both the vocal lessons and the opportunity to sing with the guys. Steve is fabulous I learned a tremendous amount and enjoyed every minute of the experience.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further details or to pre-register call 866-537-1584 or contact: sing@soundsofconcord.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*A $10 materials fee is the only cost. There is no other obligation.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come upstairs and to the left.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Seth Orenstein</member_name><member_id>8462409</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan W</member_name><member_id>10812501</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327885667000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singers / Brothers / Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>VocalRevolution</urlname><id>1064944</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Area Acapella Barbershop Quartet/Chorus Singing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292790198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Voice Classes for Men</name><id>bkrbqypdbfb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296778500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/VocalRevolution/events/16434766/</event_url></item>