<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BRAND NEW TECHNIQUES FOR SPRING From A Former Student Turned "Approach Machine"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you get nervous about approaching someone new and starting a   conversation with them?  Do you wish you knew how to approach people   that you're attracted to, and talk to them in a way that will make them   interested in getting to know you?  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you answered yes to   either of those questions, then you're going to love this month's   workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We are bringing in a special guest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to help you really learn from someone who is an alumni.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;What this means&lt;/strong&gt;: He used to sit in our classes and now he is coming back to help you transform by sharing everything he did to transform himself from a lonely wallflower into the most social guy in the room!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll learn simple, proven conversation starters that are   non-threatening, and practically rejection-proof.  Once you master this   simple skill, you'll have the confidence to approach people in any   situation, and you will know what to say to get them talking.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Imagine   being at a Meetup event and gliding around the room talking with  anyone  and everyone.  You'll surprise yourself with how easy and  effortless it  is to strike up conversations with total strangers and  get to know  them.  Once you have this skill, you'll be able to make  friends and  attract lovers anywhere you go, anytime you want.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How you can go almost overnight from feeling fear when approaching someone new to being able to quickly walk up and talk to anyone with out fear and have them wanting to learn more about you. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A little know trick you can use that actually will make starting a conversation 110% easier. (Most people miss this one and its the biggest reason a conversation doesn't start.)   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A simple secret you can do with normal words that will instantly improve your ability to start conversations with people and have them respond positively.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Little-known places where people are more friendly and open to being approached.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The quickest way you can go from feeling fear and anxiety to become an unstoppable approaching machine where you can meet as many people as you want with out feeling like you have to force yourself.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The   meeting is limited to 35 people due to the size limitations of the   classroom (we'll be moving around a lot).  Our meetings usually sell out   quickly, so here's what I recommend.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your   calendar right now, and see if you have &lt;strong&gt;Sunday, April 24th&lt;/strong&gt; available.    The meeting runs from &lt;strong&gt;3:30pm to 5:30pm&lt;/strong&gt; and is conveniently located in   Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.    &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#2   - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop   right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#3   - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please   arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal networking.   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The   cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for a professional   training that includes these skill-building drills + personality   feedback.  Please remember to bring:  &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20 cash &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Eric &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;P.S.   - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the   event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you   should have no problems.  My cell is: 617-903-7371. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door. The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Edgemont</member_name><member_id>12651136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304907272000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><why>Unusual tricks for approaching attractive people with out the fear - WARNING : Don't Miss Out On Spring and Your chance to meet someone new during the nice weather.</why><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303173324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPECIAL - Approaching Attractive Strangers Made Easy</name><id>17353125</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303673400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/17353125/</event_url></item>