<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>195 Freight Street</address_1><state>Co</state><zip>06702</zip><lat>41.554020</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sin City</name><city>Waterbury</city><id>1999121</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.051064</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I've been wanting to do Sin City for a while. I love the place. Great atmosphere, good music, oxygen bar (i swear that works wonders!)... and the design to the place is awesome! It's probably my 2nd favorite club in CT... Kiss 95.7 Broadcasts live there every Friday night. I might look into VIP and post up if people want to do it. Sin City is near a lot of restaurants. So if anyone wants to grab some dinner or appetizers before the club we can do that probably 2 hours, hour and half prior to the event. I think this is a good hype event to be followed by a very chill night the next day at Brett's Bon Fire. Here's the link to Sin City if you wanna take a look: &lt;a href="http://www.sincityct.com/"&gt;http://www.sincityct.com/&lt;/a&gt; Sin then, confess later... See you @ Sin City Next Friday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Update 9/29**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the number we have RSVP attending Sin City, i think it's a good idea we have a personal spot for ourselves than us being spread around. Especially since there aren't really much places to relax at this club. It's definately worth the investment. Plus, If all goes as planned we'll have 3 bottles of Vodka to have a good time with. Here's the info for VIP @ Sin City &lt;br /&gt;

 I have a VIP section at Sin City tomorrow limited up to 16 maybe more if needed.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Price: $20 &lt;br /&gt;

 Includes: No waiting in line, Your cover to get into the club, A bottle of 3 Olive Vodka for every 6 people we have (6 people = 1 bottle), and basically a comfortable lounge spot to chill at with each other if we're not on the dance floor. &lt;br /&gt;

 PLEASE REPLY BACK IF YOU ARE OR NOT INTERESTED.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 TEXT ME @ (860) 357-7264 WITH YOUR NAME AND ANSWER OR REPLY DIRECTLY BACK TO ME HERE.... Thanks &lt;br /&gt;

 Christian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christian (860) 357-7264&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John </member_name><member_id>6728192</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317667049000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316660064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sin City</name><id>34508092</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317436200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/34508092/</event_url></item>