<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me at the Brattle for two stunning crime dramas by top-notch directors.  ZODIAC and EASTERN PROMISES are the kick-off to the &amp;quot;Recent Raves: Best Of 2007&amp;quot; repertory series in which &amp;quot;the Brattle likes to highlight the films that sometimes fall through the cracks.&amp;quot;  We'll meet and discuss after ZODIAC.  Since this is a double-feature, you may be interested in catching the 5:00 PM screening of EASTERN PROMISES as well. Please indicate so when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ZODIAC (screens at 7:00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both a New York Times Critics' Pick and an &amp;quot;Honorable Mention&amp;quot; on A.O. Scott's list of the best films of 2007, ZODIAC is a film that is concerned with more than just laying out a thrilling serial killer story (although it does just that).  While the film its share of spine-chilling sequences, director David Fincher is more interested in how the effort to comprehend evil deeds can consume the lives of innocent people.  The snappy back-and-forth script and scene-stealing performances from Mark Ruffalo, Robert Downey Jr. and Brian Cox as colorful figures from the real-life Zodiac case makes this film a thoroughly entertaining slice of 1970's San Francisco life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read a complete review at: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2007/03/02/movies/02zodi.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EASTERN PROMISES (screens at 5:00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also a New York Times' Critics' Pick, the story told in EASTERN PROMISES is a grim and violent one, set in London's expatriate Russian underworld.  The film, directed by David Cronenberg from a script by Steve Knight, revisits a number of themes and motifs that are staples of the genre: the ties of family and culture that bind criminal organizations; Oedipal drama; honor among thieves.  The audience stumbles into this realm in the company of an innocent outsider (Naomi Watts) who finds herself at once fascinated and repelled by it, as well as in considerable danger.  But even as the turns of its narrative and the contours of its characters are recognizable, very little about EASTERN PROMISES feels predictable or secondhand.  Mr. Cronenberg's deliberate, almost stately pacing -- the way he lingers in scenes for an extra beat or two, as if studying the faces of his actors for clues -- transforms what might have been a routine thriller into something genuinely troubling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read a complete review at: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2007/09/14/movies/14east.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it's off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198426743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zodiac + 1 at The Brattle</name><id>6959120</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200096000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6959120/</event_url></item>