<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>donation</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is the second in a six-part series on mindfulness meditation. Following the first week where we had a good turnout with engaging discussion, we will be focusing on the body in this second lesson with particular focus on our own mental commentary as we try to turn the mind's attention inward to noticing our present experience. The body is a present source of sensation, and by focusing our attention in the body, we can begin to direct ourselves to what is happening in the present moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Gil Fronsdal, our 'virtual' teacher: &amp;quot;At the heart of insight meditation is the practice of mindfulness, the cultivation of clear, stable and non-judgmental awareness. While mindfulness practice can be highly effective in helping bring calm and clarity to the pressures of daily life, it is also a spiritual path that gradually dissolves the barriers to the full development of our wisdom and compassion.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The course will be supported with audio instruction provided by Gil Fronsdal, primary teacher for the Insight Meditation Center in Redwood City, California. Each week for six weeks we will start the group by listening to his talk, which lasts about one hour, and will follow with discussion about the content and our experiences. This will be a good refresher course for those who have experience meditating, as well as those who may be new to mindfulness or meditation. Please join us in mindful community as we seek to bring more awareness into our lives and into the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you know you can't make a session and still want to participate, you can listen to the talk here (all six weeks are included) as well as homework for each class which you can download on the individual page of each lesson:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://amberstar.libsyn.com/index.php?post_category=Mindfulness%20Meditation%20Course" target="_blank"&gt;http://amberstar.libs...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best wishes,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TomC, Organizer&lt;br /&gt;Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>TomC</member_name><member_id>7931343</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254173539000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250550118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup</name><id>11133979</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253570400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/11133979/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/0/global_10129760.jpeg</photo_url></item>