<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(50 yards south of Route 140 junction)</address_2><address_1>Thomas St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01583</zip><lat>42.379811</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass Central Rail Trail Parking Lot</name><city>West Boylston</city><id>745557</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.794194</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Take a ride on the Mass Central Rail Trail (MCRT), a converted section of unused railroad right-of-way. This section parallels the meandering Quinapoxet River and ends in the town of of Holden. Along the way is an old textile mill site and its nearby tenements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail's fairly level with slight rutting. The surface is hard dirt with a bit of small-pebble gravel: mountain bikes are better-suited than road bikes. Mosquitos can be a problem, so bring some protection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail opens with a three-mile-long flat stretch. After that, we can swing to the north and continue onto a hillier portion. We could also optionally swing south, returning to the start along the opposite side of the river.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions from Worcester:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;1. Take &lt;b&gt;I-190&lt;/b&gt; to &lt;b&gt;EXIT 4&lt;/b&gt; (Rt. 12, West Boylston). &lt;br /&gt;2. At the end of the exit ramp is a T-intersection: turn &lt;b&gt;LEFT&lt;/b&gt; onto Route &lt;b&gt;12 North&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;3. Go through four more sets of lights (two miles). &lt;b&gt;NOTE&lt;/b&gt;: At the fourth light is a junction with Route 140.&lt;br /&gt;4. Cross the reservoir (landmark: Old Stone Church) and immediately bear &lt;b&gt;LEFT to follow Route 140&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;5. At the next intersection (one mile), you'll see the &lt;b&gt;MCRT parking area across the road&lt;/b&gt; and slightly to the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From points southeast:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;1. Take &lt;b&gt;I-290&lt;/b&gt; to &lt;b&gt;EXIT 23B&lt;/b&gt; (Rt. 140 North). &lt;br /&gt;2. Follow Route &lt;b&gt;140 North&lt;/b&gt; about five miles to the second traffic light (junction with Route 12).&lt;br /&gt;3. Continue on Route 140 North.&lt;br /&gt;4. After crossing the reservoir (landmark: Old Stone Church), bear &lt;b&gt;LEFT tofollow Route 140&lt;/b&gt; another mile.&lt;br /&gt;5. At the next intersection (one mile), you will see the &lt;b&gt;parking area across the road&lt;/b&gt; and slightly to the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Leominster and points north and west:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;1. Take &lt;b&gt;I-190&lt;/b&gt; South to &lt;b&gt;EXIT 5&lt;/b&gt; (Rt. 140). &lt;br /&gt;2. At the end of the ramp turn &lt;b&gt;LEFT&lt;/b&gt; onto Route &lt;b&gt;140 South&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;3. Go one mile south. &lt;b&gt;NOTE&lt;/b&gt;: DO NOT turn left when Route 140 jogs left: just go straight.&lt;br /&gt;4. Immediately after Route 140 jogs left, you will see the &lt;b&gt;parking area on your right&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rain date&lt;/b&gt;: September 19th, same time.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the parking area. Look for the "Meetup" sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce W</member_name><member_id>7844918</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284392118000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282603489000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rail Trail Bike Ride</name><id>14517357</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284298200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/14517357/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/5/e/global_17428190.jpeg</photo_url></item>