<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Allison Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.191242</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Liberty Books &amp; Comics</name><city>Concord</city><id>7215332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.538422</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sander Hicks comes to Concord, New Hampshire (Liberty Books and Comics, 75 Allison Street) to announce and promote his new book, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sanderhicks.com/slingshot.html"&gt;Slingshot to the Juggernaut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. You remember him from his Truth Party tour last year when he talked a little about the book-in-progress, but now he'll have copies for your reading enjoyment - and he'll autograph them in the store!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==========&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please buy a book or donate in the store to help finance Sander's travels. If you are unable to donate, please attend anyway - we don't want anyone to miss this for any reason!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==========&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Following after his heroes Gandhi and Jesus, Hicks uses &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sanderhicks.com/slingshot.html"&gt;Slingshot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to accomplish an ‘experiment in truth’ that enlivens our hearts and opens our eyes to the central issues of our time. His experiment ranges from autobiographical scenes of direct action to impressive journalistic research and political analysis. He concludes with the offering of an original political program that arises out of heart-felt theological reflections. This rich piece of passionate writing is a huge gift those of us who have wondered about the deeper meanings of 9/11 truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;—Byron Belitsos, cofounder of 9/11Truth.org and coauthor of A Return to Healing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Hicks's &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sanderhicks.com/slingshot.html"&gt;Slingshot to the Juggernaut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; provides detailed 'filling in of the blanks' in the 9/11 saga. This book serves as a wake-up call for an independent investigation of 9/11, which has had disastrous effects on America's democracy. Read it and demand accountability from your government!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;—Wayne Madsen, author, journalist, and nationally-distributed columnist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sanderhicks.com/slingshot.html"&gt;Slingshot to the Juggernaut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is about 9/11 Truth, peace, love, and how to confront evil in a confused time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start with the issue of 9/11 Truth, by covering: &lt;br /&gt;

 The life and death of Dr. David Graham of Shreveport LA (who met two of the 9/11 patsies, and warned FBI. Graham died a mysterious death on the verge of publishing his own book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author then recounts his head-on personal confrontations and conversations with Able Danger's Anthony Shaffer, Rudy Giuliani, Dick Cheney, Eliot Spitzer, and Anthrax cover-up artist Jerry Hauer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this darkness, we go back into light. Is it possible that the USA's legacy as a "truth machine" is a legacy not forgotten forever, but just temporarily misplaced?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Could a Truth Party unite Americans around simple virtues of peace and honesty?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 For a more detailed view of this book's guts, please review the &lt;a href="http://www.sanderhicks.com/SlingshotTOC.html"&gt;Annotated Table of Contents&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sanderhicks.com/slingshot.html"&gt;Slingshot to the Juggernaut:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Total Resistance to the Death Machine Means Complete Love of the Truth. &lt;br /&gt;

 by Sander Hicks &lt;br /&gt;

 February 2012. Soft Skull Press.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soft Skull Press, Berkley, California. &lt;br /&gt;

 Distributed Nationwide by PGW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We only mention a price for this meetup, since guys like Sander spend a lot of time and money of their own to get the truth out and often don't even break even. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We hope you can donate generously to make his tour pay for itself&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Sander thanks you!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the meeting space in the rear of the store.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337798200000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337108206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sander Hicks "Slingshot to the Juggernaut" tour date</name><id>64914092</id><headcount>6</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337292000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/64914092/</event_url></item>