<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>194 Cranberry Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.839191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-2526</phone><name>Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Carver</city><id>727813</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.691455</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>John Galluzzo, Adult Program Coordinator and Citizen Science Coordinator, Mass Audubon South Shore Sanctuaries, will present: &lt;i&gt;MSSF and the Breeding Bird Atlas, 2010 Update&lt;/i&gt;.  Meet at the MSSF headquarters' conference building (across the street and up the stairs from the headquarters).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John will follow the talk with a training walk on Saturday, June 19 to show volunteers how to count birds for the Breeding Bird Atlas 2 project. &lt;a href="http://www.massaudubon.org/birdatlas/bba2/index.php" target="_blank"&gt; More about BBA2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please consider helping with the BBA2 project. Volunteers will receive training on Saturday, June 19, 1:00 p.m. The training will enable you to count birds and complete the forms correctly. The data you collect will be used to track bird population changes since 1979, when the BBA1 was completed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you sign up for John Galluzzo's talk, we'd like you to sign up for the atlas training walk, but it's not mandatory. Also, you may go on the training walk without committing to bird counting. The walk will begin at the headquarters parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a wonderful hike for young people or for people just getting into bird watching or bird support, as John points out many interesting things to look for when learning about birds. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW- John is an accomplished historian and is an incredibly interesting person to spend time with! Check him out on Amazon.com and  &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/johnjgalluzzo" target="_blank"&gt;Linkedin.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharl</member_name><member_id>712534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276969934000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266091161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Talk: MSSF and the Breeding Bird Atlas, 2010 Update by John Galluzzo</name><id>12597275</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276815600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/12597275/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/4/global_13074596.jpeg</photo_url></item>