<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>UPDATE: Forty of us partied last evening at Glastonbury's &amp;quot;Billy Joel&amp;quot; Tribute show... 15 stayed well after the show ended to party by the Fire Pit!  Several &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; folks (not able to RSVP via MeetUp) indicated that they'd be joining us this evening's Bloomfield Caribbean Fest!  New friends welcome!&lt;br /&gt; - Rob P.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An Evening in the Caribbean - On the Bloomfield Town Green (Town Hall lawn) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reggae! -  Calypso! -  Steele Drums! -  African Drumming! - Stilt Walkers &amp;amp; Dancers! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Colorful West Indian Costumes! /  Caribbean Food &amp;amp; Drinks for sale! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS THURSDAY, 08/02  6:00 - 9:00 - FREE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Look for me/us: FACING the Town Hall steps/stage... find us on the RIGHT half of the crowd mid-way back, or farther, toward the Bloomfield Ave. side, near a tree (rather than the Park Ave. side).  I'll be (casually, colorfully attired) on a blue-on-blue U-Haul blanket with 2 red reflectors atop white sticks (shiny, deflated, Blue Star-shaped balloons, attached, low to the ground)!  If you can't find us, call my cell# from an easy-to-spot location and I'll direct you to us by waving a reflector.  Also, look for Al-R's orange traffic cones. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***  &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: I invite both my &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; MeetUp AND &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; friends (even those I haven't met yet!) to join me/us!  During the summer months, we are trying to do more casual, BYO type gatherings, featuring different types of outdoor musical entertainment, moving around to various towns to encourage new folks to join us and make new friends! Typically 8-24 (or more!) come together each time.  These new introductions lead to invitations to each other's events and the opportunity to enjoy varied activities and make even more new friends!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; BYOB and snacks/Picnic dinner, if you'd like.  As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Gather @ 5:45.  Entertainment starts @ 6:00.  Some optionally stay after the event ends (and/or move to some other nearby park or private home) to continue the party (often beside Al-R's propane Fire Pit, until the cops chase us away!).  In anticipation of this, please bring extra food and beverage with you!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF RAIN: we'll more likely go to a bar!  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Not applicable... it's gonna be a BEAUTIFUL night to listen to &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot;! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; All the details are here... please do NOT hit &amp;quot;reply&amp;quot;, email, or phone me (unless lost) - simply show up, OR, for upcoming events, any UPDATES, and to RSVP, please go directly to my &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; MeetUp site (free) by 2:00 on the day of the event:  &lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/"&gt;http://livemusic.meet...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Invite your friends!  See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney  &lt;br /&gt;C: 860-690-9595  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please MapQuest DIRECTIONS to:  &lt;br /&gt;Bloomfield Town Hall &lt;br /&gt;800 Bloomfield Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Bloomfield , CT 06002 &lt;br /&gt;860-243-2923 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186263988000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185983988000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Caribbean Evening in Bloomfield 5:45</name><id>6109299</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186091100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6109299/</event_url></item>