<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The film starts at 6:30PM.   I will be there by 6PM and want us to head into the theater by 6:15.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To find me and the group depends on where the movie is playing.  If it is upstairs, I will be near the windows by the coffee concession stand at the top of he escalator.  I will try to grab a table.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be just inside the ropes in front of the concession stand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If for some reason you miss the group before the film, we generally congregate outside the auditorium we have just seen the movie in (not all the way outside of the building).   Generally we talk for a bit about the film and those who are interested go out for drinks and munchies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note, since we see most of these movies during the first weekend the film is released, it is a good idea to consider buying your tickets ahead of time.  Fandango sells tickets for this theater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Title:  Max Payne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director: John Moore&lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Beau Thorne&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Mark Wahlberg, Mila Kunis, Beau Bridges, Chris &amp;quot;Ludacris&amp;quot; Bridges, and Olga Kurylenko&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.maxpaynethemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.maxpayneth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Maverick cop Max Payne (Wahlberg) is hell-bent on revenge against those responsible for the brutal murder of his family and partner. His obsessive investigation takes him on a nightmarish journey into a dark underworld. As the mystery deepens, Max is forced to battle enemies beyond the natural world and face an unthinkable betrayal.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Movie Group Badge.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230918582000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221342742000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Max Payne</name><id>8751885</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224280800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8751885/</event_url></item>