<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;John Zogby discusses:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Way We'll Be: The Zogby Report on the Dramatic Changes Transforming the American Dream&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a &lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Book Store&lt;/a&gt; Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome one of today’s most successful predictors and trend spotters, John Zogby, for a discussion of what's to come in the United States as he sees it, as discussed in The Way We'll Be: The Zogby Report on the Dramatic Changes Transforming the American Dream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Zogby, whom The Washington Post calls “the maverick predictor,” the conventional wisdom about the United States–that we’re isolated from the world, politically fragmented, and inclined toward material pleasure–isn’t just flawed; it may be 180 degrees from the truth. In this far-reaching and illuminating look at contemporary American life, Zogby draws  on thousands of in-depth surveys conducted especially for the book and points out where we’re headed–politically, culturally, and spiritually.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The American dream is in transition; it is rapidly being redefined by four meta-movements: living with limits as consumers and citizens; embracing diversity of views and ways of life; looking inward to find spiritual comfort; and demanding authenticity from the media, our leaders, and leading institutions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spearheaded by today’s eighteen-to-twenty-nine-year-olds–the “First Global” generation–Americans are becoming more internationalist, consensus-oriented, and environmentally conscious and less willing to identify themselves by the things they do to earn or spend their money. But this is more than a youth tide. Americans of all ages are moving beyond old divides to form a new national consensus that will shape the nation for decades to come.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside before and after; Renoir pinned to my jacket.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222902516000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217942529000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Way We'll Be (Zogby)</name><id>8480938</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222383600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/8480938/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/f/global_5049647.jpeg</photo_url></item>