<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Boston Aussies Bushfire Fundraising Appeal:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A wine tasting on the Charles&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, 21 February, 2009&lt;br /&gt;3:00 – 6:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Consulate General of Britain&lt;br /&gt;Suite 1500, 1 Memorial Drive, Cambridge MA &lt;br /&gt;$20 entry (includes food and drink)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the truest of Australian traditions, we come together to support to those who are suffering a result of the recent bush fires in Australia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come along and enjoy great Australian wine and food that has been kindly donated by our Australian, New Zealand, American, and other supporters.  You are also most welcome to bring a plate of some cultural delicacy.  Lamingtons, pies, anyone?!   There is a magnificent view of the Charles River and Boston, thrown in for free by our kind hosts the British Consulate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be lots of exciting raffles and silent auction items up for grabs, so don’t forget to bring cash or your check book.  We will provide more details of the items closer to the date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceeds will be donated to the Red Cross Bushfire 2009 Appeal and the RSPCA Victoria Bushfire Appeal.&lt;br /&gt;Because of security restrictions at the consulate, all attendees must be over the age of 21 and must register by 8pm, Friday, 20 February.  Please bring identification to gain entry to the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further information and updates, please contact Brian Beattie on 857 207 9044 or at brian@bwbtrade.com or see our blog at bostonaussies.blogspot.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go to &lt;a href="http://www.advance.org/en/cev/reg/748/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.advance.or...&lt;/a&gt; to register.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please put Boston fundraiser in subject line for replies to Brian</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236218458000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Larrikins</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aussie-145</urlname><id>222356</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Aussie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234134918000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bushfire relief fundraiser. </name><id>9701340</id><headcount>57</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235246400000</time><rsvp_limit>57</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aussie-145/events/9701340/</event_url></item>