<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Join us for a hike that will include a  climb to 4000 Ft Cannon Mountain, and the Cannon Balls with autumn views of Lonesome lake and beautiful Franconia Ridge. Cannon Mountain was the site of the Old Man of the Mountain. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance  9.34 mi  Time  8 hr 0 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +3658 ft  Elev Loss  -4604 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will spot cars at Mount Kinsman Trailhead Hwy 116  and then drive to the  starting point of this hike at at Kinsman Ridge Trailhead (north). We need all hikers to help with the carspot for this &amp;quot;thru hike&amp;quot; to be successful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Itinerary:&lt;br /&gt; From the Cannon Mountain Tramway parking area near the main buildings, the trail turns left and follows a gravel road to a picnic area (sign) for 150 yd., then turns right and follows the left edge of a field for 80 yd. to the bottom of a steep slope. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turning left (sign) into the woods, the trail climbs moderately and then steeply by switchbacks, with some gravel sections that are severely eroded. Then it enters a semi-open area of ski glades and climbs steeply with rough and rocky footing, including some slippery ledges. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hiking trail crosses the ski route four times, with occasional views north; follow markings carefully. From the top of the glades, it ascends along the left edge of a ski trail, and it turns left off the ski trail (signs), enters the woods, and climbs moderately, then easily. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a level area, a side path diverges from the left side of the trail (straight ahead) and descends easily southeast for 60 yd., emerging on ledges where there is a magnificent view across the notch to the Franconia Range.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Rim Trail  hike 0.05 mi/2 min/-6 ft on the Rim Trail&lt;br /&gt; The Rim Trail diverges off the Kinsman Ridge Trail and follows a gravel path to the Tramway terminal.   hike 0.13 mi/7 min/+88 ft on the Rim Trail&lt;br /&gt; The gravel pathway climbs briefly from the Tramway terminal to the summit observation tower.to &lt;b&gt;Cannon Mtn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance  2.20 mi   Time  1 hr 12 min  Elev Gain  +2201 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.04 mi/1 min/-41 ft on the Rim Trail,  The trail leaves the summit observation tower and descends gradually to its southern junction with the Kinsman Ridge Trail.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.40 mi/16 min/-127 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail  From this junction with the tourist paths, the Kinsman Ridge Trail descends gradually to the junction with the Hi-Cannon Trail, which continues straight where the Kinsman Ridge Trail turns right, and soon drops very steeply down a rough path among huge boulders to Coppermine Col.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Hi-Cannon Trail&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.40 mi/27 min/-490 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt; It then climbs for a few yards to the junction on the left with the Lonesome Lake Trail, which leads southeast to Lonesome Lake Hut (water can be found down this trail). hike 2.40 mi/1 hr 41 min/+323 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The Kinsman Ridge Trail now begins the traverse of the Cannon Balls, the three humps that make up the ridge leading to Kinsman Mountain. It ascends a steep and rough section above the Lonesome Lake Trail junction and passes several scattered viewpoints while climbing over the first (northeast) Cannon Ball, then descends to a col. The trail circles to the north of the second (middle) Cannon Ball and descends moderately to a deep ravine where a small, sluggish brook usually contains some water, then ascends sharply and passes near the top of the third (west) Cannon Ball. After crossing another hump (3,812 ft.) and dropping to a flat region,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; it reaches Kinsman Junction.  Distance  5.44 mi   Time  3 hr 37 min Elev Gain  +3513 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/6 min/+112 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail  Here the Fishin’ Jimmy Trail (a part of the AT) enters on the left from Lonesome Lake, and the Kinsman Pond Trail runs straight ahead, leading to Kinsman Pond and Kinsman Pond Shelter.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mt Kinsman Trail     hike 1.60 mi/1 hr 31 min/-1441 ft on the Mt Kinsman Trail&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Kinsman Ridge Trail, the Mt. Kinsman trial descends straight down from the ridge top. It levels out a bit, crosses several brooks and then continues winding down the mountainside at easy to moderate grades, with good footing except for short, scattered steep pitches with rough footing. In this section, it follows Flume Brook through an ax-blazed trail. It passes a spur path on the left which descends briefly, then makes an easy ascent to Bald Peak, a bare ledgy dome with fine views that crowns a western spur of Kinsman Mountain. The main trail continues on a road, reaching another side path on the left. This spur descends close to the brook bank for 150 yd. to small, steep-walled Kinsman Flume, a classic eroded dike with an overhanging boulder at the top that presents a reasonable facsimile of a profile. The main trail crosses Flume Brook then crosses a small brook that falls over a mossy ledge to the right of the trail.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Bald Peak spur  hike 2.10 mi/1 hr 46 min/-1391 ft on the Mt Kinsman Trail&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It crosses a substantial brook near the site of the former Kinsman Cabin. It leaves the road then, in 30 yd., it turns onto another road (cairn and arrow), and leaves the WMNF. It makes a short bypass to the right of a wet section of road, passes an old sugarhouse that stands on the left, then follows alongside the edge of a grass-grown log yard. Many roads enter from the right. The trail always takes a left at these forks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail follows a sandy logging road that descends moderately under tall pines to the gate to Mount Kinsman Trailhead Hwy 116  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  9.34 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  7 hr 0 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +3658 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -4604 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  -946 ft&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will try to start on time in order to set up our cars.  Please keep your RSVP up to date. With a carspot/traverse, every hiker is important to make sure that we set up successfully.  If you are running late, phone immediately en route/before 8am for instructions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The days are getting shorter and cooler.  pack for fall conditions and don't forget your headlamp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury. Review the trail maps and itinerary available in the White Mountain Guidebook. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This group will average a 1pm turn around time. If trail or hiker conditions slow the group, you need to understand that the goal for the day can change and we must start back to end the hike safely.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHM disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Limited Parking- Look for the group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter G</member_name><member_id>2906700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252412716000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249417189000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cannon Mountian and the Cannon Balls  via Mt Kinsman Trail</name><id>11035379</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252239300000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11035379/</event_url></item>