<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 West Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.346043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>530-736-9189</phone><name>Marlborough Public Library</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>966581</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.554450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Forgive me! I procrastinated getting this meeting together and apologize for the short notice. If you can't make this one, don't worry, there will be other meetings the third Thursday of each month, unless we change that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting is in the Story Hour Room. Go to the bottom of the stairs and turn right. The room is near the entrance to the Children's library, on the right hand side. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start at 6:30 with some networking and then I'll give a *short* presentation at 7:00 PM. There will be plenty of time to ask questions and give suggestions. The meeting will end at 8:15, latest, because the library closes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A goal of mine is for everyone to leave each meeting feeling that they got something worthwhile out of the meeting, so we'll have some discussion about what you'd like the group to provide to accomplish that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to get a feel of what each of us is procrastinating about, so please come prepared to describe, succinctly, those areas of your life where your procrastination causes you real problems. Be as specific as possible. And, what things do you NOT procrastinate about? Maybe others can learn from you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One major area of interest to me is procrastination in getting rid of paper clutter. I am drowning in paper. The picture that the original organizers chose is wonderful!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll bring some book recommendations, and some mechanisms that have worked for me. I hope some of you will have some helpful hints too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to email me with any suggestions, comments, or questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Alice&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alice</member_name><member_id>7648322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271786796000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Procrastinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers</urlname><id>1357989</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>Metrowest Procrastinators and Clutterers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271186769000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metrowest Procrastinators April 2010 Meetup</name><id>13172510</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271370600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers/events/13172510/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/a/global_6942970.jpeg</photo_url></item>