<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;My Maria's... Don't you know I've gone a long, long way... I've been longing to eat there, just sit down and start to munch away...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh... Hi, again, everybody. Sorry, you caught Mike in one of his rare Country moods. He reckons he's entitled, once in awhile...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That isn't to say, mind you, that he needs to give you a song and dance about our &amp;quot;M&amp;quot; restaurant; &lt;a href="http://www.marias-braintree.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Maria's&lt;/a&gt; in Braintree.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located on Quincy Avenue, Maria's is one of those &amp;quot;been there forever&amp;quot; restaurants that could easily be overlooked by diners in search of newer, more glamorous destinations. In fact, Maria's is bracketed by competition in the same Italian/Mediterranean niche: Spazio (one of our destinations last December) is a stone's throw to the south; Gennaro's (last May, just over a year ago) is a few minutes north down the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite this, you may be surprised to learn that Mike eats at Maria's regularly. The reason is simply that  they offer a combination of convenience, economy and well-prepared food that is just too good to overlook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be heading there for dinner on Tuesday, May 19th at 6:45. Mike hopes that you will join us to experience for yourself just why this old neighborhood favorite is still worthwhile; things like the yummy Greek salads offered with every meal at dinnertime, the always interesting specials and a regular menu that ranges from pizza to shish-kabob.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're undecided, there's plenty more info on their &lt;a href="http://www.marias-braintree.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; and in Mimi Claffey's &lt;a href="http://www.patriotledger.com/archive/x682884154/TASTE-TELL-Old-style-comfort-food-at-Maria-s-Restaurant" target="_blank"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; for The Patriot Ledger. Please feel free to have a look, then include us in your plans next Tuesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maria's Restaurant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;240 Quincy Ave., Braintree&lt;br /&gt;(781) 843-3730&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.marias-braintree.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.marias-bra...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, May 19th @ 6:45 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maximum number of attendees:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Spaghetti or ziti with meat or marinara sauce ($8.25) represents the low end of the dinner menu. Quite a few dishes are under $14.00: the rest top out at $16.25 with only three or four exceptions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Monday, May 18th @ 7:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Maria's is on &lt;b&gt;Quincy Avenue in Braintree&lt;/b&gt;, just a short distance from Weymouth Landing. The section of Quincy Ave. where Maria's is located is also part of Route 53. Please note that we are giving directions from Route 3 because this will provide a prominent reference point for anyone who lives in the immediate area and would likely be the route of choice for people coming from a distance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3, take Exit 17 (Union St). This is the Union Street Rotary. Exit the rotary by turning onto the Union Street, East Braintree exit, passing the Braintree Police Station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through two traffic lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next major intersection is Weymouth landing, where you will see a 7 Eleven convenience store on your left. At this point you can either bear right, heading into Weymouth Landing, or go straight, which brings you immediately to a traffic light. Go straight, then take a left at the light onto Quincy Avenue, keeping the 7 Eleven and Eastern Bank on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Immediately after you turn left there is another light at the entrance to the new Weymouth Landing MBTA station. Go straight through this light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next traffic light is at Gordon St. You will see a yacht club on your right. Go straight through this light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next traffic light is Bickford Rd. You will see a strip mall on your left containing Spazio, a closed West Coast Video store and a Curves franchise. The mall is followed by a large white building that hosts several small businesses. Maria's is located &lt;b&gt;immediately&lt;/b&gt; after this building. If you pass a Sunoco station on your left, or the Pan Asia restaurant on your right, you've just passed Maria's!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243705123000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242236998000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>My Maria's!</name><id>10403120</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242773100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10403120/</event_url></item>