<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 3rd Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Intrepid Labs</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6978782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.080132</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Media Marketing&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 You may have a brilliant product, but do you know how to market it? Without a cutting edge marketing strategy the most amazing products can fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Founders are not always the best marketers and often their product suffers as the result. An exciting new social media campaign can easily bring recognition, new customers, and ensure the success of your business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Don’t let your company suffer! Join EFactor for an information packed event that will bring social media and marketing professionals to teach you everything you need to know about startup marketing. Learn from a panel of leading experts how to develop and implement an exciting new social media marketing strategy. Network with fellow entrepreneurs and meet marketing professionals to ensure your company’s success!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Speakers:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Shannon Jamieson.&lt;/strong&gt; Shannon is an attorney and co-founder of New Leaf Legal, a progressive flat-fee law firm specializing in corporate and intellectual property matters, offered exclusively for artists, entrepreneurs and emerging businesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Molly DeLong.&lt;/strong&gt; Molly leads the Real Bullets Branding strategy team with a passion for creating exhilarating branding with a thorough understanding of consumer trends in the digital age. Molly works to create meaningful partnerships for her clients and digital strategies that can translate across multiple channels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Register Now! &lt;a&gt;http://www.efactor.com/smmboston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Buy your tickets online @efactor.com and save $5 off admission ($20 at the door). Click the link to buy your tickets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;The Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30PM - Networking &lt;br /&gt;

 7PM - Keynote &amp;amp; Panel Discussion &lt;br /&gt;

 8PM- Q &amp;amp;A &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30PM - Networking&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 *Make sure to check out EFactor.com, the world’s largest network for entrepreneurs to find useful resources, network with entrepreneurs in your industry, funding resources, and all event information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350437711000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Marketing Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising</urlname><id>984032</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Internet Marketing and Advertising  Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349972132000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EFactor Presents: Social Media Marketing </name><id>86537812</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350426600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising/events/86537812/</event_url></item>