<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It’s also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people! &lt;br /&gt;******** &lt;br /&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;   It's time for our Conscious Movie Night again. This month's film is &lt;i&gt;The Passion of Joan of Arc.&lt;/i&gt; As you can see from the editorial and reviews that I've pasted below, it is supposed to be one of the most amazing films ever made! (That's quite a statement! And every single review I looked at said the same thing, in different ways.) So I think we are in for a beautiful experience. And we do have the version that has the Voices of Light music included with it, which I also cannot wait to hear.&lt;br /&gt;   For those who are interested, we will be gathering before the movie, beginning at 6:30, for dinner. We will be ordering take-out Thai food from the Rice Pot on State St. If you want to have dinner with us, please RSVP and let us know, so we know how much food to get. &lt;br /&gt;   Looking forward to seeing you all! And meeting you if you haven't been here before!&lt;br /&gt;Blessings,&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Carl Dreyer's The Passion of Joan of Arc is as truly mythic as any film ever shot, its artistic achievement rivaled by its turbulent history. The focal point of controversy when released in 1928, the original film was lost for a half-century until an intact copy of Dreyer's original version was recovered in the early '80s. &lt;br /&gt;Seeing Joan of Arc today remains a cinematic revelation, its approach to storytelling, set design, editing, and especially cinematography (by Rudolph Maté) radical then, and still strikingly modern many decades later. Although the story is epic in its implications, the film is composed primarily of extreme close-ups, especially of Joan and her principal interrogator, Bishop Cauchon, and medium shots of small groups, often shot from low angles. Dreyer and Maté shot their cast in bright light, without makeup, giving each wrinkle, blemish, or tuft of hair sculptural detail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For all its visual invention, however, Dreyer's film is most devastating in its central performance by Falconetti (née Renee Falconetti), a French stage actress who made her only screen appearance here--one critic Pauline Kael has suggested &amp;quot;may be the finest performance ever recorded on film.&amp;quot; Through Falconetti, Joan's spiritual devotion, simple dignity, and suffering become utterly real; even without a dialogue track and only sparse inter-titles, the film achieves a fevered eloquence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meticulous restoration also includes composer Richard Einhorn's beautiful oratorio, Voices of Light, inspired by Dreyer's film and set to texts by women mystics from medieval and early-Renaissance Europe. A luminous work on its own, Einhorn's oratorio matches both the dramatic arcs and tremulous emotions of Dreyer's film, while its juxtaposition of choral and solo voices (with early-music vocal quartet Anonymous 4 evoking Joan herself) echoes the martyr's confrontation with the court. --Sam Sutherland&lt;br /&gt;------&lt;br /&gt;Worth the purchase price &lt;br /&gt;By  FrontPage &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Passion of Joan of Arc&amp;quot; was beautiful. Other reviews have said that &amp;quot;Passion&amp;quot; was the best of the films of Joan of Arc, and after viewing this masterpiece directed by Carl Theodor Dreyer, it's hard to think that something better could be out there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Five stars across the board for the presentation, quality (sound and video) and for the film itself. This comes from the Criterion Collection, and make no mistake about it, they did what this archive in cinematic achievement demanded. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The DVD contains a digitally restored, black and white transfer from an original negative which was discovered in 1981 in a Norwegian mental institution . Originally a silent movie, the film is accompanied by a digital stereo composition performed by Anonymous 4 with soloist Susan Narucki and the Radio Netherlands Philharmonic and Choir. The audio, which is optional to the viewing of &amp;quot;Passion&amp;quot; is GORGEOUS. The music alone is worth the price of admission. Kudos to composer Richard Einhorn. &lt;br /&gt;For the movie, I was stunned at the cinematic approach to filming &amp;quot;Passion.&amp;quot; This is why I am certain that no one has come to within the state border of being close to the depth of passion that pours out of EVERY frame. From the opening scene to the bitter end, this DVD keeps you involved. By the end, you may be in tears, as I was. Lead actress Renee Falconetti  is flawless in her role as Joan of Arc. She only made two films. It seemed as though she became Joan from the start, and as she presented her role, she seemed to almost be consumed by the spirit of Joan's demise herself.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347578000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235499382000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night:   The Passion of Joan of Arc</name><id>9812483</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235781000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/9812483/</event_url></item>