<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Volunteers, free. Or pay</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>ATTENTION CAMPERS and those interested in sustainable living!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join me for a camping trip to Tinmouth, VT, a little village near Middletown Springs, VT for &lt;a href="http://www.solarfest.org/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;SolarFest&lt;/a&gt; 2007! New England's Renewable Energy Festival features organic foods, presentations, demonstrations, hands-on activities, concerts powered by the sun, and a Saturday night bonfire not to be missed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Affordable ticket prices: $25 weekend pass; $20 Saturday only pass; $15 Sunday only pass. Camping in the woods is free; they will accommodate car/rv campers for an additional fee of $20 per car/rv. Camping is free, unless you choose to camp right next to your car, which costs $20. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in volunteering (total of 3-6 hours over the weekend, depends on what day you come) just shoot me an email. I directed traffic for about 3 hours last year and got a nifty volunteers' t-shirt for helping out. VOLUNTEERS ATTEND FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND, FREE. NO TICKET REQUIRED, NO FEE FOR CAMPING. Two meals per day are also provided for volunteers, so if you're squeamish about camping, you're really out of excuses! No canned tuna necessary on this trip! Please email me your contact info (and last name) so that I may email the organizers by June 28th, as requested by them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did the car camping last year, but I really think I missed out on the &amp;quot;community&amp;quot; aspect, because the car-camping was sequestered from the tents-only section of the farm. The two areas aren't too far apart, so if you can't live without your car stereo or XM radio, you can still come over and visit us. I still met some really great people, but this year I want to do it right!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Four of us plan on leaving New Haven around 3pm Friday, so we're not setting up our tents in the dark. The location is beautiful; a theraputic horseback-riding farm (the horses are moved off-site during the festival) in scenic Vermont...lush grass pastures and clear, dark skies for stargazing! Therefore, please do not bring any glass bottles! Broken glass + horses = painful, sad death (they eat the glass with the grass).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have sent out an email to those who have a &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP detailing carpools, suggested gear, and community supplies. Brian is bringing a huge tent with a &amp;quot;screened-in area&amp;quot; in case someone has a tent malfunction, or we need shelter during inclement weather (not likely, but it's good to plan just the same).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in coming up, but can't make it until Saturday, that's ok too...it takes about 3.5 hours to drive up. Please note in your rsvp if you're coming up Friday or Saturday. There are area hotels if you're not interested in camping, but I think that's part of the fun! There's a cool spring located on-site for swimming, SOLAR POWERED HOT WATER SHOWERS (keep 'em short for the next person in line), and water from a spigot as well as portapotties are available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out SolarFest.org for event details and pictures from last year! The musical performances are awesome; last year Dar Williams was the Sunday afternoon entertainment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric will be the contact for this event. I emailed my phone number to all &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; people, so I'll remove it from the site here; if you Google &amp;quot;solarfest&amp;quot; you'll notice this page is at the top of the list!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z9aPHfL3pG0" target="_blank"&gt;A YouTube video of last years' event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*if you wish to volunteer, but have not (as of Friday Jun 29, 11pm) signed up, please email the Solarfest people directly, or state your intentions when you arrive. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are available before you leave for Vermont; Roger in Fairfield has purchased 3 tickets but is unable to go this weekend. Tickets for non-volunteers are not refundable, so Roger will be suffering a small loss; I'm sure he would agree to meet you halfway to sell you his tickets. Again, if you're volunteering, you don't need tickets and if you purchased one (like me) it will be refunded at the gate. Citronella candles (in metal pots) are a good idea too.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184599944000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181058958000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SolarFest.org's Solar Energy Festival, Tinmouth, VT (camping!)</name><id>5855810</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184353200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5855810/</event_url></item>