<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>141 Middlesex Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.488703</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 270-4800</phone><name>Guard Up! Family Swordsmanship</name><city>Burlington</city><id>803767</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.222199</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Buddy Night: Battle for the North Pole&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Friday, December 19, 7:00-9:00pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Abominable Snowman and his army of yetis are marching on the gates of Santa's workshop at the North Pole! The battle for Christmas is heating up this year! Santa has to prepare for his Christmas Eve journey, but the sleigh isn't ready yet. Santa and his elves have to hold back the yeti armies and give Santa enough time to escape so he can complete his mission of bring toys and happiness to all the good boys and girls around the world. Will the elves be able to withstand the yeti onslaught or will the Abominable Snowman bring terror to the North Pole?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pre Reg*: $10/members and friends $20/non&lt;br /&gt;At Door: $25/members and friends $35/non&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Previous swordsmanship experience is not required. We provide the padded weapons (and spell packets). This is a family event with adults, teens and kids (ages 6+). If not in costume, Sweats and T-shirts are suggested. No shorts or tanktops allowed. Under 18 must have signed waiver by parents. 18 and over must have their own signed waiver. Waivers can be downloaded here: &lt;a href="http://www.guardup.net/sword/documents/event_waiver.doc" target="_blank"&gt;Waiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $10 for Meet Up members (and their friends) who pre-register ($20 for non). Pre-registration required as these events DO fill up and we cannot take anyone else after our capacity is reached. To pre-register you must call (781) 270-4800 and pay ahead with a credit card or cash. Make sure to tell them that &amp;quot;Meghan sent you&amp;quot; so that you get the Meet Up rate which is the same as the Member Rate (a savings of $10).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: RSVP with YES does NOT PRE-REGISTER. You MUST call (781) 270-4800 and pay ahead to complete the pre-registration process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At-Door is $25 and you may be turned away if there is not enough room. Since we fill up before the event more than 1/2 the time, pre-registration is highly recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure to be ontime for required safety instruction at start of event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the front desk... they can help you!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>5106555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231546095000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Sword Fighters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Swordsmanship-and-Fencing-for-Beginners</urlname><id>1313138</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Swordsmanship and Fencing for Beginners</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229385085000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddy Night: Battle for the North Pole</name><id>9343958</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229815800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Swordsmanship-and-Fencing-for-Beginners/events/9343958/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/8/global_6162840.jpeg</photo_url></item>