<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>DETAILS HAVE CHANGED!  Our September LIGHTNING ROUND has changed to &lt;b&gt;Thursday&lt;/b&gt; 9/24/09 at 7pm, and the location has changed as well.  Also, those who RSVPed who had not been regularly attending Regular Cashflow meetups have been removed from the list.  REMEMBER:  This is for EXPERIENCED PLAYERS ONLY.  Lightning Round games move VERY quickly and require a strong knowledge and proficiency of the basics of Cashflow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take note of the date and location changes, and RSVP as soon as possible.  There are only SIX positions available for the Lightning Round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Russ&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Previous Lightning Round description)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case you haven't heard, our Lightning Rounds are geared to the more experienced players who want to learn how to analyze deals faster, navigate around their Financial Statement, and get out of the Rat Race faster. NO INSTRUCTION WILL BE GIVEN at this meetup. EXPERIENCED PLAYERS ONLY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup particularly will focus on whipping through the Financial Statement--CORRECTLY!!--so that the game can move at a faster pace. There will be drills before we play the game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Currently the RSVP is limited to six so as to provide efficient training to all attendees. Also because the location is not conducive to a larger meeting. So RSVP early!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Russ&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Big table on the left as you enter</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Russ</member_name><member_id>3610750</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1254077710000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Will-Be Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCashflowMeetup</urlname><id>302998</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Cashflow Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251512507000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LIGHTNING Round of Cashflow</name><id>11229141</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253833200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCashflowMeetup/events/11229141/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/8/global_1225096.jpeg</photo_url></item>