<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ski House</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03812</zip><lat>44.081680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>872006</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.231277</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Where are you going to stay this winter when you snowboard?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wedeln Ski House is my favorite place to stay, located in the heart of the White Mountains just north or North Conway.  Cost is only $20 per night for guests but the best part is meeting other riders and skiers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't wait for Winter!!  During the Fall we try to get potential guests up to the house so you can find out what a cool place it is.  If you like it hopefully you will visit again during the winter or even become a full member.  During the winter we only allow a limited number of first time guests per weekend so please take advantage of the our New Guest Weekend on Oct 1st.    We still have some details to finalize but wanted to be sure to get this on meetup so you can save the date! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Current plan is to do a round of Frisbee Golf on Saturday and a hike up Kearsarge Mountain on Sunday. We'll start the weekend with a BYOB social on Friday night around our bar or on our screened in porch. We're working out the details on meals, but we may do a BYOG (G=Grillables) and have a Grillfest on Saturday night or hit a great restaurant in Cornish, ME, depending on numbers. Could be a great board game or camp fire night, depending on weather...so we'll see how the rest comes together!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basic fees are $20 per person per night for over night lodging. Everyone brings their own towels, toiletries, pillow, sleeping bag. Accommodations are dormitory-style bunk beds, in bedrooms separated by gender. Check out the lodge at www.wedeln.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for main events...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Folf course is in Limerick, ME., about an hour away from the house. There are 36 holes of varying difficulty set on 120 acres. Have a look: &lt;a href="http://www.woodlandva..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.woodlandva...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;The Kearsarge mountain trail head is a quick walk from the Wedeln Lodge. The hike will take 4 to 5 hours, depending on how long we spend up top. It's a moderate to challenging hike, good hiking boots are highly recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let us know if you think you can make it. Whether you are a super duper brand new guest, a repeat guest, or a member, we'd love to have you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions or suggestions, please let me know. More details to come!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Lane&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email directions to all that sign up.  I will be at the house bar by 8pm Friday.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285982341000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Snowboarders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>snowboard-46</urlname><id>389975</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Somerville Snowboarding Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284577195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Guest Weekend at Wedeln Ski House</name><id>14782085</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285977600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/snowboard-46/events/14782085/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_6288127.jpeg</photo_url></item>