<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Southport Island</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04538</zip><lat>43.821194</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-800-221-5924 </phone><name>Ocean Gate Resort</name><city>Boothbay Harbor</city><id>1240491</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.664490</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>270.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>For those of you planning to join us on the Boothbay Harbor Trip and want to extend your stay for a couple of days and obtain some advanced kayak skills with two of the best kayaking instructors this side of the Mississippi, then come join us for Ben &amp;amp; John's Kayak Camp. We'll stay at the Ocean Gate Resort and the Kayak Camp will take place at the Ocean Gate as well as in the coastal areas near Southport Island and Boothbay Harbor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;To view Ben &amp;amp; John's Biographies click on the link below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.benlawry.net/www.benlawry.net/Bens_Bio.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Ben Lawry Bio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seacliffkayakers.com/John_Carmody.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;John Carmody Bio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Kayak Camp will consist of one day of advanced paddling strokes including perfecting your forward stroke as well as turning and boat control strokes. The second day will consist of using the strokes you learned on the previous day in areas of current and possible rougher coastal conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The prerequisite for this Kayak Camp is an ability to perform wet exit and re-entry both unassisted as well as assisted and be comfortable in moderate ocean conditions. This is an advanced course designed to take intermediate sea kayakers to the next level. You will need to wear a drysuit or wetsuit and have the appropriate additional gear such as pump, paddle float, spray skit and have a sea kayak of 16ft or more with bulkheads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the link below for info on Ben &amp;amp; John's Kayak Kamp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.benlawry.net/www.benlawry.net/Kayak_Camp.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.benlawry.n...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost for the 2 day Kayak Kamp per person is $270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to stay at the Ocean Gate for the 2 nights during the Kayak Camp the cost per night is $70 per person based on 2 people per room. We may be able to get a cabin that will accommodate the Kayak Camp group as well as save a few bucks for lodging. There is also a local campground for those who prefer to camp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This Kayak Camp is limited to 8 people and payment is required in advance.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277118937000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269444460000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Two Day Kayak Camp with Ben Lawry &amp; John Carmody June 16th &amp; 17th </name><id>12978721</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276700400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/12978721/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/5/d/global_7562653.jpeg</photo_url></item>