<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Lexington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.577200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978 525 3343)</phone><name>Magnolia Library</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1336500</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.712400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Great Food, Wine, Beer and a Raffle what could be better?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;2.12.11 UPDATE:&amp;nbsp; This event WILL sell out if you plan on going and haven't reserved/got your ticket we suggest that you do it soon.&amp;nbsp; All you have to do is call &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;Magnolia Library Center, 978-525-3343&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;to reserve your ticket and then pay for it at the door.&amp;nbsp; Please remember to come back to the site and let us know that you are attending so we are looking for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's go check out the 2011 Tast of Magnolia.   This is a fundraiser for Magnolia's Library and it is their biggest fundraiser, so come out and support the Library and have fun with our friends. It will be a Winter Wonderland in Magnolia.&amp;nbsp; We will be walking around sampling great food by local restaurants, don't forget the Wine and Beer samples also, casual dress.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: We willl be meeting at 6:45, the event runs from 7:00-9:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: $30.00 in advance/$35.00 at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you are responsible for purchasing your own tickets.&amp;nbsp; Tickets are on sale at the Magnolia Library Center, 978-525-3343 &amp;amp; Extreme Truck and Auto, 14 Kondelin Rd. Gloucester MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We we will be in the entrance waiting for everyone to arrive, if you get there and can't find us, then walk in and I am sure you will be able to find us.&amp;nbsp; Please note we may not all be able to stay together as a group, if that doesn't work for you then this event may not work for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;When you have gotten your ticket, remember to log back into the site and change your status to "have ticket" so we know to be looking for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&amp;nbsp; 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&amp;nbsp; Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Looking forward to seeing you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in by the entrance or walk around and look for us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298186565000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>It will be fun to sample all the dishes from local restaurants.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297128102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taste of Magnolia</name><id>16482652</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298072700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/16482652/</event_url></item>