<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Lang Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.899410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>664559</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.702910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>My son made his own arrangements to get back to UConn for a party last night.  Leave it to a college student to choose a party over hiking with mom!  So, just like many of you, I'm not going all the way to Mashamoquet either (as much as I like that trail, it's just too far).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But I want to get out this afternoon, and if you do to, join me at Northwest Park in Windsor for 2 to 3 mile walk.  We will be hiking a combination of yellow, pink and green trails, making a loop.  This is a moderate hike at a social (ie slow!) pace, which most people should be able to do.  Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the parking lot by my red Ford Taurus wagon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224350122000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223130897000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Change of plans -- not Wolf Den but Northwest Park</name><id>8894763</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223233200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8894763/</event_url></item>