<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Put on your Sherlock Holmes hat, we are going on an adventure&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5W!TS premier show, TOMB, now at 5W!TS-Boston, is a 45-minute interactive adventure experience set in an incredibly realistic pharaoh's tomb in an archaeological dig site in ancient Egypt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.5-wits.com/shows/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.5-wits.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests begin their expedition by meeting with their Guide and receiving their final instructions from Director Cavendish. Groups then begin to explore TOMB in hopes of discovering the mystery of the lost professor. However, once inside the TOMB the spirit of an ancient Pharaoh is awoken and things take a turn for the worse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No one knows quite what will happen, but there are a few things you can be certain of: You'll be using your mind and body to solve physical and mental challenges, working together as a team to progress through to the pharaoh's burial chamber. Your choices matter in this hands-on adventure. No one said it would be easy, and there are consequences if you fail! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A new TOMB adventure begins every 15 minutes. Tickets are available online, over the phone (617-375-WITS) or at the door for your adventure today! Groups of 12 or more may reserve private expeditions, so let us know and we can schedule a private adventure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Ananta for digging this one up!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am putting this down for Friday, its likely to snow but you never know. If more people are interested in any other day please update the discussion board so we can  buy tickets accordingly. I will close the discussion board on Wednesday so we can actually buy tickets, hope thats good enough time for interested people to respond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Expeditions last approximately 45 minutes. Shows depart every 15 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;• Groups of 12 or more may reserve private expeditions by calling 617.375.WITS.&lt;br /&gt;• Tickets may be purchased up to two weeks in advance.&lt;br /&gt;• Tickets are sold based on availability for specific times.&lt;br /&gt;• You should plan to arrive 10 minutes prior to your expedition. Latecomers will be admitted at the discretion of the management. Latecomers may not be accommodated subject to availability. Latecomers will not receive refunds or exchanges.&lt;br /&gt;• Tickets are not refundable and may not be exchanged. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price &lt;br /&gt;$20 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location&lt;br /&gt;186 Brookline Avenue in Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.5-wits.com/directions/#" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.5-wits.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let the adventure begin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karan</member_name><member_id>8985082</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264431960000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262543098000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5W!TS !!!!</name><id>12206814</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263157200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/12206814/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/c/global_10053356.jpeg</photo_url></item>