<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For our second Book &amp;amp; Brew meet-up, The Elegant universe seems like  a good book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what a Book and Brew Event is meant to be: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's basically a SOCIAL event that includes reading a book and getting together once a month (at a pub/restaurant) to discuss the book, Then having some beer and grabbing a bite(if you're hungry). This Book &amp;amp; Brew meet-up, which I hope to offer once a month, is aimed at sharing, good, scientific literature, philosophical literature, inspiring stories, and the occasional piece of fiction in a social atmosphere. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month we will try a Book Then Brew style, i.e. we will discuss the book in a private lounge at Evans complex and go for a beer after. The Place is 100 Memorial drive, Cambridge MA its a 2 minute walk from Kendall/MIT on the red line. My number is the one posted with the location, call me if have any issues getting there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/elegant/everything.html" target="_blank"&gt;Preview of the book&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The place is a 2 minute walk from Kendall/MIT on the red line. and its at the Sky Room. Call me if you have any questions(7743604702)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264460927000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261378315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January Book, Then  Brew!  (The Elegant Universe, Brian Greene)</name><id>12124471</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264287600000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/12124471/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>