<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>213 Burlington Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.501306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-275-8200</phone><name>Flatbread Company</name><city>Bedford</city><id>729384</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.235498</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;This is actually a Boston Vegetarian Society dinning out event that happens to be in Bedford at The Flatbread Company!&lt;br /&gt;This place is great and they have vegan pizza listed on the menu!&lt;br /&gt;It’s this Tuesday the 21st  - I apologize for the short notice.  &lt;br /&gt;Please see details below: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear Boston Vegetarian Society,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're having another event that is convenient for our friends to the&lt;br /&gt;Northwest!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get to know each other over some chewy gourmet flatbreads piled with&lt;br /&gt;organic veggies.  A portion of $ from each delicious pizza goes to the rabbit&lt;br /&gt;rescue and adoption efforts of the House Rabbit Network (HRN).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Note: Several of our members volunteer with HRN.  HRN arranged the benefit and&lt;br /&gt;we're giving it an extra boost with this event.  $3.50 from each large/$1.75&lt;br /&gt;from each small flatbread we order will go to HRN!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TUESDAY, OCTOBER 21, 2008&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 8:30 PM (arrive whenever you can)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Flatbread Company&lt;br /&gt;213 Burlington Road&lt;br /&gt;Bedford MA&lt;br /&gt;(781) 275-8200&lt;br /&gt;Read directions at bottom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Flatbread Company uses organic produce and is on the Phantom Gourmet's&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;8 Favorite Restaurants of All-Time&amp;quot; list for their fabulous&lt;br /&gt;flatbreads wood-fired in a clay oven right in the dining room. &amp;quot;The&lt;br /&gt;exceptional, free-form crust is made from wheat, cake yeast, and spring water,&lt;br /&gt;resulting in awesome chewiness and slim structure,&amp;quot; says the Phantom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Listed on their menu of pizzas:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vegan Pizza - Our organic wood-fired cauldron tomato sauce, organic caramelized&lt;br /&gt;onions, organic&lt;br /&gt;mushrooms, Kalamata olives and homemade organic garlic oil with our own blend&lt;br /&gt;of organic herbs&lt;br /&gt;Whole $14.50, Small $7.75&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also add-on organic veggies from their list: Fire-roasted red peppers,&lt;br /&gt;organic red onions, Kalamata olives, sulfate-free organic sun-dried tomatoes,&lt;br /&gt;organic mushrooms, organic rosemary, organic herb mix, wood-fired cauldron&lt;br /&gt;tomato sauce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also on their menu is a highly acclaimed salad -- no $ from this goes to the&lt;br /&gt;bunny benefit, but it's a great side dish to your pizza:&lt;br /&gt;Organic mesclun and organic sweet leaf lettuces tossed with organic celery and&lt;br /&gt;carrots, toasted sesame seeds, organic Arame seaweed and homemade berry&lt;br /&gt;vinaigrette  $6.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Bunnies:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They can be wonderful companions for a vegetarian household! Rabbits are&lt;br /&gt;natural vegetarians, can be litterbox trained, and can make joyful, affectionate&lt;br /&gt;housemates.  Shelters and rescue groups are full of domestic rabbits needing&lt;br /&gt;their &amp;quot;forever home.&amp;quot;  Thinking about adoption? Learn more from the&lt;br /&gt;experts at HRN, who will be present at this event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rabbitnetwork.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rabbitnetw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Flatbread Co. is in a complex of buildings that looks like an office park. &lt;br /&gt;Also in that complex are Bamboo and The Melting Pot, and you can see their signs&lt;br /&gt;from the road. (It is across Rt. 62 from MITRE Corp.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 128 take Exit 32 onto Rt. 3 North towards Lowell.&lt;br /&gt;Drive 4/10 mile and take Exit 26 (Rt. 62 Burlington/Bedford); turn right off&lt;br /&gt;the ramp onto Burlington Rd. (Rt. 62 East)&lt;br /&gt;Drive 3/10 mile and turn right at the second light into the parking lot at&lt;br /&gt;Network Drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evelyn Kimber&lt;br /&gt;Boston Vegetarian Society&lt;br /&gt;www.BostonVeg.org &lt;br /&gt;617-424-8846&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225647781000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224369096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maynard Area Vegan Meetup Meets up with the BVS Dinning Out in Bedford</name><id>8986997</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224624600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/8986997/</event_url></item>