<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us in mindful community as we seek to gain greater awareness of understanding in our lives. All levels of meditators and practitioners welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday evening we will offer Sharon Salzberg's talk on The Three Skills of Meditation.  Below is her description of her talk.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sharon Salzberg. . .&lt;br /&gt;The most compelling part of my practice right now comes in the form of my writing. For a long time, I've focused my teaching and writing on lovingkindness. Now as I look more deeply into lovingkindness, I find that it actually rests on another foundation, the expression of faith. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Faith is the topic I am exploring most in teaching and writing. Today there is a tremendous upsurge of interest in a new kind of faith, based on a practice where people can experience a direct spirituality, one without rigid dogma or compulsory belief in a specific cosmology. This is a spirituality that rests on personal transformation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vipassana allows us to take a method of mind training and craft a way of life that is more compassionate, more ethical and more powerful than our unawakened lives. The Buddha's teachings give us an immediate experience of what we can do to change. Faith in the teachings means we align ourselves with a vision of our greatest possibilities. This is the heart of the practice.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263424215000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263073047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekly Meetup</name><id>12272305</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263250800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/12272305/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/1/global_12020385.jpeg</photo_url></item>