<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>6.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Hi -&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;A bit of a unique hiking and picnic opportunity; not suitable for everyone, so please read through the description before deciding if this day long outdoors venture is for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Once per year, the York Land Trust (of which I am a member) leads a slow-paced hike in and around the entire Mount A area, starting at the top of Mount A through all kinds of beautiful unmarked trails ending very close to the York River.  Their partial description is as follows:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;Mount Agamenticus to the York River is a critical Maine natural area and home to Maine's greatest diversity of plants and animals.  To learn what makes this landscape so special, join York Land Trust and two of our conservation partners for a spectacular trek that offers great views of Mt.A. and its pristine ponds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;As hikers descend the mountain,  they will hear the stories of local land use change over time and learn interesting facts about some of the area's oldest trees and endangered wildlife, such as the Blanding's turtle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;For this daylong adventure of moderate difficulty, hikers should bring water and food, and dress for protection from weather and insects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;Included is a stop of about 1/2 hour or so for a picnic, so pack lunch, water, snacks.  Dress for comfort and insect protection with appropriate footwear with sturdy grips for wet spots.  You might also want to bring a camera and binoculars for pictures and bird sightings and foliage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;I have been on this outing before and it is a lot of fun!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;It is very slow paced - but - also very long, all of the 5 hours as advertised, but with a stop for a nice picnic and for snacks.  Hard to say the amount of miles covered due to the slow pace, but my best estimate is about 5 - 7 slow and well paced miles in total.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;Then at the very end of the hike, a little shuttle bus awaits to take us for the ride back to the top of Mount A and to our vehicles!  Some of us then opt to head out for a late lunch or early dinner, but that is optional and not part of the itinerary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;I can only take 4 others with me (each York Land Trust member is allowed 5).  All told there should be about 20 - 25 people or so.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;Suggested donation is $5 per person (plus the $1 Meetup fee).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;Hopefully, you can join us - but please be certain that you can do so before committing.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;It is a day long outing, very early start (we have to be there by 08:45 AM; no later than that) lots of walking - but lots of fun in a rural outdoors setting.  A great day for peak foliage! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;Look forward to seeing you there!  This hike, as with all Meetups, is as Members' risk. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff ; font-size : small"&gt;Randy &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the TOP of Mount A;look for silver Subaru Forester in parking lot near lodge</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351010784000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350132604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guided 5-hour hike and picnic Mount Agamenticus in York!</name><id>86801132</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350823500000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/86801132/</event_url></item>