<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Western Massachewsetts Paddling Group is having an evening paddle on the Congo Lake just a bit north East of Bradly airport and the NewGate Prizon this Friday evening (provided the weather is good enough).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;I see a rainy&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;forecast &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;for friday, But you can check for yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;FROM WHAT IS INDICATED, looks like sparodic rain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*YOU ARE ON YOUR OWN* &amp;nbsp; , look for fellow kayakers in the area listed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;or sign up on the Western Mass group site for info, cancellations or whatever.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;I am concentrating on SATURDAYS event and wont take a chance in any friday rain or stay out late causing me to be late or tired for SATURDAY !!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;SEE You instead at the &amp;nbsp;SATURDAY's &amp;nbsp;at the "Cold Springs River" Event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Friday:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Showers likely and possibly a thunderstorm. Cloudy, with a high near 76. South wind between 6 and 10 mph. Chance of precipitation is 70%. New rainfall amounts between a quarter and half of an inch possible.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Friday Night:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;A chance of showers and thunderstorms. Areas of fog before 9pm, then Patchy fog after 10pm. Otherwise, mostly cloudy, with a low around 61. South wind between 5 and 8 mph becoming calm. Chance of precipitation is 50%. New rainfall amounts of less than a tenth of an inch, except higher amounts possible in thunderstorms.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;and a graphical view:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KBDL&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KBDL&amp;amp;state=CT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Its looking&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;on friday&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;to be near the end of the front though, but that may mean winds above 10 mph.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;additional weather:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WEATHER for this location:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Close up view:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/northeast_loop.php"&gt;http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/northeast_loop.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prediction:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KCEF&amp;amp;state=MA"&gt;http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KCEF&amp;amp;state=MA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;National View:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/index_loop.php"&gt;http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/index_loop.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Congo Lake is about 30 or so minutes from Hartford if no traffic when traveling on I-91 north, (at 6:15 its winding down)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am debating with my self on if its something we should join them on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I usually skip the evening paddles in favor of offering a full day on Saturday or Sunday with an after party that lasts into the evening if we have to drive to a distant location or Ocean Events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event on the Congo Lake is we paddle some of the lake in the evening then those interested can go to Crabby Joe's food place on the shore after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some reviews of Crabby's (ahh sounds to me like its the avrage food place anywhere)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/place?rlz=1C1RNNN_enUS367US377&amp;amp;um=1&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;q=crabby+joe's+ma+reviews&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=crabby+joe's&amp;amp;hnear=0x89e3656d"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps/place?rlz=1C1RNNN_enUS367US377&amp;amp;um=1&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;q=crabby+joe's+ma+reviews&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=crabby+joe's&amp;amp;hnear=0x89e3656d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally would like to have a more intimate area where we converse and possibly having some Wine and Italian Table Chez or other healthy food by the gas firepit along this shore area next to the dirt parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As many of you know i don't care for loud people in restaurants, bands and odd seating arrangements that destroy social interaction and of course the cost of some greasy un healthy hunk of grub or even a supposedly good healthy meal for 20 bucks when i can&amp;nbsp;deliberately&amp;nbsp;choose only the things i must be eating wether from home or at our Pot Lucks..etc..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, An inexpensive healthy sandwitch is OK for me preferably if we get served fast and its kind of intimate inside for conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A loud interior, any distorted band sound from outside or nearby, and some long table or split up table arrangements where you are plooped down and not able to move about to converse ..nope...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whats your opinion ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next thing of concern is I have the "Cold Spring River" Listed for Saturday Morning if the weather is good enough. (so far its looking Just under "OK" but too soon to confirm based on the weather predictions).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If paddling out on the Congo, we are out till 10:00 pm or even 9 pm adding the drive time and equipment loading etc..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will you be able to go for the Saturday Morning Event &amp;nbsp;??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are boat ramp areas nearby, they generally charge $5 for each boat in the water,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The money grabbers may leave by 7 pm but im clearly assuming they are NOT going unless they have to poop or something --- so forget using the pay lot since the blood suckers are looking for money any way they can get it. (ok i understand paying some money for the boat areas but only if i catch fish in the water or use it all day long in the day).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a free dirt area before Crabby Joe's but parking may be difficult at times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously since the money grabbers charge kayakers ready to be bitten by buggs right up to the minute they leave in the dark-- &amp;nbsp;not many will park there but will opt for the dirt lot instead..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is also a possibility of parking at Crabby Joe's and carrying down to the water for free also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I opt for the free only and adequate parking for all interested, else forget about it...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OK ..LEAVE YOUR OPINION IN THE RSVP AREA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This helps me determine if i will list this event for this friday or some other day if the decision is made that the weather is not good enough this friday night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~&amp;gt; Remember i usually list an event &amp;nbsp;for Saturday mornings as long as the weather is good enough untill fall season (maybe Sunday if Saturday is not good enough)..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh if you want to join the Western Mass. group and don't want to go to Cold Springs River its an option for you too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the other events they have if you like more river (up to class 2 WW) - lake events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My events are more flat rivers (up to class 1.5 max with 18 footers) to general ocean events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the groups hyperlink,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Kayakers/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Kayakers/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;see ya soon..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;al-r&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Info From Tom of the Westen Mass Padle Group:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Al you can use my write up if you want&amp;hellip;I met you again at Judy&amp;rsquo;s house in Enfield after the&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;Scantic river race&lt;/span&gt;, my son was with me. I would like to get over 20 boats out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom&amp;rsquo;s Famous First 2011&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;Friday night&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Paddle and Chow&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;on June 17 th&amp;nbsp;2011, at 7 PM&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;on Congamond Lakes. Free dirt &amp;ldquo;Put In&amp;rdquo; on Route 168 has room for about 10 cars; we can also park at Crabby Joes with a short portage to the water, or at the state launch for a fee of about $5. I hope to get a good turnout for this event. We will have a fun easy cruise around middle pond with a slow shoreline pace. Return trip will be after dark, so headlamp or white 360 degree light required by the state to warn off boaters. You should bring a pair of&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;glow sticks&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;to put on your boat. After dark we will travel with just the&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;glow stick&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;and wear the headlamps (in the off position) in case we need to warn off an approaching boater. That way we don&amp;rsquo;t lose our night vision. Bug spray might also be a good idea or a sweat shirt as the temps might drop after dark. Afterwards we will go to Crabby Joes for some dinner and or drinks. I hope to paddle about 2 hours. It is calm flat water with some boat traffic. Folks are responsible for themselves. New paddlers, youths and friends all welcome. We may decide to break into 2 groups if we have a great turnout. Bring money for your food. Only yes RSVP&amp;rsquo;s required. Rain will postpones this event. Look for weather updates around noon the day of the paddle. Hope you can make it&amp;hellip;Tom&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You are on your own --- Look for the Western Mass Kayak Group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308356544000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308079392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opinion Needed for an Evening Paddle Event</name><id>22191011</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308351600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/22191011/</event_url></item>