<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is our first social mixer of the summer, and it's going to be good!  It has been a while since we have had an event, and this is a great way for current members to catch up with the group.  If you are a new member (or have joined but never made an event), this is a great way for you to find out about our nightlife events and to meet other new members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to ALL members.  I would encourage new members to come early around 5pm, and for other members to come at 6:30pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bar Lola has great atmosphere and they serve a wonderful selection of tapas, along with wine and sangria, of course!  This will be a very laid back, no agenda meetup - just good drinks (and food!) with good people.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: New member meeting time is 5pm, current members meeting time is 6:30pm.  If you come after 7:30pm, be sure to give me a call.  We will meet in the bar area at Bar Lola, which is on the right hand side of the restaurant when you first walk in.  If you have any problems finding the group, give me a call.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVENT FEE:  Feel free to buy your hard working organizers a drink!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bar Lola is a Spanish Tapas Restaurant/Lounge located at 160 Comm Ave, on the corner of Dartmouth St.  It is located 5 minutes from the Copley Square T station on the Green Line.  You will need to walk downstairs to enter the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan to have drinks and food, be sure to bring extra cash to for easier bill paying. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*FOR ALL MEMBERS!*&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site, call my cell if you need help finding the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>35</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213147358000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><why>This is our first summer event, should be a great one!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212459351000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join Us for Summer Mixer 1!  All Members Welcome! This Sunday, June 8</name><id>8065933</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212958800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8065933/</event_url></item>