<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076322</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rusty Hammer</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1023192</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/9/0/event_109268592.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The book club selection for May is &lt;strong&gt;The Sense of an Ending&lt;/strong&gt; by Julian Barnes. &amp;nbsp;It is the winner of the 2011 Man Booker Prize. &amp;nbsp;Here is the synopsis for &lt;strong&gt;The Sense of an Ending&lt;/strong&gt; from Amazon.com:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By an acclaimed writer at the height of his powers,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Sense of an Ending&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;extends a streak of extraordinary books that began with the best-selling&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Arthur &amp;amp; George&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and continued with&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Nothing to Be Frightened Of&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and, most recently,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Pulse.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;This intense new novel follows a middle-aged man as he contends with a past he has never much thought about&amp;mdash;until his closest childhood friends return with a vengeance, one of them from the grave, another maddeningly present. Tony Webster thought he&amp;rsquo;d left all this behind as he built a life for himself, and by now his marriage and family and career have fallen into an amicable divorce and retirement. But he is then presented with a mysterious legacy that obliges him to reconsider a variety of things he thought he&amp;rsquo;d understood all along, and to revise his estimation of his own nature and place in the world.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;A novel so compelling that it begs to be read in a single sitting, with stunning psychological and emotional depth and sophistication,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Sense of an Ending&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a brilliant new chapter in Julian Barnes&amp;rsquo;s oeuvre.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;And a review from Publishers Weekly:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;In Barnes's (Flaubert's Parrot) latest, winner of the 2011 Man-Booker Prize, protagonist Tony Webster has lived an average life with an unremarkable career, a quiet divorce, and a calm middle age. Now in his mid-60s, his retirement is thrown into confusion when he's bequeathed a journal that belonged to his brilliant school-friend, Adrian, who committed suicide 40 years earlier at age 22. Though he thought he understood the events of his youth, he's forced to radically revise what he thought he knew about Adrian, his bitter parting with his mysterious first lover Veronica, and reflect on how he let life pass him by safely and predictably. Barnes's spare and luminous prose splendidly evokes the sense of a life whose meaning (or meaninglessness) is inevitably defined by "the sense of an ending" which only death provides. Despite its focus on the blindness of youth and the passage of time, Barnes's book is entirely unpretentious. From the haunting images of its first pages to the surprising and wrenching finale, the novel carries readers with sensitivity and wisdom through the agony of lost time.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336590942000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333587011000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club May - The Sense of an Ending</name><id>dpskncyqhblb</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336518000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/59306392/</event_url></item>