<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>First film from the director of &lt;b&gt;Rebel Without a Cause&lt;/b&gt; plus an additional short &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This boy...and this girl...were never properly introduced to the world we live in.&amp;quot; With this superimposed opening title, director Nicholas Ray inaugurates his first feature, &lt;b&gt;They Live by Night&lt;/b&gt;. Farley Granger and Cathy O'Donnell play a &amp;quot;Bonnie and Clyde&amp;quot;-type fugitive couple, who in trying to escape their past are hell-bent down the road to Doom. Despite their criminal activities, Bowie (Granger) and Keechie (O'Donnell) are hopelessly naïve, fabricating their own idyllic dream world as the authorities close in. The entrapment -- both actual and symbolic -- of the young misfit couple can now be seen as a precursor to the dilemma facing James Dean in Ray's 1955 film &lt;b&gt;Rebel Without a Cause.&lt;/b&gt; A box-office disappointment upon its first release, &lt;b&gt;They Live by Night&lt;/b&gt; has since gained stature as one of the most sensitive and least-predictable entries in the film noir genre. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Ray's remarkable 1949 debut, one of the many Hollywood precursors to Bonnie and Clyde,&lt;br /&gt;is an unusually pure representation of the doomed outlaw couple—perhaps the most romantic of all films noir.”&lt;br /&gt;– J. Hoberman, The Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ray’s extraordinary film debut reveals the major themes and dark romanticism that would recur across his remarkable career. A clear-eyed tragedy of a sensitive, emotional boy and wise-beyond-her-years girl who find in each other a fleeting solace from a cruel, uncaring world, They Live By Night travels deep into the dark, cold night of the American heartland whose desolation would exert a permanent hold on Ray’s imagination. A hybrid crime thriller and love story – whose bifurcation reflects the conflicting worlds between which its protagonists are caught – They Live By Night features deeply moving, resonant performances from Farley Granger and Cathy O’Donnell and an immediacy and rawness of emotion that lends an air of desperate poignancy to the doomed lovers. HFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be holding a Meetup Sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then we will go to a nearby restaurant for our group's discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277514127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nicholas Ray's They Live By Night</name><id>13913615</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278802800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13913615/</event_url></item>