<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-245-1525</phone><name>Harrington's Pub</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>733190</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From FRANK:   Cover charge of $10.00 starts at 1:00pm when there will be live music on both floors. So if you want to avoid the cover charge be there before. If you plan to stay a while and order food I suggest putting your name in for a table. Wear Green, bring Irish Red Heads and Happy St. Patty's Day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A large group of us attended each of the last 3 years. This year St Patricks Day is on a Sunday! &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/b/7/0/event_104539312.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives and Wakefield Weeknights are going Green on Sunday, March 17 to celebrate St Patrick's Day at Harrington's Food and Spirits in downtown Wakefield. Harrington's is a cozy Irish Restaurant and Pub with two floors. We have been there before. The food is great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harrington's is all Irish, all day, all night, on both floors. There is live entertainment all afternoon and night at Harrington's led by the owner Dan's band Casterbridge Union and Terry Weir and others. There is a $10.00 cover after 1 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear your Green and be there at 1:00 pm or whenever. The place will be packed all day and all night! I suggest any RSVPs coordinate by E Mail to meet other attendees at whatever times works best. Please RSVP and let us know approximately what time you will join us! Some of us will be there well into the evening just like last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking in downtown Wakefield in the public lot across from Harrington's and along Water and Main Streets. The location is T accessible by the 136 and 137 Bus from the Orange Line in Malden Center. And Commuter Rail accessible from North Station via the Reading and Haverhill Trains stopping at Wakefield with a less than 10 minute walk up Albion to Main to Water Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to pay in cash as you order or maintain your own bar tab and settle with your server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Melody Joy Gaeta, Realtor</member_name><member_id>3036353</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363709790000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361641802000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate St. Patrick's Day at Harrington's Irish Pub - multi-group</name><id>106031492</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363539600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/106031492/</event_url></item>