<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 Meeting Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.829072</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 453-9727</phone><name>Providence Byblos Hookah Lounge</name><city>Providence</city><id>961382</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.400450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in Providence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Byblos Hookah Lounge near Thayer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Byblos is a small Middle Eastern restaurant on Meeting Street near Thayer.  We'll be meeting upstairs in their Hookah lounge.  It is a very casual atmosphere with many comfy couches and benches to relax on.  They have a full bar upstairs, and I encourage you to try some of the Middle Eastern cuisine which they bring to you from the restaurant downstairs.  If you enjoy a smoke, they have many flavors to choose from.  However, smoking isn't required, and thanks to that variety of flavors the place usually smells really good.  Parking near Thayer can be a little tricky, so be sure to read the street signs closely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the chatty blonde near the bar, but we are usually a hard group to miss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephanie</member_name><member_id>8926850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266448059000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265835743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Byblos Hookah Lounge near Thayer</name><id>12573372</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266274800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/12573372/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>