<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The MARCnic: A Vegan Potluck Festival at Sunny Meadow Sanctuary Hosted by The Massachusetts Animal Rights Coalition (MARC) &lt;br /&gt;When: July 25, 2009, 2:00pm on. &lt;br /&gt;RSVP for Info/Directions: info@MassAnimalRights.org; www.MassAnimalRights.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MARCnic @ Helen &amp;amp; Steve's on July 25th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT: A vegan potluck picnic in the country!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Our place in Central Mass, about 1.5 hours west of Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Saturday, July 25, from 2pm on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHO: You and anyone else you would like to bring. The more the&lt;br /&gt;merrier. Just bring a vegan potluck dish or beverage---please let us&lt;br /&gt;know what you plan to bring if you can. (We will be providing vegan&lt;br /&gt;burgers and hotdogs on the grill.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP/DIRECTIONS: Email us anytime from now till the MARCnic at:&lt;br /&gt;rayshick@msn. com to RSVP yes, find or give a ride, get directions,&lt;br /&gt;help with arrangements, casually coordinate food, etc. Or just&lt;br /&gt;answer this email. After noon on the 25th, it is best to call at 978-&lt;br /&gt;257-7062.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHY: Okay, okay, we know we are always &amp;quot;inviting&amp;quot; you to work for&lt;br /&gt;animals, but we all deserve some fun now and again. :-) So please&lt;br /&gt;try to join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW: Let us know if you'd also like to bring a tent and spend the&lt;br /&gt;night. We live on 15 acres, so there's lots of room. And we have a&lt;br /&gt;few spare bedrooms, so let us know if you would like to stay in one&lt;br /&gt;of them. Or, there is a pricey but beautiful inn in town; let us&lt;br /&gt;know if you would like info about it. We always have a campfire in&lt;br /&gt;the evening (and vegan smores!). Plus, if you play an instrument,&lt;br /&gt;please bring it along and let us know; in the past we have been&lt;br /&gt;blessed by folks singing and playing around the campfire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DOGS: We have one big dog, a cat, goats, ducks, turtles, and chickens&lt;br /&gt;so if you want to bring a dog, that's great, but please let us know&lt;br /&gt;so we can discuss if it will work. There will be children attending&lt;br /&gt;so keep that in mind. Plus, we absolutely cannot have dogs that fight&lt;br /&gt;or will harrass or bark at our rescued animals. Dogs can be off leash&lt;br /&gt;because we are in a very safe area, but we recommend, if you aren't&lt;br /&gt;sure, to start with leashed dogs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FAQs: Here are some questions that members have asked in the past;&lt;br /&gt;we thought others might be wondering the same things:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Is the picnic rain or shine? YES!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Can I bring a friend, partner, child, children, etc.? Even if&lt;br /&gt;they aren't veg? Yes! The more the merrier. In past years, non-veg&lt;br /&gt;spouses, family, friends, etc. have come and everyone gets along&lt;br /&gt;great.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Can I/we let you know later? Sure, you can let us know anytime at&lt;br /&gt;all even at the very last minute. Just be sure to contact us for&lt;br /&gt;directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Is there anything else you need? Lawn chairs and blankets would&lt;br /&gt;be great. And if there is something special you like to drink please&lt;br /&gt;bring it. There will be various juices, some vegan beer, and water&lt;br /&gt;on hand but we can always use more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Will there be other children there? Yes, there definitely will.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Do other people camp? Yes!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250361804000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245905459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MARCnic : A Vegan Potluck Festival at Sunny Meadow Sanctuary hosted by MARC</name><id>10731836</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248544800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/10731836/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>