<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Did you know there's a restaurant week in Winter too!  Right On!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This was such a great experience last summer that I'm cheating and heading right back to the Elephant Walk.  We may get another restaurant in over this two week span if folks are really itching to try something new (half the purpose of these prix-fixe prices, eh?).  Give me a buzz with your burning desires (um, correction...I really only want to hear about those restaurant related :-) and we'll see if we can get them on the calender.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the Restaurant week website for other location options (for yourself or to guide us for a Meetup event) at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.restaurantweekboston.com/?gclid=CIiz4Lm2wZECFQhzHgod6FjRyQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.restaurant...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the Elephant Walk and links to their prix fixe menus at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.elephantwalk.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.elephantwa...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting inside the door at 6:30.  The reservations are for 10 folks.  It's a fairly small place so I have to limit our numbers some, so please respect your peers and keep your RSVP's accurate.  Will send more details (including my cell phone number), as the date approaches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, etc, contact Lisa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If interested, perhaps we can pack ourselves into &amp;quot;the Burren&amp;quot; in Somerville thereafter for some St. Patrick's Day fun.  Any non-dinner attendees interested in catching us at &amp;quot;the Barren&amp;quot;, drop me a note and we'll try to catch ya there (probably 9-9:30)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting inside the doors at the hostess stand/bar area at 6:30</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205966337000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202915129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Restaurant Week dinner at Elephant Walk, Cambridge</name><id>7323819</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205793000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/7323819/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/2/global_2186386.jpeg</photo_url></item>