<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>106 Prospect St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.367733</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Out of the Blue Art Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9572442</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101913</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's Meetup at the Out of the Blue gallery in Central Square to support local artists, Kerry Kelley and the Outliers, as they launch their Kickstarter project for their new CD, 'Kaizen'.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kaizen&lt;/em&gt; (改善) is Japanese for "improvement" or "change for the better".  It usually refers to continuous small improvements in business processes, but singer/songwriter Kelley makes Kaizen very personal, using it as a metaphor and framework for life. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The songs, written, played and sung beautifully, are about&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;taking those continuous small steps towards a big, scary goal, they're about risking and reinventing and growing;  ultimately, they're about having the courage to pursue your dreams. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So please stop by the Out of the Blue gallery to support a terrific local artist as she pursues her dreams.  Of course we'll have great music, but we'll also have a keg of the delicious Belgian beer, Hoegaarden, and some finger foods to help kick off your Friday night as you help Kerry and the Outliers kick off their Kickstarter CD campaign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Curious about Kerry's music?  Listen to the first track, 'Tell me no lies', from the new CD on &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/kerrykelley/tell-me-no-lies-mix-1"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also visit &lt;a href="http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/kerrykelley/the-kaizen-project-album-launch"&gt;Kerry's Kickstarter Project page&lt;/a&gt; for more information about Kerry and the new CD as well as all the details about the perks of pledging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this great event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other notes: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Central Square T Station is only 1/4 mile away.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is street parking in the area as well as some parking lots. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

There are three public parking lots behind the Cantab Lounge (738 Mass Ave) along Green St. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

There is also the Green Street Garage at the corner of Green and Pearl Streets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a small place.  I'll be in the front room near the food &amp; beer and I should be there by 7:15.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>paul</member_name><member_id>4738108</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368235060000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367425851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kerry Kelley and the Outliers 'Kaizen' CD Kickstarter Launch &amp; Belgian Beer Bash</name><id>117164182</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368228600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/117164182/</event_url></item>