<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>State Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.391875</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt Grace State Forest</name><city>Warwick</city><id>957167</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.125167</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I live in the Athol area and want to get out for more hikes, especially weekday afternoon hikes, when time permits me to do that. If anyone is interested in joining me, I would love some company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was thinking we could take turns suggesting places to hike or maybe get a few going in different areas so it works for all. I don't mind traveling when time permits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you RSVP for this hike, please talk to me (and the group) via the comment space about what is practical for you time wise, days available, some areas to hike, etc...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can use this posting as an open forum to find hiking friends with compatible schedules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comment section below to communicate with everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This posting can be used each time we hike and just simply updated for each hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll suggest hikes and hiking times too but I am looking for your suggestions and trying to coordinate something practical for everyone, if that is possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this Mt Grace Hike....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/30" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Mount Grace 
&lt;p&gt;Winchester Road (Rte. 78), Warwick, MA &lt;br /&gt;

(978) 544-3939&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mount Grace is the high point of the North Quabbin, offering breathtaking views of other mountains, ridges, valleys, forests, and settlements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 1,617 feet above sea level, Mount Grace is the high point of &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/115"&gt;Mount Grace State Forest&lt;/a&gt; and, indeed, of the whole North Quabbin region. It was a popular downhill ski area for several decades during the mid-20th century. The now unused fire tower atop the mountain affords breathtaking views of Sunny Valley in Winchester, New Hampshire; Mount Monadnock in Jaffrey, New Hampshire; part of the charming center of the town of Warwick; and ridges, fields, and forests galore. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Two loop trails are possible. The first begins at a blue-blazed trail at the back left (south) corner of Ohlson Field behind the parking area, continues on an old fire road (the right-hand choice at a summit marker), and returns by either the southbound or the northbound portion of the white-blazed &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/126"&gt;Metacoment-Monadnock Trail&lt;/a&gt; (the M&amp;amp;M). The second follows the blue-blazed Round-the-Mountain Trail from either corner of the field. Consult a state forest trail map for details; copies are usually available in a box at the former administration building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Rte. 2, take Exit 15 and take Rte. 122 into Orange center. Turn left (west) onto Rte. 2A. Turn right on Rte. 78, go to Warwick center, and continue north 0.4 miles to parking area on left, just after brown headquarters building.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a maroon Monte Carlo</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330356455000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329182343000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Afternoon Hikes/ weekend hikes too(Friday hikes)</name><id>qscvncyqdbwb</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329505200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/52247772/</event_url></item>