<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>5th Floor</address_2><address_1>38 Ash St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.348827</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-635-5129</phone><name>Boston Chinatown Neighborhood Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>484584</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come meet  my (Adele Chang) Sister, Alexandra Chang as she introduces her first book  from Time Zone 8's (Bejing*Shanghi) #1 selling book, &amp;quot;Envsioning Diaspora&amp;quot;  &lt;i&gt;Asian  American Visual Arts Collective from Godzookie to the Barnstormers&lt;/i&gt;. at BCNC.  She will be giving a presentation, Book talk, Q &amp;amp; A and Book Signing.  Her book will be available for purchase at the event or at &lt;a href="http://www.envisioningbooks.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.envisionin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this book Alexandra Chang investigates “Asian American Art” through the formation, membership and artwork of three important post-’90s Asian American artist collectives: Godzilla: Asian American Art Network, Godzookie and the Barnstormers. Through in-depth interviews with artists, arts administrators and writers, as well as the search for archival documents from university and museum archives to the storage shelves of participant artists, Chang traces the shifts within the changing historical contexts of the initial coinage of the term “Asian America.” We see how the term began as an outgrowth of the late ’60s civil rights movement, to its integration into mainstream multicultural discourse and its legacy today. Envisioning Diaspora peers into the nuances of artist collective formations and communities of affinity, and ultimately the core issues of identity politics, aesthetics and diaspora involved in Asian American Art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alexandra Chang, originally from Lexington, MA, is an Arts Writer, filmmaker, and independent curator.  She has curated exhibitions and written on conteporary art, graffiti, design, and architecture.  She has served as the managing editor for &lt;i&gt;Arts Asia Pasific magazine&lt;/i&gt; and features editor or &lt;i&gt;amNewYork.&lt;/i&gt;  Her writing have appeared in &lt;i&gt;Art Asia Pasific, ArtKrush, Asiance magazine, At in Asia,am New York, Time Magazine, Chicago Tribune, Boston Globe&lt;/i&gt;, among other publications.  She is also events coordinator at A/P/A (Asian Pacifc American) Institute at NYU and holds a Master's from NYU John W. Daper Interdisciplinary Mater's program in Hmanities and Social Thought with concentration in Asian American Art Hstory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other websites of Interest include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.envisioningbooks.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.envisionin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://asianamericanart.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://asianamericana...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dreamsomuch.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dreamsomuc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.projecttosurface.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.projecttos...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you can all make it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADELE&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adele</member_name><member_id>481803</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244561247000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238876853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet The Author:  Alexandra Chang Presents: Envisioning Diaspora</name><id>10115504</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244307600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/10115504/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/b/global_7971531.jpeg</photo_url></item>