<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 Hull St. (Route 228)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02025</zip><lat>42.240720</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(781) 383-2339</phone><name>DiNero's Restaurant</name><city>Cohasset</city><id>622462</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.802020</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Delicious news, fellow Diners! The results of our &amp;quot;D&amp;quot; restaurant poll are in - Our choice has been decisively determined and is now declared!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seriously, &lt;a href="http://www.dinerosdining.com/" target="_blank"&gt;DiNero's Restaurant&lt;/a&gt; in Cohasset has long been a favorite of many South Shore residents for its memorably modern decor and, more importantly, the quality of the Italian dishes that emerge from its kitchen. Offerings on their &lt;a href="http://www.dinerosdining.com/dinner.htm" target="_blank"&gt;online dinner menu&lt;/a&gt; range from linguine with house tomato or Alfredo sauce ($10.95) to chargrilled sirloin ($21.95), with most entrees coming in between $15.95 and $18.95.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are planning to visit DiNero's on a Wednesday night and hope that a good number of SSDOMG members will be able to join us and experience this well regarded venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DiNero's Restaurant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;235 Hull St., Cohasset&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, May 28 @ 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; S2.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Monday, May 26 @ 9:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; DiNero's is located on Hull St. in Cosset, which is also Route 228. Route 228 can be reached directly off Route 3 by taking exit 14 (head North on Route 228 towards Nantasket and Hull). When you reach the intersection of Routes 228 and 53, go straight across Route 53, remaining on Route 228 North, and see directions in the next paragraph.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternatively, Route 228 intersects with Route 53 at Queen Anne's Corner in Hingham: From Route 53, turn North onto Route 228 (passing the Scarlet Oak Tavern on your left), following it through Hingham and going straight across Route 3A when you come to it (this is also the way to Glastonbury Abbey). Very shortly after crossing Route Route 3A, you will pass Glastonbury Abbey on your left. At this point, DiNero's is almost exactly one mile ahead - it will be a large, off-white building on your right. If you find yourself passing Victoria's Subs &amp;amp; Salads on your left, you have just passed DiNero's and need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 228 also intersects with Route 3A in Hingham: From Route 3A, turn North onto Route 228, following the signs for Glastonbury Abbey. You will shortly pass Glastonbury Abbey on your left. At this point, DiNero's is almost exactly one mile ahead - it will be a large, off-white building on your right. If you find yourself passing Victoria's Subs &amp;amp; Salads on your left, you have just passed DiNero's and need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"If you don't see any of your fellow Meetup members whan you arrive, please just ask to be shown to our table. The names "Mike" and "South Shore Meetup Group" have been noted on our reservation."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212292639000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210569129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Destination: DiNero's!</name><id>7920722</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212015600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7920722/</event_url></item>