<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This information is for those wishing to understand how to survive what will happen energetically in 2012.  Since the planetary energetics are complex to explain, we will be meeting in a classroom with an overhead projector.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The reason we must prepare energetically ahead of time is to shield against the effects of increased planetary merkaba speeds, a topic  which is not generally understood.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who don't even know what merkaba means, here is a definition:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.keylonticdictionary.org/Words/M/Merkaba.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.keylonticd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is also a U-Tube presentation to view, which will help you to understand from a multi-dimensional galactic level what this is all about.   This is even more complex, so please  plan on devoting a total of 6 hours to view all 3 parts before this meetup.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep a note-book handy to jot down your questions, and bring them with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.krystalspi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup adjourns at 9:00 PM.  Please bring your own refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Get on I-93 from wherever you are. We are approx. half an hour north of Concord, NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get off on exit 22. At the end of the ramp go North on Rt. 127 (toward Gaza). In approx. 1.5 miles you will come to a stop sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn left, going North on Rt 132. Watch for mailbox number 298 on the right side of the road, approx. 1.5 mi. up. A tan building with semi-circular window is across the street, on the left side. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go up the first driveway into the property, which has a Meetup sign at the end. Do NOT go up the second driveway which has a sign &amp;quot;ULCS Clinic&amp;quot;. No parking is allowed there, so if you get that far, turn around in that driveway and go back and up the first driveway. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enter through the front door, where you will see another Meetup sign. No need to knock. Just go on in and down the stairs and have a seat in the classroom. If you are arriving early for a private appointment, have a seat in the waiting room instead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go up first driveway, which has Meetup sign at end.  Go in front door, which has another Meetup sign. No need to knock.  Just have a seat in the downstairs classroom.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289960608000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Co-Creative Planetary Stewards</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Back-to-Basics</urlname><id>1438479</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Back to Basics: Sustainable Self-Sufficient Healthy Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282582148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Understanding what will happen in 2012</name><id>14512617</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289948400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Back-to-Basics/events/14512617/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/e/3/global_8253811.jpeg</photo_url></item>