<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi, All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's still a little time to RSVP YES for Jonathan Demme's award winning thriller Silence of the Lambs as part of the repertory screenings of Demme's films in conjunction with the 2010 Coolidge Award Ceremony.  The film will be introduced by medicolegal expert Dr. Thomas Gutheil.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies (SYATM!) Betsey &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, February 23, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;6:45 Silence of the Lambs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be aware that current MAYBE's will be considered NO's unless changed to YES by Monday evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Silence of the Lambs is Demme’s best known film and winner of 5 Oscars, including Best Picture, Best Screenplay, Best Actor (Anthony Hopkins), Best Actress (Jodie Foster), and Best Director (Demme).The film follows FBI cadet Agent Clarice Starling (Foster), who must trust and confide in imprisoned killer Dr. Hannibal Lecter (Hopkins) to stop the infamous serial killer, Buffalo Bill. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intro and Q&amp;amp;A by Dr. Thomas G. Gutheil, M.D., Professor of Psychiatry in the Department of Psychiatry, Beth Israel-Deaconess Medical Center, Harvard Medical School. Dr. Gutheil is an internationally known expert on medicolegal issues and the insanity defense.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Jonathan Demme, w/ Anthony Hopkins, Jodie Foster, Chris Isaak, 1991, 1h58m, 35mm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$9.75/ $6.75 Coolidge Members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coolidge Award Repertory Screening in honor of Jonathan Demme, recipient of the 2010 Coolidge Award&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From IMDB: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taglines: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Hannibal Lecter. Brilliant. Cunning. Psychotic. In his mind lies the clue to a ruthless killer. - Clarice Starling, FBI. Brilliant. Vulnerable. Alone. She must trust him to stop the killer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prepare yourself for the most exciting, mesmerising and terrifying two hours of your life! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To enter the mind of a killer she must challenge the mind of a madman. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May The Silence Be Broken!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>5:45 meetup at Panera's for light supper and chat.  I'll have the BIA meetup logo on red card stock in plain view. 6:15/6:30 gauge when we need to get in line for optimal seating for this star-studded thriller.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264899089000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Silence of the Lambs</name><id>12470496</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266968700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12470496/</event_url></item>