<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>27 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.613570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cape Ann Historical Museum</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>471801</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.661860</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Cape Ann Photography Excursion Group January Meetup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cape Ann Quarries: Part One&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.capeannhistoricalmuseum.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Cape Ann Historical Museum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;27 Pleasant Street&lt;br /&gt;Gloucester, MA  01930&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet Time:&lt;/b&gt;  1:15PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Place:&lt;/b&gt;  On Pleasant Street in front of the Museum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission:&lt;/b&gt;  Cape Ann residents are free during January.&lt;br /&gt;                            Members of the  museum are free, and may bring a guest for free.&lt;br /&gt;                            $6.50 for non-residents / non-members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;  There is metered street parking available through downtown Gloucester, a few spots on Pleasant Street, and in a metered lot across from the museum.  I can't remember if Gloucester requires meters be fed on Sundays, I'll check into this, but bring change for parking just in case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special Exhibit:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Chapters on a Quarry Wall: The Natural Stone Photography&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leslie D. Bartlett, Photographer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.capeannhistoricalmuseum.org/" target="_blank"&gt;CAH Museum&lt;/a&gt; presents an exhibition of photography by Leslie D. Bartlett, &amp;quot;Chapters on a Quarry Wall: The Natural Stone Photography&amp;quot;. It is the culmination of eight years of climbing around quarry ledges to capture the unique light and beauty of the area's granite quarries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After our visit to CAH Museum we'll walk to the nearby Pleasant Street Tea Company to discuss the exhibit over tea/coffee/snacks.  Additionally we'll talk, and share as a group, how lighting, angle, camera/lens, and post-processing techniques, can help bring a very different look to our own photography.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring some of your own work to share.  Whether a successful photo that utilized lighting/angle/post-processing to the max,  or one that had potential, but didn't quite live up to expectations. Members of the group can offer helpful suggestions and experiences.   Please note--If the photos you wish to share haven't been printed, but are available online, e-mail me a link to the photos and I'll setup a way to share them at the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One final note... consider bringing your camera even though this event is a little different than others we've held, there are many photogenic buildings near the CAH Museum, and weather cooperating it could be a beautiful sunset!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is part one, of two, for Cape Ann quarries.  Please see &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/643/calendar/7044522/"&gt;February&lt;/a&gt; for information on part two! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Links related to this event that maybe interesting or beneficial:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.naturalstonephotography.com/"&gt;Natural Stone Photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.followthegleam.com/"&gt;Follow the Gleam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201026279000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196529105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group January Meetup</name><id>6836805</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200852900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/6836805/</event_url></item>