<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Hunt Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.836670</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Amesbury Sports Park</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1486796</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.945374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a pay your own way event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here at the Amesbury Sports Park we are very excited for our first full Summer Season for our Summer Tubing and OGO attractions.  If you had fun in the winter, you will LOVE the summer.  Just like the snow tubing, summer tubing offers you the chance to rocket down our hill with friends but without the heavy coats!  And if you have not been in the OGO ball, you will definitely want to give it a try.  With you, two friends and five gallons of water, it is a wild ride.&lt;br /&gt;What is the OGO? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Outdoor Gravity Orb is an 11 foot transparent inflated sphere with a 6 ft suspended smaller sphere inside with a 2 ft air cushion around it. The extreme sport of sphering, or zorbing was invented and made popular in New Zealand.  Now, it is here in New England.  With our 800 ft run, you can reach speeds up to 30 miles an hour. Wet or Dry, climb into the OGO for the ride of your life.  Now you will know what a hamster feels like!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How do I ride the OGO? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The OGO can be ridden 2 ways, both are fun and crazy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first is to strap into a harness inside the OGO and roll head over heels and watch the world go by.  This is the dry way of getting down the hill, no need to change clothes, just come as you are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The second is the H2OGO.  Climb in either by yourself, or with up to three people, and we toss in five gallons of water into the mix and drop you into a wet and wild ride, all without a harness.  You will flip, flop, slide, scream and laugh your head off all the way down.  Bring a change of clothes and a towel for this one because it is just like being in a washing machine!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember the OGO is one of two things they have here, the second of which is summer tubing &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT IS WET! PLEASE WEAR CLOTHES YOU DONT MIND GETTING WET (I.E. BATHING SUITS) &lt;br /&gt;THEY DO HAVE CHANGING AREAS HERE SO BRING A CHANGE OF CLOTHES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i AM GOING TO MAKE THIS EVENT KID FRIENDLY..... SO IF YOU HAVE LIL ONES BRING THEM THEY'LL HAVE A BLAST&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lets meet out front on the deck before we head inside to purchase tickets</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246292011000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244404910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Amesbury Sports Park</name><id>10597820</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246118400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10597820/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>