<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>29 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.387009</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Trish's House (near Porter Square T-stop)</name><city>Somerville</city><id>6191162</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114326</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;It's a last minute party! More events soon. Hope you can make it this weekend...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's get together and kick-off summer (even though its been such a cold week -- perhaps a hearty welcome to summer will help!)! We will start of the evening with cocktails and conversation and move into dancing as the evening progresses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will be for several of Trish's meetups – a great chance to cross-pollinate! You never know what creativity, innovation and provocative thoughts can come from the mix of entrepreneurship, arts, sustainability, spirituality and eros! For those of you that are single – wear a sticker on your badge to show your interest in meeting other singles. Join us for some great company, stimulating conversation and some groovy moves!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Bring EITHER&lt;/strong&gt;: Something significant to share such as a good bottle of wine, an appetizer or dessert (no chips or bread unless part of an appetizer please!) &lt;strong&gt;OR&lt;/strong&gt; $10 to contribute towards the food and drink I will be providing. (If you are unable to contribute for financial reasons please come anyway.) :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The city of Somerville has agreed to waive parking permits for the event in the area around my house. You can park anywhere there is a legal space (no fire hydrants, etc.). If you get a ticket let me know and Ill give you the email of the women that will take care of it for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loose Schedule:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conversation, Networking, General Schmoozing: 7-9pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dancing, Singing, Etc: 9-12am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hanging out, Telling Jokes, Etc: 12am til….&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to call  &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;413-320-3991&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or email me if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Trish B</member_name><member_id>41335552</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339378166000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>128</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339082940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Kick-off Party</name><id>68163442</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339282800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/68163442/</event_url></item>