<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Some Quotes From the Weight Loss Meet Up Page:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Invited to 1st Anniversary Celebration: &lt;br /&gt;West Haven, Connecticut. Look At Me Now, a Wellness Center located at 487A Campbell Avenue, &lt;br /&gt;will host their First Year Anniversary Celebration on Saturday, May 17th, 10 am to 9 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;West Haven Mayor John M. Picard will officiate at the ribbon cutting ceremony at 1:00 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live music from 7:00- 8:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no fee to attend, and those attending may enter a drawing to win various prizes, including &lt;br /&gt;Gift certificates, Swedish massage, and free weight loss services until you achieve your desired results.&lt;br /&gt;End of Quote&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://weightloss.meetup.com/463/calendar/7827564/"&gt;http://weightloss.mee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;weightloss.meetup.com/463/calendar/7827564/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being from West Haven, I am aware of the parking &lt;br /&gt;Problems on Campbell Avenue. &lt;br /&gt;I am also aware of parking areas &lt;br /&gt;That others might not be aware of or use. &lt;br /&gt;Most of the time, I use the large parking area that is behind &lt;br /&gt;Loris store. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, turn into the side street &lt;br /&gt;Of Curtis Place next to &lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony s Pizza Italian Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a large parking area behind there. &lt;br /&gt;Going to Campbell Avenue, you can walk over towards &lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony s. &lt;br /&gt;Then turn right on Campbell Avenue to Lori s store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I walk over toward the right from the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;There is an alley between the buildings. &lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, I turn left. Loris store is a few stores in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember not to leave anything of value within view &lt;br /&gt;Inside your vehicle that might attract some undesirables.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be a healthy and fun Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember that while you are there that&lt;br /&gt;you can also purchase a healthy smoothie and other items from&lt;br /&gt;Glen, who runs Catch A Healthy Habit Café in West Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.catchahealthyhabit.com/"&gt;http://www.catchaheal...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.catchahealthyhabit.com/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Event starts at 10:00 am, but I have our Meet Up time at 12:30. &lt;br /&gt;You can go there earlier than 12:30 if you want to. &lt;br /&gt;I will try to be there at 1:00 for the Ribbon Cutting by the West Haven Mayor. &lt;br /&gt;I might still be there an hour or so after the Ribbon Cutting to see what else &lt;br /&gt;Is happening at the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unknown Zone Members, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember that we have another Meet Up Event in Wallingford that  the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://conspiracy.meetup.com/83/calendar/7704815/"&gt;http://conspiracy.mee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;conspiracy.meetup.com/83/calendar/7704815/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B&lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lori Larsen a member of UZ is main POC at this Event.     She is the Owner of the Business.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>maribeth</member_name><member_id>2893690</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211215113000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Who likes to attend festive One Year Anniversary Events.</why><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209872972000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Look At Me Now 1st Year Anniversary Celebration on May 17</name><id>7868019</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211041800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/7868019/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/f/global_2489375.jpeg</photo_url></item>