<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be the first meeting of the Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group. Bill, the organizer of the Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group will offer some welcoming words of introduction to everyone! Then,  Jim J. Zebrowski, President of the Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc will run a PowerPoint slide Presentation called &lt;b&gt;Backyard Astronomy 101&lt;/b&gt; : &lt;i&gt;Simple Tips to Jump Start Your Night Sky Viewing!&lt;/i&gt; We will offer some coffee, juice and simple munchies to all who attend.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can arrive at 6:45 PM on Wednesday, March 4th - we plan to have some displays set up for information about night sky viewing with free handouts. The slide Program will run about 35 minutes with plenty of time for questions and introductions. If the weather is good, we will try to set up telescopes outdoors behind the library for a look at Saturn, the Orion Nebula and Comet Lulin as it moves higher in the night sky! Questions about how to observe, finding night sky objects, using binoculars or a telescope or how to make a great fashion statement under the stars will all be addressed!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please stop by, plan to say hi to all your fellow like minded Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group members and have a great time learning about astronomy and space! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---Jim J. Zebrowski&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Carol Geary, librarian will direct you to the reserved  meeting room!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3613014</member_name><member_id>3613014</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240091783000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235420436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group : Backyard Astronomy 101!</name><id>9805491</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236210300000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/9805491/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/5/global_7130005.jpeg</photo_url></item>