<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>72 Locust St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.193184</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Guppey Park</name><city>Dover</city><id>2986151</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.875519</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=141226362631262" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; OFFICIAL EVENT LISTING: 
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=229201243789715"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=229201243789715&lt;/a&gt; Dover, NH - The Strafford County Republican Committee will host a First in the State Gubernatorial Straw Poll and Picnic on August 21. The Strafford County GOP Picnic is a time honored family friendly tradition among local Republicans, and this year marks the first ever Gubernatorial straw poll for the local GOP committee. All major prospective candida...tes will be invited and will have a chance to speak, including Ovide Lamontagne..., John Stephen, Senator Jeb Bradley, Mayor Ted Gatsas, and Cornerstone Director Kevin Smith. Each attendee will receive a vote, and sponsors may purchase varying amounts of tickets. In addition to the Gubernatorial Straw Poll, the Strafford County GOP Committee is pleased to welcome several Presidential candidates. Confirmed 2012'ers are U.S. Rep. Thad McCotter, Former New Mexico Governor Gary Johnson, and Former Louisiana Governor Gary "Buddy" Roemer. Tickets are only $15 per person, $25 for a couple, and $40 for a family of four. In addition, all Republican and conservative non-profit organizations and PAC's are invited to set up a 6' x 6' table space (for only $50) on the lawn of Guppey Park in Dover. The event will be catered by Rochester GOP Chair Randy Bowen, and will run from 1:00pm to 5:00pm. Seating is limited. For more information, or to purchase tickets, please visit 
&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;http://SCRCpicnic.eve...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313951339000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313098610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presidential/Gubernatorial Straw Poll and Family Picnic</name><id>29162221</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313946000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/29162221/</event_url></item>