<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.522500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ben and Jerry's Ice Cream</name><city>Salem</city><id>1373426</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.896100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;OH NO Salem is haunted, what should we do.... let's go check it out!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Salem, MA is the place to be for Halloween so let’s go check it out!  Nobody celebrates Halloween quite like Salem, Massachusetts. Whether you are seeking the changing leaves and cooler weather New England Autumn brings or the ghosts and goblins that Halloween is known for, you will find it all in Salem this October.  For the most exciting month long Halloween Festival the place to be is Salem, Massachusetts!  If you would like to come in costume feel free, there will be a lot of other costumes so you will blend right in.  For more information for all the events that will be going on this day check out the information on this site,&lt;a href="http://www.hauntedhappenings.org/"&gt;www.hauntedhappenings.org&lt;/a&gt; you can even print out a map on the last page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is A LOT going on in Salem, the city will be buzzing w/lots of interesting people and attractions, let’s meetup at 6:30 in time for us to get into town, walk around, people watch and check everything out.  There will be a lot of people in town if crowds are not your thing then this event may not be for you, we call all hang out as a group or if you want to prowl around yourself you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

There is some on street parking, parking lots and parking garages scattered around the town. If you want to drive in be aware that they may shutdown the roads early as they did last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking the Train:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Seeing that parking or road closings may be an issue I suggest taking the train into Salem. If you do take the train in here is the link to the website that will give you the train schedule: &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to Meetup:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

We will be meeting in front of Ben &amp;amp; Jerry’s on Washington St. (on the map #28) at 6:30 or there about if you are running late or get lost call the meetup phone @ &lt;strong&gt;978-304-2811&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you in Salem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/54916378942021045586710/img/smileys/shock.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be outside waiting. (This is just a meeting spot)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351388681000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349669716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk around Salem</name><id>85993672</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351377000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/85993672/</event_url></item>