<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mt Auburn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371239</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10532532</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;i thought some members of our meetup might find this interesting...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us for The Zeitgeist Movement’s Massachusetts Chapter annual outreach and awareness event, Z-Day, on Saturday, March 16, 2013 from 5pm-8pm at the Democracy Center, 45 Mount Auburn Street, Cambridge MA 02138.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is FREE. RSVP via Eventbrite: &lt;a href="http://zday2013massachusetts-efbevent.eventbrite.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://zday2013massachusetts-efbevent.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event in Cambridge will feature portions of Peter Joseph’s ground-breaking documentary film Zeitgeist: Moving Forward, as well as a panel of TZM members, comedian Matthew Filipowicz (matthewf.net) and Carol Moses from the Boston Time Trade Circle (www.timetradecircle.org). Light refreshments will be served.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

With the financial crisis always in the headlines, “superstorms” related to global warming occurring more frequently, perpetual unemployment, and political gridlock that refuses to address our concerns, we are all looking for solutions to the problems of our world. The Zeitgeist Movement's principle focus includes the recognition that the majority of the social and economic problems that plague the human species at this time are not the sole result of some institutional corruption, scarcity, a political policy, a flaw of "human nature" or other commonly held assumptions of causality. Rather, The Movement recognizes that issues such as poverty, corruption, collapse, homelessness, war, starvation and the like appear to be "symptoms" born out of an outdated social structure. By recognizing the root cause of our world’s problems as the very monetary system, the defining goal of The Movement is the building of a new socioeconomic model, a resource based economy, based upon technically responsible resource management, allocation and distribution through what would be considered the scientific method of reasoning out problems and finding optimized solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363479394000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Libertarians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>libertarian-349</urlname><id>593245</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Libertarian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363364421000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zeitgeist Day 2013 Boston</name><id>109415722</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363467600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/libertarian-349/events/109415722/</event_url></item>