<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Granite Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.219971</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tokyo Japanese Steak House</name><city>Braintree</city><id>5258482</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.022766</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join members and guests of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group as we start off the long weekend and warm-up on a Friday Night in February w/ Hotpot @ Tokyo Japanese Steak House @ the South Shore Plaza in Braintree!! &amp;nbsp;Hot pot consists of cooking your food in pots on your table. &amp;nbsp;It could be called 'shared dining' as you all share the pots and the various items you order to cook-up. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight we will split the cost of all of the food since we are sharing it. &amp;nbsp;We will attempt to get separate checks for the food and beverages to make it a little bit easier for those who do not order drinks. &amp;nbsp;Estimated cost of food: $15-$25pp, will update closer to the event as the menu I have does not have the hot pot pricing, and this is based on my personal experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tables are set-up for 4, 6, 12 and 16 people. &amp;nbsp;Most of the tables are set for 4, with 2 set for 6, and 1 each set for 12 and 16. &amp;nbsp;While we will do our best to be seated at the table for 12 or 16, we may be split into a table or two of 6, depending on the size of the group and # of Yes RSVPs @ the Thursday Night Deadline. &amp;nbsp;If we have an odd number of RSVPs at the deadline we will round it up to the nearest even number that the table(s) can accommodate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be aware that due to food allergies and dietary restrictions it is important to note these in your RSVP Comments so we can do our best to exclude them from the table. &amp;nbsp;(Since the foods and utensils are all mixed into the pots it's not feasible to have one herb in one pot and not the rest. &amp;nbsp;For instance, no garlic at my end of the table due to my garlic allergy. &amp;nbsp;If we are split into a couple of tables it may be easier to facilitate.) &amp;nbsp;Please note this is based on my experience at a similar hot pot establishment. &amp;nbsp;Better to be safe than sorry. &amp;nbsp;This may not be the best situation for someone with severe food allergies or dietary restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This should be a fun night of dining and getting to know each other over a hot meal cooked to perfection over hot pot on a Friday night in mid-February. &amp;nbsp;Hope you enjoyed the alliteration. &amp;nbsp;You do know I love them, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday Night Hotpot in February with Fun Friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, February 17th @ 7pm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tokyo Japanese Steak House&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South Shore Plaza&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;250 Granite Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;781-380-4040&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Please meet outside the front door. We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please Note&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. We may be separated into two tables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Please state any food allergies or dietary restrictions in your RSVP Comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: Current Annual Members &amp;amp; 1 Guest - FREE, Members - $2 each; $12 to become a 2012 Annual Member&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: Minimum of 6 people by Tuesday, February 14th @ 6pm. &amp;nbsp;The Maximum number @ 9:30am on Thursday, February 16th is 12 people. &amp;nbsp;If we get 2-3 more on the WaitList prior to tonight's RSVP Deadline we will extend the invite to 16 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Welcome, 1 per member. &amp;nbsp;For exceptions please contact the Event Organizer directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: 8pm on Thursday, February 16th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event. &amp;nbsp;Also, this will be the number we call in and will determine our table seating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please bring cash.&lt;/em&gt; You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&amp;nbsp; This has been the SSDOMG's policy for over 5 years now and it helps avoid confusion when paying the bill. &amp;nbsp;Absolutely positively no credit card charges for the food. &amp;nbsp;There is an ATM just inside the mall around the corner from the restaurant. &amp;nbsp;Either that or you can buy a gift certificate and pay that way. &amp;nbsp;(We will not give more than $5 change on a gift certificate.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; This event takes place rain, snow or shine.&amp;nbsp; In the case of an extreme weather forecast we will update this&amp;nbsp;information at least 24 hours prior to the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the Pages for more information about the SSDOMG's policies and procedures which help ensure a smoother, relaxed, fun&amp;nbsp;dining experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overview: Located at 250 Granite Street/Route 37 in Braintree next to the parking garage between Legal Seafood and Nordstrom/Target (behind Dave &amp;amp; Buster's).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Routes 93/128/95/3: Get onto Route 93 heading towards Braintree/Boston (NB) or Braintree/Cape Cod (SB).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Route 93:&amp;nbsp;Exit 6 off Route 93 onto Route 37 South.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Take a right off the Exit.&amp;nbsp;There are entrances to the Mall at 3 lights. &amp;nbsp;Pull in at the middle entrance (2nd one from Routes 37 northbound and southbound) and drive straight down the road. &amp;nbsp;As you round the bend Tokyo is on the right. &amp;nbsp;Park in the parking garage on the left or out in the open lots up past the 99 Restaurant and parking garage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Route 37 Northbound: Once you pass through 5 corners, take a right at the first light. &amp;nbsp;Follow the road behind Dave and Buster's. &amp;nbsp;At the intersection w/ the lights, Tokyo is on the left. &amp;nbsp;Go straight to park in the parking garage or take a right to park out in the open lots past the 99 Restaurant and parking garage. &amp;nbsp;(If you miss the first entrance, go in the 2nd entrance and following the 2nd half of the directions "From Route 93."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside the front door or at our table after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329863014000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327016547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Hotpot in February with Fun Friends</name><id>48833152</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329523200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/48833152/</event_url></item>