<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 778-0089</phone><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>668965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084130</lon></venue><fee><label>sliding scale</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to $10 at the door.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;What may seem like just another liberal social group is really the start of a revolution. What can we create together?&lt;/i&gt; Find out by meeting like-minded progressives at &lt;b&gt;Connecting for Justice&lt;/b&gt; - one of SoJust's biggest events of the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always we'll help you meet people - so no worries if you're new to SoJust, plus we'll have &amp;quot;looking for&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;ask me about&amp;quot; tags, a Catalyst Corner staffed by our amazing STARZ (regular attendees)  and Action Stations to make it even more likely you'll find the right connections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Arrive early! Dance Party starts at 8pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With deep respect for Emma Goldman, who said, &amp;quot;If I can't dance, I don't want to be part of your revolution.&amp;quot; We're changing things up this time and hosting a Dance Party from 8-9 after 2 awesome hours from 6-8pm of building and strengthening relationships.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns?&lt;/b&gt; Looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? Join us if you are ready to go BEYOND ALLIES and build a CROSS-ISSUE PROGRESSIVE MOVEMENT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; Members are all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HEY ORGANIZERS!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers for the free lit table. &lt;b&gt;New this event &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;ACTION STATIONS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - if you have an action that can be done in 2 minutes (sign a petition) or within 2 weeks of the event (attend rally, stuff mass mailing) bring it so SoJusters can get connected to you and your work. This is not a typical tabling event there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The venue is open to anyone over 18 and is wheelchair accessible - elevator is at the back of the venue. Lir is across from the Hynes Convention Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Help spread the word!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Spread the word by inviting your friends to the facebook event:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=111425225551881" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join the SoJust Facebook group:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=8770189934" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Follow SoJust on Twitter:&lt;/b&gt; @SoJust &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/sojust" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.twitter.co...&lt;/a&gt; and SoJust's Co-Founder @RobbieSamuels &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/robbiesamuels" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.twitter.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over 1300 members and 3 1/2+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find  the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>20</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286174323000</updated><rating><average>4.53999996185</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>62</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269311897000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connecting for Justice (Open House)</name><id>12963879</id><headcount>90</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274392800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/12963879/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/3/global_11324323.jpeg</photo_url></item>