<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2190 Broad Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02905</zip><lat>41.765241</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-780-8700</phone><name>L'Attitude Modern Eatery</name><city>Cranston</city><id>1396157</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390326</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's hang out and listen to some music on a Wednesday night in "the Village"!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L'Attitude's is a well-known and very popular restaurant/bar in the heart of cute Pawtuxet Village. If you've never had the opportunity to check out this place, here's your chance!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jerry has graciously offered to host this one and will be posting more information about the band that will be playing. We'll start at 7:30, the band goes on at 8:30 and then we'll hang out until whenever. This is a great place to have a drink, socialize and enjoy a Wednesday night. So come on down and let's celebrate the mid-week!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, Pawtuxet Village, NOT to be confused with Pawtucket (don't worry, when you've been in RI long enough, you'll get it) is on the border of Cranston and Warwick, near the water and only 10 minutes from Providence but feels totally different!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, so a little about the band Travis Colby and Friends. They are a three piece trio that play&amp;nbsp;Funk,&amp;nbsp;Blues, and R&amp;amp;B,&amp;nbsp;Travis&amp;nbsp;which plays keyboards and his Trumpet player Doug Woolverton currently are members of the national recording artists band&amp;nbsp;Room Full of Blues(from right here in little Rhody), each week any number of fellow musicians stop by to play a few songs with the band and add to the fun. On this night the bands special guest of the month Diane Blue from Boston is scheduled to come down to add to the fun, Diane is an excellent singer and Harmonica player that is sure to blow your socks off!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a great opportunity to hear some good music and enjoy each others company!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jerry is hosting this one! Please look at his picture!!! We will be in the restaurant in our own private room, tell the hostess that you are part of the meetup group and that person will guide you where to go. I will have on jeans &amp; a tan shirt</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerry </member_name><member_id>33887922</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329972761000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327727433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Night Music Hang Out in Pawtuxet Village!!!</name><id>49948332</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329352200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/49948332/</event_url></item>