<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 William T Morrissey Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.313005</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-3110 </phone><name>UMass Boston -Field Stage</name><city>Boston</city><id>759719</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.038587</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's all meet right before 12 noon, just inside the gate...near the  Crafts and Food vendors.&amp;nbsp; You can see a map of the venue here:  &lt;a href="http://www.bostonfolkfestival.org/FestMap2011.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bostonfolkfestival.org/FestMap2011.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will have a MeetUp Sign.&amp;nbsp; My cell phone is 774-262-9620 - I suggest you text, because it may be noisy and hard to hear!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A schedule and list of performers, as well as more info about the Festival, can be found here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonfolkfestival.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bostonfolkfestival.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't have a ticket yet, you can buy them at the door!&amp;nbsp; It should be a really fun day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WUMB is holding their annual music Fest at the UMass Boston Campus from 12 noon - 7:00pm on Sunday, June 5.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"It's a world class Music Festival in your own backyard - and, on the waterfront!&lt;/strong&gt; What's your pleasure? Is it singer-songwriters, cajun or Americana  music? Do you like to celebrate tradition or to discover new,  up-and-coming artists? Or, music from Nova Scotia? The breadth of music  at this year's WUMB Music Fest is again as rich as it is diverse. You  don't have to be a connoisseur to enjoy our music festival - but it  helps to have a love for all different forms of music. And if the first  thirteen years are any indication, you'll experience it all at our 14th  Annual Music Fest. We've got three stages and more for you to choose  from. So, whether you prefer to sit outside under a tent (new this year)  stretch out a blanket or sit in an auditorium or our big coffeehouse  setting, you'll be hearing some of the best music around. It's the  biggest festival of its kind in the Boston area, and the greatest place  to be if you like live music. Overall, it the best music from quality  talent, the finest food and craft vendors from the New England area, and  a fun, friendly atmosphere for the entire family."&amp;nbsp; (&lt;a href="http://www.bostonfolkfestival.org/index.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bostonfolkfestival.org/index.html&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just inside the front gate, near the food/craft vendors!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307368468000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Lots of music!</why><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302005593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WUMB Music Fest!</name><id>17189211</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307289600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/17189211/</event_url></item>