<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>269 Newbury st</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-2996</phone><name>Pazzo</name><city>Boston</city><id>1154598</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be discussing the role of sites such as Myspace, Etsy and Twitter in the marketing of music and fashion and ways of using those platforms effectively. We will also be discussing The Boston Fashion Intiative 2010. There will also be time for networking.&lt;br /&gt;We have 2 featured speakers for the November 2 Meetup, Christine Mastrengelo of the Un-stitched blog and myself (Evan Shapiro).&lt;br /&gt;Christine will talk about her blog and it's use in the promotion of fashion.&lt;br /&gt;I will discuss the use of podcasting in relationship to the promotion of fashion and music.&lt;br /&gt;About Christine Mastrengelo:&lt;br /&gt;Christine Mastrangelo, Un-stitched&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://un-stitched.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://un-stitched.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christine Mastrangelo has over eight years experience as a freelance editor and writer. Her former clients and collaborators include the Somerville Arts Council, NYC-based artist Christine Wong, and various designers from around the world. In 2008, she merged her passion for writing with her love of fashion to form a blog. She currently blogs at Un-stitched, where she shares her discoveries of emerging designers, fashion illustrators, and social networks built around fashion. Christine originally began blogging when she saw a disconnect between emerging designers and a potential customer base. Since then, she has created relationships with other bloggers and designers, and has successfully navigated the social networking phenomenon which connects brands to their customers. Her most recent interviews and articles for Un-stitched have been featured on Kickstarter.com, Smashingdarling.com and Heartifb.com. Christine holds a BA from Boston University.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>2523024</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>yasu</member_name><member_id>3356319</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289030198000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>fashionandmusiceventplanning</urlname><id>1408370</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Fashion and Music Event Planning</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287076108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fashion and Music Marketing and The Boston Fashion Initiative 2010</name><id>fkbznynpbdb</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288735200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fashionandmusiceventplanning/events/15109320/</event_url></item>