<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Chapel View Blvd</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02920</zip><lat>41.779533</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>REI Cranston</name><city>Cranston</city><id>1151481</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.462975</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>******CLASS IS FULL*******&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you that have been on one of my hikes....you know I really need this class! Join me in what we all know is a doomed attempt to learn direction sense! We'll meet 15 minutes before class at the front of the store. Its 20 bucks for REI memberes and 40 for non members....but since an REI membership is only 20 bucks for life it obviously makes sense to get one. Make sure you call and register. This is an INDOOR class. Full description from REI website below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REI Outdoor School Map and Compass Basics-Class&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1/26/2010 6:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;Type: Class &lt;br /&gt;Host Store: Cranston &lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: Cranston REI &lt;br /&gt;Start Time: 06:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;End Time: 08:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;Duration: 1.5 hrs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: Join REI Outdoor School guides as they lead you through the basics of using a map and compass. Come find your way in the forest and begin to learn skills that will provide a lifetime of safe outdoor enjoyment! &lt;br /&gt;Content: Learn how to use a map and compass in tandem to pinpoint a location. Learn how to interpret topographical maps. Learn the features of a compass. Learn to identify your position and plan routes using only a topographic map. Learn to take bearings and triangulate your position using a compass. This is a &amp;quot;hands-on&amp;quot; experience with some lecture components. &lt;br /&gt;Audience: Those new to land navigation and interested in learning the basics of map and compass. &lt;br /&gt;Included: Compass units and sample maps. &lt;br /&gt;Gear List: Your compass, however, compasses &lt;br /&gt;Location:REI Cranston Store&lt;br /&gt;Contact:REI Cranston 401-275-5250&lt;br /&gt;Cost:$20 member; $40 non-member&lt;br /&gt;Registration Required? Yes. Please call REI Cranston Customer Service 401-275-5250&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/outdoorschool" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/ou...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the entrance, call my cell if you have trouble 508-414-8544</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264721115000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264041213000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>REI Class: Map and Compass Basics</name><id>12378569</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264547700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/12378569/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>