<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>behind Woodstar Cafe, 60 Masonic St</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.325089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Frances Crowe Community Room</name><city>Northampton</city><id>6566592</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.641205</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/b/6/event_116292982.jpeg" width="190" height="259" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;November 22, 2013 will mark the 50th anniversary since the assassination of President John F. Kennedy. Many are convinced that it was a coup d'etat of the US government. The cover-up continues to this day. There are many similarities to that 1962 operation with the events regarding September 11, 2001. John Hankey, filmmaker of Dark Legacy: George Bush and the Murder of John F. Kennedy, had listed a few a few of these:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both JFK and 9-11 involved The Big Lie -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1: The crime is unspeakable, for the mainstream media and ALL politicians who want to live. Our job is to speak the unspeakable. the Big Lie -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2: Even when spoken by the likes of us, the crime is too terrible to be believed. The average human being is incapable of conceiving that anyone could be so horrible, that they could kill their own people, or their own president. This is the main defense of 9-11 perpetrators. The true conspiracy theory is unbelievable. However, JFK's murder is a chink in this armor of people's incredulity: 80% believe Warren Report is a lie. They know there is more out there than what they have been told.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The video, Dark Legacy, has the potential to teach the common citizen valuable lessons regarding 9-11&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) Both crimes were committed by the same perpetrators: the military industrial complex; the CFR; with Bushes heading the attack. JFK was murdered in order to carry out Vietnam; but the only discernible goal there was to increase the defense budget: they knew they couldn't win. All the best evidence said so. They didn't care about winning. Just about keeping money from going for education and medicare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) In both crimes, the media and politicians are worse than useless; these crimes are unspeakable. The truth must be denied emphatically whenever the topic comes up; and those who raise the questions must be viciously attacked by every politician in the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) Don't get lost in details; The names of the knoll shooters doesn't matter. It doesn't matter whether Oswald or a double went to Mexico. Was there a plane, or not, at Pentagon? It doesn't matter. What matters is that, with all the cold-war defenses in place, not a shot was fired in defense. "We don't know" is a good answer to all detailed questions. The broad outlines are clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relying exclusively on government documents, statements from the best witnesses available, and the words from the mouths of the killers themselves, Dark Legacy produces a thoroughly substantiated criminal indictment of George Herbert Walker Bush, establishing beyond a reasonable doubt his guilt as a CIA supervisor in the conspiracy to assassinate John F. Kennedy. If we could present this evidence to a jury in Texas, he would pay with his life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***********&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Valley 9/11 will be only screening the prologue and part one, which present the overwhelming mountain of evidence that President Kennedy was hit by bullets from the front and rear. Every witness in the Dallas emergency room attests, on camera, to the fact that a bullet from the right front blew a fist-sized whole in the back of the President's head. The New York Times carried these statements on the day of the murder; and has covered them up ever since. (John Hankey has given us copies of the film available to share on community access television and for individuals to purchase for only $5.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One film clip is by James Corbett, called &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.corbettreport.com/911-a-conspiracy-theory/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9/11: A Conspiracy Theory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Everything you ever wanted to know about 9/11 conspiracy theory in under 5 minutes.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Jonathan Mark will facilitate discussions on how these and other events are inter-related, and why it is critical to connect the dots to show the real perpetrators of the big lies of our lifetime. Additional clips from documentaries and music videos will also be presented and discussed. The program's focus is to expose the intense deceptions conducted by a Military Industrial Complex, especially since President Kennedy's assassination, and what we can possibly do about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://thedarklegacy.com/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dark Legacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;George Bush and the Murder of John Kennedy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "Provocative to say the least. Using materials familiar to researchers, Dark Legacy makes a series of tantalizing connections between the rich and powerful to suggest that Kennedy was brought down by a vast web of powerful conservatives and that George H.W.Bush was close to all of them. Hankey invites viewers not only to draw their own conclusions but also to check out his sources."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Kevin Thomas Los Angeles Times&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more details of the June 13th program, visit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/59532652/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/59532652/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343835559000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>filmgroup</urlname><id>1279822</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Western MA Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336162248000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dark Legacy - JFK and 9/11</name><id>63450572</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339628400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/filmgroup/events/63450572/</event_url></item>