<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Copley Square</address_2><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349493</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Public Library</name><city>Boston</city><id>1452790</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079011</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From the library website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Drew Gilpin Faust is the 28th president of Harvard University and the Lincoln Professor of History in Harvard&amp;rsquo;s Faculty of Arts and Sciences. Her talk is titled, "Telling War Stories: Reflections of a Civil War Historian."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;A historian of the Civil War and the American South, Faust was the founding Dean of the Radcliffe Institute for Advanced Study at Harvard. Previously, she served as the Annenberg Professor of History at the University of Pennsylvania, where she was a member of the faculty for 25 years. She is the author of six books, including Mothers of Invention: Women of the Slaveholding South in the American Civil War (1996), for which she won the Francis Parkman Prize in 1997. Her most recent book, This Republic of Suffering: Death and the American Civil War (2008), looks at the impact of the Civil War&amp;rsquo;s enormous death toll on the lives of 19th-century Americans. It won the Bancroft Prize in 2009 and was a finalist for both a National Book Award and a Pulitzer Prize.The theme of the 2011-2012 Lowell Lecture series is &amp;ldquo;Remembering the Civil War.&amp;rdquo; This is part of the Boston Public Library&amp;rsquo;s commemoration of the 150th anniversary of the Civil War.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This talk is part of the library's very long running (175+ years) Lowell Lecture series&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org/central/calendar.htm#/?i=1"&gt;http://www.bpl.org/central/calendar.htm#/?i=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and Harvard's 375 years celebration:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://375.harvard.edu/john-harvard-book-celebration"&gt;http://375.harvard.edu/john-harvard-book-celebration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This talk sounds interesting, at the very least to hear the president of Harvard give a speech. I'm guessing this is more social history which many people enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know getting to the library by 6:00PM is pretty tough unless you work downtown but I'm going to this one and thought others might be interested. It is being held in the Rabb lecture hall-- the big one in the basement of the new (Johnson) building. I'll hang out outside the lecture hall until 5:45 and then go in to get seats. I expect this one will be busy. After the talk I'd be happy to grab a snack / coffee near by.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wait in front of the lecture hall until 5:45 and send my # the day before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>2367399</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334160601000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333555209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Civil War history talk by the president of Harvard</name><id>59229102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334094300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/59229102/</event_url></item>