<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Interested in networking with professionals from the Health &amp;amp; Wellness field? &lt;br /&gt;Would you benefit from meeting local area business owners, who are experts in their fields? &lt;br /&gt;Are you looking to learn the 'inside scoop' on Health &amp;amp; Wellness, including new techniques, strategies, and ideas? &lt;br /&gt;Looking for a weekend networking opportunity in a laid-back atmosphere that is both productive, educational, and FUN? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday, July 24th from 10:00am until 2:00pm - Successful Anonymous will be at Energize Fitness Studio in West Newton, 1387 Washington Street, hosting our Debut Health &amp;amp; Wellness Expo. Rachel Kobey, our gracious host, will also have demonstrations on the new and unique fitness techniques. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The studio will have booths set up, much like a Trade Show, where as an attendee, you will be able to chat with Acupuncturists, Massage Therapists, Chiropractors, Nutritionists, and MANY MORE - all under one roof! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will be open to the public, but as a SUCCESS ADDICT you will get VIP treatment! Personal introductions to all of the presenters, facilitated networking based on YOUR desired focus, and much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a GREAT opportunity to network, jumpstart your career, meet new people, learn new health and wellness techniques, and kickoff the weekend in a great, productive way! SPREAD THE WORD! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dimitry</member_name><member_id>10566344</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>VandD Partnership</member_name><member_id>10820762</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280263021000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Success Addicts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>successfulanonymous</urlname><id>1551084</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Successful Anonymous</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278266684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Successful Anonymous: Health &amp; Wellness Expo - Sat. July 24th </name><id>13999837</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279980000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/successfulanonymous/events/13999837/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/3/global_13312019.jpeg</photo_url></item>