<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Tory's Cave is a great but modest marble cave w/a few rooms &amp;amp; crawl space. We'll park and hike in a little bit to a sink hole entrance. This is a true cave but being a marble cave there are generally no flow/mineral features you would find in a limestone cave.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the cave see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.berkshirehiking.com/hikes/torys_cave.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.berkshireh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet up at the parking area off of Rte. 7 at Noon and spend no more than a couple hours at/in the cave so we should be done by 2 PM.  We can stop for dinner in New Milford or Danbury if there is the will.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: There is a hike our group is doing before this event at 9:30 AM very nearby (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/calendar/6429190/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ). You may wish to consider doing too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equipment:&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp (preferable) or flashlight is essential.&lt;br /&gt;* A helmet of some kind is needed in the cave to protect your head from bumps. Acceptable helmets are: caving, bike, rock climbing, skateboard, or hard hat (cheap helmet is fine).&lt;br /&gt;* It is cool/cold/wet in the cave so dress warmly into the cave (no cotton as will stay wet/cold!). Clothing into the cave may get snagged from rocks so best not anything expensive or new.&lt;br /&gt;* Footware should be something with a good grip for a little climbing and which is OK to get wet/muddy.&lt;br /&gt;* You will get wet and muddy to some degree so a change of clothing/shoes is strongly advisable for after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions (a *bit north* of New Milford on Rte. 7):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;latitude=&amp;amp;longitude=&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;phone=&amp;amp;level=&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;cat=&amp;amp;address=480+Kent+Rd&amp;amp;city=New+Milford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode="&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Textual directions:&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 7 north out of New Milford center for about 3 miles at which point you'll pass the intersection of Rt. 37 west and Rt. 7. &lt;br /&gt;* A short distance later a gas station will be on your left. Drive 1.3 miles (passing the first street sign for the semi-circular Squash Hollow Road) and turnleft into a large dirt parking area (in two parts: a semi-circle and then a huge open field).&lt;br /&gt;* Look for Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan!&lt;br /&gt;* The blue trail markers can be seen at the apex of the semi-circular parking lot.   The parking lot is at an old quarry construction site.&lt;br /&gt;* The trail heads uphill into the woods. Tory's Cave is about 100 yards into the woods.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Note:  If you see the second street sign for SquashHollow Road, you've gone too far. Drive back  about 0.4 of a mile.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leader on this one is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is available from Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan from the Hartford area and potentially available for pick-ups along the I-84 corridor heading west of Hartford, CT. Please arrange with Kevin S as soon as possible and indicate in RSVP if you want in on the carpool. The van will leave the northcentral CT area starting at 7 AM and should arrive at the meetup location at about 9:15 AM (given a couple stops for carpool pick-ups). This carpool leaves early for the the hike event and returns to the northcentral CT area by about 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191255005000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190775303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Caving in Tory's Cave near New Milford CT</name><id>6428837</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191081600000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6428837/</event_url></item>