<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>615 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02132</zip><lat>42.074337</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 826-2532</phone><name>The Winery on 53</name><city>Pembroke</city><id>851283</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.781559</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;That was spectacular.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The words were spoken in October, roughly three months ago, by a friend not much given to flights of verbal fancy, at a booth in the dining room of &lt;a href="http://www.thewinery53restaurantandtavern.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Winery on 53 &lt;/a&gt; in Pembroke.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Haven't heard of The Winery? Well, you may know the building better as Bobby Hackett's, which it was for quite a few years until Mr Hackett decided to retire. Fortunately, the new ownership has brought in Ken Wisneski, chef-owner of the short-lived Cherrywoods in Norwell, as executive chef, and he's created a wonderful menu of American favorites with eclectic additions. There is a menu on their website (fair warning: I'm told that this needs alittle updating); you may also be interested in what &lt;a href="http://www.patriotledger.com/entertainment/dining/x1588593320/TASTE-AND-TELL-The-Winery-succeeds-in-Pembroke" target="_blank"&gt;Christine Ordway&lt;/a&gt; had to say in The Patriot Ledger.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be heading there on Wednesday, January 21st at 7:00 PM. I look forward to having some of you join me to see whether or not my friend's opinion can be confirmed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Winery on 53&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;615 Washington St., Pembroke&lt;br /&gt;781 826-2532&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thewinery53restaurantandtavern.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thewinery5...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; $2.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; A few entrees are surprisingly affordable, including chicken pot pie at only $12.50. On the high end, filet mignon is $32.00. Average entree is about $18.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps us to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Tuesday, January 20th @ 6:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; The Winery on 53 is located on &lt;b&gt;Washington St. (Route 53)&lt;/b&gt; in Pembroke. We are providing directions from Route 3 for members who may be coming from a distance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3 North (Coming from Cape Cod):&lt;/b&gt; Take Exit 11 (Route 14) and head West on Route 14. Follow Route 14 until it intersects with Route 53 (There is a highly visible Marylou's News at this intersection), then turn right (North) onto Route 53. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Winery will be on your left after about half a mile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you pass Christina's Restaurant on your right or come to a stoplight, you've gone a bit too far and need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3 South (Coming from Braintree/Boston):&lt;/b&gt; Take Exit 12 (Route 139), coming off the ramp turn left (West) onto Route 139. You will immediately have two stoplights in front of you (Brigantine Mall and North River Plaza) - Go straight through both of them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After about one mile you'll come to the intersection with Route 53. Turn left (South) onto Route 53.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Landmarks to watch for include a large Sunoco station on your right and Christina's Restaurant on your left. The Winery is on your right, about 3/4 mile after Christina's, just past a sign indicating a right turn for drivers going to Duxbury.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you come to a Marylou's News on your right, you've gone about 1/2 mile past The Winery and need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233357895000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231858580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Winery!</name><id>9513037</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232582400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/9513037/</event_url></item>