<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Oxford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.378188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.495.3045 </phone><name>Harvard Museum of Natural History, Geological Lecture Hall </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>845303</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116422</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>RE: Design is a fascinating dramatization of the 30 years of correspondence between Charles Darwin in England and Asa Gray in Boston, produced by the English theatre group, Menagerie, and commissioned by the Darwin Correspondence Project at the University of Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adapted exclusively from their own words—including previously unpublished letters—&lt;br /&gt;RE: Design offers a window onto the minds and worlds of these two groundbreaking 19th century naturalists as they debate the consequences for religious belief of Darwin’s new theory of evolution by natural selection. Intellectual debate around science and religion is interwoven with gossip, opinion, and anecdotes about everything from war and slavery, to family incidents and unfortunate gardening accidents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The one-act play will be followed by a panel discussion with RE: Design director Paul Bourne and Janet Browne, the Aramont Professor of the History of Science at Harvard. (This event is in lieu of Professor Janet Browne’s lecture, Corresponding Naturalists: Asa Gray, Charles Darwin, and the Making of American Botany.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public, Geological Lecture Hall, 24 Oxford Street. Part of &lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/lectures-classes-events/asa-gray-bicentennial.html" target="_blank"&gt;the Asa Gray Bicentennial series&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth</member_name><member_id>8893636</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287753639000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285784413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RE: Design, A Dramatization of the Correspondence of Charles Darwin and Asa Gray</name><id>14939998</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287698400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/14939998/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>