<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>22 John F Kennedy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372978</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-497-1530</phone><name>Uno's Chicago Grill</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1139661</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119681</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Marx: 18th Brumaire of Louis Bonaparte (&lt;a href="http://www.marxists.org/archive/marx/works/download/pdf/18th-Brumaire.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.marxists.org/archive/marx/works/download/pdf/18th-Brumaire.pdf&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jim (Williiams) suggested this text with the following words: &lt;br /&gt;Two weeks ago the group read a few short articles, "Judenfragen" and "Intro to a Critique..." from 1843 which show Marx engaged in the conversation with Bauer and Feuerbach and being an active participant in the Young Hegelian Idealist tradition.  &lt;br /&gt;This week we are looking at the "Economic and Philosophic Manuscripts" of 1844 where he starts to expand (or expand beyond) that tradition. &lt;br /&gt;A month ago we read "The German Ideology" of 1845 which shows the break up of the Young Hegelians. &lt;br /&gt;I was thinking it would be good to read the "18th Brumaire of Louis Napoleon" of 1852 which looks back on the revolutions and the coup that brought and end to the Second Republic. I feel this is a valedictory work coming at the end of his Hegelian/Idealist phase--a conclusion to the work of pure philosophy and a moving beyond to the realm of economics and social action. His work after this would be very different from what we have been reading so far. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;David's (Whitehouse) response: &lt;br /&gt;Works for me. Seems like a crucial piece to understand Marx's social / political theory. Other presentations of his views are more schematic, either applying to multiple cases or long spans of time (German Ideology, Manifesto) -- or, when applied to particular cases (Germany in the Intro to a Critique), restricted to a virtually static sketch of social forces / social history. The 18th Brumaire is like a medical case study, full of particulars and their concrete interaction in real time. The general theory gets used here, but it also gets advanced.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please ask about the philosophy group from the staff.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298063164000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Reading this text at this time is part of our long term plan.</why><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296827327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Marx: 18th Brumaire of Louis Bonaparte</name><id>16440069</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297944000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/16440069/</event_url></item>