<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>162 Front Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02066</zip><lat>42.196247</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Restaurant Oro</name><city>Scituate</city><id>2138671</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.724823</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We're continuing our Sunday Supper Series with a restaurant that has been on Mike's To Try list since it opened to enthusiastic reviews a year or so ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located on the Front Street loop in Scituate, Oro is a small restaurant where food, service and atmosphere are all taken seriously. And very recent reports, including a mention by Devra First in the June 12 issue of the Globe Magazine, indicate that this attention to detail continues to pay off for both Oro and its patrons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that, due to space restrictions, this event is limited to ten attendees. We hope you'll be one of them on Sunday, June 26th as we take another trip to the edge of the Atlantic to experience for ourselves the luster of Oro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Restaurant ORO&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

162 Front Street &lt;br /&gt;

Scituate, MA 02066&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;781-378-2465&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.restaurantoro.com/"&gt;Restaurant Oro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer:&lt;/strong&gt; Mike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. One per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact Mike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price Range:&lt;/strong&gt; Be advised that this is not a "cheap eats" type of venue. Entrees listed in the &lt;a href="http://www.restaurantoro.com/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=4&amp;amp;Itemid=3"&gt;online menu&lt;/a&gt; range from $18.00 (Orecchiette Pasta with veal and tomato ragout) to $28.00 (Grilled Veal Porterhouse).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; Current Annual Members - None, Group Members - $2.00, Guests - $2.00; Cost to become a 2011 Annual Member is now $6.00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over four years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Saturday, June 25th @ 3:00 pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer. Changes to "No" after the deadline will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us Pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Oro is located on Front Street in Scituate: This is the main road that loops down to the waterfront. Oro is close to both The Mill Wharf and Riva, two restaurants where we have dined as a group.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Michael' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309222416000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307934294000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Supper Series: Oro</name><id>21972261</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309125600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/21972261/</event_url></item>