<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Arrive at 10:00 and launch by 10:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Mark Roberts, mroberts@CIA.com  401-533-1883 cell&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check RICKA Message Board for last minute cancellations: &lt;a href="http://members.boardhost.com/FLATWATER/" target="_blank"&gt;http://members.boardh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A unique location suitable for everyone and all boats. This is a fairly short paddle, 4 miles, but it winds its way throughout all the various ponds and lakes in the park. It’s fun paddling through the Japanese Gardens by the carosel. We break for lunch by the Greek Temple.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the put-in:  From 95 South take exit 17- From 95 North take exit 16. Both exits lead to Elmwood Avenue.  Drive south on Elmwood until you come to the traffic light at Elmwood and Park Avenue.  Turn left onto Park Avenue and drive past the RT. 10 on/off ramps.  Stay on Park Avenue until you come to the traffic light at the Park School.  The school is on the right and the entrance to the Roger Williams Park is on the left.  Enter the park and bear left-the launch site and parking will be on the right side of the road at the lake.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check RICKA for additional paddles scheduled&lt;br /&gt;RICKA Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;a href="http://www.ricka-flatwater.org/ricka%20schedule.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ricka-flat...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RICKA Blackstone Paddlers has additional free instruction and beginner paddles&lt;br /&gt;Blackstone Valley Paddlers&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;a href="http://www.ricka-flatwater.org/bvschedule.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ricka-flat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Orange/Yellow Riot Voyager Kayak, shaved head</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250430962000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237225474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Roger Williams Park and Zoo, Providence RI</name><id>9966224</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248530400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/9966224/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/4/global_7704628.jpeg</photo_url></item>