<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>381 Connecticut 80</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06419</zip><lat>41.362172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chatfield Hollow State Park</name><city>Killingworth</city><id>1191601</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.581165</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;NHRC is going rock climbing at Chatfield Hollow!  All members are invited to climb for FREE and join us for the BBQ to follow.  No experience required but basic belay training is nice. We'll have ropes set up and extra harnesses and helmets on hand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Climbers MUST RSVP here to participate for food budget and liability reasons!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experienced members with ropes wanted! Email: nate@ctrockgym.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the climbing at Chatfield visit &lt;a href="http://mountainproject.com/v/connecticut/chatfield_hollow/106051782" target="_blank"&gt;http://mountainprojec...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=&amp;amp;daddr=Chatfield+Hollow+State+Park,+Killingworth,+CT&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=42.310334,93.076172&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=4" target="_blank"&gt;Directions to Chatfield Hollow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll climb from 12p-5p then hike out to the pond for swimming and BBQ. BYOB and bring dessert or a side dish. We'll provide burgers, dogs, veggie burgers, buns, condiments and the grills.  &lt;b&gt;We're asking for a $5 (cash) donation from each climber to help offset food costs.&lt;/b&gt;Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please read: This event is NOT sanctioned by the CT Rock Gym and participation is at your own risk. Climbers must RSVP through this site beforehand to participate.  Review the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/terms/"&gt;Meetup Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're running late on Sunday, this is how to find the climbing area from the dirt parking lots at the entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Chatfield Hollow Rock Climbing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Meet at the left of two dirt parking lots (free parking) at the entrance to the park. If you pass the guard booth, you've gone too far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.  Walk into the park entrance (road) and pass the guard booth (no charge for walk-ins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.  Take the first left toward the bus parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Pass the toilet on your right and continue straight ahead until you see the entrance to the wooden boardwalk (Paul Wildermann Boardwalk)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Follow the boardwalk and at its end angle slightly to the right as you cross the road and locate the Deep Woods Trail (orange on the map)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6.  Follow this trail until it delivers you right at the top of the climbing area (this will be quite obvious).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7.  You can access the cliff through a steep gully/scramble on the right before the obvious ledge or continue on the trail until you see an obvious trail take a sharp right towards the base of the cliff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8.  At this point you will see ropes and climbers who can help direct traffic to the base of the climbs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the dirt parking lot on the right side of the entrance to Chatfield Hollow S.P.  - Free parking area!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate McKenzie</member_name><member_id>10557655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284548983000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctrockclimbing</urlname><id>1388805</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>CT Rock Climbing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>51</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281470938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Outdoor Climbing &amp; BBQ - Chatfield Hollow State Park</name><id>14381855</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283097600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctrockclimbing/events/14381855/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/e/global_16760462.jpeg</photo_url></item>