<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>345 Somerville Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.381008</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>PA's Lounge</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1213917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099039</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;OPEN MIC/Party with Free Live Music at PA's Lounge in Union Square, Somerville. &lt;/b&gt;  Singers, musicians, horns, percussionists - everyone is welcome to attend the open mic in a relaxed atmosphere, to play or listen.  Sax and horns encouraged.  We plan to play this Wednesday, and will probably switch the day to Sunday late afternoon/early evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a continuation of the East Cambridge Galleria area open mic that went on hold ~ a month ago.  It a blues style open mike for all types of music, but we are try to do at least 1 least a jazz set and some well known standards.  There are at least 3 musician/singer meetup groups participating, and usually other social/meetups/groups.  Songs on the songlist are:  What a wonderful world, Over the rainbow, sunshine of my life, summertime, and good ideas would be songs like She’s come Undun, Blue Skies, Take Five, improvisations on great jazz/blues riffs &amp;amp; themes.  &lt;b&gt;Even if you don't play, come to check it out and have a drink to support the effort!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention Party goers,  Musicians &amp;amp; Singers!!  Come join the party at the Wed Night Open mike!  Everyone Welcome.  No cover charge - Play or sing music solo or with backing band.  All instruments and styles welcome.  Originals, covers, blues, jazz, classic rock, R&amp;amp;B, Motown, folk, etc.   Back up band with drums, bass, guitar, and Songlist for singers.  Bring your friends for the party, network, and meet interesting people.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm Bill, 6'4" on the keys.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285200776000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans/Musicians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>jazz-190</urlname><id>1202977</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge/Somerville/Boston Jazz Meetup/Jam</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284960093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RESTARTING OPEN MIC, Networking, Party in Union Square</name><id>14828884</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285196400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/jazz-190/events/14828884/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/b/global_6953227.jpeg</photo_url></item>