<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;UPDATE 5/27/11: Current roster is 8 men 3 women. Can take 5 or 6 more players, preferably women. Registration instructions are below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturdays in May we will be holding outdoor volleyball QK doubles    series. These are friendship tournament event meetups that are reverse    coed doubles matches played in a King-Queen format, meaning that you    will be playing with and against different people during pool play.  Top   players after pool play will compete in a playoff format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a friendship tournament format, meaning call your own faults, as there are no referees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The organizer for this event will be Matt BenDaniel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be using the ruleset listed in the first post on the following: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/messages/boards/thread/8548572?thread=8548572" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/messages/boards/thread/8548572?thread=8548572&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  events will start at 9 AM and will likely last at least until   the early  afternoon (~2 PM). If you would like to play in this event   you must  commit to staying at least through the end of pool play.   Remember to  bring snacks/food and water/beverages, as this event will   involve a  significant amount of volleyball play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is intended for  players with experience playing reverse   coed doubles format. Signup for  these events is a little different. To   sign up for one or more of these  events, please send me an email using   the following link on meetup: &lt;a href="http://volleyball.meetup.com/122/message/?recipientId=4774008" class="linkified"&gt;http://volleyball.meetup.com/122/message/?recipientId=4774008&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the email, provide the following information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Name  &lt;br /&gt;Gender  &lt;br /&gt;Event date(s) that you would like to sign up for  &lt;br /&gt;Outdoor rating (AA/A/BB/B), if you have one; otherwise, short description of reverse coed doubles experience  &lt;br /&gt;Confirm that you have read the ruleset at the link above and that you agree to play by those rules.  &lt;br /&gt;Confirm that you can commit to play from 9 AM to 2 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;Signup partner name (if you have a signup partner)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preferably, each player in a signup pair should send an email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For  this event we will have a strict cap of 16 players (8 men, 8   women) to  simplify the event management. Preference is given to AA/A/BB   players  who sign up in male/female pairs, although some single  signups  will be  allowed. Note that sending an email does not guarantee  a spot  to play;  spots are only guaranteed if you are assigned a Yes  RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt BenDaniel</member_name><member_id>1878223</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310051897000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301871092000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advanced Outdoor (Sand) QK RevCoed Doubles Volleyball</name><id>17168719</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306587600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/17168719/</event_url></item>