<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Roundtable Discussion for Models and Photographers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You all asked for it so here it is....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Worcester Photography Center is giving Photographers and Models the opportunity to meet and build a rapport! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a photographer looking to take your images of people to the next level this event is for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a model looking to meet and exchange ideas with a group of photographers this event is for you, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Worcester Photography Center believes strongly in collaboration. We know it would be valuable for the photographers to hear first hand from the models and modeling agencies just what their point of view is on working with photographers and how to be the consummate professional. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The evening is planned as a round table style discussion between the Mass Modeling Agency, Believe in You Model Training, a professional male model, a professional female model, and photographers from all over New England. The event is free and open to the public. Please feel free to forward this email to any photographers and models you have in your networks. Please ask them to RSVP to donna@erbphoto.com if they are not MeetUp members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 2nd from 7-8:45&lt;br /&gt;Worcester Public Library&lt;br /&gt;www.worcpublib.org&lt;br /&gt;3 Salem Sq&lt;br /&gt;Worcester, MA 01608&lt;br /&gt;(508) 799-1655&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be meeting in the Banx Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236726452000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228925656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Roundtable Discussion for Models and Photographers</name><id>9314535</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236038400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9314535/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/8/global_6578232.jpeg</photo_url></item>