<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>No particular meeting on this day has been planned yet (but there might be one...), participation in this Meetup is performed by turning off non-essential lighting for one hour at 8:30PM on Saturday, March 27, 2010.  Hundreds of millions of people across the globe will show their support for lasting action to protect Earth’s natural resources, environment and climate, now and into the future. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Led by the World Wildlife Fund, Earth Hour has grown from a city-wide effort in 2007 to a global phenomenon that has captured the world’s attention. Each year, individuals, organizations, businesses, and state and local governments come together to show their support by turning off the lights in homes, the workplace and at iconic landmarks such as the Empire State Building, Las Vegas Strip, Sydney’s Opera House and more. In 2009 alone, hundreds of millions of people turned out for Earth Hour – spanning 4,100 cities in 87 countries on seven continents. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greater Worcester Humanists is proud to be an official supporter of Earth Hour.  We encourage you to join with us and millions of Americans in making Earth Hour 2010 the biggest effort yet. Getting involved is easy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Sign up at &lt;a href="http://www.earthhour.org" target="_blank"&gt;EarthHour.org &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Show your support, find out what Earth Hour events are happening near you and get tips on organizing fun events in your community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Spread the Word&lt;br /&gt;Invite your friends and family to join the movement, become a fan on Facebook and post a link to EarthHour.org on your profile page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Turn off the lights&lt;br /&gt;Turn off your non-essential lighting at 8:30 p.m. local time on Saturday, March 27. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>7626345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269909399000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265594770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate Earth Hour with us!</name><id>12547181</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269736200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/12547181/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/c/global_12993468.jpeg</photo_url></item>