<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>485 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.415200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-643-0943</phone><name>Punjab</name><city>Arlington</city><id>1067720</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.152219</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lunch location: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=475%20Moody%20St%2C%20Waltham%2C%20MA" target="_blank"&gt; Punjab&lt;/a&gt;, 485 Massachusetts Ave, Arlington, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximate cost: $18 (includes lunch, tax, tip, and $1 to support the meetup). May be a little less depending on location. Additional cost for anything you add from the menu (breads, beverages, chai).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the book:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GOODREADS &amp;amp; AMAZON - &lt;span&gt;From Pulitzer Prize-winner Katherine Boo, a landmark work of narrative nonfiction that tells the dramatic and sometimes heartbreaking story of families striving toward a better life in one of the twenty-first century’s great, unequal cities. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In this brilliantly written, fast-paced book, based on three years of uncompromising reporting, a bewildering age of global change and inequality is made human. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Annawadi is a makeshift settlement in the shadow of luxury hotels near the Mumbai airport, and as India starts to prosper, Annawadians are electric with hope. Abdul, a reflective and enterprising Muslim teenager, sees “a fortune beyond counting” in the recyclable garbage that richer people throw away. Asha, a woman of formidable wit and deep scars from a childhood in rural poverty, has identified an alternate route to the middle class: political corruption. With a little luck, her sensitive, beautiful daughter—Annawadi’s “most-everything girl”—will soon become its first female college graduate. And even the poorest Annawadians, like Kalu, a fifteen-year-old scrap-metal thief, believe themselves inching closer to the good lives and good times they call “the full enjoy.” &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

But then Abdul the garbage sorter is falsely accused in a shocking tragedy; terror and a global recession rock the city; and suppressed tensions over religion, caste, sex, power and economic envy turn brutal. As the tenderest individual hopes intersect with the greatest global truths, the true contours of a competitive age are revealed. And so, too, are the imaginations and courage of the people of Annawadi. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

With intelligence, humor, and deep insight into what connects human beings to one another in an era of tumultuous change, &lt;em&gt;Behind the Beautiful Forevers&lt;/em&gt; carries the reader headlong into one of the twenty-first century’s hidden worlds, and into the lives of people impossible to forget.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Book on table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>6571667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355704256000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333328023000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December 2012 - Behind THE Beautiful Forevers by Katharine Boo</name><id>58835522</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355590800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/58835522/</event_url></item>