<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>FREE w/ Promo T-shirt</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I gather various MeetUp Groups and the &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; for &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot;, whereby we meet a couple of times per month to attend the new Funny Bone Comedy Club inside Manchester's Buckland Hills Mall. The majority of our attendees are Singles in their 40's-50's, but all (over 21) are welcome to join us! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weekend headliner (Jimmy Dore) will cost @ $20 but by attending the WEDNESDAY show, the one-time $15 purchase of their promo tee-shirt allows access to this, and just about every WEDNESDAY performance, for FREE forever! Such a deal! We'll gather @ the Funny Bone Bar @ 6:00-6:30 for a chance to get to know each other and have a drink. When the doors open @ 6:30, we'll enter together and optionally order drinks, an appetizer or dinner (separate checks have been pre-approved) before the show starts @ 7:30 (lasting to @ 9). Seating is &amp;quot;first come, first seated&amp;quot;, so even if you RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot;, if you show up after 6:30 without notifying me in advance (by 3:00, please), we'll not necessarily be able to hold a seat for you (but we'll try), as otherwise there's no way of knowing if you are going to truly join us, or not. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between my various affiliations with different MeetUp Groups and the &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot;, and due to the poor weather forecast, I suspect we'll gather at least 10 people.  If more than that RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; (ASAP!), I'll try to have them hold more tables/seats for us. I'm sure you'll have a good time and enjoy meeting new friends! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; IF you arrive after 6:30, buy your promo tee-shirt at the Box Office, THEN request they give you a FREE ticket. When entering the theater, inform the ticket-taker to seat you with or near &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; group! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney &lt;br /&gt;new to West Hartford / work in Bloomfield &lt;br /&gt;rep06450@cox.net &lt;br /&gt;C: (860) 690-9595 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: The &amp;quot;Funny Bone Comedy Club&amp;quot; is located INSIDE the Buckland Hills Mall, Manchester , CT 06042&lt;br /&gt;Once you arrive at the Buckland Hills Mall: Head toward the Sears / Vinnie T's / Barnes &amp;amp; Noble / JC Penney area. Between Penney's and Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, you'll see a sign for the &amp;quot;Blue Turtle&amp;quot; - enter via that exterior entranceway. The Funny Bone Box Office / Bar / Club is immediately inside, to the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.symfonee.com/funnybone/hartford/home/index.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;HartfordFunnyBone.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184968911000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184768944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TONIGHT: "Funny Bone" Comedy Club - Manchester 6:30</name><id>6041441</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184796000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6041441/</event_url></item>