<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>94 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.808808</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-4428</phone><name>Newburyport Public Library</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>880292</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870878</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The April meeting of the Greater Newburyport Edible Garden Group will be on Monday, April 9th, 7 PM at the Newburyport Public Library Program Room. Our guest speaker is Kate McDonough, co-owner of Stout Oak Farm in Brentwood, NH. Kate will give an overview of her edible garden knowledge, her skills and her farm's resources as well as take questions from the audience. Kate knows her stuff: come and ask those burning questions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kate has been an organic vegetable grower for the past 12 years, having worked for and managed Certified Organic vegetable farms in California, Massachusetts, and New Hampshire. At Stout Oak they use ecologically sound farming practices, demonstrating their commitment to enhance soil health, use resources efficiently, create a safe working environment for themselves and their crew, and grow safe,healthy food. In addition to a farm stand and a CSA, Stout Oak Farm offers seedlings and skill-building workshops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Edible Garden Group was formed by community members who are interested in getting together to learn and share information about sustainable food growing &amp;#150; veggies, fruits, nuts. The meetings are focused on building community resilience through increasing the availability of safe, nutritious, sustainably-grown local food. To learn more visit the website at &lt;a href="http://hyperlocavore.ning.com/group/egg" class="linkified"&gt;http://hyperlocavore.ning.com/group/egg&lt;/a&gt; and feel free to join the discussion on-line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Deb Carey boiester@gmail.com, 617-922-1831 or Marsha Bogart branett@comcast.net, phone 603-401-8134.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth </member_name><member_id>389569</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334017477000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332953388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Newburyport Edible Garden Group</name><id>58235502</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334012400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/58235502/</event_url></item>