<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Harvard Symposia on Architecture&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Return of Nature&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preston Scott Cohen&lt;/b&gt;, Gerald M. McCue Professor in Architecture and Chair of the&lt;br /&gt;Department of Architecture, GSD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Erika Naginski&lt;/b&gt;, Associate Professor of Architectural History, GSD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm - 8:00pm · Piper Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That Nature has returned with a vengeance in architectural theory and practice goes far beyond the transmutation of the Vitruvian qualities of firmitas, utilitas and venustas into sustainability’s motto of equity, biodiversity, and wise development. The relation of architecture and nature found in the abundant literature on sustainability rests on a moral imperative provided by the current environmental crisis, which sets, as in a Greek tragedy, the finitude of natural resources over and against the dismal and infinite cycle of human production and consumption. From this agon emerges the quest for a responsible architecture. The apocalyptic drama is rehearsed in such movements as natural architecture, which reifies the presumed mysteriousness and fragility of natural materials by disposing and exposing leaves, branches and rocks in ephemeral interventions. By the same token, hope is made to reside, resolutely and problematically, in the promise of technology (this despite the specter of historical modalities such as pollution and obsolescence); thus there is biomimicry, to give but one example, in which the emulation of natural forms and processes undergirds the creation of such materials as adhesives replicating the bonding materials found in mussels, ceramic tiles with the strength of abalone shells, or glass with the air purifying capacities of certain plants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gsd.harvard.edu/events/pdf/return_of_nature_description.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Read More&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No organizer will be present.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316506092000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266615607000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Architectural Symposium: Return of Nature</name><id>12650559</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267056000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12650559/</event_url></item>