<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The map/info feature is above is now fixed and correct for the location indicated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kathy K, has recently seen the beauty of this location and suggested it as something the new members would like, some of us were up here a while ago and yes we should all go back again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im going, you are all invited if you are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a simple walk to the top via the big grass hill for a peacefull sunset and dinner on the round rock above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Share conversation over some tasty beverage and dinner on the mountain top..and posibly a moonlight walk in other areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a chair and coat..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford take Interstate 84, take Exit 60 (Manchester-East Hartford). take a left ...The route is 44 Burnside Ave heading to East Hartford..The park begins about quarter mile west of the exit but DO NoT use the gate. The park actually locks the gate at sunset.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE WILL MEET on the side of the road (Vernon Road, east hartford, ct) between the MARCO POLO RESTARUANT and the &amp;quot;hill&amp;quot;... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is road about 1 mile away from that exit going towards east hartford, as you just pass the hill on the right. you will see a citgo station and mack donalds to the left and marco polo restaurant on the right just before the street.... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Vernon/Rockville &lt;br /&gt;Im not sure exactly what exit number but as best i know of its the one that goes to the mall but its the one 3 miles before rte 44...Please look at your maps first...&lt;br /&gt;use the RTE 44 exit go towards east hartford&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;anyway..Vernon Street, East Hartford, CT is the destination.. use that for your GPS, or mapquest map info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have the dark blue toyota avalon and will put a orange cone somewhere to see..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at 6 we got to get to the top...it gets dark too early now..so we cant waite at the bottom for long..or just go to the top if you are late..you will spot us..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will cook for us some bonless skinless chicken brest on the grill up there..put it on some potatoe bred ..and have some white zin..&lt;br /&gt;you bring what you think goes with this..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191793986000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191517912000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk to the top of Wickham Park for a Sunset Event</name><id>6487599</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191620700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6487599/</event_url></item>