<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Movie:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;The Big Lebowski&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Showtime:&lt;/b&gt; 7:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt; Coolidge Corner Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duration:&lt;/b&gt; 1hr 57 mins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although the show starts at 7:00 pm let's get in line at &lt;u&gt;6:15 pm&lt;/u&gt; when the line starts forming; it gives us more time to socialize. Within 10 minutes the line for these Monday night movies wraps down the alley and around the corner. We can try to save a few seats though! We'll be standing next to the people in bowling shirts and bathrobes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. will be there around 6:10 pm. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair spiked in the front, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. He will not be wearing a bathrobe, nor will be be drinking a white russian... in public. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a pre-show and the judging for the &amp;quot;best costume&amp;quot; contest (&lt;i&gt;see below&lt;/i&gt;) we probably won't be out of there until 9:45 pm. I'm thinking of calling &lt;b&gt;Finale&lt;/b&gt; at 1306 Beacon St in Brookline a few blocks away and making a reservation for fifteen or twenty, if they take reservations. It's pricey... you can easily spend ten dollars on a dessert, but I have heard they are to die for... [ &lt;b&gt;Dessert Menu&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.finaledesserts.com/menus-viewmenus.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.finaledess...&lt;/a&gt; ]. You can get regular food such as eight dollar salads up until 10:00 pm from their Prelude menu &lt;a href="http://www.finaledesserts.com/pdfs/July2009/FIN_Prelude_Menu_July2009.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.finaledess...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I need a rough headcount... how many people might want to go to Finale after, if we get out of the movie by 9:45? Update your RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About The Big Lebowski:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/node/2378" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;Yeah, well. The Dude abides&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What is THE BIG LEBOWSKI, you say? Well, if you have to ask... not only is it one of the biggest and best cult movies of our time, but more importantly, this Coen Brothers classic is an outrageously insane comedy of bowling, confused identities, naked performance art, porn-obsessed nihilists, a sex offender named Jesus, and some unforgettable musical dream sequences -- Oh, and some guy called 'The Dude.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sure, just bringing this lovably oddball slacker classic back to the BIG screen is cool enough on its own. But that's not all! We're throwing our fifth annual pre-show bowling party extravaganza celebrating the greatness of his dudeness and his laid back misadventures. Here's your chance to compete for sweet Lebowski-themed prizes in tests of wit and skill including, but not limited to: best costume (break out those bowling shirts, bathrobes, and skintight purple Jesus lounge suits!), most convincing nihilist quip, most impassioned Walter rant, and of course, bowling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;dir. Joel Cohen, w/ Jeff Bridges, John Goodman, Julianne Moore, Steve Buscemi and John Turturro, 1h57m&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Purchase tickets:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/showtimes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt; .. &lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; $9.75 (plus sevice charge if bought online)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions, Public Transporation:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;By train&lt;/u&gt;: take the Green Line (C branch to Cleveland Circle) trolley from downtown to Coolidge Corner via Beacon Street. The Coolidge Corner stop is at Harvard Street, 5-10 minutes from Kenmore Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Nearby metered public parking is available behind the theatre (on Center St. one block from Harvard St.) and along Beacon Street. Meters are free after 6:00pm and on Sundays and holidays. Please note that the lots tend to fill up on weekends or during large events, so please plan a little extra time to find space. We strongly reccomend public transit for events and films you anticipate will be very busy! Additional Parking at an hourly rate is available across Beacon and Centre Streets at the Courtyard Marriott Hotel garage on Webster St&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trailer:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r_GCRFRcWxA" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;And another trailer:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YHuyjYJCCOA" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257958241000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250620716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Big Lebowski @ Coolidge Corner</name><id>11140440</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251152100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11140440/</event_url></item>