<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From June to September, celebrate Nights on the Neck on the first Thursday of the month from 5:30 to 9pm. Many galleries host receptions with refreshments. Musicians, dancers, authors, historians and other entertainers give performances and lectures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've done this several times, and it's always been a great night out. We can walk the neck, visit the open galleries, listen to music, and end up at one of the restaurants for drinks &amp;amp; / food. This is a combined event with other meetup groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*WE WILL MEETUP @ 5pm at The Rocky Neck Art Colony sign- the sign is at the public lot at the base of Rocky Neck Avenue. If you are unable to join us at 5, join us when you can. Here is my contact # is: 978.289.7679. This is a mostly outdoor event - therefore, weather dependant. Please make sure to check for an update if weather is questionable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

**You can find July 5th schedule at: www.rockyneckartcolony.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7/5/12: Events begin at 5pm just across from the public parking lot - Mamadou is scheduled from 5pm-6pm. The last event scheduled is from 8:45- 9:30 - Jazz at The Center, on 6 Wonson St&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>please read description for where to meetup</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341592188000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>travel-575</urlname><id>418980</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Old and Not so Old Ladies Travel</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341426325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nights On The Neck- Rocky Neck Art Colony</name><id>71951792</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341522000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/travel-575/events/71951792/</event_url></item>