<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come for an evening of fun --and improve your health and well-bring at the same time!  Meet people who love to laugh! Our own Mark Sherry, a certified Laughter Yoga instructor, and Ingrid, are graciously hosting this event for us. LAUGHTER YOGA DOES NOT USE YOGA POSTURES, ONLY SIMPLE BREATHING TECHNIQUES, eye contact, and child-like playfulness to elicit laughter. &lt;b&gt;You DON'T have to be flexible you just need a desire to have FUN!&lt;/b&gt; We will start the evening with a 45 minute Laughter Yoga session. Following that we will walk down the street to the Northampton Brewery to enjoy the locally brewed beers, food, and each other. There is plenty of parking across the street in the Northampton parking garage. You do not need to be happy, have a sense of humor, or even have a reason in order to laugh.  Laughter Yoga bases itself on the philosophy of “acting happiness.” In time fake laughter becomes genuine and flows out like a fountain! Speaking of fountains, this venue is located right off of Pleasant St just behind Sylvester's Restaurant by the &lt;i&gt;big&lt;/i&gt; fountain. The community room is just inside the entrance on the first floor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Donations accepted.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the Brewery click here: &lt;a href="http://www.northamptonbrewery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northampto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Mark &amp; Ingrid are hosting this event</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232930315000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1514</urlname><id>824401</id><group_lat>42.0999984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5899963379</group_lon><name>Single Mingle Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231541791000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Laughter Yoga &amp; the Northampton Brewery   </name><id>9487925</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232757000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1514/events/9487925/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/e/global_3300622.jpeg</photo_url></item>