<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;March's &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;FREE Community Evening&lt;/span&gt; at Roots and Wings, our gift to you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Connecting to Your Best Self&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Wed. evening, March 14th, 7:15 - 8:45 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;I also did this event at Earthsong Yoga on March 2nd, and it was phenomenal! Everyone left having deeply connected to a better feeling place and positive inner resources they weren't acknowledging; AND with strategies they could continue to use.&amp;nbsp; Please join us so YOU can experience this, as well!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are there times when you're not feeling quite sure about yourself ,or good enough in some way for what you want?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Or are there times when you'd like to be prepared to be your best?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Would it be nice to have some easy ways to access your Best Self?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Tonight I'll guide you through three transformative meditations, along with some instruction and discussion, too: one to the deep core of your being, one with a tree, and one with clouds! They'll be meaningful AND fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My intention is to connect you to your inner brilliance, all the resources available to you, and the perfection that you are. Sound good? If so, join us, and invite your friends and family to join us, too!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Written comments after this event a prior time:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am leaving refreshed, optimistic, empowered, full of love and excited about bringing more spirit into everything I do.&amp;nbsp; I&amp;rsquo;m sure that practicing the techniques I learned tonight will help me very much.&amp;nbsp; Thank you!!! &amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;ldquo;It is always a great experience.&amp;nbsp; Thank you!&amp;nbsp; The tree meditation was especially poignant.&amp;nbsp; I always feel so much clearer after these evenings.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So treat yourself to this wonderful free event for you. Please invite others to sign up and join you. Share this with your friends, family and groups. The class is appropriate for everyone, and all are welcome!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Space is limited, so registration is required.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We've recently been having a waiting list, so if your plans change, please, please let us know so someone else can take your place.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Please plan on arriving around 7:05 to get settled. No need to bring anything, unless you want to.&amp;nbsp; Chairs, yoga mats, pillows and yoga blankets are available there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hope you'll join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Ann&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., spiritual life coach with www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com, certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann coaches people to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, clients become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness they want. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;This public event is co-sponsored by Roots and Wings and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the Wings studio on the first floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331841397000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328730460000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connecting to your Best Self: a free community event</name><id>51584262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331766900000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/51584262/</event_url></item>