<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>An opportunity for us to be inspired by a &amp;quot;professor, political scientist, historian, social critic, democratic socialist, activist and playwright, best known as author of the bestseller &lt;u&gt;A People's History of the United States.&lt;/u&gt;, the only 'textbook' I ever used when teaching American history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Best-selling historian &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Howard Zinn&lt;/span&gt; introduces his favorite film as part of the Coolidge's 75th anniversary celebration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sir William Walker (Marlon Brando) is called to the island of Queimada to instigate a slave revolt in order to make sugar trade more lucrative for the British. Years later, when the very same rebels whom Sir William had amassed grow to be too powerful, he is called back to regain balance on the island.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is a reworking of the events of the the 1790s in the French colony of Guadeloupe. It was also meant to reflect upon the situation in the &lt;i&gt;Vietnam War,&lt;/i&gt; which was going on at the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brando had the opportunity to have a role on &lt;u&gt;Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid&lt;/u&gt; but chose instead to work on this film. He also had to turn down a major role in &lt;u&gt;Ryan's Daughter&lt;/u&gt; because of this film's production problems.  In an interview with Larry King, Brando claimed that Burn! was his personal favorite film to have worked on. In his autobiography he claims, &amp;quot;I did some of my best acting in Burn!&amp;quot; Evaristo Márquez, Brando's co-star, was a non-actor and a real-life sugarcane plantation worker. His role was originally to be played by Sidney Poitier, but Pontecorvo insisted on a non-professional actor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As this film is on a Monday night, and Mr. Zinn's presentation is likely to extend the showing of the film towards 10 pm, the meetup will occur before the film so that members can get a bite to eat and discuss the state of world affairs, their histories with Howard Zinn and Marlon Brando, and sit together for what should be a fascinating evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be at &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Panera Bread&lt;/span&gt; across the street from the Coolidge Theater at 6:00.  Please join us whenever you can.  We will go over to the theater at 6:45.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be at Panera Bread starting at 6:00 at a  table with a Meetup Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234661309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Burn! (1969)</name><id>9743567</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236639600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9743567/</event_url></item>