<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Financial District</address_2><address_1>184 High Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.356556</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-292-4695</phone><name>Howl at the Moon</name><city>Boston</city><id>1342099</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052368</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;WOW! Another wonderful year of happy times with great drinking buddies. THANK YOU!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's (w)ring out one last happy hour in 2011 at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.howlatthemoon.com/locations/location-boston"&gt;Howl at the Moon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;where they party with a purpose.....the purpose of FUN FUN FUN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy live entertainment, great food, and tons of fun. Expect a high-energy dueling pianos throwdown&amp;nbsp;where the piano players and staff not only entertain you but if you choose to, you can&amp;nbsp;become part of the show too.&amp;nbsp;Showtime is from 6 PM until 10 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is another amateur drinking day (as Luis and Vinnie call it), so I'll be there at 4 to get the prime seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive when you can and stay as long as you're able.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first new member who finds me, gets a free drink. Don't be shy...Say hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you RSVP Yes, are at least 21 and arrive between 6 PM and 8 PM you receive:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No cover until 8 PM if you leave and want to reenter after 8 PM you must pay an entry fee and if you arrive after 8 PM you must pay an entry fee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$4 vodka drinks (type of liquor to be named that night)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$4 rum drinks (type of liquor to be named that night)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$3 beer (type of beer to be named that night)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complimentary buffet from 6 PM until 8 PM (so get there early so you can have some grub).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to pay for your food and are interested in the drink list here are the&lt;a href="http://www.howlatthemoon.com/images/howl/corporate_packages/bostonfoodmenu.pdf"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Howl Food Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.howlatthemoon.com/downloads/bostonfoodmenu.pdf"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.howlatthemoon.com/images/howl/assets/drinkmenu2.pdf"&gt;Howl Drink Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to create your route by public transit. Nearby subway stations are&amp;nbsp;Aquarium (blue line), Haymarket (green &amp;amp; orange lines), State (orange &amp;amp; blue lines), Government Center (blue &amp;amp; green lines), and South Station (red line &amp;amp; commuter rail) subway stations are no more than a fifteen (15) minute walk away&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Howl at the Moon Party Terms and Conditions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You understand that Howl at the Moon does not reserve or allow guests to hold tables. If you are interested in a guaranteed table, there is special party pricing. You understand that these are the privileges for the date specified only. No rights, privileges or drink offers will apply to this Happy Hour Party other than what is stated above. You've read and understand these privileges prior to arriving for our party.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Happy Hour Meetup Party With Tonya</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325506933000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324384651000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Howl at the Moon on the Eve of New Year's Eve</name><id>45004422</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325278800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/45004422/</event_url></item>