<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hanover Street</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.364319</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North End - Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>6757602</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053917</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be the first monthly event of 2013 and it is a "trio" of events.  Since there are so many of you interested in attending, other than starting at 12:30, I have added a second group that starts at 3:30. I have booked the Private Tasting Room at the Wine Bottega (341 Hanover Street) for wine tasting and hors d'oeuvres, then we will all gather for a tasty family-style lunch at Assaggio (29 Prince Street), followed by the showing of an Italian movie (with English subtitles) on the huge screen in the basement classroom at Caffè Paradiso (255 Hanover Street). I have several movies to choose from, but I was thinking of showing either 'Cesare deve morire' (Caesar must die), or '20 sigarette' (20 Sigarettes).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'Cesare deve morire' was the top prized Italian film of 2012 (&lt;a href="http://www.cinemaitaliano.info/piupremiati/annouscita/2012.html) and" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.cinemaitaliano.info/piupremiati/annouscita/2012.html) and&lt;/a&gt; was the Italian entry for the Academy Awards as 'Best Foreign Film' of 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'20 sigarette' was one of the top prized films in Italy in 2010 &lt;a href="http://www.cinemaitaliano.info/piupremiati/annouscita/2010.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.cinemaitaliano.info/piupremiati/annouscita/2010.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These events have always been a favorite of the students in the Italian Program (www.italianprogram.com), and now I would like to extend an invitation to the members of this Meetup group.  &lt;span&gt;There is a 25 person limit, and we are close to full.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Total price for this event is $42 (You will be notified of Payment methods once you contact me with the following information: your full name, email address and cell phone number.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here are more details about what is included:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. The Wine Bottega - Tasting of 4-5 Italian wines from a variety of locations around Italy as well as hors d'oeuvres (variety of cheese, salame, fresh veges, crackers, etc...)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Assaggio - 3-course lunch (Choice of 3 pasta dishes, Choice of 2 meat dishes, salad or soup, roasted potatoes or vegetable.....drinks NOT included)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Caffè Paradiso - Italian Movie + Coffee and dessert (choice of a regular coffee, espresso or tea + a mini-cannolo)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in attending, other than answering this post, I ask that you please email me at the following email address: italianprogram@gmail.com AND that you provide a way for me to contact you via cell phone.  I will need to email the entire group at times before the events of January 20th, and I will need to be able to call/text you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to call me at 617-233-9876 at any time if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this takes place on MLK Weekend, it is interesting to note that several cities in Italy have streets or squares named after Martin Luther King, Jr....including Napoli and Bologna....a fact that many of you probably didn't know!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for your interest in these events...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>john jordan</member_name><member_id>3198507</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358775320000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members of this group</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>italian-374</urlname><id>288923</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Italian Language Meetup Group &amp; Lunedì Italiano</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356242853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UPDATE - Wine Tasting, Family-Style Lunch and Italian Movie Event</name><id>96308062</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358703000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-374/events/96308062/</event_url></item>