<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>September will feature Doug Stewart, Master Flight Instructor. He'll talk with us about how to fly the Hudson River Corridor. Providing it's open, we'll plan our flight there for the following weekend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lucky us to have Doug come and speak at our meeting. I asked him at Oshkosh and he agreed. This will be a packed house again. Probably in the hangar instead of our meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doug Stewart is the “National Certificated Flight Instructor of the Year for 2004”. A Master Certified Flight Instructor, Gold Seal Instructor, and Designated Pilot Examiner, he is based at the Columbia County Airport (1B1) in Hudson, NY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dsflight.com/about.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dsflight.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FLYING THE NEW YORK VFR CORRIDOR&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Flying the NY VFR corridor is an effective way to transition the New York Metropolitan area and is also an awe-filled scenic flight. However, the risks are numerous and the flight could become awful rather than awe-filled. This seminar presents all the hazards and risks, and then shows how to fly the route safely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn all the important reporting points, safe altitudes, where and how the helicopters operate, and proper frequencies to use. The knowledge gained from this seminar will allow you to fly the corridor more safely and with reduced risk to all aircraft in the airspace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This award winning seminar is now available as a DVD to be used as an excellent reference if you are thinking of flying this route. You can buy it now for just $29.95. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE: THE FAA HAS DISALLOWED THIS PROGRAM AS A WINGS PROGRAM. YOU'D THINK THEY WOULD LIKE INSTRUCTION ON FLYING THE CORRIDOR! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE'LL HAVE SOME POSTERS MADE UP AND SEND THEM TO OTHER AIRPORTS FOR THIS EVENT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, food at 6:00 and meeting at 7:00.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where else can you have this much excitement for $25 bucks a year?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fly Often and Fly Safe, &lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252846701000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250032309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FPA EAA Chapter 1454 September Meetup with Doug Stewart!  </name><id>11089788</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252447200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/11089788/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/c/1/global_4198801.jpeg</photo_url></item>