<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1154 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.346428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 536-1608</phone><name>Massachusetts Historical Society</name><city>Boston</city><id>631419</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089930</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003300"&gt;Students of a new Boston University course "Making History" discuss the MHS exhibit on King Philip's War they have researched and compiled. The semester-long project on the bloody conflict between English colonists and Native Americans includes work on letters and diaries, sermons, early printed books, and objects from the war.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;James H. Johnson, who teaches "Making History," is Associate Professor of History at Boston University. He is the recipient of the University's highest teaching award and the author of two prize-winning books, Listening in Paris: A Cultural History and Venice Incognito: Masks in the Serene Republic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We can walk over to Dillon's on Boylston afterwards for a drink/discussion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src="http://25.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lh9e130YnV1qf7y3ro1_500.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;King Philip's War (1675-76) is an event that has been largely ignored by the American public and popular historians. However, the almost two-year conflict between the colonists and the Native Americans in New England stands as perhaps the most devastating war in this country's history. One in ten soldiers on both sides were wounded or killed. At its height, hostilities threatened to push the recently arrived English colonists back to the coast. And, it took years for towns and urban centers to recover from the carnage and property damage.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;The war is named for King Philip, the son of Massasoit and chief of the Wampanoag nation. In his language, his name was Metacom, Metacomet, or Pometacom. In 1662, the court at Plymouth Colony arrogantly summoned the Wampanoag leader Wamsutta to Plymouth. Major Josiah Winslow (later Colonel) and a small force took Wamsutta, Philip's brother, at gunpoint. Soon after questioning, Wamsutta sickened and died and his death infuriated the Wampanoag nation.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Upon the death of his brother, whom the Indians suspected the English of murdering, Philip became sachem and maintained a shaky peace with the colonists for a number of years. Friendship continued to erode over the steady succession of land sales forced on the Indians by their growing dependence on English goods, and Plymouth's continued unyielding policy toward Native leaders, it is reported by the Connecticut Society of Colonial Wars (&lt;a href="http://www.colonialwarsct.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;www.colonialwarsct.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) and other sources.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Suspicions of the Indians remained, and in 1671, the colonists questioned Philip, fined him and demanded that the Wampanoag surrender their arms, which they did&lt;/span&gt;... (continued at &lt;a href="http://www.militaryhistoryonline.com/horsemusket/kingphilip/default.aspx" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.militaryhistoryonline.com/horsemusket/kingphilip/default.aspx&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="https://dnbweb1.blackbaud.com/OPXREPHIL/EventDetail.asp?cguid=76FBBAD5%2D59FC%2D442D%2D8347%2DA5AE40DBF561&amp;amp;eid=43150"&gt;https://dnbweb1.blackbaud.com/OPXREPHIL/EventDetail.asp?cguid=76FBBAD5%2D59FC%2D442D%2D8347%2DA5AE40DBF561&amp;amp;eid=43150&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There is a pre-lecture reception at the top of the stairs with wine, beer and cheese. Let's meet upstairs between 5:30 and 5:45. the event starts at 6:00</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>8776856</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1355464758000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354569470000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Lecture - King Philip's War (1675-76) in documents and artifacts</name><id>93918392</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355438700000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/93918392/</event_url></item>