<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday at Market Boston  130 Water St. Financial District   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's Financial District 6:30-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a 3  month hiatus  The Afterwork mixer returns this Thursday October 16th. Its Fall,  the best time of the year, weather is great,  the college football season is in full swing, the baseball playoffs are finally here and full seasons of Entourage and the Hills are going strong!!  With  Halloween right arond the corner its time to get the Afterwork party started!!   So please join the group as we head to the Financial district's newest afterwork hotspot  MKT (Market) Boston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MKT Boston  is one of the premier afterwork spots in the Boston area. If you enjoy making new contacts and friends, while enjoying some of the best cocktails on a wonderful fall evening then this is the event for you!! Also if you are new member and have not been to an afterwork mixer, or have only been to a few events, I highly encourage you to attend and meet many of our wonderful members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So what better way to come out this Thurs and have a few cocktails with the group as we gear up for another festive weekend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting details:  Check out the venue website  at &lt;a href="http://www.mktboston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mktboston....&lt;/a&gt;  This will give you a better overall sense of the venue and provide pinpoint directions from your destination. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We will meet at the bar area . Like any event, when arriving please &lt;b&gt;be sure to&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;locate the organizer.&lt;/b&gt; Please do not hesitate to call or text me upon arrival if you are having trouble finding the group. My picture is on the site under the Assistant Organizer section so I should not be hard to find. &lt;br /&gt;To find the group with ease  I highly ENCOURAGE you to attend early as possible. My phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Please email me if you have any questions.   Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;Green/Blue Line to Govt Center&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to State St&lt;br /&gt;Red Line to Park st. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event cost: Free. (However please feel free to grab a beverage for your hard working organizers) &lt;br /&gt;**Note please see the message board regarding meetup/event etiquette**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Also if you're around this weekend, be sure to check out Charlie's event Friday nite at Kitty O'Sheas should be a fun time! **&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224369450000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223830584000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>We're Back!!!  Afterwork Mixer this Thursday! </name><id>8947383</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224196200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8947383/</event_url></item>