<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1228 Riverdale St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.137860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>On The Border Mexican Grill</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>669419</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.625950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/6/8/event_189838472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;My Stroke of Insight by Jill Bolte Taylor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;On December 10, 1996, Jill Bolte Taylor, a thirty-seven-year-old Harvard-trained brain scientist, experienced a massive stroke in the left hemisphere of her brain. As she observed her mind deteriorate to the point that she could not walk, talk, read, write, or recall any of her life-all within four hours-Taylor alternated between the euphoria of the intuitive and kinesthetic right brain, in which she felt a sense of complete well-being and peace, and the logical, sequential left brain, which recognized she was having a stroke and enabled her to seek help before she was completely lost. It would take her eight years to fully recover.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For Taylor, the stroke was a blessing and a revelation. It taught her that by "stepping to the right" of our left brains, we can all uncover feelings of well-being that are often sidelined by "brain chatter." In My Stroke of Insight, Taylor provides a valuable recovery guide for those touched by brain injury and an inspiring testimony that inner peace is accessible to anyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: Shawna&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Baker's Daughter by Sarah McCoy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In 1945, Elsie Schmidt was a naïve teenager, as eager for her first sip of champagne as she was for her first kiss. But in the waning days of the Nazi empire, with food scarce and fears of sedition mounting, even the private yearnings of teenage girls were subject to suspicion and suppression. Elsie’s courtship by Josef Hub, a rising star in the Army of the Third Reich, has insulated her and her family from the terror and desperation overtaking her country. So when an escaped Jewish boy arrives on Elsie’s doorstep in the dead of night on Christmas Eve, Elsie understands that opening the door puts all she loves in danger.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sixty years later, in El Paso, Texas, Reba Adams is trying to file a feel-good Christmas piece for the local magazine. Reba is a rolling stone, perpetually on the run from memories of a turbulent childhood, but she’s been in El Paso long enough to get a full-time job and a full-time fiancé, Riki Chavez. Riki, an agent with the U.S. Border Patrol, finds comfort in strict rules and regulations, whereas Reba knows that in every good story, lines will be blurred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reba's latest assignment has brought her to the shop of an elderly baker across town. The interview should take a few hours at most, but the owner of Elsie's German Bakery is no easy subject. Elsie keeps turning the tables on Reba, and Reba finds herself returning to the bakery again and again, anxious to find the heart of the story. For Elsie, Reba's questions have been a stinging reminder of darker times: her life in Germany during that last bleak year of WWII. And as Elsie, Reba, and Riki's lives become more intertwined, all are forced to confront the uncomfortable truths of the past and seek out the courage to forgive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: Catherine&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shawna</member_name><member_id>10937608</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine</member_name><member_id>12990945</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1364142226000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355102899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>My stroke of Insight &amp; The Baker's Daughter</name><id>94743072</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361921400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/94743072/</event_url></item>