<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Arthur Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.184989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waushakum Live Steamers</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1356738</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.469482</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>(This is a RAIN or SHINE event.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For kids, young and old -- and in between:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BON Family-Friendly Fun Event, Sunday, August 29th, Noon - 5PM:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Waushakum Live Steamers Annual Meet (Noon - 3PM)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.waushakumlivesteamers.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waushakuml...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.waushakumlivesteamers.org/about/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waushakuml...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post-Train Dinner at Bertucci's (3:30PM - 5PM)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bertuccis.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bertuccis....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark Shar says, &amp;quot;My 6 year old has loved trains since he was 1 and a half! Every year since, at the end of the summer, we go to the Waushakum Live Steamers Open Meet. What are live steamers? Not clams, but coal-burning, live-steam powered operating model trains. It's pretty cool to see the different types of steam trains that folks bring from around the country and run on the miles of track at this club in Holliston, MA. Better still, you don't just have to watch! There are almost always two to five engines pulling human stock! Yes, you can ride the trains as much as you want -- and for free too! This year I am bringing my son and friend of his to the event.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where to Meet at the Meet:&lt;br /&gt;My son, his friend and I will be waiting at the &amp;quot;train station&amp;quot; from Noon - 12:15 PM. After that we'll be walking around or riding the trains. For my cell info, please email me off list just in case you have trouble finding us at the meet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Waushakum Live Steamers: please see &lt;a href="http://www.waushakumlivesteamers.org/directions/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waushakuml...&lt;/a&gt;. If you have trouble with that web page, use an online mapping site or your GPS to get you to: Arthur Street in Holliston, MA 01746; it's a short, little cul-de-sac in a residential . This is key: the entrance to the Waushakum property is at the end of Arthur Street. The Waushakum driveway is just to the left of their engraved rock sign at the far end of the cul-de-sac. No matter how many cars are parked on the street, make sure you head down their driveway to the on-site parking lot -- unless you are directed to park in the cul-de-sac or on the street. The driveway is only a few tenths of a mile so it isn't a terribly long walk from the street to the &amp;quot;train station&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nota Bene:&lt;br /&gt;1. Please be aware of the Travel Detour post at the WLS site if your directions will bring you into Holliston on Rte. 16 (&lt;a href="http://www.waushakumlivesteamers.org/2010/05/11/travel-detour/)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waushakuml...&lt;/a&gt;. Although it was posted in May, I don't know whether it is still active or not.&lt;br /&gt;2. Please see &lt;a href="http://www.steamingpriest.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.steamingpr...&lt;/a&gt; for additional photos and videos.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where to Meet for Dinner:&lt;br /&gt;Meet us inside the Bertucci's at 414 Washington St., Holliston, MA 01746. Phone: 508-429-4571&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Unless you are only joining us for the dinner, make sure your directions are from WLS to Bertucci's.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gavin Pitt</member_name><member_id>4194885</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283102498000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282694736000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waushakum Live Steamers Annual Meet</name><id>14530903</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283097600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/14530903/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/2/global_17451746.jpeg</photo_url></item>