<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1060268</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369168</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Friends,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We just had our third meeting together as we looked together at the stories of Sr. Joan Chittister in our book, Tent of Abraham: Stories of Hope and Peace for Jews, Christians and Muslims. Her wonderful way to reflect the Abrahamic Journey with women, Jew, Christian and Muslim, searching for peace in the Middle East was inspiring to us all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We were visited by a columnist and photographer from the Boston Globe. We hope it helps to encourage interfaith encounters in other areas of Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We went ahead and scheduled our next meeting for December 18, 7:30 pm - 9 pm. We will look at the final third part of the book, Muslim Interpretations of Abraham's Journey with Imam Murshid Saadi Shakur Chishti. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As we come close to completing our first book of our bookclub, we will need to choose another selection at our next meeting. Joe and I will bring a list of possiblilities, please feel free to bring your own suggestions. Keep in mind the purpose of our book club in the suggestions you bring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are also looking to have our next meetin at the Peace Abbey, a nice way to spend our Christmas meeting in a beautiful interfaith environment. This still has to be verified and I will get back to you that soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace and see you next time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Carl Chudy&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;Our Lady of Fatima Shrine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out our Interfaith Book Club Blog at www.interfaithbookclub.wordpress.com &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198197553000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195609272000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club December Meetup</name><id>6779833</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198024200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/6779833/</event_url></item>