<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>259 Massapoag Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02334</zip><lat>42.059466</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-238-6566</phone><name>Borderland State Park</name><city>Easton</city><id>793864</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.166649</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wednesday is forecast to be sunny so let's get out and go for a 7.5 mile hike.  Yes I know is a weekday, but for those who don't have to work that day, let's hike!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll hike along several trails on the northern section of the 1906 estate of botanist Oakes Ames. First, the West Side Trail, then French Trail, Northwest Trail to Ridge Trail where we’ll veer off to Quarry Trail to visit Moyles Quarry. This quarry provided stones for the Boston + Providence Railroad in the early 1800’s.   After visiting the quarry, we’ll head on the Morse Loop, pick up the Quarry Trail again and then hike along the Granite Hills Trail towards Split Rock Trail to see Split Rock.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Providence: Head north on Hwy 95 and take Interstate 495 South towards Cape Cod.   Take Exit 10 and go East on MA Hwy 123 for 3.4 miles. Turn left on Poquanticut Avenue  which becomes Massapoag Avenue to reach the entrance on the right. Follow the signs to Borderland State Park while driving on Poquanticut and Massapoag.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailhead: Visitors Center for the Northern Trails Hike. There is a $2.00 parking fee.  Let's meet at 10 AM.  We should be done early afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy</member_name><member_id>5560956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256307408000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255872660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Borderland State Park Hike</name><id>11652753</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256133600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/11652753/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>