<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>From the cult director of &amp;quot;Shallow Grave,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Trainspotting,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;28 Days Later,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;The Lovable Millions,&amp;quot; comes a film with an unconventional story set in the world's most populous city, Mumbai. For Danny Boyle, it is a personal triumph. Here he combines the suspense of a game show with the vision and energy of a &amp;quot;City of God&amp;quot; and never stops sprinting. The film uses dazzling cinematography, editing, music and headlong momentum to explode with narrative force, wrapping in a poignant romance at the same time. The movie is already generating a lot of Oscar buzz for 2008 after winning the Best Picture (Peoples choice award) at the Toronto Film Festival, official selections at Telluride &amp;amp; London Film festivals ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Bollywood failing to produce films that feed to the platter of world cinema, many foreign studios are increasingly showing interest in capturing the heart of India, and &amp;quot;Slumdog Millionaire&amp;quot; certainly is one of the best that's come out in the recent past. I'm personally looking fwd to see this film for it's soundtrack. A R Rahman [ &amp;quot;Elizabeth (2007)&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Lord of the Rings Musical (2007)&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;The Warriors of Heaven and Earth&amp;quot; and over a hundred Indian films ], is hailed as the greatest contemporary Indian composer, and Danny Boyle himself attributed that the best part of this film is &amp;quot;it's background score.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, as usual, we'll go to a nearby pub/restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SYNOPSIS:&lt;br /&gt;The story of Jamal Malik (Patel), an 18 year-old orphan from the slums of Mumbai, who is about to experience the biggest day of his life. With the whole nation watching, he is just one question away from winning a staggering 20 million rupees on India's &amp;quot;Who Wants To Be A Millionaire?&amp;quot; But when the show breaks for the night, police arrest him on suspicion of cheating; how could a street kid know so much? Desperate to prove his innocence, Jamal tells the story of his life in the slum where he and his brother grew up, of their adventures together on the road, of vicious encounters with local gangs, and of Latika (Pinto), the girl he loved and lost. Each chapter of his story reveals the key to the answer to one of the game show's questions. Each chapter of Jamal's increasingly layered story reveals where he learned the answers to the show's seemingly impossible quizzes. But one question remains a mystery: what is this young man with no apparent desire for riches really doing on the game show? When the new day dawns and Jamal returns to answer the final question, the Inspector and sixty million viewers are about to find out...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OFFICIAL SITE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxsearchlight.com/slumdogmillionaire/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foxsearchl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TEASERS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://content.foxsearchlight.com/videos/node/2954" target="_blank"&gt;http://content.foxsea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W9VBofFZPsM&amp;amp;feature=related" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UhrQkGur2Ps&amp;amp;feature=related" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REVIEWS:&lt;br /&gt;100% on the tomato meter scale - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/slumdog_millionaire/?name_order=asc" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rottentoma...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Roger Ebert calls it, &amp;quot;A Triumph!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rogerebert.suntimes.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/20080907/FILMFESTIVALS03/809079996" target="_blank"&gt;http://rogerebert.sun...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Broadcast's Toronto Film Festival review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IXaBrXJ7MqM&amp;amp;feature=related" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Imdb reviews -  &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1010048/usercomments" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** PLEASE REMEMBER TO BOOK YOUR FREE TICKETS HERE FIRST BEFORE RSVPing on meetup.com **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rsvp.foxsearchlight.com/RSVPSystem/screenings.php?MoviesId=62" target="_blank"&gt;http://rsvp.foxsearch...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scroll down to November 20th date, select AMC Loewes Boston Common&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that if you don’t RSVP on the Fox Searchlight website, you will not be able get in. If it says SOLD OUT, do not show up at the theater hoping to get in, because you won’t. And even if you do RSVP on their website, it does not guarantee a seat. They overbook these screenings to ensure a packed house. Promotional screenings are on a first-come, first-served basis and not guaranteed seating. Seating is limited to theater capacity. My advice is to show up at least 30-45 mins early, to ensure you get a seat.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the front row with a meetup sign after the movie</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225556959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Screening - Slumdog Millionaire at AMC Boston Common!</name><id>9071882</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227225600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9071882/</event_url></item>