<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Union St</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.205990</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wompatuck State Park</name><city>Hingham</city><id>3234632</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.850258</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the South Shore, Hike, Bike &amp;amp; Social Club Meetup Group and the South Shore Walkabouts as we walk a 3-4 mile loop in Wompatuck State Park. The loop should take about 1.5 hours depending on our pace. &amp;nbsp;(We'll base that on the group's fitness and comfort level.) &amp;nbsp;We may hike some trails as well, all of which are Beginner-Friendly. &amp;nbsp;This will be the Walkabouts' first time at Wompatuck State Park and we are looking forward to exploring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located just a 35-minute drive from downtown Boston, Wompatuck State Park offers 262 wooded campsites (140 of them with electricity), 12 miles of paved bicycle trails, and many miles of wooded bridle paths and hiking trails. &amp;nbsp;One of the most notable features of the Park is Mt. Blue Spring which is a popular source of fresh drinking water. Visitors can help themselves for free. The park is named for an Indian chief the local colonists knew as Josiah Wompatuck. In 1665, Chief Wompatuck deeded the park and the surrounding land to the English settlers. During WWII the park was used as an ammunition depot by the US military.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended&lt;/em&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water/sports drink&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sturdy shoes (although terrain will be flat)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hat or Visor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunglasses&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunscreen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Suggested&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bug Spray&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snacks (fruit/granola bars, etc.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekday Morning Walk @ Wompatuck State Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monday, April 16th @ 9:30am&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wompatuck State Park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Union Street (no #)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hingham, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone: 781-749-7160&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/womp.htm"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/womp.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: Map in parking lot nearest the Visitor's Center. &amp;nbsp;Restrooms and trail maps are available at the Visitor's Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela &amp;amp; Kathy (Walkabouts)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: At&amp;nbsp;least&amp;nbsp;3 Yes RSVPs 24 hours in advance.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Attendance is unlimited. &amp;nbsp;(Angela and Kathy will walk alone if there are no other takers.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Welcome! &amp;nbsp;1 adult per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Late Arrivals&lt;/em&gt;: We will wait 5-10 minutes for late arrivals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Please finalize your RSVP by&amp;nbsp;8pm on Sunday, April 15th.&amp;nbsp; Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our No-Show policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Heavy rains will cancel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We will walk if it is overcast or there is a slight drizzle.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please plan to bring a lightweight jacket with a hood just in case.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(We will do my best to notify everyone if this event is cancelled by 8am on the day of the walk.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain Date:&amp;nbsp;Wednesday, April 18th @ 9:30am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview&lt;/em&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Wompatuck Stae Park is located near Hingham on Boston's South Shore.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the South and Cape Cod&lt;/em&gt;: Rte 3 North to Exit 14 and the interscetion with Rte. 228. FollowRte. 228 North approximately 5 miles to Free Street on the right. Turn right onto FreeSt. one mile to the park entrance on the right. Continue straight through the park andyou will see the visitor center on the right. Park in parking lot there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the North&lt;/em&gt;: Follow Rte. 3 South to exit 14 and and the intersection with Rte. 228. Follow Rte. 228North approximately 5 miles to the intersection with Free St. on the right. Turn rightonto Free St. and follow it one mile to the Park entrance on the right. Continue straightthrough the park and you will see the visitor center on the right. Park in parking lot there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Map in parking lot nearest the Visitor's Center.  Restrooms and trail maps are available at the Visitor's Center.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334663065000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334332993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Morning Walk @ Wompatuck State Park</name><id>60437572</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334583000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/60437572/</event_url></item>