<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Railroad Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06426</zip><lat>41.351620</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(860) 767-0103</phone><name>Essex Steam Train Station</name><city>Essex</city><id>388273</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.405980</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You will be swept away by the hiss of steam, the blast of the whistle, and the clickety-clack of the tracks. From the exciting &amp;quot;All Aboard&amp;quot; to the engineer checking the locomotive before the run, you will experience an authentic journey back to the days of steam. In the Autumn, the colors of New England are an unforgettable sight. The Steam Train fits right in with the cider, falling leaves, and cool snap in the air that makes autumn in New England so special. We travel northward from Essex Station, through the scenic towns of Deep River and Chester. You will see pristine meadows, picturesque farms, a millpond with waterfall, and several bridges over rivers and creeks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next we'll board a riverboat for a relaxing and informative ride up the beautiful Connecticut River, from Deep River to East Haddam. You will see more of the natural wonders that make the Connecticut River special - coves and inlets, islets and deep water, each home to fish, fowl, and river vegetation. You can also get a glimpse of man-made wonders - bridges, ferries, and river-front homes. Highlights include the historic Goodspeed Opera House and Gillette Castle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can all meet at the Station and purchase our tickets individually.  I'll wait by the ticket booth betwwen 11:45 and 12:05.  I'll be wearing an orange, red and green scarf so you can recognize me.  The trip does sell out, they recommend to be there 45 minutes early - the train leaves at 12:30, so don't be late!  The total trip is about 2 1/2 hours.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From Interstate 95 North and South &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 69 (Route 9 North) &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 North to Exit 3 (Essex) &lt;br /&gt;At the end of the ramp, take a left &lt;br /&gt;Valley Railroad is approximately 1/8 mile on the left (across from the Sunoco Station) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From Route 9 South &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 South to Exit 3 (Essex) &lt;br /&gt;At the end of the ramp, take a right &lt;br /&gt;Valley Railroad is on the left (across from the Sunoco Station) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions From Route 9 North &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 North to Exit 3 (Essex) &lt;br /&gt;At the end of the ramp, take a left &lt;br /&gt;Valley Railroad is approximately 1/8 mile on the left (across from the Sunoco Station) &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192663334000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>BBW/BHM and their Admirers.</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BigAttractions</urlname><id>667139</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Big Attractions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191259857000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>All Aboard!  Fall Foliage Trip aboard the Essex Steam Train and Riverboat</name><id>6464318</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192290300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigAttractions/events/6464318/</event_url></item>