<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>144 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01301</zip><lat>42.587477</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-773-9567</phone><name>Green Fields Market</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>767380</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.606092</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.nosmokewithoutfire.co.uk/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;The Elephant in the Room&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2008 Documentary Takes a Look at the 9/11 Truth Movement&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br /&gt;September 10, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Documentary Takes a Look at the 9/11 Truth Movement&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the anniversary of the attacks of September 11th, British filmmaker Dean Puckett releases &amp;quot;The Elephant in the Room,&amp;quot; a new award-winning film documenting his journey into the 9/11 Truth Movement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles September 10, 2008 -- On the anniversary of the attacks of September 11th, British filmmaker Dean Puckett releases &amp;quot;The Elephant in the Room,&amp;quot; a new award-winning film documenting his journey into the 9/11 Truth Movement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Movement can best be described as a group of citizen activists from around the world who don't believe the U.S. government's explanation of what happened on September 11th. While there are a growing number of law enforcement personnel, pilots, architects, engineers, and scientists joining the ranks, they have been called everything from 'patriots' to 'conspiracy theorists' - with some right wing talk show hosts going so far as to call them 'jihadists.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But In the documentary, &amp;quot;The Elephant in the Room&amp;quot;, the viewer is introduced to folks who aren't as dangerous as some would believe. They just happen to be average citizens asking some very simple questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film features interviews with numerous 9/11 Truth activists including Former Georgia Congresswoman Cynthia McKinney (who is currently running for President) and William Rodriguez, a janitor of 20 years at the World Trade Center, who testified that he heard and felt explosions in his building before it was hit by a plane. Also in the film is Richard Gage, a San Francisco based architect with experience in steel framed, high-rise buildings. He claims that the WTC towers could not have come down without help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The filmmaker also travels to New York City to meet 9/11 first responders who are suffering from various life-threatening illnesses due to breathing the toxic dust at Ground Zero. Few people realize that when the buildings came down, the cement was turned into dust resembling talcum powder. Rescue dogs died within days and now the responders are meeting the same fate, but with little help from the government.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the Best Documentary at the 2008 London Independent Film Festival, &amp;quot;The Elephant in the Room&amp;quot; is now available on DVD at www.nosmokewithoutfire.co.uk/buy.htm. What's the best part? The filmmaker is giving the public permission to make as many copies as they like to distribute freely to family and friends. For more information or to watch it online for FREE log on to the film's official website at www.nosmokewithoutfire.co.uk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Filmmaker: Dean Puckett has directed over seven short films, produced two independent feature films and worked on several commercial and charity projects. For the award-winning feature length documentary 'The Elephant in the Room', he wore many hats as the film's director, producer, editor and cameraman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All media inquiries should contact Dead Dean Films at (+44) 7709 443 794 or dean@nosmokewithoutfire.co.uk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distributed by Good Karma Productions goodkarma@goodkarmapr.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussions follow film screening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost to use screening room is $20&lt;br /&gt;recommended $2 per person to cover rent and promotion for event..&lt;br /&gt;and help spread the word.. see link for &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/270/files/"&gt;FILES&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to download a flier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional information and resources, see Flyby News&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1014738186,11057,"&gt;Bush and 9/11 Investigative Reports, looking into the unanswered questions.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>upstairs in meeting room</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232409708000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227380516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Elephant in the Room - film and discussion</name><id>9213191</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229639400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/9213191/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/f/global_6395535.jpeg</photo_url></item>