<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In April we'll meet on the last Wednesday of the month at our favorite hangout, Chaibo in Fitchburg. Chill out on Chaibo's comfy couches and enjoy a latte, smoothie, Panini or dessert (Try their gelato. Yum!) as we discuss &lt;em&gt;The Comedians&lt;/em&gt; by Graham Greene. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Below is a description of the book by an Amazon reviewer. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;The novel opens on a cruise ship steaming toward Haiti. We meet a diverse group of characters who are revealed as they play a game of cards on board ship.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Brown, the primary character and narrator is returning to Haiti to reclaim a hotel he inherited and through his eyes we see the political changes occurring in the country and are made aware of the ominous threat of the Tonton Macoute secret police that hangs over the entire story adding dramatic tension.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Jones, his fellow passenger is revealed to be a con-man who gets by on his ability to make others laugh (one of the comedians) . Smith a failed presidential candidate from the US is naively seeking to establish a vegetarian center in Haiti seemingly oblivious to the turmoil all around him.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Brown's romance with the wife of a diplomat provides a subplot that mirrors the theme that everyone is deceiving someone. The comedians all prove to be actors playing on a stage filled with political violence and the ever present threat of more to come.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;This was a very engaging novel and if not Greene's most well known book it may be one of his best. I enjoyed it and highly recommend it for it's memorable characters and stunning evocation of a country approaching chaos.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335450418000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333114575000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - The Comedians by Graham Greene</name><id>58518952</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335394800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/58518952/</event_url></item>