<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Bela Fleck will be in attendance at our July 9th preview screening which will be held at 7:00 pm in Movie House II.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;THROW DOWN YOUR HEART&lt;/u&gt; follows American banjo virtuoso Bela Fleck on his journey to Africa to explore the roots of the banjo and record an album. Bela's boundary-breaking musical adventure takes him to Uganda, Tanzania, The Gambia and Mali, and provides a glimpse of the beauty and complexity of Africa. Using his banjo, Bela transcends barriers of language and culture, finding common ground and forging connections with musicians from very different backgrounds. In his trailblazing 30-year career, Béla has brought the instrument into jazz, pop, classical, and world music settings, and won eight Grammys along the way (not to mention the 20 nominations, in more distinct categories than anyone else, ever).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Sascha Paladino, documentary w/ Bela Fleck 1h37m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.throwdownyourheart.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Bela Flek TDYH official site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the New York Times Critic's Pick Review:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gentle, upbeat documentary “Throw Down Your Heart” chronicles the African pilgrimage of the American banjo virtuoso Béla Fleck in search of the origins of his chosen instrument, which he sheepishly admits is “associated with a white Southern stereotype.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At every stop on a journey that takes him from Uganda to Tanzania to Gambia and finally to Mali, Mr. Fleck plays and records with gifted local musicians. Early in the film, a Ugandan villager insists that the common perception of Africa as a continent ravaged by war and disease is “just a very small bit of what Africa is,” and “Throw Down Your Heart” sets out to prove him right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meetup at Panera Bread before the film for a chance to get a quick bite and conversation.  Look for the MEETUP sign posted at a table, preferably outside.  We'll probably go into the theater at 6:40.  If you miss us at Panera, look for the rowdy group of talkative folks sitting near the front of the balcony.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Bela Fleck in attendance, there is a possibility that this event will sell-out.  I encourage you to purchase your tickets ahead of time at &lt;a href="http://coolidge.org/showtimes" target="_blank"&gt;Coolidge Tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at a fun, music filled event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be at Panera Bread starting at 5:45 at a  table with a Meetup Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245935718000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THROW DOWN YOUR HEART w/BELA FLECK</name><id>10733058</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247180400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10733058/</event_url></item>