<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Warren Ave, Route 3a</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.958435</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Plymouth Long Beach</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>582379</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.667259</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hike to the tip of Plymouth Beach and then return via the bay side of the beach. We will stop for a snack at the end of the beach and admire the great views of Plymouth Harbor, Duxbury Bay, Saquish,  Gurnet Point and Bug Light.   Bring binoculars if you are interested in bird watching as the peninsula is a bird haven and is one of Mass Audubon's Important Bird Areas.  Although this is not a birding walk, if anyone has special expertise in this area, they are welcome to share their knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully we will get a good sunset over Plymouth Harbor on the way back. &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring a headlamp or flashlight as we will be finishing up in the dark walking back on Ryder Way. Sorry no dogs allowed on this walk, as the town has prohibited them on the outer half of the beach during nesting season, leash or no leash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared to walk in loose sand at certain ponts of the walk. The hike will be 5+ miles and casually paced with many photo opportunities. Low tide is at 7:08PM and sunset at 7:59.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are restroom facilities at Sandy's snack bar in the beach parking area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Drive to the far end of the Parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Vickstrom</member_name><member_id>11406046</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cj Dunn</member_name><member_id>11633479</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344088949000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343264345000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Plymouth Beach Sunset Walk</name><id>74924952</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344031200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/74924952/</event_url></item>