<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Great Path</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.762304</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Manchester Community College</name><city>Manchester</city><id>965187</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.566981</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is one of the BEST events CT has to offer! CT NOFA - Growing Together Since 1982! KEYNOTE!!!! Join us in celebrating our 30th Annual Winter Conference with keynote international bestselling author Jeffrey M. Smith. Mr. Smith is the leading spokesperson on the health dangers of Genetically Modified Organisms (GMOs). He documents how the world&amp;#146;s most powerful Ag biotech companies bluff and mislead critics, and put the health of society at risk. His first book, &amp;#147;Seeds of Deception&amp;#148; became the world&amp;#146;s best-selling and #1 rated book on GMOs. His second book, &amp;#147;Genetic Roulette&amp;#148; is the authoritative work that presents irrefutable evidence that GMOs are harmful. Jeffrey will be speaking on the Politics of GMOs and what may be the #1 food and health issue in the U.S. today. His nonGMO campaign has been highly successful&amp;#150;now at the tipping point&amp;#150;where the GMO industry could begin to collapse. Please save the date and join us at Manchester Community College for this important event. REGISTRATION NOFA Members $50 Non-Members $60 Students/Seniors $35 NEW - Introductory membership - $15 per year. For first time members, you'll get our newsletter, Farm &amp;amp; Food Guide, event notices and discounts, without the quarterly The Natural Farmer. Join now and take the member discount for the Winter Conference. A printer-friendly pregistration form is available here. Online registration is available here. Beginning Farmer scholarship information available here. WORKSHOPS INCLUDE Organic Seed vs. Monsanto: The Lawsuit Challenging Patents on Seed - Attorney Daniel Ravicher, NYC Certified Organic Nutrient Dense Small Fruit - Julie Rawson &amp;amp; Jack Kitteredge, Many Hands Organic Farm, MA Wild Bees and Pollination - Dr. Kim Stoner of CT Ag Experiment Station Root Cellars &amp;amp; Food Storage &amp;#150; Chris Chaisson, Whole Farm Services, VT Public Act 490 - Joan Nichols, CT Farm Bureau Nitrogen Management on Farms &amp;#150; Tom Morris, UConn Plant Scientist Science and Principles of Soil Microbiology &amp;#150; Joe Magazzi, Green Earth Agriculture Pasture Raised Laying Hens - Brianne Casadei, Exec. Director Terra Firma Farm Better Choices in Rx, Cosmetics, Household Products &amp;#150; Valerie Cookson-Botto Raising Garlic &amp;#150; Farmer Wayne Hansen, Wayne's Organic Gardens Honey Bees &amp;#150; Marina Marchese, Red Bee Honey Growing Nuts in Connecticut - Dr. Sandra Anagnostakis, CT Agricultural Exp. Station Mushroom Growing on a Small Scale - Carol Brzozowy &amp;amp; Jim Peppin, Maggie's Farm Biotech Threats to Organic Agriculture - Ed Stockman, Summit Farm Animal Welfare Approved Certification - Brigid Sweeney, Animal Welfare Approved The Dynamic History of the Connecticut Forest - Jeffrey Ward, CT Agricultural Exp. Station Collards &amp;amp; Other Cold Weather Greens for Health &amp;amp; Flavor - Chef John Turenne, Farmer Wayne Hansen and Naturopathic Physician Leigh White Winter Farmers&amp;#146; Markets Are Hot! - Winter Caplanson, Coventry Regional Farmers&amp;#146; Market Worm Composting Simplified - Nick Mancini, Organic Gardening Simplified Co-ops Build a Better World: Co-operatives and Food Security - Erbin Crowell, Neighboring Food Co-op Association How You Can Easily Grow Fresh Greens All Winter - David Zemelsky, Starlight Gardens Climate Change In Connecticut: What Can We Expect and Do - Jennifer Pagach, CT Department of Energy and Environmental Protection Raising Dairy Goats and Making Cheese - Paul Trubey, Beltane Farm Soil Management Techniques - Bryan O'Hara, Tobacco Road Farm Food as Medicine - Dr. Leigh White, Natural Family Health, LLC Surviving on an Acre - Wyatt Whiteman, 1760 Farm House, LLC Transition Movement Workshops: First: Transition Success Stories - Tina Clarke &amp;amp; Terry Halwes Second: Permaculture and Transition - Cynthia Rabinowitz &amp;amp; Joan Spear Third: Transition: Lighting the Fire for Action - Coleen Spurlock Lead in Soils &amp;#150; Concerns and Corrections - Dawn Pettinelli, UConn Soil Nutrient Analysis Laboratory Edible School Gardens - Dan Levinson, Green Village Initiative (GVI) Can I Eat This? Fermented Foods - Discussion and Preparation - Jane Maher Brewing your Own Organic Beer - Michael Stefanowicz Regenerative Hillside Farming &amp;amp; Gardening - Keith Zaltzberg Websites as a Marketing Tool For Farms - Patty &amp;amp; Erick Taylor, Devon Point Farm CSA Crop Planning - Dina Brewster, The Hickories and more to come...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330818208000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330352386000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT NOFA's 30th Annual Winter Conference</name><id>54002202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330781400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/54002202/</event_url></item>