<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The show time is 6:45 and it is showing upstairs.   So let's meet up at 6:15.  I will be upstairs near the coffee concession area, near the escalators.  There are tables there and I will try to snag one, if not I will be standing in the area.  I will have on a badge, so those who are new to the group can find me.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are running late and miss the group before the show, you can catch us after.  We usually hang outside the theater after the show for a bit and discuss the movie....as well as decide if the group wants to go out afterwards and where.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is called &amp;quot;The Kingdom&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Chris Cooper, Danny Huston, Jamie Foxx, Jason Bateman, Jennifer Garner, Jeremy Piven, Richard Jenkins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thekingdommovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thekingdom...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Academy Award® winner Jamie Foxx leads an all-star ensemble in a timely thriller that tracks a powder-keg criminal investigation shared by two cultures chasing a deadly enemy ready to strike again in &amp;quot;The Kingdom.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When a terrorist bomb detonates inside a Western housing compound in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, an international incident is ignited. While diplomats slowly debate equations of territorialism, FBI Special Agent Ronald Fleury (Foxx) quickly assembles an elite team (Oscar® winner Chris Cooper and Golden Globe winners Jennifer Garner and Jason Bateman) and negotiates a secret five-day trip into Saudi Arabia to locate the madman behind the bombing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upon landing in the desert kingdom, however, Fleury and his team discover Saudi authorities suspicious and unwelcoming of American interlopers into what they consider a local matter. Hamstrung by protocol?and with the clock ticking on their five days?the FBI agents find their expertise worthless without the trust of their Saudi counterparts, who want to locate the terrorist in their homeland on their own terms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fleury?s crew finds a like-minded partner in Saudi Colonel Al-Ghazi (Ashraf Barhoum), who helps them navigate royal politics and unlock the secrets of the crime scene and the workings of an extremist cell bent on further destruction. With these unlikely allies sharing a propulsive commitment to crack the case, the team is led to the killer's front door in a blistering do-or-die confrontation. Now in a fight for their own lives, strangers united by one mission won't stop until justice is found in &amp;quot;The Kingdom.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update with specific meetup times when the actual movie times become available.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191736715000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188510681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Kingdom</name><id>6271666</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191104100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6271666/</event_url></item>