<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1455 Westminster Street</address_1><state>RI</state><lat>41.816502</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-273-4375</phone><name>Loie Fuller's</name><city>Providence</city><id>1173236</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.433616</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;This week's location is: Loie Fuller's on the West Side/Armory District&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Loie Fuller's is a charming, warm &amp;amp; intimate restaurant beautifully decorated in the Art Nouveau style with murals, woodwork and a mosaic floor making you think you're in Paris instead of the West Side. Its truly stunning, and of course I spent a few minutes up close to the murals to examine the painting technique. They are known for their wine selection, AND have Lindeman's Framboise on tap! The food is also excellent and the Moules Frites (mussels &amp;amp; fries) is a special on Mondays - and its &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; good! There is plenty of parking in their lot and also on the street. The parking lot is much bigger since the old diner that was taking up half of it has moved to its new home up the street and will be opening shortly! New and exciting changes are happening to that area of Westminster St.! So if you've been wanting to go or haven't ever been, here's your chance! So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the scarf or hat in the picture, but we're not hard to find!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360765303000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360000660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Loie Fuller's on the West Side!</name><id>102966492</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360623600000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/102966492/</event_url></item>