<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Market Talk by Fred Sears&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is our regular forum for market discussion. The talk starts with a market prediction by the speaker. The speaker then makes a short case for the prediction - about 10 minutes. The audience participation of this 30 minute talk should be 20 minutes. The discussion is lively; insights come from around the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Long time members of Boston IBD know and love Fred Sears. He started attending meetings back at Buddha's Delite and delivered a regular talk every month until October 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fred Sears is a 4 Star (AFTER 5.75% load, 1.5% management fee) Morningstar rated Mutual Fund Manager. FYI stars are earned after 3 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has made more than 75 worldwide television appearances – CNBC – interviewed by Maria Bartiromo, Tyler Matheson, Dylan Ratigan, Bloomberg Television, TechTv, Fox Television – interviewed twice by Neil Cavuto, Reuters Televison, quoted and or interviewed in the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, Investor’s Business Daily, The Street.com, New York Post, Kiplingers, plus frequent radio appearances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Feature Talk: Valuation of ETFs by Harlan Rieur&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At a previous meeting there was a debate about the Direxion 3X funds and why they behave as they do.  The answer lies in their valuation.  Harlan has studied ETFs and has some answers, not only on the 3X funds, but also the doubles and maybe some others.  Harlan's talks are always inciteful and well researched.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Tips, Tricks and Techniques by Jeff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If time permits, we will have a &amp;quot;sharing&amp;quot; session.  Bring your ideas on great websites, blogs, newsletters, books, trading techniques, money management, etc.    Please present your idea as concisely as possible, as we will try to get through as many as possible.  Keep your idea to 2 to 5 minutes.  If it is online, Jeff will &amp;quot;drive&amp;quot; to the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The agenda: &lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;7:15 Market Talk by Fred Sears &lt;br /&gt;7:50 Break &lt;br /&gt;8:10 Stockpicks by Chris&lt;br /&gt;8:40 Feature Talk: Valuation of Double and Triple ETFs, Harlan Rieur&lt;br /&gt;9:40 Tips, Tricks &amp;amp; Techniques by Jeff (if time allows)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING Announcement:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Tiger Meeting of the Tiger Financial Network meets during the hour from 5:30 PM to 6:50 PM. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; to see the full announcement. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com. The meeting is the same room as the 7:00 meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt; &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to Jeff Orrik at orrik@comcast.net &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to identify people who evidence expertise in particular interests we have virtual trading. &lt;br /&gt;To join in our virtual trading, go to this link for instructions and signup links:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/browse_thread/thread/ff5e030eb15a6c7c" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250035280000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>74</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245929074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Group July Meetup</name><id>10732642</id><headcount>74</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248303600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/10732642/</event_url></item>