<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>449 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373295</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Public Library Main Branch</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6816032</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111115</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The True Cost of Energy: Coal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Film and Panel Discussion&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

With a film screening of "The Last Mountain" &lt;br /&gt;

Wednesday, May 9, 2012, 5pm to 8:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

Cambridge Public Library, 449 Broadway Cambridge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Join us for the must-see film!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join the discussion and learn about of the true cost of energy derived from coal.  The evening will include a showing of the documentary “The Last Mountain” and film short “The Cost of Power.” The evening will feature a panel discussion regarding the impact of coal energy from a health, human rights and environmental perspective. There will be exhibits and ways to get involved! This is a free event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Last Mountain&lt;/strong&gt;: The fight for the last great mountain in America's Appalachian heartland pits the mining giant that wants to explode it to extract the coal within, against the community fighting to preserve the mountain and build a wind farm on its ridges instead. Delves into the health, environmental, and economic impacts of coal, while also looking at some of our energy alternatives. Produced by Eric Grunebaum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cost of Power&lt;/strong&gt;: Details the effects of two open-pit mines operating in Colombia, owned by multinational conglomerates. The documentary illustrates the forced displacement of several communities that existed before the mine was built. The company bulldozed over homes, schools and farms, causing massive property damage and the loss of many villagers’ livelihood. Produced by Avi Chomsky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panelists include: Avi Chomsky, Prof. Salem State U., Co-Editor, The People Behind the Coal on Colombian miners Pat Gozemba, Prof. Salem State U., organizer in efforts to close the Salem coal plantDrew Grande, Massachusetts Sierra Club Beyond Coal Organizer Eric Grunebaum, Producer, “The Last Mountain”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVPs encouraged! &lt;a href="http://t.co/9XQIkjbI"&gt;http://t.co/9XQIkjbI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Sierra-Club/events/61760542/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Sierra-Club/events/61760542/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Auditorium (lower level)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mass Sierra</member_name><member_id>3278292</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336654840000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Environmental Activists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Sierra-Club</urlname><id>229402</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Sierra Club Environmental Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335195154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The True Cost of Energy - Film and Discussion</name><id>61760542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336597200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Sierra-Club/events/61760542/</event_url></item>