<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ski House</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03812</zip><lat>44.081680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>872006</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.231277</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>UPDATE: This event is filling up fast, RSVP will be cut off on Dec 26th or earlier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking to combine New Years fun with skiing?  Come up to North Conway NH from Dec 30th to Jan 2nd. The Wedeln Ski house is only 5 minutes from Cranmore mountain and less than 20 from Wildcat Attitash and Black. The Wedeln Ski House is only $20 a night per person - check out &lt;a href="http://www.wedeln.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wedeln.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The house is ski hostel style with 2 bunkbeds per room, bring your own sheets, blankets, clean up after your self type of place. Its a cool atmosphere with a lot of skiers and riders hanging out in the bar room or in front of the fire. Yes plenty of fun activities for New Years, more details when we get closer to the event. The house is always 21+ only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wedeln Ski House has a commercial style kitchen, dining room, cable TV, 6 Full baths (+ 3 half). By New Years we should be around 60 people - don't worry the house has 78 beds in 19 bedroom, oh yeah, its pretty big. The Wedeln Ski Club is a not-for-profit with all $ put back into the house to cover expenses. If I confirm you for the weekend I will send your directions, the house is tucked up against National Forest land right along the town border of North Conway and Bartlett.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294117377000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292279639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Years at wedeln Ski House</name><id>15724533</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293753600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/15724533/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/7/global_11666887.jpeg</photo_url></item>