<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Garden Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381539</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics (CfA)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1343951</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.128653</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event takes place at 7:30 p.m. on Thursday, October 7, at Phillips Auditorium, 60 Garden Street, Cambridge. Doors open at 7:00 p.m., but &lt;b&gt;get there early . . . even before 6:45 p.m.&lt;/b&gt; Seating is first-come, first-served for the main lecture room and admission is free. The overflow crowd sits in a separate screening room. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If weather permits, rooftop stargazing through telescopes will follow the presentation. Dress for stargazing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free parking is available to everyone after 5 p.m. (Ignore the &amp;quot;staff only&amp;quot; signs.) Drive up to the back, up the hill. The presentation is up the stairs that are opposite the observatory-in-a-box. Mass Ave buses (to points in Arlington and North Cambridge) originate in Harvard Square on the Red Line and travel along Massachusetts Avenue, which is about a 10-minute walk from the auditorium. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information and directions, go to &lt;a href="http://www.cfa.harvard.edu/events/public_events.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cfa.harvard.edu/events/public_events.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cfa.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or call 617.495.7461.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A line forms early for this event. No need to cut in line because we will meet inside the auditorium: go to the back left of the seats. The overflow crowd goes into a separate screening room, so everyone gets in to see the presentation. Even if we don't sit together, we will meet in the courtyard after the lecture and before we go up on the roof. At this point, we can collect everyone from the lecture hall and the overflow viewing room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the CfA: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Event&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, October 7, 2010, 7:30 pm: &amp;quot;Fall Sky Viewing,&amp;quot; David Aguilar, CfA &lt;br /&gt;Fall is one of the best times to view the changing skies. The familiar summer constellations like Cygnus the Swan and Scorpius give way to the arrival of Andromeda, Taurus the Bull and Orion the Hunter. Join us tonight as we highlight these easy to find constellations and the marvelous deep sky objects hidden among them. Then, let's go out and observe with our telescopes!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a meetup sign. Sit in back left of hall, then meet in courtyard after lecture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286647386000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286054160000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harvard-Smithsonian Observatory: Lecture and Stargazing Open to the Public</name><id>14977103</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286491500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14977103/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/1/global_17076769.jpeg</photo_url></item>