<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Tickets for the 7:30 show are sold out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well it took them long enough to release this movie!  I read the book so long ago and have probably forgotten so much of it that the movie will have a lot of surprises for me.   I did love the books and the movies have been pretty good so far, which means I have high hopes that this one will be good too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be at the theater before 6:30 PM.  The movie is going to be showing downstairs which means things will be very crazy.   I will wait near the ropes by the concession stand for a bit, but I plan on getting in line as soon as they let me.  So come find me in the line.   The actual film time is 7:30, but unlike with other films, going in for seats a half hour before the movie will not work.  If we stand around waiting, by the time we get in theater all the seats will be taken.  Once we have our seats, we can take turns visiting the concession stand and/or restroom while others guard our seats.  I will have a meetup badge on and a meetup sign.  I also have a bright blue purse that is kinda hard to miss.  I strongly advise buying your tickets in advance for this film.   Tickets are on sale on Fandango right now.  Please update your rsvp's with the message that you've got a ticket after you buy one, so I know you are coming.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: November 19, 2010 (3D/2D theaters and IMAX 3D) &lt;br /&gt;Studio: Warner Bros. Pictures &lt;br /&gt;Director: David Yates &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Steve Kloves &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Daniel Radcliffe, Rupert Grint, Emma Watson, Ralph Fiennes, Bill Nighy, John Hurt, Rhys Ifans, Helena Bonham Carter, Robbie Coltrane, Imelda Staunton, Jason Isaacs, Miranda Richardson, Warwick Davis, Alan Rickman, Maggie Smith, Brendan Gleeson, Ciaran Hinds, Timothy Spall, David Thewlis, Julie Walters, Tom Felton, Bonnie Wright, Jamie Campbell Bower, Richard Griffiths, Matthew Lewis, Evanna Lynch, Fiona Shaw, Helen McCrory, David O'Hara, Natalia Tena &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Adventure, Fantasy &lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://harrypotter.warnerbros.com/harrypotterandthedeathlyhallows/" target="_blank"&gt;http://harrypotter.wa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Part 1 begins as Harry, Ron and Hermione set out on their perilous mission to track down and destroy the secret to Voldemort's immortality and destruction—the Horcruxes. On their own, without the guidance of their professors or the protection of Professor Dumbledore, the three friends must now rely on one another more than ever. But there are Dark Forces in their midst that threaten to tear them apart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meanwhile, the wizarding world has become a dangerous place for all enemies of the Dark Lord. The long-feared war has begun and Voldemort's Death Eaters seize control of the Ministry of Magic and even Hogwarts, terrorizing and arresting anyone who might oppose them. But the one prize they still seek is the one most valuable to Voldemort: Harry Potter. The Chosen One has become the hunted one as the Death Eaters search for Harry with orders to bring him to Voldemort... alive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harry's only hope is to find the Horcruxes before Voldemort finds him. But as he searches for clues, he uncovers an old and almost forgotten tale—the legend of the Deathly Hallows. And if the legend turns out to be true, it could give Voldemort the ultimate power he seeks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Little does Harry know that his future has already been decided by his past when, on that fateful day, he became &amp;quot;the Boy Who Lived.&amp;quot; No longer just a boy, Harry Potter is drawing ever closer to the task for which he has been preparing since the day he first stepped into Hogwarts: the ultimate battle with Voldemort. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Movie Group Badge and have a Meetup Sign.  If the movie is showing upstairs I will grab a table at the top of the escalator, if it is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825907000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285767700000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows - Part 1</name><id>14936892</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290295800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/14936892/</event_url></item>