<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi to All!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been called away for this date, and Mike Sexton has agreed to be the Host for the August 4 meeting.  He will present to the group about Financial Destination, a terrific tool for credit repair and identity protection.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investors, networkers and those looking to improve their financial standing...Financial Destination, Inc. (FDI) is a 5 year old, multi-million dollar, debt free, full service financial solution company based right outside of Boston, MA.   FDI's systems are addressing the 4 major areas of concern for you, your family &amp;amp; friends, your clients and potential clients.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;            1.  Debt and Finances &lt;br /&gt;            2.  Restoring or rebuilding their credit and protecting their identities &lt;br /&gt;            3.  The Rising Cost of health care&lt;br /&gt;            4.  Creating  strong, passive Residual Income and generational wealth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone of you can use these services in conjunction with what you are doing in your own lives because EVERYONE needs this stuff in this recession and we have regular information sessions explaining what we do.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Come on August 4th to hear all about FDI and learn to take care of the 4 major areas of concern for everyone you know! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be time set aside as well for vital networking and exchange of real estate ideas and information.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now that the passage of the FHA stimulus package - just passed yesterday by the House, the Senate needs to pass the amended version now in play, and the Bush administration has given it support- and its implementation is imminent, there will be relief for about 1/2 million homeowners facing possible foreclosure.  That is about 20% of all the property owners who are likely to face the possibility of foreclosure over the next 2 years.  The new program does not remove the foreclosure problem, but it goes a ways toward relieving some of the pressure.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set the day aside- August 4,  7-9 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that our regular first Monday will fall on Labor Day in September, so the next meeting will not take place until October!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warmest regards,&lt;br /&gt;Annie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come in and go down the stairs to our meeting room on the lower level.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218318079000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Experienced investors and newbies.  We all can learn from one another.</why><group><who>New Normal RE Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>GreaterBostonREIClub</urlname><id>320990</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Real Estate Investing Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215475638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GBREI Club Guest Host</name><id>8295119</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217890800000</time><rsvp_limit>99</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/GreaterBostonREIClub/events/8295119/</event_url></item>