<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374401</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-903-7371</phone><name>Private Location #2</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>832579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121895</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>How would you like to suddenly start experiencing more pleasure every time you have an orgasm?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Here's what this is all about.  My friend Sheri Winston (who happens to be a master sex teacher) agreed to come up from New York to teach you some of her best-kept secrets to having (and providing) the longest, strongest orgasms you ever dared to experience.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Whether you're single right now or in a relationship, you're going to love what Sheri has to share with you, and here's why.  If you're single, you'll radiate the kind of sexual confidence that is magnetically attractive out in the dating world.  And if you're in a relationship, you can start having more powerful and fulfilling sexual experiences as soon as you come home from class!&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This is a “clothes on, hands off” class for both men and women.  No matter what your level of experience, Sheri will help you take your sex life to new heights.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&lt;br /&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sheri's proven method for expanding arousal (both yours and your partners).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to have longer, stronger, mind-blowing orgasms (and how to trigger those orgasms in your partner).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A simple method for lasting longer in bed that works every time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both men and women can learn how to have orgasms that last longer.  Most men have 15-30 second climaxes.  Most women, 30-45 seconds.  After this class, both men and women will be able to double, triple, or quadruple the duration, starting that same night!  (And hey, women love a man who takes his time!)&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  Please plan on arriving by 3:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members.  We start promptly at 3:30 and go until 5:30 (with a break in the middle).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to 35 people due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, April 11th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal networking.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your love life whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329108758000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270512480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Orgasmic Abundance:  How To Have The Best Sex Humanly Possible</name><id>13097099</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271014200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/13097099/</event_url></item>