<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Thanks to those who showed up for our July discussion on the ethical implications of Darwinism, which had people arguing about whether a definite human nature exists and how quickly it evolves, perhaps under cultural pressure.  We didn't agree on any particular ethical implication of Darwinism, except the fact that if we're naturalists then ethical norms obviously derive from human nature and culture. There are no external foundations or moral benchmarks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For our next meeting, I thought the following question posed by philosopher Shaun Nichols in a recent paper (url below) might provide food for thought:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If people came to believe in determinism, would this lead to major changes in our everyday lives? Should it lead to major changes?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In particular, Nichols asks if moral anger is still justified (p 12), and if so, on what grounds? It's an interesting paper, so check it out and see what you think. Let's try to focus on moral anger, but of course feel free to raise your own favorite ideas about how things might change if determinism were widely accepted.  This seems to me one of the major implications of naturalism: that some things might indeed change were people to accept it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://dingo.sbs.arizona.edu/~snichols/Papers/AfterIncompatibilism3r.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://dingo.sbs.ariz...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP, and I hope you can make it.  Any ideas for future meetings most welcome (can include discussions, outings, movies, etc).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;best,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ps: Red Line is sometimes over air-conditioned, so dress accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187318183000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184026331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Can determinists justify moral anger?</name><id>5998189</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187046000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/5998189/</event_url></item>