<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>USNH</name><city>Hamden</city><id>180814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Humanist Association of Connecticut's main meeting for March will feature a return visit by CCSU's &lt;a href="http://www.physics.ccsu.edu/Larsen/alliance.html" target="_blank"&gt;Professor Ken Feder&lt;/a&gt;, Ph.D., author of &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0874849713/humanistassoc-20" target="_blank"&gt;Frauds, Myths, and Mysteries: Science and Pseudoscience in Archaeology&lt;/a&gt;. This year Ken will talk about a mysterious short-lived village in Northwest Connecticut, the Lighthouse Community of Barkhamsted. &lt;br /&gt;According to the legend of the Barkhamsted ?Lighthouse,? the community?s first inhabitants were a wealthy white woman and an Indian man who had married against her father?s wishes and then fled. According to a newspaper article which appeared late in 1854, the destitute village was inhabited by a group of Indians, the descendants of African slaves, and poor whites.  From 1986 to 1993, Ken directed a research project focusing on the Lighthouse community, combining documentary and archaeological analysis. The results indicate how the Lighthouse evolved from a community of iso-lated outcasts to one connected to a world economic system and how, ultimately, it became the stuff of legend. The results of this research formed the basis of &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1559342552/humanistassoc-20" target="_blank"&gt;A Village of Outcasts: Historical Archaeology and Documentary Research at the Lighthouse Site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a Q&amp;amp;A session after the presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start with coffee and conversation at 7:30 PM.  Professor Feder's talk will follow brief announcements at 8:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(It is not necessary to RSVP for this event; I'm listing it as a meetup so that you can get e-mail reminders from meetup.com)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Siddall</member_name><member_id>1140632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541114000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173371982000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halfway between a wood-pile and a log fence: Life at the Lighthouse, Barkhamsted</name><id>5549354</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174347000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/5549354/</event_url></item>