<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>ROute 2</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.366783</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Castle Trail Trailhead</name><city>Randolph</city><id>3982712</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.314148</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lets hike to Mt. Jefferson up the Castle Trail along Castellated Ridge and descend Castle Ravine Trail and Israel Ridge Path.This is a 10 mile,very strenuous hike with a lot of exposure and some rock scrambling required.Wet weather will cancel the trip&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trailhead is located US 2, 3 miles west of the Appalachia parking lot and 4.2 miles east of the junction of US 2 and NH 115.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Booktime is about 7 1/2 hours.We hope to be faster&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As meetup organizers, our primary function is social. We are getting people together for this trip. We are not functioning as guides or protectors. The risk of injury due to accident or overuse will be significant. While we attempt to head off many problems that we can see and anticipate - hiking for extended hours and hiking in the dark at average speeds better than 2 mph will definitely pose significant risks. Any attempts on our parts to increase the comfort and safety of the group should not lead you to believe that we are taking responsibility for your safety or that there will not be substantial risk involved. Our underlying assumption is that if you come on this trip, you are a responsible adult who will use good judgement and that you have the skills and ability complete this hike as safely as possible, and that we are all equally responsible for its success, but individually responsible for our own safety and knowing our own limits. This hike has inherent risks due to the nature of the trail and the speed with which we will hike it. Ultimately your safety and your assessment of whether the risks are worth it is up to you. If you have any uncertainty about the advisability of completing this trip from a medical standpoint - please consult a physician.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==========================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ad364c"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback with bike racks</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fred W-R</member_name><member_id>7507974</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343695645000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343099322000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt.Jefferson via the Castles</name><id>74640022</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343565000000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/74640022/</event_url></item>