<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Walk-In Registration</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Turning the Key:  Financing Deals with an IRA/401k&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us in November for our monthly networking and education event, Turning the Key, with industry expert, Mike Hurney.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know that you can use not just your own IRA or 401k, but other peoples IRAs and 401ks to finance your investments? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike Hurney will be teaching us how we can buy real estate, notes and businesses in our IRA to supercharge the investment making it either Tax Free or Tax Deferred. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He'll also cover how to use our 401k money on something WE DO have influence over, such as Foreclosures, Short Sales and Private Lending. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not only a source of funds for us to use on our own deals, but a huge source of money from Investors eager to increase their returns far beyond meager bank CDs and fluctuating Stock Market returns. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He'll also show us the latest method to establish our own Health Savings Account. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike Hurney is a Successful Real Estate Investor who lives on the North Shore of Boston. He's not only a landlord, but he also rehabs and flips properties to sell. In addition, he is also the Director of Entrust New England, LLC, a company that handles Self Directed IRAs, which is what Mike personally uses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/6/" target="_blank"&gt;Pre-Register for Turning the Key&lt;/a&gt; and save $5.00!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3372062</member_name><member_id>3372062</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542312000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191542696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turning the Key: Financing Deals with IRA/401k</name><id>6490849</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193958000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/6490849/</event_url></item>