<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Meadow Brook Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.889378</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Carver Public Library</name><city>Carver</city><id>2456541</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.768898</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This seminar is open to the public and de-signed to illustrate how international poli-cies impact the environment and local landuse laws. Through a vast network of un-elected counsels and committees, initiativeslike Agenda 21, the Wildlands Project, &amp;amp;Smart Growth threaten our local control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

GUEST SPEAKERS &lt;br /&gt;

Dave Kopacz Sr.— Dave is a municipalConservation Agent, Chair of the Conserva-tion Commission &amp;amp; Chair of his Open Space&amp;amp; Recreational Committee. Dave will sharehis experiences with regional planningcommissions relentlessly instituting un-proven global schemes in our local land &amp;amp;environmental regulations. He’ll also ex-plain the hidden role of Land Trusts &amp;amp; en-vironmental activists and how “consensus”and “Visioning” have replace standard par-liamentary procedures in building fraudu-lent public approval.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hal Shurtleff — Hal is the North East Re-gional Director for the John Birch Society.Hal has been touring the area educatingcommunities on the UN’s program knownas the International Counsel on Local Envi-ronmental Initiatives (ICLEI), now called“Local Governments for Sustainability” todisguise its origin. Hal will describe exactlywhy this NGO formed and what its goal is.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350610276000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349282697000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Agenda 21: HOW REGIONALIZATION &amp; FOREIGN POLICY KILLS ECONOMIES &amp; LOCAL CONTROL</name><id>85314482</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350599400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/85314482/</event_url></item>