<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;You've got to respect the HFA for putting together some great themes. On this night they monkey-around a bit with two shorts and a Buster Keaton film, The Cameraman. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight we bring two short gems to the big screen. When we watched Monkey Tale, we knew we had to share this bicycle safety film with our friends out there in the dark. Next up, monkeys do grammar in Monkey See, Monkey Do: Verbs. In The Cameraman, a monkey effects the vast world of monkey cinema, even as he yields the spotlight to his more famous, human pal Buster Keaton.  HFA description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a review of the Buster Keaton film: &lt;a href="http://www.slantmagazine.com/film/film_review.asp?ID=1368" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.slantmagaz...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Screening afterward is the pre-Hays Production Code &amp;quot;Tarzan and His Mate&amp;quot;.  I think we'll pass on this one since it would make for too late of a night- but if enough people are interested .... I would have preferred  Woody Allen's Bananas as the second feature. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway, after The Cameraman Tom will be holding a Meet-Up sign near the front row and then its off to discuss at a local restaurant. And yes this restaurant does serve fried bananas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187050087000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185234263000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HFA Monkeys Around- 2 Shorts and a Silent Comedy</name><id>6066795</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186873200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6066795/</event_url></item>