<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On Saturdays in May we will be holding outdoor volleyball QK doubles series. These are friendship tournament event meetups that are reverse coed doubles matches played in a King-Queen format, meaning that you will be playing with and against different people during pool play. Top players after pool play will compete in a playoff format.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If few women sign up, then the format converts to men's height, King of the Beach format.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This is a friendship tournament format, meaning call your own faults, as there are no referees.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The organizers for these events will be Matt BenDaniel and Brian Lee.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be using the ruleset listed in the first post on the following: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/messages/boards/thread/8548572?thread=8548572" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/messages/boards/thread/8548572?thread=8548572&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We understand that not everyone has a car. The tournament organizer can help you get a carpool ride to/from the event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Transportation&lt;/strong&gt;: The 8:30 a.m. MBTA Newburyport/Rockport Commuter Train from North Station to Lynn Station is only a 19-minute ride, then a 6-block (15 minute) walk to Nahant Beach. MBTA buses which go there include: 439, 441, 442, 448, 449, 426, 429, 431, 435, 436, 455, and 456. Use &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com&lt;/a&gt; click on "Get directions" and "By public transit" and travel to "Lynn Commuter Rail". The location for directions to is "42.455619,-70.93634". Easy search: Click on the following link and change the starting location (A)  &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/GN2zn" class="linkified"&gt;http://goo.gl/GN2zn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;There are public restroom facilities at the beach.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The events will start at 9 AM and will likely last at least until the early afternoon (~2 PM). If you would like to play in this event you must commit to staying at least through the end of pool play. Remember to bring snacks/food and water/beverages, as this event will involve a significant amount of volleyball play.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is intended for players with experience playing reverse coed doubles format. To &lt;strong&gt;sign up&lt;/strong&gt; for one or more of these events, please send an email to Matt using the following link on meetup: &lt;a href="http://volleyball.meetup.com/122/message/?recipientId=1878223" class="linkified"&gt;http://volleyball.meetup.com/122/message/?recipientId=1878223&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;In the email, provide the following information:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Name&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Gender&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Event date(s) that you would like to sign up for&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Outdoor rating (AA/A/BB/B), if you have one; otherwise, short description of reverse coed doubles experience&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Confirm that you have read the ruleset at the link above and that you agree to play by those rules.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Confirm that you can commit to play from 9 AM to 2 PM.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Signup partner name (if you have a signup partner)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Preferably, each player in a signup pair should send an email.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;For this event we will aim to have player numbers in a multiple of four so that there are no sitouts for players. Preference is given to AA/A/BB players who sign up in male/female pairs, although some single signups will be allowed. Note that sending an email does not guarantee a spot to play; spots are only guaranteed if you are assigned a Yes RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt BenDaniel</member_name><member_id>1878223</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338165982000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332710975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advanced Outdoor (Sand) QK RevCoed Doubles Volleyball</name><id>57816472</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338037200000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/57816472/</event_url></item>