<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Runtime: ~1hr 30min. | PG-13 violence, terror and disturbing images

Director: Matt Reeves

Starring: Michael Stahl-David, Mike Vogel, Lizzy Caplan, Jessica Lucas, Odette Yustman, T.J. Miller

Genres: Sci-Fi Disaster Film, Monster Film, Science Fiction

Description: Five young New Yorkers throw their friend a going-away party the night that a monster the size of a skyscraper descends upon the city. Told from the point of view of their video camera, the film is a document of their attempt to survive the most surreal, horrifying event of their lives. 

Review: 
1. (read this w/a whole bag of salt) &lt;a href="http://www.aintitcool.com/node/35236" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.aintitcool.com/node/35236&lt;/a&gt;
2. &lt;a href="http://www.darkhorizons.com/reviews/cloverfield.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.darkhorizons.com/reviews/cloverfield.php&lt;/a&gt;

Trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/trailers/paramount/cloverfield/hd" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.apple.com/trailers/paramount/cloverfield/hd&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/ufYF0f-zMgY&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

Notes: Please do not RSVP YES if you do not intend to come. Yes is not a MAYBE. If you can't figure out what your going to do in the future, please do not burden us with that. Please buy your tix AHEAD of time! I'm going to watch this regardless of people coming, but it will more fun with people.

If it's downstairs, I'll be right behind the corded rope after ticket stubs have been ripped in front of the popcorn counter. If it's upstairs, I'll try to grab one of the tables in front of the coffee house near the large monumental windows.

I'll be there a few minutes before 7:30PM and plan to enter cinema to by 7:45PM SHARP. The movie begins @8PM. Make sure you come early because it will be SOLD OUT and will be PACKED!</description><how_to_find_us>I"ll be wearing my trademark green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in front as usual. After the film ends, I'll be waiting right in front of the big screen near the exits. Pls wait for us.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206381649000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><why>We won't bite. Love to have discussions about the films after movie ends. The group often goes out afterwards and socialize.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196579735000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cloverfield</name><id>6840319</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200702600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6840319/</event_url></item>