<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are hiking up the 3,491-ft. Mt. Greylock, the tallest peak in Massachusets. The path we'll hike will be a looping hike of about 9 miles in length and with a roughly 2,248 ft. altitude gain. Overall, the hike should be no more than 6 hrs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would be starting in Greylock Glen on the east side of the mountain, following the Bellows Pipe Trail and connect to the Appalachian Trail (AT) to the peak. We will lunch and take in the views at the peak. From the peak, we head south on the AT, then take Gould trail back to Greylock Glen. Both on the way up and the way down we will see waterfalls. Greylock Glen will have bathroom facilities and there are bathroom faciliities at the peak too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No cotton is acceptable for this hike. Hiking boots required. Hiking poles are advised. Please dress in layers and bring plenty of water and food containing protein and carbohydrates. The wind at the summit could be strong and the temperature could be much less, up to 15 degrees cooler than at the base. Make sure to have a windbreaker or hiking coat to keep warm at the summit. We will hike at a moderate pace with small breaks when folks need them. The trail will be steep.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because the trail can be agressive at times, I am not going to allow dogs on the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to approximate meetup location at parking area at end of Gould Rd. (299 Gould Rd., Adams, MA):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Adams&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=299+Gould+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=01220-1057&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.62884&amp;amp;longitude=-73.147359&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt. Greylock State Park:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(413) 499-4262&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/mtGreylock/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/Mt.Grey-Summer.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greylock Glen Map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/GlenMap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1272323209000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271215350000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike up Mt. Greylock in Adams MA</name><id>13177386</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272114000000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13177386/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/a/global_5697370.jpeg</photo_url></item>