<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Salem Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.260864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Public Library</name><city>Worcester</city><id>5671092</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.800133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Images for the show have been selected, and it was NOT easy to do!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can go to this web site and see the final choices:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/scotterb#104332" class="linkified"&gt;http://gallery.me.com/scotterb#104332&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you were in the last show, "Nature in Our City" please come pick up your work this day as well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your image appears there you need to make a print and have it matted to a 16x24 outside dimensions. Please use a white mat... read on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This meeting will be for the members who are participating in the upcoming show&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;"People of Worcester County&lt;/span&gt;" &lt;span&gt;to get details, learn about framing the prints, and discuss the opening of the show.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Participants; We will have your frame ready for you at this meeting. We will show you how to take your matted print and put it in the frame with the glass and how to seal it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;What you need to bring to the meeting: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please bring with you a Flat Head Screw Driver!! Everyone will need one to put the frames together.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Your Print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Your Mat - cut to fit your print.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Your Print should be mounted to a back board and attached to your mat. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, Bring your matted print. This means you need to have a mat cut! The frame size is 16x24 so the over all mat must fit into a 16x24 frame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We suggest making your prints 11x14 or 9x12 so they can have a nice white boarder around the image. We will not be accepting images that are not matted. SO no flush mounted images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VERY IMPORTANT:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IF YOUR IMAGE IS SQUARE---- PLEASE MAKE THE MAT VERTICAL!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bayda Asbridge, Mike McCool, and Sharon Freed- This means you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Email me if you have a question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want everyone to sign the mats in the lower right corner of the mat's opening- if you do not know what this means -don't sign it- just bring it to the meeting and we will discuss where to sign the mat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need a back board to mount the print to and then place the mat over it. This back board should be the exact same size as the mat you had cut for your print. I recommend it be the same material as the mat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simply tell whomever is cutting the mats that they need to fit into a 16x24 frame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check in with me about the title of your print and the price you want to sell it for before you leave this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to our next show...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Banx Room on the Left as you enter the library.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330993791000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329162752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framing Party for the City Hall Gallery: People of Worcester</name><id>52201612</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330281000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/52201612/</event_url></item>