<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Salisbury Beach </address_2><address_1>4 Ocean Front North </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.843468</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 462 5888</phone><name>Tupelo Music hall </name><city>Salisbury </city><id>1046594</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.816143</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets go check out 3 great comedian's right on Salisbury Beach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11/19/09 UPDATE: I am changing the Meetup time to 7:00.  That way we can get in a little earlier get settled and get a bite to eat right there at the hall.  Tupelo Music Hall offers a Menu of Appetizers, Soups, Salads and Sandwiches. You can check out their menu on their site.  If you are not able to make it for the 7:00 time just show up anytime after that we will be at the tables!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;11/15 UPDATE: Tickets for tables 31 &amp;amp; 32 are sold out, and the rest of the tables are filling up quickly!!  If you have RSVP'd &lt;b&gt;YES&lt;/b&gt; on the site here and you haven’t gotten your ticket yet then you will need to find another table to sit at.  Seeing that there are only 6 seats at each table some of us are sitting at table 38.  As of now I see that there are openings at tables 39 which is close to us and 40 which is sort of near us, so if you want to go and don’t mind meeting new people at another table come on out and join us for this event!  I have been inside of this venue and it is a really nice inside.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you buy your ticket and update this site please put what table you are sitting at so if some one else gets a ticket at your same table then you will see a familiar face at that table, or bring a friend w/you so you already know someone at the table. Or if you don’t want to sit at a table with out members from the group, please change your RSVP here on the site, so then someone else can take the opportunity to go to this event. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10/29 UPDATE: Here’s the information to reserve your seat for this event, so far we have 8 people (between the 3 groups) I have picked tables 31 &amp;amp; 32 for us to sit at, all the tables fit 6 people, these tables are &lt;b&gt;NOT&lt;/b&gt; reserved for us until we have ordered/filled the tables, anyone can (outside of the group) make reservations at these tables.  If you wait to long to order your ticket these table(s) may be filled, and you may not be sitting w/the rest of us from the meetup group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;Ordering is easy and only takes a few minutes, so order your seat soon so we are sure to sit together!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note to order your ticket on the site there is a $3.00 Service fee (for each ticket purchased) and a print and a mailing ticket cost to use this service. For The Will Call Tickets choice - The box-office will generally be open 2 hours before every performance. For Will Call tickets, you will need to pick up your physical tickets before the show. “Will Call” is a term that means you will pick-up your tickets at the box office the night of the show. “Will Call” does not mean that we will call you. Will Call tickets will not be sent to you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticketing fee:&lt;br /&gt;Every ticket sold has a fee associated with it. The fee is over-and-above the posted ticket price. All fees are clearly outlined in our ticketing system. Fees are charged for each ticket, regardless of how the ticket was purchased.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To reserve your seat go to &lt;a href="http://tickets.tupelohallsalisbury.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://tickets.tupelo...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Click on schedule, &lt;br /&gt;Scroll down to Tupelo Night of Comedy, &lt;br /&gt;Click Buy Now,&lt;br /&gt;Click on either one of those tables and you will see a grid of 6 yellow framed empty squares (as seats are being reserved at that table you will see that the squares get highlighted &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;red&lt;/span&gt; which means that seat is sold).&lt;br /&gt;To reserve your seat click on one of those squares that is not highlighted red.&lt;br /&gt;Then all you have to do is put in your credit card billing information and you are all set.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to change your RSVP on the site to “reserved seat” so we know to look for you on the night of the event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;KENNEY ROGERSON&lt;/b&gt; For the past 20 years Kenney Rogerson has been one of the top comedians in the region &amp;amp; among the best comics nation wide. Frequently referred to as “the funniest man you’ve never heard of,” Rogerson combines a brilliant wit &amp;amp; an understated sarcasm that has led him to the nation’s top clubs as well as appearances on the late night talk shows including Letterman, and Conan O’Brien as well as appearances on Comedy Central, Showtime’s “A Pair of Jokers,” Evening at the Improv, and MTV. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BRAD MASTRANGELO&lt;/b&gt; Since Brad Mastrangelo was first pushed on the stage from a dare in 1991, he has been in constant demand from Boston to Las Vegas. The ultimate story teller, Brad's unique routine never fails to hit home with audiences of all ages and backgrounds. The following rave reviews attest to his talent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JON RINEMAN&lt;/b&gt; Jon Rineman is a 25-year-old writer and comedian based in Boston, MA. Jon also rom Emerson College, where he was head writer for the 24th Annual EVVY Awards, &amp;amp; was published in the Improper Bostonian’s 2005 Humor Issue. After graduating, he began selling jokes to a top-rated 11:30 p.m. TV show. Jon is a regular at The Comedy Studio in Harvard Square, where he tackles such hot-button issues as Google Maps and Where’s Waldo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are only: $15.00 all seats (please note you are responsible for ordering and getting your own ticket).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup location: We will meet at table 31 &amp;amp; 32&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Time: TBD, show starts at 8:00.  &lt;br /&gt;To Purchase tickets: 978-462-5888 or check out their website &lt;a href="http://www.tupelohallsalisbury.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tupelohall...&lt;/a&gt; to see the other options for getting your tickets.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Tupelo Music Hall Salisbury is literally on the beach in Salisbury, MA&lt;br /&gt;From 95 or 495, take the Salisbury exit, route 110. Follow 110 East through town. You will come to a set of lights near Simmies garage, take a left. At the second set of lights, take a right onto Beach Rd. Follow Beach Rd until you reach the beach center. At that stop sign, take a left onto North End Blvd and then a right onto Driftway. We are in “The Pavilion” building that is on the beach.   &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Parking is free.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At 7:00 we will be at the entrance, if later than that then we will be at the table(s).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259021680000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252769853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tupelo Night of Comedy </name><id>11354158</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258848000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11354158/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/b/a/global_10653770.jpeg</photo_url></item>