<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>106 Prospect Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.367650</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)354-5287 or (857)417-4021c</phone><name>Out Of The Blue Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>839245</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101909</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brian Sous&lt;/strong&gt;a is the author of the novel-in-stories Almost Gone and his fiction and poetry has appeared in numerous journals and anthologies. He teaches at Boston College, edits the music and culture online magazine Mule Variations, and plays sweet, sweet guitar in the band Ocean*Transfer.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dan Memmolo&lt;/strong&gt; grew up in the suburbs of Boston, Mass., where he discovered the virtues of a three-chord stomp, a 15-foot jump shot, and the seven dirty words. His book Fist City won the 2011 Holland Prize from Logan House Press and will be published in the latter half of 2012. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

He is also the author of the chapbook Beat Surrender (Main Street Rag) and his poems have appeared in numerous magazines, including Atlanta Review, Gargoyle, New York Quarterly and Southern Poetry Review. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Dan holds degrees from Florida State University and the University of Rhode Island, as well as an MFA in Creative Writing from Virginia Commonwealth University. He lives in Barrington, Rhode Island with his wife and son.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Betsy Retallack&lt;/strong&gt; lives and works in Beverly, Mass teaching music in the public schools. She lives on Poets Hill with her two sons, Kyle and Garth , and her husband Mark. Her day job is teaching classroom music and by night she writes. Her poetry recently appeared in The Best American Poetry 2006 (Scribner) edited by Billy Collins and David Lehman.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365217325000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363724248000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dire Literary Series: Sousa, Memmolo, and Retallack</name><id>110046752</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365206400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/110046752/</event_url></item>