<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>43 Base Lodge Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02777</zip><lat>41.747051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-678-5793</phone><name>Lori's CM Studio</name><city>Swansea</city><id>319115</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183296</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Saturday, November 17, 2007&lt;br /&gt;10:00am ? 4:00pm (Drop by anytime)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start your holiday shopping early and treat yourself at the same time! &lt;br /&gt;All of the latest Creative Memories products will be on display as well as some great gift ideas for those ?hard to buy for? family members and friends.  I will have various albums on display, Open House specials, exclusive Open House gifts, door prizes and refreshments.  AND?ideas and inspiration are guaranteed!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ______________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some of the things I?ll be offering to those who attend the Open House:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An exclusive Open House gift and raffle ticket just for stopping by! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP by Wednesday, November 14th and receive an exclusive Open House Idea Sheet! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A chance to win 4 DOOR PRIZES:&lt;br /&gt;                     Grand Prize: 2008 Season Crop Pass (10 FREE workshops?$100 Value!)&lt;br /&gt;                     First Prize: 7x7 Limited Edition Coverset &lt;br /&gt;                     Second Prize: $25 Gift Certificate  &lt;br /&gt;                     Third Prize:  Mini Journaling Mate Case with 8 Pens &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A bonus raffle ticket for leaving me your completed wish list at the Open House.  Email me your wish list BEFORE the Open House, complete with the names of Santa?s Helpers, and you?ll be included in an exclusive raffle for an Everyday Display Board ($49 Value)!  Free gift-wrapping is offered on all wish list orders! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A coupon for a FREE regular workshop when you bring a friend to the Open House who is new to Creative Memories and/or new to ME! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An exclusive Host Gift and 5 additional raffle tickets for scheduling a Get Together or Catalog Show at the Open House! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Receive 5 additional raffle tickets for submitting a referral list! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join my CM Team and receive a FREE Premiere Album! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purchase $50 in product and receive an EXCLUSIVE Creative Memories Open House Gift with purchase! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discontinued products will be available at a discount (while supplies last)! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE Make-and-Take (while supplies last)!&lt;br /&gt; ______________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark your calendar and RSVP to (508) 678-5793 or chiknsoup7@aol.com TODAY!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are unable to attend, phone and e-mail orders will be accepted Friday, November 16th, thru Sunday, November 18th, and Open House specials will apply!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early for the best selection!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discontinued items and exclusive gifts are only available while supplies last!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cash, Personal Checks, Visa, Master Card and Discover accepted!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gift Certificates and Workshop Certificates Available, too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lori</member_name><member_id>4519990</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542596000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scrapbookers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>scrapbook-1653</urlname><id>559492</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2200012207</group_lon><name>The Swansea Scrapbooking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194972806000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HOLIDAY OPEN HOUSE</name><id>6733641</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195311600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/scrapbook-1653/events/6733641/</event_url></item>