<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Gainsborough St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.341120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jordan Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>668980</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086105</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;Well  to quote Amit, here's another event for the group which is completely different. This will be the first film for our group where the composer will be present. And the film will be screened at Jordan Hall- another first. Also we have a block of 20 seats reserved for the group, on the main floor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A special event about the intersection of music and world events. Encounter Point is a feature documentary film which follows a former Israeli settler, a Palestinian ex-prisoner, a bereaved Israeli mother and a wounded and bereaved Palestinian brother who risk their lives and public standing to promote a nonviolent end to the conflict between Arabs and Jews. Their journeys lead them to the unlikeliest of places to confront hatred within their communities. Afterward, special guest Kareem Roustom, the composer of the award-winning score for the film, will lead a discussion about the film and the making of it by an Israeli/Palestinian/North American/Brazilian production team of young women. Refreshments will be served. Audience Award for Best Documentary at 2006 San Francisco and Montreal Film Festivals; Official Selection at the Tribeca, Dubai and Jerusalem Film Festivals, 2006. Presented by NEC's Intercultural Institute. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete review: &lt;br /&gt;PICK  ENCOUNTER POINT In a corner of the world defined by long-running intransigence, it comes like balm to the soul to meet the Bereaved Families Forum, a fragile but determined association of Israelis and Palestinians whose hearts were softened, not hardened, by losing loved ones in their region?s ongoing conflict. In this fascinating documentary, directors Ronit Avni and Julia Bacha ask what kind of person counters malicious violence with activist conciliation, but offer neither pat answers nor false redemption. Instead they observe the forum?s members, who crisscross the region promoting peace as best they can given the ubiquitous checkpoints, roadblocks, and the reactive vengefulness of their countrymen on both sides. They?re a disparate bunch ? a graduate of an Israeli jail who read Martin Luther King Jr., Mandela and Gandhi while in prison; a former right-wing settler whose daughter was killed while riding in their car; a burly Israeli army veteran whose daughter died in a Tel Aviv suicide bombing; a Bethlehem teacher who lost his own daughter. But they?re united, however temporally, by their commitment to nonviolence, by their fiercely independent minds and their willingness to risk the antagonism of their own compatriots. Encounter Point  is not a sentimental film: Its most piercing moments are about the uphill internal and external struggles of these good people, bound together more by forgiveness than by love. Just how badly these voices of reason are needed grows crystal clear when Roni, the South African?born, leftist mother of a soldier killed by a Palestinian sniper, visits a Jewish settlement and, angered by the more rabid speakers at a meeting, compares their separatism to apartheid. You don?t have to agree with her to be horrified when a settler sitting next to her asks incredulously, ?What?s wrong with that??  LA Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link to the composer's biography: &lt;a href="http://www.layalimusic.com/bio.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.layalimusi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information about the NEC's Intercultural Institute and  their other upcoming events can be found here :  &lt;a href="http://www.newenglandconservatory.edu/worldmusic/events.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newengland...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Needless to say, this should provide for a good group discussion afterward.&lt;br /&gt;And is our custom, Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. Please be aware that when there is a lecturer present at the movie it is sometimes difficult to find our group because it can be more crowded than usual.  So be patient, we'll get everyone together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189724939000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188005058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middle East Doc  Composer Present</name><id>6238700</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189551600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6238700/</event_url></item>