<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christine has a great idea ... Lets do another evening Hike at the Blue hills this Wednesday. A quick hike up and down the red loop that we can easily do in 45 minutes, 30 if we hurry, or an hour if we are walking at a slow pace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can join us ... I'll Be the brunette at the ski lodge parking lot, down by the red loop trail's entrance, in the white vintage, old, audi with my cute puff of a bichon Breezy ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want more fun ... Lets go to the halfway cafe&lt;/b&gt; where we can dine on the patio and Josh will welcome us and our Pups with open arms.  Our pups can be leashed to the outside of the patio on the walkway, if other guests are on the patio ... or if we are the only patio visitors ...  pups and people can relax together.  Best of all Josh will hold tables for us if I can get an idea of who would like to enjoy a drink and a bite after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking for directions to the hike  - Here are the ones I grabbed of bluehillsski.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 South / US-1 South.&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 2B / Milton onto MA-138 North / Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Blue Hills Ski Area is approximately 1 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;From the Cape: Take MA-3 North towards Boston.&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 20 on the left onto I-93 South / US-1 (toward I-95 / Dedham).&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 2B / Milton onto MA-138 North / Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Blue Hills Ski Area is approximately 1 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;From Providence: Take I-95 North (Crossing into Massachusetts).&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 12 towards Boston (I-93 North / US-1 North).&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 2B / Milton onto MA-138 North / Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Blue Hills Ski Area is approximately 1 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To the 1/2 Way cafe&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will go 138 south, toward stoughton&lt;br /&gt;about 1 mile / 1.5 miles we will be at a light with a liquor store on the right&lt;br /&gt;we take this right onto washington st &lt;br /&gt;Follow down about 4 - 5 miles and we are there&lt;br /&gt;Village shop at Cobbs Corner &lt;br /&gt;turn in between starbucks and cvs&lt;br /&gt;and we will be next door to especially for pets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chat soon,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kristan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll Be the brunette at the ski lodge parking lot, down by the red loop trail's enterance, in the white vintage, old, audi with my cute puff of a bichon Breezy ...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristan</member_name><member_id>8717151</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253450315000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dog-hiking</urlname><id>1123750</id><group_lat>42.2299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8899993896</group_lon><name>Dog hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252957985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Evening Hike @ the Blue Hills</name><id>11370510</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253140200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dog-hiking/events/11370510/</event_url></item>