<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374905</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Loeb Drama Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1217786</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123021</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A poignant examination of how war affects the mind of a soldier,  Sophocles&amp;rsquo;s tragedy speaks directly to our times.&amp;nbsp; Second only to  Achilles in greatness and strength, the legendary Greek warrior Ajax  struggles under the weight of psychological and physical injuries,  trying to maintain his dignity, identity, and honor. Director Sarah  Benson brings the voice of the community to this production, exploring  the relationships between soldiers and civilians. I plan to stay for the post-performance Q&amp;amp;A discussion with the actors and then maybe have drinks and appetizers or a late lunch after if there is interest. I will give my cellphone number to the yeses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The American Repertory Theatre in Cambridge has gotten better and  better, and I have season tickets because everything they  are doing this season is fantastic. &lt;strong&gt;PLEASE NOTE: I already have my  ticket, since I have season tickets, so we won't be able to sit together  as a group (unless you decide to buy tickets together), I just wanted  to see if people wanted to join me. There is no group rate. YOU ARE  RESPONSIBLE FOR BUYING YOUR OWN TICKET IN ADVANCE, RSVP-ing here does  not guarantee attendance! Tickets are now on sale. Showtime is 2 p.m. Link to buy tickets: &lt;a href="http://www.americanrepertorytheater.org/events/show/ajax" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.americanrepertorytheater.org/events/show/ajax&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anna</member_name><member_id>404606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298210263000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Classical Greek theater!</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296395583000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ajax by Sophocles at A.R.T. in Cambridge</name><id>16366587</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298140200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/16366587/</event_url></item>