<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Night entrance: 294 Washington St</address_2><address_1>10 Milk St, Suite 632</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356812</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-423-5775</phone><name>Sierra Club Offices</name><city>Boston</city><id>190621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058185</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join Greater Boston Group Leaders and Volunteers for informal socializing at the Chapter Office. Begin implementation of your 2011 Resolution to volunteer with the Sierra Club.  We will share information on volunteer projects you can begin working on and meet the staff and volunteers heading up the Greater Group Transportation, Climate Change, Parks and Recreation, Energy and Clean Coal Campaigns!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 6 pm, we will have a brief program where we'll highlight last year's activities and our plans for 2011.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an incentive to arrive for the program, we'll be raffling off four 2011 Sierra Club Wilderness Calenders and four 2011 Sierra Club Engagement Calenders.  [Plus we have a grab bag from our sponsor which is not an endorsement of either the company or the product but a requirement of its sponsorship of our Meet-up. Please contact Mary Ann! if you have any questions about it.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free event but we will be accepting any money you would like to give towards refreshments.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winter weather advisory- If the subway is running, the event will occur.  You can still call to confirm if you want.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be greeting people and talking at 6pm.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary Ann!</member_name><member_id>618637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295622275000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Environmental Activists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Sierra-Club</urlname><id>229402</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Sierra Club Environmental Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294957450000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Boston Group Winter Warmer and Open House</name><id>16040366</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295559000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Sierra-Club/events/16040366/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/3/global_7614675.jpeg</photo_url></item>