<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Durham</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.130001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UNH</name><city>Durham</city><id>333069</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.980003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>UPDATE: rally and demonstration of support - at 5:30 at the Whittemore Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's show more than we did last time at St. Anselm's College!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: Still looking for debate tickets for Wednesday? You're in luck; just go to &lt;a href="http://www.nhgop.org/reg-tickets-sponsor-code/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhgop.org/...&lt;/a&gt;, and enter sponsor code 018RP3 (along with all of the other required information). You'll be in, at no expense, for the full program--so come on out and clap for Dr. Paul. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NH Debate will be held Sept 5th at the Whittemore Center at UNH. Tickets &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.acteva.com/booking.cfm?bevaID=141395" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.acteva.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get your tickets NOW! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information visit...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhgop.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhgop.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ron Paul will be at the debate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00 pm- 8:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;Pre-Debate Reception featuring prominent political and media personalities&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Doors close to the Whittemore Center (no guests will be admitted after this time)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:oo pm- 10:30 pm First in the Fall Presidential Debate &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those not attending the actual event, we will plan to stage a rally of support for Dr. Paul outside of the event with banners and signs, in the same way we did at the CNN debates. Details will follow as we know more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: We may want some people to go to Young's. Apparently Carl Cameron is going to be broadcasting live from there. Here's the UL story: &lt;a href="http://www.unionleade.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.unionleade...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DEBATE WATCHING PARTY at KELLEY's....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us at Kelley's Row in Dover for a debate party, Wednesday, September 5th. We will be meeting at 8:00 PM to watch the debate and network with fellow Ron Paul supporters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelley's Row is a brick building on the river before you go over the bridge on Central Ave. There is plenty of street parking. There is also a parking lot across the street on 1st Street and past the bridge at TD Bank North. Also parking at the municipal lot, right on Orchard, just past Kelley's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelley's Row &lt;br /&gt;421 Central Ave &lt;br /&gt;Dover, NH 03820&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Whittemore Center to Kelley's Row&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Start out going SOUTHEAST on MAIN ST. toward KENDALL HALL &lt;br /&gt;2) MAIN ST becomes NH-108 &lt;br /&gt;3) Turn RIGHT onto NH-108 N / NH-9 E / WASHINGTON ST. continue to follow NH-108 N / NH-9 E. &lt;br /&gt;4) Turn SLIGHT LEFT onto CENTRAL AVE / NH-108 S / NH-9W &lt;br /&gt;5) Follow CENTRAL AVE and turn RIGHT at 1st set of lights on to MAIN ST &lt;br /&gt;6) Follow loop past SMILEY'S PIZZA at turn left at set of lights back onto CENTRAL AVE &lt;br /&gt;7) End 421 CENTRAL AVE Kelly's Row.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Est. Time: 15 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189200933000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185604461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GOP Debate at UNH and Rally</name><id>6088708</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189027800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6088708/</event_url></item>