<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Harvard Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373570</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Dudley House, Harvard University</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>11868052</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118454</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Because the last one was such a success and well, it's been awhile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations, everyone; we did it! We survived a blizzard named after a cartoon fish. We endured Facebook feeds saturated with blizzard pics, Disney memes, and "SNOMG!" I'd like to think that we're a lot closer now as a city. &lt;br /&gt;

 We've walked out into some strange bleached-white morning without motorcars, a bounty of pristine snow that we would later turn into igloos and retarded snowmen with a little encouragement from our 40oz friends. &lt;br /&gt;

 Our lats are so ridiculously buff with all the shoveling and re-shoveling, and we've added to our collection of chairs (Thanks, street-chair fairy!). The roads were claimed by giddy kids on skis, snowshoes and insane joggers and we transformed greasy pizza boxes into makeshift sleds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But a lot of us were stuck inside for far too long (did anyone NOT watch House of Cards?) and let's face it, we're fucking stir-crazy! Now is the perfect time to get out of our hibernation dens and rock out to sweet tunes and hangout with righteous dudes and dudettes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just like before if you feel inclined then make a short playlist of your favorite blizzard/winter tunes to share with everyone else, or just shit that you like to dance to. BYOB and snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My apartment is much too small to host this type of event but because of my connections at Harvard I'm able to reserve a room large enough to make this awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please vote for a date in the poll below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://doodle.com/btfagca3epd5qpii" class="linkified"&gt;http://doodle.com/btfagca3epd5qpii&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff</member_name><member_id>8416626</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364918351000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>48</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361491600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indie Rock Easter Social</name><id>105769312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364680800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/105769312/</event_url></item>