<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>265 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.361805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-253-5927 </phone><name>MIT Museum </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>777893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097664</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We all know atheists love science. And eating. So partake with us in both for a visit to the MIT Science Museum in lower Central Square followed by a late lunch afterwards. On the menu at the MIT Science Museum- Robots, Gestural Engineering, and the Cell among others! Yum. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the main lobby of the museum at 1130, wander around, and then gather back together at 1 downstairs to go to lunch at a nearby eatery such as The Miracle of Science or the Middle East depending on what the group wants. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;MIT Science Museum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MIT Museum admission cost is $7.50 for adults, and $3.00 for college students with ID, children under 18, and seniors. Free for MIT students/staff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Por favor please update your RSVP if you decide not to come so that other people can fit in/we can have an accurate group reservation, especially since we have to limit the group size to 20 due to the size of the museum. Thanks!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note the time change. We just found out that the museum is free Sundays from 10-12 and as long as people enter the museum before 12, admission is free. Feel free to still come at 12 if this is too short notice for the time change, you will just have to pay admission. Justin or I will be downstairs greeting the group at 1130 and 12 regardless and we will split up, wander, and then meet up at 1 downstairs for lunch. ***&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be waiting in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jess M</member_name><member_id>7718913</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264568214000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263482149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MIT Science Museum Visit</name><id>12318253</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264350600000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/12318253/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>