<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/7/4/event_133425172.jpeg" width="150" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Smart Ass the board game is the ultimate fun trivia game for 2 to 12 players, where everybody plays every turn, the game doesn't labor on for hours, and even if you are a "Dumb Ass", you can win!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smart Ass is an all play game. With every question asked, every player can yell out the answer at any time and as soon as they think they know the answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are four question categories: Who am I? Where am I? What am I? and Hard Ass! The 500 questions are formulated into lots of clues. The clues get easy as the question is being read out, but don't wait too long to answer, as the first person to yell out the right answer, wins the round and moves closer to the Smart Ass. If you yell out the wrong answer, then you are out of that round and have to wait 'till the next question is asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beware of the "Dumb Ass" and "Kick Ass" squares, as penalty awaits!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first person to land on the donkey's butt is declared the "Smart Ass".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smart Ass was created by Rob Elliott, the long time host of Australian Channel Seven's "Wheel of Fortune". So come and enjoy the real Aussie flavor of this inclusive and fun, but still competitive game&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send out my house number the day before the event to those who have RSVPed 'Yes'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nidal</member_name><member_id>8949503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1344394096000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340757202000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Night: Smart Ass</name><id>70891422</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344295800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/70891422/</event_url></item>