<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>40 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.492.1557</phone><name>Algiers Coffee House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669147</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121338</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You're welcome to join us for another Portuguese Table, which will be a fun easy going get together. No pressure to speak completely in Portuguese.  You can become comfortable by just listening then jump in when you're ready to talk. Conversation will continue until 8 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;RSVP EARLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; because seating is limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please PLEASE Please answer the questions, so our reservation is accurate and conversations are balanced. THANK YOU!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Algiers is a quiet, cozy, friendly place with a variety of tasty dishes for carnivores as well as vegetarians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to eat or just drink while we chat.  &lt;br /&gt;Here is the &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/CMSPages/GetFile.aspx?guid=45165708-59fa-48c1-83f4-69d3da6d0887" target="_blank"&gt;Algiers Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There will &lt;span&gt;NOT&lt;/span&gt; be a group bill.   &lt;br /&gt;Our server will write individual bills for which you are expected to pay at the cash register...please be&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometime ago in separate conversations Ramzi and Alvaro suggested we have simple lessons during our Portuguese Table. If there is an interest, we could play a game which can also serve as an ice breaker. Each person has five cards and the object of the game is to be the person with the most cards after five statements have been made, in Portuguese of course. The statement is "I have never...." and then you complete the sentence. For example, "I have never learned how to fly a plane." or "Nunca aprendi como voar um avi&amp;atilde;o." Then those who know how to fly a plane would put a card in the middle of the table. Then the next person will say "I have never...." and so on and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another option suggested by Lucy is to read Brazilian magazines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're not required to take part, you're welcome to have individual conversations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;MBTA:   &lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route. Less than five (5) minute walk from Harvard subway station on the Red Line and the last stop of the #1 and #66 buses on Mass Ave in Harvard Square.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS:   &lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your driving route&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING:   &lt;br /&gt;Very limited parking at meters on Brattle, Dunster and JFK Streets as well as Massachusetts Avenue.   &lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Square Public Parking&lt;/a&gt; for garages and lots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can always get in touch with me through the "Contact Organizer" link on Meetup: &lt;a href="http://portuguese.meetup.com/316/suggestion/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://portuguese.mee" target="_blank"&gt;http://portuguese.mee&lt;/a&gt;...  &lt;br /&gt; or   &lt;br /&gt;email snowrover@yahoo.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservation will be under Tonya/Portuguese Meetup. We'll be seated upstairs at the tables against the back wall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299009789000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295926919000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portuguese Table - Monday  February 28th  6:00 PM</name><id>ckcjqypdblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298934000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/16362456/</event_url></item>