<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Update 11/16: This is fourth and final class in four-part series being run by the AMC at their Boston office located a few blocks from the State House. If you haven't attended the first three classes I would suggest that you contact them (information posted below) before making plans to go. RSVPing YES on this site DOES NOT register you for this class - you still need to contact the AMC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the Random Group has offered an introduction to winter hiking and backpacking program in the past, we will not be offering such a program this year.  As an alternative I would strongly recommend the Winter Hiking and Backpacking Program being offered by the Boston Chapter of the AMC.  I participated in this program years ago and still find myself referring back to the information that I learned. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be coordinating some of our own introductory trips so be sure to watch for the trip postings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This course teaches winter hiking and backpacking. Taught by Boston Chapter AMC leaders, students will have lectures, small group breakout sessions, and hands-on opportunities with winter gear. Topics include heat management and clothing, group hiking techniques, energy management and nutrition, winter travel and snowshoeing, winter safety and injury prevention, above tree-line hiking, non-technical use of ice axe and crampons, weather, camping techniques, equipment, food prep and more. There will be weekend trips throughout the winter offered exclusively or preferentially to participants in this class so you can put your learning in practice.  Plus, this is a great opportunity to meet lots of other people who love the outdoors, and to make new friends.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program runs on four Tuesday nights from 7:00 PM - 9:00 PM. The program takes place at AMC Cabot Auditorium located at 4 Joy Street in Boston, MA. It's near the Park Street T Station, the Massachusetts State House and the Boston Common. Discount parking passes are available for the Boston Common Garage.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program costs $45 for AMC members/$50 non-members w/advance registration (before November 2). At-the-door registration is $50 AMC members/$55 non-members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions contact the Coordinator Brian Glenn (brianjglenn@gmail.com) or the Registrars Dan Westerberg (lefthandblue@gmail.com) or Abby Driscoll (atdriscoll@gmail.com). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hbbostonamc.org/registrationSystem/login.php?event_id=31" target="_blank"&gt;Click this link to go to the AMC Registration Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291344116000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286126615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC's Introduction to Winter Hiking and Backpacking</name><id>14984036</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291161600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/14984036/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/1/global_18435649.jpeg</photo_url></item>