<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Venez vous rechauffer les mains avec une tasse de cafe (ou du the) et discuter avec nous!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: (Look up the street address at &lt;a href="http://maps.yahoo.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.yahoo.com...&lt;/a&gt; to see a map of the location.) Take Route 95 to Market Street (Exit 7) and turn toward Portsmouth (not Newington). Follow Market Street as far as you can go into Market Square (the road follows straight along the port, then curves right to continue into the &amp;quot;square&amp;quot;). When you reach the stop sign at Congress Street, the café (Breaking New Grounds) will be on your far left and a church across and to the right. Turn right onto Congress (one way), and stay in the right driving lane. The first right should have a green Parking sign (Ladd Street, I think); turn right into the back entrance of the Hanover Street garage. Park, then walk back to the café. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anne will try to choose a large area where the group can sit together; look for the Meetup sign sur le table. She has all the administrative stuff for the group and will be able to collect dues for October; merci!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that when you leave the parking garage, you must exit onto Hanover Street (because Ladd Street is one way). Turn right onto Hanover, then left onto Market Street to return toward the Route 95 on ramps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breaking New Grounds is located in Market Square, Portsmouth, on the corner of Market and Congress Streets. On-street parking is limited, but the Hanover Street parking garage is very convenient (1 block from Market Street) and cheap (75 cents/hour). If you're not familiar with this part of Portsmouth, I suggest that you drive by the café first to get your bearings, then park and walk back. (By the way, this is a beautiful part of the area, so if you have time, come early to stroll and shop!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you'd like, bring something to talk about -- pictures, a favorite book, a souvenir. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://maps.yahoo.com/maps_result?addr=16+Market+St&amp;amp;csz=Portsmouth%2C+NH+03801-3704&amp;amp;state=NH&amp;amp;uzip=03801&amp;amp;ds=n&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;desc=&amp;amp;lat=43.077328&amp;amp;lon=-70.757687&amp;amp;mlt=43.077328&amp;amp;mln=-70.757687&amp;amp;zoomin=yes&amp;amp;BFKey=&amp;amp;resize=l&amp;amp;trf=0&amp;amp;mag=1" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.yahoo.com/maps_result?addr=16+Market+St&amp;amp;csz=Portsmouth%2C+NH+03801-3704&amp;amp;state=NH&amp;amp;uzip=03801&amp;amp;ds=n&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;desc=&amp;amp;lat=43.077328&amp;amp;lon=-70.757687&amp;amp;mlt=43.077328&amp;amp;mln=-70.757687&amp;amp;zoomin=yes&amp;amp;BFKey=&amp;amp;resize=l&amp;amp;trf=0&amp;amp;mag=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.yahoo.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam Angulo</member_name><member_id>789593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastNHFrench</urlname><id>63967</id><group_lat>43.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>Seacoast NH French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1128089711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seacoast NH French Language October Meetup #2</name><id>4774151</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1129762800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastNHFrench/events/4774151/</event_url></item>