<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;[ 
&lt;em&gt;If this Meetup fills up,&lt;/em&gt; you can take a chance and come anyway-- early, I might suggest, to sit at a table nearby: &amp;nbsp;typically one or more people do not show up, so you could take their place; or if everyone does come as planned, you might be able to hear all you need to hear from a nearby table ... it could be worth the experiment!]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At all of our recent meetings, a common feeling mentioned has been that of 
&lt;strong&gt;Overwhelm&lt;/strong&gt;: about life being so full ... too full, it sometimes seems! Come learn how to cope with the suffocating or drowning feelings associated with overwhelm- to take control of life once more and head confidently in the direction that we ourselves choose, freed of as much unnecessary baggage as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin Martin will join us again to share insights gleaned from neurolinguistic programming (NLP)- which I have been finding so beneficial, along with many others in our Meetups this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin also&amp;nbsp;will be sharing a new, fantastic strategy called 
&lt;strong&gt;S.O.R.T&lt;/strong&gt; that can be used to help 
&lt;strong&gt;clean up mental clutter,&lt;/strong&gt; which can be the source of 
&lt;strong&gt;Overwhelm&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free also to come share your SUCCESSES in tackling Overwhelm - as well as to raise any other particular clutter-related challenges for which you seek solutions. Feel welcomed to post comments here about topics you would 
&lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; to see addressed in our upcoming meetings, along with information about subject-matter experts you know of who can shed light for us all on the matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-And perhaps come away with a Decluttering Buddy to help you steer into the coming weeks with a more cleared-out living space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;(Please arrive by 6:30 pm&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to order refreshments, ALLOWING EXTRA TIME TO FIND PARKING in or near Central Square. Parking is available ONLY&amp;nbsp;in City Lots 4, 5 , and 6 ("back of Central Sq.") off Norfolk St. &amp;amp; Bishop Allen Dr. -- NOT in the private lot to the left of Harvest Co-op, i.e., off Essex St., which is carefully monitored and ticketed ... meters in the city lots and on the streets around Central Square operate until 6 pm.&amp;nbsp;While no purchase minimum for refreshments is specified by our host venue, participants are encouraged to order something substantive to 
&lt;em&gt;support the business in appreciation&lt;/em&gt; of Management's permission to meet in their space. PLEASE ALSO BE ADVISED: Commercial eating establishments generally cannot permit on-site consumption of refreshments brought from elsewhere, due to liability concerns.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;AGENDA&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Approximate)&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;6:30 pm- Order refreshment or dinner: $2.10 (for coffee) or upward ... PLEASE BE ADVISED: THERE IS OFTEN A WAIT LINE at the counter, so allow some time to order prior to our meeting at 7 pm
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:00 pm- Intro to neurolinguistic programming (NLP)
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:15 pm- Roots of Overwhelm
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:30 pm&amp;ndash; NLP and perhaps other therapeutic technique(s) described
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:45 pm - Demonstration(s) on volunteers, with application to others' volunteered situations
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;8:30 pm- Q&amp;amp;A
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;8:45-9 pm- Wrap-up
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Notepad &amp;amp; pen or other note-taking device, calendar to schedule Action Items (next steps). Dress in layers (e.g., wear a sweater in case the restaurant is cooler than you'd prefer) and comfortably, as Kevin sometimes has us do NLP/EFT physical exercises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;OUR&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;VENUE WISH LIST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We welcome suggestions for alternative Venues&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;especially quieter, preferably free spaces under friendly, fairly flexible management, with ample free parking nearby and public transportation that runs on a frequent schedule until at least 9:30 pm (permitting our participants to linger and converse after meetings). ...OR we might meet outside in a public park (with shelter nearby in case of rain) during warm weather, perhaps over a potluck dinner, since group members have said they especially like to be out in Nature- where we don't have to feel too responsible for how everything looks, and maintenance! (...I also noticed that a Travel Meetup group might meet in a restaurant at Logan Airport- neat idea: such 
&lt;em&gt;relevance!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Might we do something similar?&amp;nbsp; I welcome ideas!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;VIDEO PREVIEWS&amp;nbsp;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Bandler: NLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S. Andreas: Compulsion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: EFT/procrastination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: Tapping&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;RECOMMENDED READING&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Hung by the Tongue: What You Say is What You Get&lt;/em&gt;, by Francis P. Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Biology of Belief: Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter, &amp;amp; Miracles&lt;/em&gt;, by Bruce H. Lipton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Get the Life You Want&lt;/em&gt;, by Richard Bandler&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Richard Bandler's Guide to Trance-formation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;- EXCERPTS viewable in previous Meetup descriptions, e.g., August 1, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;CLARIFICATION FROM KEVIN--&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Misconceptions&amp;nbsp;about hypnosis&amp;nbsp;abound- formed through TV, movies, and staged entertainment. The most prevalent misconception is that hypnosis is a form of mind control - that a hypnotist can make someone rob a bank or do terrible or absurd things. This is absolutely false! A hypnotist cannot make anyone do anything against their values. No one will do anything they would not normally do or that they have not wanted to do. Onstage, a hypnotist provides a 'safe' atmosphere for people to have fun and act on things they may not normally do socially; however, if they have never wanted to do some particular thing, they will not do so under hypnosis. In a clinical offfice session, people under hypnosis do only what they feel safe doing, and no more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hypnotist is only a guide; the person under hypnosis is actually doing the work by following suggestions. That is why we say that all hypnosis is self-hypnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another general misconception is that someone under hypnosis is sleeping. This is far from true: Most people are totally aware of what is happening around them, and can remember everything. Most&amp;nbsp;hypnosis&amp;nbsp;sessions are experienced as deep relaxation - approximating the state of awakening in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;MEETING FEE&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;The $10-per-person meeting fee (payable via PayPal, preferably, or in cash to Judy Stitt at the event&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;before presentation&lt;/em&gt;, please) helps to compensate (1) the presenter for his time, training, and specialized knowledge so generously shared with us, and (2) the organizer(s) for time spent planning, administering, and coordinating events, and interfacing with members as needed, e.g., answering questions, linking with various people and resources - also to defray Meetup.com's charge that is assessed organizers for this Meetup Web site and other resources to serve our group.)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Probably in the corner of the lounge on the lower level directly beneath the stairs. I'll post a small Meetup tent sign to flag our location for participants.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314707878000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312491466000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dealing with Overwhelm- FAST!!</name><id>28291021</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314658800000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/28291021/</event_url></item>