<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I'll be outside by 8:45. You recognize me by my lovely cane. (It doubles as a nerd prod! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/devilish.gif' border='0' alt='devilish' /&gt;) The showing starts at 9:30, and you should get there early.  There is no scheduled dinner, sorry. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NEW TICKET DETAILS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to &lt;a href="http://brattlefilm.org" target="_blank"&gt;brattlefilm.org&lt;/a&gt; to reserve your space! It's listed on the main page under &amp;quot;Coming Soon.&amp;quot; Five dollars per showing, or spend $25 and you'll also walk away with a snazzy T-shirt. Hooked on Who does sell-out, so please, please reserve your tickets now. Brattle has good popcorn, real butter, and beer on tap from Cambridge Brewing Company. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is just night one of a two-night event. I've added the second of the Tom Baker selections on Saturday (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/11279776/"&gt;The Invasion of Time @ 9:30&lt;/a&gt;) There is also an earlier batch of Baker at 2:30 (The Invisible Enemy &amp;amp; K9 &amp;amp; Company), which I will be attending, but not organizing formally. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hooked on Who returns to the Brattle. Come see one of David Tennant's last turns as the Doctor in PLANET OF THE DEAD. Michelle Ryan (Jekyll, Bionic Woman, Merlin) co-stars as the companion of the day. There's a red double-decker bus in a desert, and presumably a threat of death. Any more information would qualify as spoilers, and the Doctor is staunchly in the no spoilers camp. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please include in your RSVP if you are interested in dinner before PLANET OF THE DEAD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On a personal note, this is my very first time as an assistant organizer. Please be gentle with me, my fellow nerds.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KateMcQ</member_name><member_id>6532193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296062823000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251495435000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Doctor Who at the Brattle: Planet of the Dead</name><id>11227352</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252719000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11227352/</event_url></item>