<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for meetup fees</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We are pleased to welcome Samantha Langley-Turnbaugh, soil scientist from of USM's Department of Environmental Science, to discuss the very important issue of using plants to mitigate the problem of lead and heavy metals in soils destined (hopefully) to grow food.  She will discuss her experiences with phytoremediation, give recommendations and refer us to any additional resources we might need.  This is a very important session for anyone working with urban gardens or, in fact, any gardens in the environs of older homes and buildings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Portland Location TBD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 Potluck Supper&lt;br /&gt;7:15-ish Presentation and Discussion&lt;br /&gt;8:45-ish Wrap-up&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our Meetup Event RSVP Guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://permaculture.meetup.com/58/messages/boards/thread/5233158#20208623"&gt;http://permaculture.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)! Please consider bringing your digital camera and posting up a few photos after the event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Samantha Langley-Turnbaugh is Professor and Chair in the Department of Environmental Science at the University of Southern Maine.  She has a B.S. in Forest Engineering from the University of Maine, an M.S. in Soil Science from the University of New Hampshire and a Ph.D. in Forest Soils from University of Wisconsin-Madison.  Dr. Langley-Turnbaugh’s areas of research interest include the role of soils and dust in triggering adult and childhood asthma, the applications of phytoremediation techniques in mitigating lead contamination in urban soils, and the interactions between soil quality and vegetation health in urban and forest ecosystems.  Dr. Langley-Turnbaugh is currently Principle Investigator on an NSF funded project with a mission of increasing the numbers of students with disabilities majoring in science, technology, engineering and mathematics (STEM) disciplines. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237939749000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228494013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Meetup:  Using Plants to Remove Lead from Soils</name><id>9286429</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236724200000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/9286429/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/3/global_255395.jpeg</photo_url></item>