<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This Valentine's Day related hike has a tragic star-crossed love theme. Hear how the Indian Princess Lillinonah, her hand sought by many a man for miles around, met her love in the early 1700's and how because of her deep love she met an untimely death in the area of this hike. We can contemplate love, true love, and those people and circumstances that work against the same. (Or you can just enjoy a hike!) We will be hiking the hillside and cliffs on either side of the Housatonic River at the north end of Lake Lillinonah. We will even hike in the area Lillinonah and her lover may be buried per the story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike will be an easier hike of about 3.65 miles though we may have steep sections to hike up/down for short distances and we will have snow and possibly some ice to deal with. We will have clifftop views of Lake Lillinonah from Lovers Leap and we will cross over the Housatonic river on an abandoned iron bridge built in 1895.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will be divided into three sections. The first loop of about .8 mile we will explore the ruins of the Silex Factory on the Old Factory Trail. The next loop of 1.25 miles on the Waramaug Loop will explore the Indian Spring House ruins as well as get us lakeside views. The third looping/out-and-back hike of about 1.6 miles will take us over the river, to the Lovers Leap cliffs (I'll read the story of Lillinonah here), to ruins of the Tea House, then to the "Castle" ruins, then up to a lookout (in area where Lillanonah and her lover may be buried) and then back to the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Those who wish to go MUST have:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* Backpack - To carry extra layers of clothing, trail food, water, gear  &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots or comfortable winter boots (no sneakers!)  &lt;br /&gt;* Hiking poles (or snowshoe poles)  &lt;br /&gt;* Gators or snowpants - To keep snow out of boots  &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Snowshoes&lt;/span&gt; - Given all the snow this year we&amp;nbsp;will need this  &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet.  &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too.  &lt;br /&gt;* Gloves  &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket  &lt;br /&gt;* Warm hat  &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advised/optional equipment depending on conditions:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;span style="color : #DC143C"&gt;MICROspikes&lt;/span&gt; (or other traction device) -for ice and if low snow amounts (not likely&amp;nbsp;this year)&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food - (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.)  &lt;br /&gt;* Fanny sled - OK, we might have opportunity to use them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meetup will be at 2 PM at the parking area of the State park (see location/directions below). We will hike (with rest stops and sightseeing) about 3 hr. and get back no later than 5 PM to the cars. Then the plan is to head out to eat somewhere if people are interested, otherwise head home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail map:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/loversleap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lovers Leap State Park - more information:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=433316&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8B0000"&gt;Lillinonah's Leap - the story:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.friendsofthelake.org/downloads/lillinonah_leap.20031211.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.friendsoft...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate location/directions to meet at Meetup location&lt;/strong&gt; (around 40 Pumpkin Hill Rd., New Milford, CT):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=New+Milford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=40+Pumpkin+Hill+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06776-4625&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.542727&amp;amp;longitude=-73.409438&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;(approx. Lat=41.542727, Long=-73.409438)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the entrance to the park parking area looks like heading northbound&lt;/strong&gt; (Interesting Google Maps lists this section of road as Still River Dr. instead of Pumpkin Hill Rd.) :  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=40+Pumpkin+Hill+Rd,+new+milford,+ct&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=50.424342,69.433594&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=40+Pumpkin+Hill+Rd,+New+Milford,+Litchfield,+Connecticut+06776&amp;amp;ll=41.542666,-73.409486&amp;amp;spn=0,359.964681&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;layer=c&amp;amp;cbll=41.542611,-73.409577&amp;amp;panoid=0M5R1N8FpJTERtoojbm1lw&amp;amp;cbp=12,36.32,,0,5" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Song of Lillinonah's love - "LOVER'S LEAP (Lillinonah)" words &amp;amp; music by Bob Brophy &amp;amp; Felicia Michael at Blue Yodal Music:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Song to hear: &lt;a href="http://soundclick.com/share?songid=8689718" target="_blank"&gt;http://soundclick.com...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Lyrics: &lt;a href="http://blueyodelmusic.com/LoversLeap.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://blueyodelmusic...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;strong&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/strong&gt; ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297693602000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288186551000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Valentine's Hike at Lovers Leap State Park in New Milford CT</name><id>15245794</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297623600000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15245794/</event_url></item>