<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Rockwell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01225</zip><lat>42.553696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mount Greylock</name><city>Lanesborough</city><id>13583482</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.213158</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Before signing up for this event, please read and understand the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;entire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Write-Up and the Liability Waiver. By signing up for this event you agree to the terms of the waiver.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This hike is limited to well-conditioned hikers with an appropriate level of fitness and prior above-treeline experience. Please do not try this if you are not ready.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elevation Gain:2950 ft Hike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time:5.5 hours (says the Magic Eight Ball)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Difficulty:Strenuous&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail Condition:Well maintained trail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike Type: Loop&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blaze Orange: I'd appreciate it, so YES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the title suggests- I have never done this hike before. Excited yet? Yeah, so am I! When I grow-up, I'm gonna be an explorer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be included in this epic (Jason, I hope you don't mind my usage of your word) you must have hiked with this group a minimum of 5 hikes, have above tree-line experience, proper equipment, and nerves of steel. If you have not hiked at least five, you will get an email from me, asking you to remove yourself from the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Money Brook trail starts gradual and works its way up the deep valley between Greylock and Mt Prospect. The trail passes a beautiful waterfall that is worth diverting from the trail for or so I've read.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proper footwear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High-calorie, snacks and lunch&lt;/strong&gt;. You will be burning a lot of fuel to keep your engine running.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2 liters of water&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emergency whistle&lt;/strong&gt;. Worn outside, in plain view.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Headlamp w/ fresh batteries&lt;/strong&gt;. No hand-held flashlights. An emergency could require a late exit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Safety First!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Trailhead: The trailhead is located on Hopper Road in Williamstown MA. From Route 7 traveling North take a right at the five corners store in South Williamstown. Follow the Green River Road for a few miles and take a right across a bridge at Mt Hope</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liz</member_name><member_id>31266642</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369696257000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368498152000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pre-hike Mt Greylock via Money Brook Trail</name><id>119269202</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369486800000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/119269202/</event_url></item>