<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Audubon St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.311544</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 624-5189</phone><name>The Neighborhood Music School</name><city>New Haven</city><id>853944</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.921895</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey gang, &lt;br /&gt;    Since I'll be at the show tomorrow and Devorah can't make it, we agreed I'll be the contact. Much thanks to Dev for the great posting below. Many of you have heard Alexis play, but if you haven't, or you're new, these performances really are a terrific thing to catch, and I highly recommend them. In addition to the refreshments, we'll also go to Anna Liffey's afterwards, an Irish pub around the corner thats a nice place for food, drinks, and socializing. A few other NHCers who can't make the show will be meeting up with us there. See you tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008 (Its best to just call me if you have questions, since Dev won't be there and Alexis is necessarily very focused on her art.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As part of the faculty recital series at Neighborhood Music School in New Haven, violinist Mark Rike and our very own extremely talented Alexis Zingale on piano, play on the Bach's Brunch series at 12:00 on Sunday, October 18 at the Neighborhood Music School at 100 Audubon St., New Haven, CT 06510.  Not only is the concert free, there are free refreshments too! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entitled &amp;quot;Viennese Classicism&amp;quot;, the program is just under an hour: Beethoven Sonata in G Major, Webern Four Pieces, and Brahms Sonata in G Major.  Mark is an incredible violinist that has played all over the world, and anyone that has come to any of the other recitals or the Obama fundraiser last year can confirm that he is absolutely amazing, and that anything that Alexis is a part of is bound to be wonderful.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256055416000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255352749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NHCer Alexis Zingale, piano and Mark Rike, violin in FREE recital</name><id>11606809</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255881600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/11606809/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/3/global_11188659.jpeg</photo_url></item>