<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>559 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353710</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Paramount Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>7170782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062431</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2011, Norway&lt;/strong&gt; Norwegian director Joachim Trier made his feature debut in 2006 with &lt;em&gt;Reprise&lt;/em&gt;, which received numerous international awards and earned Trier’s selection as one of &lt;em&gt;Variety&lt;/em&gt;'s 10 Directors to Watch at Sundance. &lt;em&gt;Oslo, August 31st&lt;/em&gt;, Trier’s second feature, premiered in Cannes’ Un Certain Regard section last year, took top prize at the Stockholm International Film Festival and was selected for the Film Society of Lincoln Center and the Museum of Modern Art’s 2012 New Directors/New Films festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loosely based on Pierre Drieu La Rochelle's 1931 novel &lt;em&gt;Will O’ the Wisp&lt;/em&gt; (filmed before by Louis Malle as &lt;em&gt;The Fire Within&lt;/em&gt; in 1963), &lt;em&gt;Oslo, August 31st&lt;/em&gt; is a compelling study of loneliness existential crisis that charts a critical day in the life of Anders, a thirty-something heroin addict nearing the end of his drug rehabilitation in the countryside outside Oslo. Given a day’s leave for a job interview in the city, the handsome, intelligent and haunted young man reconnects with friends in a search for answers and the desire to start again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Festival Focus&lt;/strong&gt; is ArtsEmerson's second annual showcase of recent highlights from the international film festival circuit. Last season, the festival premiered films from Greece, Russia, England, Mexico, Romania and China; all were award winners and critic favorites on Best of 2010 polls, however only two (The Arbor and Silent Souls) have as yet received theatrical releases in Boston. The 2012 line-up offers a slate of striking new visions widely identified as the best of 2011, yet only two have been picked up by U.S. distributors: &lt;em&gt;Oslo, August 31&lt;/em&gt;, which may get a Boston release this summer, and &lt;a href="https://artsemerson.org/Online/default.asp?doWork::WScontent::loadArticle=Load&amp;amp;BOparam::WScontent::loadArticle::article_id=808AFA2C-B939-4885-BFCF-4E30F2513EE3"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Neighboring Sounds&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; —a 2012 title and perhaps the most exciting discovery of the bunch, but not necessarily the most likely to find a foothold in the city’s limited landscape for art-film theatrical bookings. We hope you share our curiosity about and commitment to cinema’s future, and invite you to discover the emerging directors of the 21st century at &lt;strong&gt;Festival Focus&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be in the theater with a handmade, authentic, and antique Meetup Sign sitting in the middle of the middle row, probably one of 3 in the theater.  After, let's get a drink at Rock Bottom</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337615157000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336859151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OSLO, AUGUST 31ST</name><id>64547132</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337379300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/64547132/</event_url></item>