<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come join and hangout with other supportive and smart, amateur but dedicated, and passionate  writers, who are seriously determined about trying to write something monumental, and getting it done! This writers support group is a wonderful opportunity to get to know all kinds of brave amateur writers (mostly unpublished) willing to try. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each week, quite a few of us meet in the heart of Beacon Hill at a classic Boston watering hole to discuss/share wonderfully diverse ideas/insights on writing, books, writers and about life if we so choose. I'm here looking to add a few more dedicated and determined amateur writers who are serious about writing/telling a story/creative something worthwhile and will appreciate being a part of a group in which its members aim high and strive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, as I said before, I got the idea for this group while I was living in Manhattan. While in NY I hung out with quite a few graduates from NYU, Northeastern, and Columbia who had started a similar group, in which they (the original members) all challenged themselves/pledged to write something ambitious/monumental and potentially life changing (their first novel). And, the good news was most did finish what they set out to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main purpose of the NY WSG wasn’t to have their work critiqued. Instead, it was about keeping each other going/on track holding each other accountable to the writer’s own self-imposed but ambitious goals and time-lines. It was about aiming high and striving, and getting it done! It was not a lax writers group for the weak at heart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Further, it was about being inspired by your peers and about helping to inspire others to find their own voice and reaching their goals. It was about connecting with people who have a similar passion in life and who may understand you better because they have the same desire inside to tell a story. It was also about forging friendships and a supportive and encouraging environment during the often lonely and difficult creative writing process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is worth mentioning that countless times throughout history many writers who succeeded in finding their own original voice had formed similar support groups of their own long before they became immortalized. Ralph Waldo Emerson, Henry Wadsworth Longfellow, Henry David Thoreau, and occasional guest Charles Dickens made up the original members of the legendary Saturday Club, where they would meet weekly at The Parker House to discuss their ideas and work. Ernest Hemingway had F. Scott Fitzgerald and Gertrude Stein to bounce ideas off of. And, Jack Kerouac had Alan Ginsberg and Neal Cassady. Hanging out in the East Village with fellow writers at the Cedar Tavern, in 1959, “We often wrote poems while listening to the painters argue,” Frank O’Hara recalled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are no prerequisites for joining this group. I don’t care where you went to school. The only thing I care about is that you have a passion or desire to write/express yourself; to find your own original voice; that you are somewhat driven and able to set ambitious yet achievable goals; that your presence in the group is a positive one and that you take the group and all its members seriously and go out of your way to inspire the people around you. I can't stress this enough!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People who will do the best in this group will be supportive amateur writers but who are also driven and ambitious enough to want to set bold goals to challenge themselves to write something monumental, whether it's a book or a very well written short story, poetry or their first screenplay. People who are able to go out of their way to help, encourage and inspire others will do very well here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, writers who are lax and disinterested in setting and achieving monumental goals, or challenging themselves by working hard by writing and striving for something more should not join. Neither should writers who love to write but have no time to write. The also group meets every Tuesday night in Beacon Hill at 7PM. It typically runs for approximately 3 hours. In addition, to setting/achieving your ambitious writing goals, if this time will not work for you or you don't see yourself being able to keep it often, please don't bother. Overly critical/egocentric people will not do well here either.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are still interested in joining this group, the goal is to meet up weekly in Boston, and as often as people would benefit from sharing their thoughts, ideas and their goals/time-lines about what they are writing, about writing in general or, about life or anything else that’s on your mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Current group members are writing everything from novels and short stories and in January some of us will be starting screenplays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in being a part of this writers support group, please email me back. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You will need to RSVP first.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275487665000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Writers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Anonymous-Writers-Wanted</urlname><id>1337150</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Writers Anonymous (Not your typical writers group) Weekly</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274800634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Writers Anonymous (Not your typical writers group) Weekly Weekly Meetup</name><id>bbpdnynjbcb</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275433200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Anonymous-Writers-Wanted/events/13589484/</event_url></item>