<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Keene, NH</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02128</zip><lat>42.380000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Keene High School</name><city>Boston</city><id>558334</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.020000</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The New England Symposium on 9/11:&lt;br /&gt;Family Members and Researchers Speak Out&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, May 17th, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Keene High School, Keene, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission $15 Doors Open at 9:30 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by Monadnock 9/11 Truth Alliance and Student Scholars for 9/11&lt;br /&gt;Truth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New England Symposium on 9/11: Family Members and Researchers Speak Out&lt;br /&gt;continues to blossom. To wit, Michael Springmann, now a member of the&lt;br /&gt;National Whisteblowers Coalition has recently been added to the program and&lt;br /&gt;will be making a short presentation. Springmann, as a CIA veteran in the&lt;br /&gt;Jeddah, Saudia Arabian consulate, has had much to say of the many troubling&lt;br /&gt;anomalies that stem from this consulate, where 11 of the alleged hijackers&lt;br /&gt;received their VISA's into the US.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.monadnock911truthalliance.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.monadnock9...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sst911.org/newsite/events.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sst911.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston911truth.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://boston911truth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.911truth.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.911truth.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Sunjata, star of FX's Rescue Me and tentatively scheduled host of the&lt;br /&gt;New England 9/11 Symposium:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bob McIlvaine, Sr. - McIlvaine lost his son, Bobby McIlvaine, Jr., on 9/11.&lt;br /&gt;Mr. McIlvaine attended every 9/11 Commission hearing and has been a vocal&lt;br /&gt;critic of the official account of 9/11. As a member of September Eleventh&lt;br /&gt;Families for Peaceful Tomorrows, McIlvaine has traveled all over the world&lt;br /&gt;speaking about 9/11, his perspective on the events of that day, and&lt;br /&gt;demanding justice for his son and the other innocents who perished along&lt;br /&gt;with him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Hopsicker - An investigative journalist, author, and documentary film&lt;br /&gt;maker, Hopsicker arrived in Florida two months after 9/11 to look into&lt;br /&gt;activities of the alleged hijackers and their connection to Huffman&lt;br /&gt;Aviation. What he uncovered became the basis for ?Welcome to Terrorland:&lt;br /&gt;Mohamed Atta and the 9/11 Cover Up in Florida.? Hopsicker is still located&lt;br /&gt;in Florida and his up to date research can be found at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.madcowprod.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.madcowprod...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michele Little - Little lost her brother, FDNY Firefighter, David M. Weiss,&lt;br /&gt;on 9/11. Along with 9/11 Family Members Donna Marsh O?Connor and Christina&lt;br /&gt;Kminek, Little called for a real investigation into 9/11 at the National&lt;br /&gt;Press Club on 9/11/06. Michele is also an advocate for the First Responders&lt;br /&gt;of 9/11 and works to raise awareness of the health issues that these heroes&lt;br /&gt;are currently facing. She is also one of the founding members of&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.2ndresponders.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.2ndrespond...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sander Hicks - An author and investigative journalist, Sander delivers the&lt;br /&gt;type of hard-hitting journalism that all journalists should. Hicks is the&lt;br /&gt;founder of Soft Skull Press and the owner of the Vox Pop, a progressive&lt;br /&gt;coffee house and outlet for independent media and publishing. Hicks has done&lt;br /&gt;extensive research into the ISI/Pakistan connection to 9/11 and published&lt;br /&gt;?The Big Wedding,? detailing the whistle blowers and the many conflicts of&lt;br /&gt;interest within the 9/11 Commission. Hicks will speak about his current&lt;br /&gt;investigation into the mysterious death of Dr. David Graham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna Marsh O?Connor - O?Connor lost her daughter, Vanessa Lang Langer.&lt;br /&gt;Along with 9/11 Family members, Michele Little and Christina Kminek,&lt;br /&gt;O?Connor called for a real investigation into 9/11 at the National Press&lt;br /&gt;Club on 9/11/06. O?Connor has been very active in recent years in spreading&lt;br /&gt;the truth about 9/11. She is also on the advisory board of&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.911truth.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.911truth.o...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Barrie Zwicker - Zwicker is an award-winning Canadian alternative media&lt;br /&gt;journalist, documentary producer, and political activist. Mr. Zwicker?s&lt;br /&gt;presentation will pertain to ?media blackout? of the alternative view of&lt;br /&gt;9/11, a subject of which Zwicker has been published a book (?Towers of&lt;br /&gt;Deception) and produced three documentaries (The Great Deception, The Great&lt;br /&gt;Conspiracy, and Deep Complicity).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason Bermas - Bermas is a documentary film maker and activist. The two&lt;br /&gt;films Bermas has produced so far, Loose Change 2nd Edition and Loose Change&lt;br /&gt;Final Cut, are responsible for bringing the 9/11 Truth Movement onto the&lt;br /&gt;brink of becoming mainstream. Bermas is also the host of Louder Than Words&lt;br /&gt;Radio on the GCN Radio Network. Please visit &lt;a href="http://www.loosechange911.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.loosechang...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jon Gold - Longtime researcher and activist. Gold was instrumental in the&lt;br /&gt;production of 9/11: Press For Truth and has been an advocate for the 9/11&lt;br /&gt;First Responders and the Feal Good Foundation. Gold is involved with&lt;br /&gt;?9/11Truth Tuesdays? at the Wayne Movie Theater in Wayne, PA, which has&lt;br /&gt;turned out to be an incredibly successful public outreach venue. To view&lt;br /&gt;Gold?s extensive 9/11 archive please visit:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yourbbsucks.com/forum/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yourbbsuck...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Keene High School, Keene, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: 15.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;URL: &lt;a href="http://www.monadnock911truthalliance.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.monadnock9...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211206062000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206747079000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The New England 9/11 Symposium</name><id>7623950</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211032800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7623950/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>