<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>48 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375577</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Graduate School of Design</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>710003</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fabricating Nature&lt;br /&gt;Kate Orff&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate Orff established the Manhattan design studio SCAPE in 2004. She is an Assistant Professor at the Columbia University Graduate School of Architecture, Planning and Preservation, (GSAPP) leading studios that integrate the earth sciences into the design curriculum. After graduating from the University of Virginia with Distinction, Ms. Orff earned a Master in Landscape Architecture from the Graduate School of Design at Harvard. She has worked on projects for many prominent academic institutions and private clients that have been published nationally and internationally. She trained for several years with Hargreaves Associates and with the Dutch architect/urbanist Rem Koolhaas at the Office for Metropolitan Architecture, and founded SCAPE shortly thereafter. Kate has built SCAPE's reputation for design innovation and collaboration, leading dynamic, open work processes with large, complex teams of collaborating consultants across the fields of engineering, science and design. The studio alternates between research and design, building new visions and understandings of urban nature. She has been nominated for several national awards, including the RISD-Surface Magazine Emerging Designer, a national award covering all design disciplines, and she was named &amp;quot;50 for the Future of Design&amp;quot; by H&amp;amp;G Magazine. SCAPE is the recipient of a 2008 ASLA Award&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230693683000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225511801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fabricating Nature?</name><id>9070214</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226619000000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/9070214/</event_url></item>