<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1230 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372617</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.497.0400</phone><name>Grafton Street Pub &amp;  Grill</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696851</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116138</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Son&lt;/b&gt; directed by Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne   Belgium/France 2002  103 min. plus a 10 minute early short. The films start at 7 PM.  We will meet at the Grafton Street Pub at 5:00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The retrospective of the Dardenne brother's films is yet another example of the HFA presenting world-reknown directors in a Q&amp;amp;A forum. Twelve of their films are to be screened from May 17- June 1 with the directors being present for the last two evenings. I have not seen any of the Dardenne's films, but they do look interesting... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Characterizing themselves as &amp;quot;one person with four eyes,&amp;quot; Belgian filmmaker Luc Dardenne and his older brother Jean-Pierre rose to the forefront of international art cinema in the 1990s with such uncompromising, socially aware dramas as La Promesse (1996) and Rosetta (1999), depicting life in Belgium's depressed industrial region near Liège on the Meuse River.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Son&lt;/b&gt; is a stylistically rigorous, emotionally wrenching drama of moral reckoning. The first half-hour may cause a lot of head-scratching because of the Dardennes' deliberately elliptical storytelling, but once the central dilemma snaps into focus, the movie becomes unusually gripping. Dardenne regular Olivier Gourmet gives a standout performance as Olivier, a carpentry teacher who encounters his child's killer many years later. Now a teenager fresh out of juvenile detention, the student (Morgan Marinne) does not know who Olivier is -- and Olivier is not eager to fill him in either. What Olivier chooses to do with his new charge becomes the stuff of this movie's suspense. All Movie Guide &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To call &lt;b&gt;The Son&lt;/b&gt; a masterpiece would be to insult its modesty. Like the homely, useful boxes Olivier teaches his prodigals to build, it is sturdy, durable and, in its downcast, unobtrusive way, miraculous. &lt;br /&gt;N.Y. Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Son&lt;/b&gt; is complete, self-contained and final. All the critic can bring to it is his admiration. It needs no insight or explanation. It sees everything and explains all. It is as assured and flawless a telling of sadness and joy as I have ever seen.  Walk out of the house today, tonight, and see it, if you are open to simplicity, depth, maturity, silence, in a film that sounds in the echo-chambers of the heart. &amp;quot;The Son&amp;quot; is a great film.   Roger Ebert &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the climax, we can hardly breathe -- The outcome is less important than our utter and complete empathy with this man. As we await what he does, we breathe with him, in and out. This is an astonishing movie.  Slate &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, &lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at a restaurant before the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242260793000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Son-  Directors Present at the HFA</name><id>10406921</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243803600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10406921/</event_url></item>