<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Yawkey Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.346672</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 267-9440 </phone><name>Fenway Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>567754</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098885</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>139.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>READ CAREFULLY PLEASE! It's Patriot's Day and this one of the most fun games to go to. I waited online for 1.5 hours and called and called. Could not get through, so I got these SUPERIOR SEATS through ACE TICKETS for a fraction more than face value. They are Loge Box 110 Row HH Seats 3&amp;amp;4. I have Seats 1&amp;amp;2 located first base side just above the RED SOX DUGOUT! They are $139.00 EACH. I am eating the cost of the service and mailing charges. When you RSVP yes, you MUST mail a check for the FULL AMOUNT to: Chris Lorant PO Box 3581 Edgartown, MA 02539-3581. Then I will mail you your tickets. THERE ARE NO EXCEPTIONS! ANYONE who wants to join the PREGAME TOAST, we will be at Boston Beer Works starting at 10am hanging out just inside the front enterance. Look for me! After the game, the tradition is to go down to Kenmore Square to watch the runners come in, so we will be in front of McDonald's. SSSWWWEEEEEETTT!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT! This is a joint meetup with some other groups. Gotta increase my chances in selling these tickets! Take chance and RSVP as YES, then email me to see if they are still available :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please see details</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271862714000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Funseeker</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>nefunseekers</urlname><id>1277691</id><group_lat>42.0299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>Funseekers!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264996116000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RED SOX/RAYS AT FENWAY!</name><id>12480004</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271689200000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nefunseekers/events/12480004/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/c/global_12892636.jpeg</photo_url></item>