<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just Ask!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/5/2/event_113480562.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Research tells us that women are far less likely to ask for anything – help, money, new opportunities – you name it, we rarely ask for it.  The true secret to personal and professional success is to ask, and ask often.  This presentation will provide the “business case” for asking and highlight some stories of success.  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Kimberly Robinson Williams, MBA, SPHR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Kimberly Robinson Williams is a corporate human resource professional with an MBA in Human Resource Management from Syracuse University and 15+ years of varied HR experience. The majority of her career has been focused on talent acquisition and development, with a focus on diversity.  She has worked for many companies in the private and non-profit sectors across many industries, including pharmaceutical, financial services, aerospace manufacturing, and now health care, and she recently earned an SPHR designation from the HR Certification Institute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Currently, she works as the Interim Diversity Director in the Office of Diversity &amp;amp; Inclusion at Baystate Health.  She is also the founder and Director of Next Level Development, an organization that exists to promote the personal and professional development of women and people of color.  She is a visiting adjunct professor at Westfield State University and Bay Path College and is also a guest lecturer at Springfield College, School of Social Wor .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Robinson Williams is the Treasurer of the Greater Springfield Chapter of Links, Incorporated and a lifetime member of the National Black MBA Association.  She is a 2008 Springfield Leadership Institute graduate, a 2010 Partnership Fellow, and a current participant in Leadership Pioneer Valley . She is actively involved in her church and community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Robinson Williams is the proud mother of two phenomenal children, Frank and Beau.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Next Level Development exists to promote the career and personal development of women and people of color across professions, industries, and levels of experience. We contend that true success comes when we substitute chance with information and preparation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;To achieve our mission, we offer a range of information, services, and interactive programming. Our cornerstone program is the Next Level Development Conference for Women of Color, which takes place in Springfield, Massachusetts annually on the first Saturday in October.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337357953000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335299011000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Breakfast Meeting- Just Ask!</name><id>61957432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337255100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/61957432/</event_url></item>