<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Church St</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>01505</zip><lat>42.353073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>10 Church St</name><city>Boylston</city><id>1616510</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.733665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;So we're looking to do some charity for a great family in Boylston. For the past few years the Chalifoux's along with local businesses and lots of local talent have helped run a 5k road race, this year we're going to give them some better pictures and hopefully some great publicity for Katie's 5k. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What i'm asking is one CD of your pictures from this day be sent to me within 2 weeks of the race. I'm not looking for 200 pictures or 300 pictures (that's awesome if you send that much though), what i am looking for is the pictures that really capture the spirit of this race. My plan is to take the top 10% of the pictures and make a photo book for the family. All the pictures will go to the Chalifoux's after they are sent to me. (Make sure to tag your pictures of course).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you wish to participate in the race as well as take photos then you get a shirt. I believe it around $20 on the day of the race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call me if you have any questions.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Mike - 508-471-0069&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a little bit about Katie from Katies5k.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Katie was born in October of 1984 to Janice and Robert Chalifoux.  &amp;nbsp;The youngest of 5 children, Katie spent her childhood growing up in  Boylston, surrounded by a closely-knit group of friends. &amp;nbsp;At Tahanto &lt;br /&gt; Regional High School, Katie was not only a scholar, but she was also  active in sports (soccer, basketball, and softball), music (clarinet and  piano), and numerous extra-curricular activities, (class officer, Model  United Nations, and Student Council).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After high school, Katie moved on to Skidmore College in New York  where she majored in International Affairs and minored in Government.  While attending Skidmore, Katie made friends from all over the &lt;br /&gt; country, and when she completed a semester at Sorbonne University in  Paris, France, she took her friendships to an international level. Katie  was well-traveled, having been to The Czech Republic, Spain, &lt;br /&gt; France, Ireland, and throughout the United States and Hawaiian Islands.  &amp;nbsp;No matter where her travels took her, Katie always made new friends  while maintaining close relationships with her friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Katie&amp;rsquo;s full life came to an unexpected and tragic end in January of  2008, after she succumbed to complications following an accident in New  York City. &amp;nbsp;At the time of her death, Katie was working as a teacher &lt;br /&gt; at Wild Blue, an enrichment program for children on the upper east side  of Manhattan. &amp;nbsp;She loved her life and was living out her dream of living  in New York City, and sharing the experience with friends, family, and  her long-time boyfriend, Phil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was the epitome of the cliche about &amp;ldquo;living life to the fullest&amp;rdquo;. &amp;nbsp;She did that everyday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Katie had a gigantic smile and a magnetic personality that made her  impossible to ignore. &amp;nbsp;Those who had the pleasure of meeting Katie were  also privileged to experience her genius sense of humor and infectious,  yet mischievous laugh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Katie was always full of love for her family. &amp;nbsp;She loved being an  aunt to Justin, Matthew, Finnias, Casey, Saige, and Vivian, and boasted  about them regularly. &amp;nbsp; She was beautiful on the inside and out, and  even with all of her &lt;br /&gt; accomplishments, she managed to be humble and completely grounded. Katie  Chalifoux was a refreshing ray of light. &amp;nbsp;To know Katie was to love  her, and to love her was certainly a blessing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We run this Katie&amp;rsquo;s 5k to remember Katie&amp;rsquo;s spirit and deep love of  life. Through the race we celebrate her life by inspiring young students  every year to live every day, in every way!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boylston's town center is the where the race starts and ends. You can find a spot anywhere along the way. From my past time doing this i know that there are very few of us out there with professional grade equipment at these events. We stand out.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hendrickson</member_name><member_id>12134347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306764695000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Great charity to be a part of and a great chance to expand your portfolio. We basically have free range over this event and can go anywhere we want and take any shots we want.  You can run it if you want as well, but show up and take pictures!</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280065965000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Katie's 5k photo coverage</name><id>14205635</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306760400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/14205635/</event_url></item>