<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076322</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rusty Hammer</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1023192</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We had some newcomers last night who I didn't get to personally say hello or goodbye to - and I wanted to! I just hope you come next time!  I looked up from compiling the bill and you were gone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/0/0/event_138027392.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The August selection for the Portsmouth Book Club is &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Other&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; by David Guterson.  The description from the publisher is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John William Barry has inherited the pedigree—and wealth—of two of Seattle’s elite families; Neil Countryman is blue-collar Irish. Nevertheless, when the two boys meet in 1972 at age sixteen, they’re brought together by what they have in common: a fierce intensity and a love of the outdoors that takes them, together and often, into Washington’s remote backcountry, where they must rely on their wits—and each other—to survive.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soon after graduating from college, Neil sets out on a path that will lead him toward a life as a devoted schoolteacher and family man. But John William makes a radically different choice, dropping out of college and moving deep into the woods, convinced that it is the only way to live without hypocrisy. When John William enlists Neil to help him disappear completely, Neil finds himself drawn into a web of secrets and often agonizing responsibility, deceit, and tragedy—one that will finally break open with a wholly unexpected, life-altering revelation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here is an excerpt from the Literary Journal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In his fourth novel, PEN/Faulkner Award winner Guterson (Snow Falling on Cedars&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;) &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;constructs a sensationalistic story that in other hands might have emerged as a page-turning potboiler. Here, events unfold in exquisitely refined prose, which creates a plot as believable as any quotidian workday while evoking an unforgettable sense of place in its depiction of Washington State's wilderness. Middle-aged narrator Neil Countryman, lately the recipient of an enormous and unexpected inheritance, traces the roots of this windfall back to an equally unexpected encounter at age 16 with a fellow runner on a Seattle high school track field. Bonded by a mutual love of the outdoors, working-class Neil and wealthy John William Barry become lifelong friends despite cultural disparities. The bond holds as their adult paths diverge, Neil choosing to teach while John William retreats to a hermit's life in remote woodlands. When Neil agrees to help his friend disappear, haunting questions of values, responsibility, and choice leave Neil-and the readers of this provocative fiction-to ponder the proper definition of a good life. Recommended for most fiction collections. [See Prepub Alert, LJ2/1/08.]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;—Starr E. Smith&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347431049000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341990679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club August - The Other by David Guterson</name><id>dpskncyqlbsb</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344985200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/72858652/</event_url></item>