<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In August we'll meet at our favorite hangout, Chaibo in Fitchburg, to discuss 
&lt;em&gt;A Thousand Splendid Suns&lt;/em&gt; by Khaled Hosseini. Chaibo has comfy couches and serves coffee, smoothies, grilled sandwiches, many unique flavors of gelato and of course their famous whoopie pies and ice cream sandwiches. Yum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is Amazon&amp;rsquo;s description of the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;After more than 189 weeks on the New York Times bestseller list for&lt;/em&gt; The Kite Runner 
&lt;em&gt;, Khaled Hosseini returns with a beautiful, riveting, and haunting novel that confirms his place as one of the most important literary writers today.&lt;/em&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;em&gt;Propelled by the same superb instinct for storytelling that made The Kite Runner a beloved classic,&lt;/em&gt; A Thousand Splendid Suns 
&lt;em&gt;is at once an incredible chronicle of thirty years of Afghan history and a deeply moving story of family, friendship, faith, and the salvation to be found in love.&lt;/em&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;em&gt;Born a generation apart and with very different ideas about love and family, Mariam and Laila are two women brought jarringly together by war, by loss and by fate. As they endure the ever escalating dangers around them-in their home as well as in the streets of Kabul-they come to form a bond that makes them both sisters and mother-daughter to each other, and that will ultimately alter the course not just of their own lives but of the next generation. With heart-wrenching power and suspense, Hosseini shows how a woman's love for her family can move her to shocking and heroic acts of self-sacrifice, and that in the end it is love, or even the memory of love, that is often the key to survival.&lt;/em&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;em&gt;A stunning accomplishment,&lt;/em&gt; A Thousand Splendid Suns 
&lt;em&gt;is a haunting, heartbreaking, compelling story of an unforgiving time, an unlikely friendship, and an indestructible love. 
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/8/3/event_46793891.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the first set of comfy couches by the door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314379290000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312830954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - A Thousand Splendid Suns by Khaled Hosseini</name><id>28713001</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314313200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/28713001/</event_url></item>