<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Newport</address_2><address_1>599 Thames St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02840</zip><lat>41.476880</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>401-841-8833</phone><name>Asterisk's Restaurant</name><city>Newport</city><id>578220</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.314000</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This event for the last &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;SATURDAY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; of the month at 6:30.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;***If you are interested, the RIPTA ferry runs during the summer and if you are interested, you can view the schedule and information &lt;a href="http://www.ripta.com/schedules/ferry.php" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.   On top of that, if you don't feel like walking the 1.2 miles to the restaurant, there is a &lt;a href="http://www.ripta.com/schedules/view.php?route=62&amp;amp;direction=2" target="_blank"&gt;RIPTA bus route &lt;/a&gt;that will takes you right to the restaurant.***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant I picked for this event is Asterisk's Restaurant on Thames St in beautiful Newport, RI.  They are a little different than your &amp;quot;traditional&amp;quot; fare, with a touch of French and fusion cuisine.  Although their menu is not as extensive as other places we have visited, they seem to have a little something for everyone.  You can view the menu on their website, &lt;a href="http://asterisknewport.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Asterisk's Restaurant&lt;/a&gt; along with pictures of the location.   Because it is Summer in Newport, and a Saturday to boot, we are really fortunate to get this reservation on the main &amp;quot;strip&amp;quot; of Newport.  As a result, we all need to be there by 6:30 in order for them to honor our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know I am pretty flexible in regards to attendance, but due to the location and time of year for this particular event, all YES RSVP's must be honored.  If you cancel after 9pm on Friday, June 27th unless you provide a valid emergency reason, I will be removing you from the group.  PLEASE don't make me do this...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because February's payment went so smoothly, I am suggesting we do it that way again. Basically we will have one bill for food, which will be divided equally among members then a second bill for beverages and alcohol. This way we can order appetizers as a table and everyone can enjoy with minimal confusion and the ones who choose not to indulge in &amp;quot;adult beverages&amp;quot; won't have to worry about paying extra when just enjoying non-alcoholic drinks. Please let me know if this is a problem for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should we fill up and you are still interested in attending, please enter a &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; RSVP and put a note stating that you want to be wait-listed. If spots open up, I will contact you in order of RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has not attended previous events, please plan on bringing a dollar to help me defray the cost of posting on meetup. For everyone who has attended, I only ask that you contribute every other event.  This would be such a big help to me!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See my picture- I'm the one with the red hair. ;-)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214865566000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>We are a great group of people who love to dine out!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205947849000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Dining-Out Group June Meetup- SATURDAY- Asterisks Restaurant</name><id>7563848</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214692200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/7563848/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/8/global_3808408.jpeg</photo_url></item>