<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Simon Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.750863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-233-1058</phone><name>Balanced Health Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>727520</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488831</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FREE video night in Nashua!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to forward this announcement around to friends who are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join our &lt;b&gt;Facebook group: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/home.php?#/group.php?gid=159949076301" target="_blank"&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;follow us on &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/mv911truth" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter: mv911truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This month in Nashua:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://video.google.com/videoplay?docid=3069943905833454241#" target="_blank"&gt;Global Warming or Global Governance?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One thing we learn in the Truth movement is to question extraordinary claims. We learn to be discerning, and it becomes especially important when leaders of state seem to be offering a solution that requires us to give up all our rights! The Global Warming &amp;quot;crisis&amp;quot; seems to be one of those types of cases. Many were shocked to find out how manipulative the climate scientists promoting the AGW hypothesis (anthropogenic global warming) were when their emails were exposed in the &amp;quot;climate-gate&amp;quot; scandal. Hence, this month's video choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sovereignty International produced &lt;b&gt;Global Warming or Global Governance?&lt;/b&gt; to present an offsetting view to the Global Warming hysteria. From &lt;a href="http://www.globalwarmingglobalgovernance.com/" target="_blank"&gt;their website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; Al Gore’s Inconvenient Truth allegedly provides incontrovertible evidence that this is the case. President Obama are committed to passing economically devastating legislation that will do little to nothing to stop global warming. Contrary to what is heard in the media, however, there is  overwhelming evidence that the warming we are experiencing is natural, with maybe a small amount contributed by man’s activities. Nor is there any scientific consensus. 31,000 scientists have signed a petition stating there is &amp;quot;no convincing scientific evidence that human release of carbon dioxide is causing...catastrophic&amp;quot; warming. The debate is still raging within the scientific community. In this DVD,   Sovereignty International has put together interviews of respected climate scientists and biologists from numerous sources who explain, step by step, why Al Gore and the global warming alarmists are incorrect. In some cases, blatantly so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The DVD also provides evidence that the global warming agenda is being funded with tens of billions of dollars as a mechanism to create global governance. Hear from congressmen, experts and even well-known news broadcasters how global governance puts global institutions, especially the United Nations (UN), that are not accountable to the American people in control of every aspect of our economy. The skyrocketing gas and food prices today are a direct result of this agenda.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also at this meeting:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Announcements to follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring your blank DVDs&lt;/b&gt; to the meeting and be sure to get a copy of each video we screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, bring your favorite short videos to show to the others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We may watch a recent interview with Dr. Leonard Horowitz if people want to stay for that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have screenings every Tuesday&lt;/b&gt; somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: &lt;b&gt;1st Tuesday-Nashua&lt;/b&gt;;; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord. The 4th Tuesday is open for a more northern meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetings are free, but we appreciate donations to continue building our video library.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive at 7:00&lt;/b&gt; if you can, in order to help set up the healthy snacks and beverages (that you bring to share with others - a gift of a box of tea for Gene's inventory would be appreciated) and enjoy the pre-meeting networking. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7:15 and then on to the video screening right after that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Newspaper&lt;/b&gt; - For an interesting paper which covers 9/11 Truth issues and other topics of concern, visit the &lt;a href="http://rockcreekfreepress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Rock Creek Free Press&lt;/a&gt; out of Washington, D.C.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bring your friends!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - Forward this invitation to everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Write us&lt;/b&gt; at MerrimackValley911Truth@gmail.com with suggestions for next month.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280933499000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280173267000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - Global Warming or Global Governance?</name><id>jmbknynlbfb</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280876400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/14219296/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/f/global_16910831.jpeg</photo_url></item>