<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Cave Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01054 </zip><lat>42.497752</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 367-2202</phone><name>Peace Pagoda</name><city>Leverett</city><id>1380535</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.497845</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Peace Pagoda in Leverett, MA is holding their 25th anniversary. This event is free and open to the public. For this silver anniversary year, author &lt;b&gt;James Douglass&lt;/b&gt; will be a speaker. His new book is called &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;JFK and the Unspeakable: Why He Died and Why It Matters&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James W. Douglass, author of &amp;quot;JFK and the Unspeakable: Why He Died and Why It Matters&amp;quot; (Orbis, 2008), will be on a speaking tour in the Northeastern US, Sept 30 - Oct 6. This superbly documented book is perhaps the most important among hundreds written on the JFK assassination.  Douglass is a highly esteemed and well-published author, professor, Catholic theologian, co-founder of Religious Leaders for 9/11 Truth, and a lifelong antiwar activist and nuclear disarmament advocate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Douglass is under contract with Orbis Books (in conjunction with Simon &amp;amp; Schuster) for publication of a trilogy, on the political assassinations of the 1960's, including those of JFK, RFK, Malcolm X, and Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his powerful new book, JFK and the Unspeakable:  Why He Died and Why It Matters, Douglass explores JFK's transformation from a conventional Cold Warrior to someone who was determined to pull the world back from the brink of apocalypse -- a transformation undertaken by JFK, Douglass writes, which then led, inexorably, to his execution, by those determined to nullify, and even exterminate his vision.  Only by unmasking those forces of what is so clearly &amp;quot;Unspeakable,&amp;quot; he argues, can we possibly free ourselves, and our country, so that we may yet pursue a global vision of peace, justice and meaningful democracy for all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and his wife Shelley were co-founders of the Ground Zero Center for Nonviolent Action in 1977, inspired by opposition to the Trident Nuclear Submarine Base near Seattle, Wash.; and, of Mary’s House, a Catholic Worker hospitality house in downtown Birmingham, Alabama.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Six lecture/presentations in New England, starting Thursday, Sept. 30th until Tuesday, Oct. 5th; concluding with a seventh in Philadelphia, Pa., on Wednesday, Oct. 6th:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sept... 30       Portland, Maine&lt;br /&gt;October 1        Cambridge, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;October 2        Leverett, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;October 3        Weston, Vermont&lt;br /&gt;October 4        New Britain, Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;October 5        Worcester, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;October 6        Philadelphia, Pennsylvania&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information will be posted at this link to &lt;a href="http://911blogger.com/news/2010-09-27/james-douglass-speaking-tour-jfk-obama-and-unspeakable" target="_blank"&gt;911blooger&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&amp;quot;The CIA Coup That Kept America on the Road of Militarism&amp;quot;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following links to &lt;a href="http://www.peaceactionme.org/book-review-jfk-and-unspeakable-why-he-died-and-why-it-matters" target="_blank"&gt;a review of the book by William Slavick&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valley 9/11 Truth will have copies of the &lt;a href="http://www.ae911truth.org/news/41-articles/338-we-wrote-it-all-down-in-a-classy-little-newspaper.html" target="_blank"&gt;9/11 Investigator&lt;/a&gt; on the display table. Please bring 9/11 truth material and help build coalitions to help peace activists overcome their denial. Note a great reference article on this topic, published by Global Research and written by Michel Chossudovsky:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.globalresearch.ca/index.php?context=viewArticle&amp;amp;code=CH020100913&amp;amp;articleId=21025" target="_blank"&gt;9/11 Truth and America's &amp;quot;Global War on Terrorism&amp;quot;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Pretext to Wage War is Totally Fabricated&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;..If unfamiliar with the amazing investigative work of Jim Douglas into the assassination of JFK shared in such a heart opening way in his masterpiece &amp;quot;JFK and the Unspeakable&amp;quot;  here are a few links to tune into: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.globalresearch.ca/index.php?context=va&amp;amp;aid=16273" target="_blank"&gt;Another review of this book&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pi19JLzD8Es" target="_blank"&gt; A brief lecture clip (Youtube - 6 minutes) of Jim Douglas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UUdqgD6-cLM&amp;amp;feature=related" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;An hour long interview with Jim Douglas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in which he links the assassinations of JFK with that of his brother Robert and Civil Rights Leader Martin Luther King Jr. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;JFK and the Unspeakable&amp;quot;  is the first of three more books yet to come covering the assassinations mentioned above as well as the murder of Malcolm X.  Have you ever wondered if and how all these political assassinations might be related?  Why were these men killed?  Does it have anything to do with the events unfolding now on our world stage?!  Come to one of the programs listed below and ask Jim Douglas these questions directly.  I am confident you will be astounded by his answers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Around this coming November 22nd JFK assassination anniversary date, keep attuned to joining a film screening or getting the DVD &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://thedarklegacy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dark Legacy: George Bush and the Murder of John Kennedy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; For more news and resources on such inter-related subjects, see &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;FlybyNews&lt;/b&gt;.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Around table display at top of trail before reaching Pagoda</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286036484000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284997259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peace Pagoda's 25th Anniversary - James Douglass</name><id>14831956</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286031600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/14831956/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/6/f/global_18115391.jpeg</photo_url></item>