<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>42 albany st.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.361949</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-253-3776</phone><name>M.I.T. SwapFest !</name><city>cambridge </city><id>1032174</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093514</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I have paid for 1 space at the M.I.T. SwapFest!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is first come first serve for the best spot. I was told by the organizer that people start arriving as soon as midnight the night before to secure the spot of choice. I suspect that I can arrive around 6-8 am and still have a prime location. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be around Three Hundred+ enthusiastic spectators participants and customers at this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I do not have many electronic items to sell so I am putting out the call for people to step up with some old electronics or anything techies/ nerds/ brilliant people may want to buy (think flea market type stuff... old tools etc... be creative.). Ideally these items should be donated so we could get a new banner or pay for dvd's that we constantly give away. (If you want to keep the $ from whatever you sell that belongs to you I only ask that you help man the space we will have in return.) So if you have some interesting things kicking around your house that you can part with please consider showing up to this event with them to sell.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will make sure that we have hundreds of DVD's and thousands of fliers about 9/11 to give away and possibly sell in order to break even with the cost of materials. If you have anything related to 9/11 to bring please do. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They start letting customers into the event at 9 am. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be sure to have some interesting conversations and possibly make some really good contacts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone interested in showing up or helping? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please email me personally at 1800capone@gmail.com my name is mark.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details from the MIT web site:&lt;br /&gt;42 albany st. garage cambridge mass.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://events.mit.edu/event.html?id=10549956&amp;amp;date=2009/08/16" target="_blank"&gt;http://events.mit.edu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SWAPFEST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 9:00a–2:00p&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: N4, Albany St Garage and Lot &lt;br /&gt;(the address is roughly @ 42 albany st. cambridge mass. google it! )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's monthly high-tech, computer, electronics and ham radio flea market. Buy, sell or swap all things nerdly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Held the third Sunday of each month, April through October. Rain or shine covered space is available for all sellers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the Albany St. Garage and adjacent lot, on Albany St. between Mass. Ave. and Main St., Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sellers, call 617-253-3776 (9-5) for more information.&lt;br /&gt;Web site: &lt;a href="http://www.swapfest.us" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.swapfest.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to: the general public&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $5, $4 with MIT or Harvard ID&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: At the gate&lt;br /&gt;This event occurs on the 3rd Sunday of every month through October 19, 2008.&lt;br /&gt;Sponsor(s): Radio Society W1MX, MIT, UHF Repeater Assn. W1XM, MIT, MITERS&lt;br /&gt;For more information, contact:&lt;br /&gt;Nick&lt;br /&gt;617-253-3776&lt;br /&gt;w1mx-officers@mit.edu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Web site: &lt;a href="http://www.swapfest.us" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.swapfest.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to: the general public&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $5, $4 with MIT Harvard ID&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: At the Gate&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251413287000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249421056000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>8/16: 9/11 Truth Booth @ M.I.T. SWAPFEST !!!!  Help Wanted.</name><id>11035974</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250427600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/11035974/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>