<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Across from the State House</address_2><address_1>9 Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357619</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 742-9991 </phone><name>No. 9 Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>910105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062793</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lucked out and got a rare reservation for fine dining at No. 9 Park during restaurant week. Expect an outstanding meal with excellent service in the company of great dining companions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;OUR SEATING IS AT 8 PM IN THE BAR ROOM&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the restaurant week menu link .... &lt;a href="http://www.no9park.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.no9park.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;MARCH RESTAURANT WEEK MENU IS $33.09 (doesn't include drinks, tax, or tip) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first serve basis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it will count as if you NO-SHOWED for THREE (3) events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it will count as if you NO-SHOWED for THREE (3) events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for THREE (3) events you are removed from the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the staffing of restaurants based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at 617 445-7549. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so, rate the event and venue by completing surveys.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239408853000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237709509000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>No. 9 Park Dinner Tuesday March 24th 8 PM</name><id>10007186</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237939200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/10007186/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/9/b/global_7777691.jpeg</photo_url></item>