<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britian Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Growing Green Co-Op</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1504658</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From 7:00 - 9:00 p.m., experience food like never before&amp;hellip; tasting, hearing, seeing, feeling, and smelling at this Soiree! Heighten your body&amp;rsquo;s awareness to everything going on around it and within it by muting another. Be fed raw chocolate while blindfolded, enjoy juicy fruits with your hands. Menu is all raw and all organic provided by Alchemy Caf&amp;eacute;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Past sensual awakening dinners have been held in Costa Rica for over 20 people at a time, with testimonials such as: "My focus is now on having a full experience with food and the people I share it with, instead of trying to fill myself up."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investment: $30 per person or $50 per couple&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email Imani@themamalution.com to register&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WEBSITE: www.sexualawakeningcentre.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Private Sexual Healing Sessions with Atia MarieRolfe ~ Healer, Sex Educator &amp;amp; Sensual Adventure Guide Thursday, July 7th @ Growing Green&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brief Bio of Atia Marie Healer, Sex Educator &amp;amp; Sensual Adventure Guide Founder of The Sexual Awakening Centre (www.sexualawakeningcentre.com) Practised in reiki, intuitive body work, shamanic healing arts, yoga and tai chi Experienced in fasting and working with native medicine Guest speaker at universities and frequent past corporate motivational speaker Former professional athlete having played beach volleyball for Canada Artist and founder of Create the Most Joy (www.createthemostjoy.com) International joy ambassador, lover and adventurer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Availability in CT/NY: Private sessions - Wed &amp;amp; Thu 9am-3pmSensual Awakening Tasting - Wed 7-9pm Coaching &amp;amp; Healing Sessions Relationship coaching sessions for developing deeper intimate connections with partners. Reiki, intuitive bodywork and shamanic healing sessions for physical, emotional, and spiritual healing and growth. Sexual healing sessions to heal from trauma (from abuse, medication or surgery), or for expanding sexual energy and intensity of pleasure and orgasm. Examples include: Sacred Yoni Massage for women, G-region massage for women or couples looking to explore female ejaculation, and guided sensual meditation to access pleasure and personal sexual power. (Nudity is never expected and all sexual healing sessions can be in a coaching format.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: Private sessions 50% off for friends/community of the Mamalution &amp;amp; Imani @ $125/hr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WEBSITE: www.sexualawakeningcentre.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>danita thomas</member_name><member_id>11226615</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309997434000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309661739000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sensual Awakening Tasting</name><id>24388281</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309993200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/24388281/</event_url></item>