<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'll be in Jefferson the weekend of the 28th/29th, and am looking for a hike. Reputation of Owl's Head is spectacular views. I am expecting this hike to be in snowshoes, though if conditions allow light traction, of course, that's what we'll do. I will update this with more details next week. Owl's Head Path Trail trailhead is on Rt 115 (map location is approximate). Lot is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; plowed in winter, so parking will be roadside (unless one of you happens to have a plow handy...) Start time is currently flexible. If you are interested, and would prefer earlier or later, let me know. I will be staying at the Applebrook a couple of miles away [might not be full].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, I did the Cherry Mountain Trail side of the mountain (to Mt Martha). This year I'd like to try from the Owl's Head Trail side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/MarthaOwlsHeadNH090818.html"&gt;Cherry Mountain Trail description&lt;/a&gt; RT: 5.4 mi Book Time: about 4 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/solitude.html#tocref3"&gt;Cherry Mountain&lt;/a&gt; RT 5.0 mi, 2000 ft Book Time 3:30&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather and trail conditions are, of course, hard to predict. The trail may or may not be broken out. As with any winter trip, if the conditions are bad, we'll turn back and go get a beer instead. We'll set a mutually agreed turn-around time before departing the trailhead. The summit is optional, returning to the trailhead is mandatory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that there are 2 trailheads on this stretch of Rt 115. The Owl's Head Trail is at a historic marker commemorating the 1885 "Cherry Mountain Slide".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Standard Disclaimer: This hike is like all others advertised through this Meetup. We start as a group, we hike as a group, we finish as a group. But all members of the group are responsible for their own preparation and safety. I am a social coordinator, not a trip leader, guide, or outfitter. If I have to tell you what the 10 Essentials are, this is not the hike for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Note about RSVPs: If you cancel, please make a phone call or send a text. Nothing I hate more than cooling my heels at the trailhead for a no-show. Ruins my whole day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another Note about RSVPs: the questions aren't optional. You don't answer them, I will change your RSVP to a No.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather looks like sunny &amp;amp; low 30's for Saturday, and NOHRSC is saying there's about a foot of snow on Cherry Mountain: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.nohrsc.nws.gov/interactive/html/map.html?mode=pan&amp;amp;extents=us&amp;amp;zoom=&amp;amp;loc=Latitude%2CLongitude%3B+City%2CST%3B+or+Station+ID&amp;amp;ql=station&amp;amp;var=ssm_depth&amp;amp;dy=2012&amp;amp;dm=1&amp;amp;dd=28&amp;amp;dh=0&amp;amp;snap=1&amp;amp;o5=1&amp;amp;o6=1&amp;amp;o9=1&amp;amp;o12=1&amp;amp;o13=1&amp;amp;lbl=m&amp;amp;o7=1&amp;amp;min_x=-71.725000000002&amp;amp;min_y=44.15&amp;amp;max_x=-71.250000000002&amp;amp;max_y=44.508333333334&amp;amp;coord_x=-71.487500000002&amp;amp;coord_y=44.329166666667&amp;amp;zbox_n=&amp;amp;zbox_s=&amp;amp;zbox_e=&amp;amp;zbox_w=&amp;amp;metric=0&amp;amp;bgvar=dem&amp;amp;shdvar=shading&amp;amp;palette=1&amp;amp;width=600&amp;amp;height=450&amp;amp;nw=600&amp;amp;nh=450&amp;amp;h_o=0&amp;amp;font=0"&gt;NOHRSC Snow Depth Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>JCarter</member_name><member_id>11575712</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327932996000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327092521000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Owl's Head (the other one) via Owl's Head Trail</name><id>48938462</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327761000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/48938462/</event_url></item>