<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Dunster Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372585</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John Harvard's Brew House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>3932782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119164</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"Everything I say is a lie." "Liar!"&lt;/p&gt;
What drives you to cheat? To bend the truth? To lie? What keeps you honest? Let us discuss Dan Ariely's new book: The (Honest) Truth About Dishonesty. To help keep people honest, should I bring a polygraph machine? ;-) "Dan Ariely, behavioral economist and the New York Times bestselling author of The Upside of Irrationality and Predictably Irrational, examines the contradictory forces that drive us to cheat and keep us honest, in this groundbreaking look at the way we behave: The (Honest) Truth About Dishonesty. From ticket-fixing in our police departments to test-score scandals in our schools, from our elected leaders’ extra-marital affairs to the Ponzi schemes undermining our economy, cheating and dishonesty are ubiquitous parts of our national news cycle—and inescapable parts of the human condition. Drawing on original experiments and research, in the vein of Freakonomics, The Tipping Point, and Survival of the Sickest, Ariely reveals—honestly—what motivates these irrational, but entirely human, behaviors."</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Jim or the Meetup group at reception.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim B</member_name><member_id>1113365</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>10</waitlist_count><updated>1370223660000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366262212000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The (Honest) Truth about Dishonesty</name><id>114936862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370192400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/114936862/</event_url></item>