<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mountain Road and Maple Street  Greenfield MA  01301  </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01301</zip><lat>42.589462</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-773-5463</phone><name>Poet's Seat Tower (see directions in detail section)</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>591187</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.587738</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be meeting at 12:00 pm on Sunday afternoon.  The hike is double-looped.  One loop is Poet's Seat and the other loop is Sachem Head.  We will start at Poet's Seat which leads into Sachem Head.  Each loop consists of a little over an hour of hiking time.  The first loop ends at the parking area.  If anyone would like to end the hike at this point, your car will be located here.  I hiked this spot two weeks ago to get a better idea of what we are all in for.  The hike is very wooded, slightly narrow paths, and lots of fun.  Please make sure that your dog is protected from ticks..Miles ended up with a few of them at the end of the hike.  Miles is two years old and thirty-five pounds.  He did well completing the whole hike.  However, I do walk and hike with him often.  He was well prepared for the two and a half hours of hiking.  Whats good is that if your dog can only make it half way..no need to turn back.  Again, the first loop ends in the parking area.  After the first loop, there is a place to sit and have a snack.  Some benches and an open ground.  Make sure to bring plenty of fluids...if you want.  I always carry my backpack and camera....This is my first time posting a hike..I am concerned that the link will not work.  If anyone has a problem reaching the direction site, please let me know and I will email it to you.  My email is Holly.Kozera@yahoo.com.  Also, feel free to email me with any other questions...I will bring my hiking book so we can plan our next hike together.  If anyone has any ides...let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NORTH&lt;br /&gt;1. Going on 91 North-Take exit 26 for RT-2A E/RT-2 W toward N Adams/Greenfield 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;2. At the traffic circle, take the 1st exit onto Mohawk Trail/RT-2A E &lt;br /&gt;3. Continue to follow RT-2A E 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;4. Turn left at Federal St/RT-10/US-5 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;9. Turn right at Maple St 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;10. Slight left at Mountain Rd  0.9 miles---turn off on your right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South&lt;br /&gt;1. Going on 91 South-Take exit 27 on the left to merge onto Mohawk Trail/RT-2 E toward Boston 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;2. Take the RT-10 S/US-5 S exit toward Greenfield 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;3. Merge onto Bernardston Rd/RT-10/US-5 &lt;br /&gt;4. Continue to follow RT-10/US-5 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;5. Turn left at Maple St 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;6. Slight left at Mountain Rd 0.4 mi---turn off on your right&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the north end of the parking area is a gate and two stone pillars.  I will be parked by the pillars.  Miles and I will be waiting in front of the pillars.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210694608000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Join us for lots of fun!!!!!</why><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209338225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>POET'S SEAT AND SACHEM HEAD</name><id>7824054</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210521600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/7824054/</event_url></item>