<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Wellesley College Botanic Gardens&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;New England Light Painters&lt;br /&gt;invite all local photographers to participate in&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Place in Time at the Wellesley College Botanic Gardens&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Saturday, May 9 from dawn to dusk (Rain date: May 16)&lt;br /&gt;Where: Wellesley College: Hunnewell Arboretum and Alexandra Botanic Garden (see attached map)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographers are invited to share in this special day of documenting the living landscape of the Wellesley College Botanic Gardens and other areas of the College. Considered one of the most beautiful college campuses in America, Wellesley College occupies more than 450 acres of cultivated and natural areas adjacent to Lake Waban. The Wellesley College Botanic Gardens consist of 22 outdoor acres with two named gardens. The Alexandra Botanic Garden has specimen trees and shrubs from around the world in a picturesque landscape. A tiny brook winds through the garden from a waterfall to Paramecium Pond. The H. H. Hunnewell Arboretum has several different habitats, including a maple swamp, meadow, and fragments of different forest types, with mostly native species. Other specialized gardens include a green roof planted with native species, a dwarf conifer garden, and a butterfly garden.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information: &lt;a href="http://www.wellesley.edu/WCBG/Welcome/welcome.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wellesley....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographers are encouraged to pursue their own creative vision for this event.  All styles are welcome: wide angle, macro, B&amp;amp;W, color, panoramic, HDR, montage, digitally processed, high key, low key – present what you see the way you wish to show it.  Our goal is to produce a comprehensive picture of a moment in time, as seen through many artistic eyes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Technical note: Phenology is the science dealing with the influence of climate on the annual cycle of plant life.  Photographic data on the state of the botanic gardens' specimens at this moment in time provides a valuable data point to help WCBG document the effect of climate change. While scientific documentation is one essential element, artistic documentation is equally valid.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Moment in Time will take place on Saturday, May 9 from dawn to dusk. The rain date is Saturday, May 16. Photographers are encouraged to explore the campus at their own pace at any time during the day. The use of tripods is permitted, but please don’t disturb any of the plants.  Orientation tours of the botanic gardens will take place at 11 am and 2 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographers are welcome to bring their own lunch. Snacks and beverages will be available from 10-4 in the Botanic Gardens' Visitor Center, adjacent to the Science Center on the east side of campus. Photographers are encouraged to park in the Gray Lot near the Science Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’re planning an exhibition of photographs from this event sometime this fall, and all photographers who participate in this event are welcome to participate in the exhibition.  Details will be announced over the summer.  If you’re not a member of NELP and want to receive exhibition details, please send your contact information to David Kahn (david@nelightpainters.org).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather is questionable, please check the NELP Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.nelightpainters.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nelightpai...&lt;/a&gt; for an update on the status.  We’ll make it clear at the top of the home page if the event is moved to the rain date.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for David Kahn!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242912823000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241572182000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photography Op this weekend! A Place in Time Wellesley College Botanic Gardens</name><id>10347424</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241866800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10347424/</event_url></item>