<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cabins</address_2><address_1>67 Island Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01516</zip><lat>42.063730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wallace Cove Cottages</name><city>Douglas</city><id>353497</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.766594</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We have an awesome photo opportunity and want to invite you to participate... We will have 2 beautiful horses, one pure white and the other a chestnut brown, as well as several champion English Spaniels dogs who will be at Wallis Cove, on Sunday Sept 19th at 8:00a.m. to frolic in our lake and pose for us!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It will last about an hour, two tops. We recently did a photoshoot for Ed Mansfield for his Champion dogs. When he asked if we’d also take photos of his two horses in the back of the house, we said of course. The lighting was dark and we didn’t get anything super, but we did recognize what beautiful animals they are. When we later were talking about his horses, he mentioned how the brown one loves swimming and frolicking in water and we decided to ask if they would like to bring them to us for a photoshoot. They are excited, we are excited and, since there is no cost to us, we wanted to open up the invitation to this group. All we’d ask is that you send any good photos you get to us to pass on to the client and for us to use for future promotions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;So, let us know if you’d like to stop by on Sunday, September 19th for an 8:00a.m. shoot!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you soon!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Michelle Fontaine&lt;br /&gt;LaMich Productions&lt;br /&gt;67 Island Rd., Douglas, MA 01516&lt;br /&gt;508-769-9137&lt;br /&gt;www.lamichproductions.com&lt;br /&gt;www.facebook.com/productionsbylamich&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285161103000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283287836000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Anyone want to Photograph a Horse on a Beach?</name><id>14608616</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284897600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/14608616/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/6/global_14360230.jpeg</photo_url></item>