<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 44A</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05089</zip><lat>43.435608</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt Ascutney Brownsville Trail</name><city>Ascutney </city><id>1117826</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.404102</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>MODERATE Day hike: 6.8 miles (5 hours) — via Windsor Trail and Brownsville Trail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Ascutney, the weathered core of an old volcano that once towered 20,000 feet into the air, stands alone over the Connecticut River. The name derives from several Abenaki words meaning “mountain of the rocky summit”. In 1825, Vermont’s first mountain hiking trail was cut on Ascutney. Later, while hiking on the mountain in 1909, James P. Taylor had the inspiration for the creation of Vermont’s Long Trail, which eventually spawned both the Green Mountain Club and the idea for the Appalachian Trail. The Ascutney Trails Association maintains the trail and can be reached at P.O. Box 147, Windsor, VT, 05089.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate Length:   6.4 total miles&lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain:  2,400 feet  (trail is shorter but steeper)&lt;br /&gt;Trail Type:  loop&lt;br /&gt;Skill Level:  moderate + due to the aerobic level of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;Duration:  5 hours&lt;br /&gt;Season:  Best spring through fall&lt;br /&gt;Top Elevation:  3,150 feet&lt;br /&gt;Other Uses:  Dogs allowed&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Map of Mount Ascutney&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.dartmouth.edu/~doc/www/images/hiking/map-mountascutney.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How To Get There:&lt;br /&gt;from  I-91  Exit 9, “Hartland-Windsor”. &lt;br /&gt;At the top of the ramp, turn left onto Route 5 South and follow it 4.1 miles through downtown Windsor. Turn right onto Route 44 West and follow it along a brook and under the I-91 bridges. Continue uphill and converge with a side road (Route 44A) coming in from the left 3.3 miles from the center of Windsor. Turn sharply left onto this road, and in 100 yards come to the Windsor Trail parking lot on the right. Park here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The two trails which form this loop hike, the Windsor Trail and the Brownsville Trail, have trail heads separated by a mile of road walk. If you brought a second car, continue on to the Brownsville Trail parking area. If not, the road walk is short and scenic. Leaving the parking lot, turn left and retrace your path back to the junction with Route 44. Continue straight on Route 44 West. After 0.9 miles, with fields on both sides of the road, the trailhead is on the left side of the road, just past a blue-green house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup at the Mancino's house after the hike for some chili.  BYO holiday cheer &amp;amp; Christmas cookies.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup stickers</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260886068000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257972767000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Ascutney and After Hike Holiday Fun</name><id>11852809</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260712800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11852809/</event_url></item>