<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>241 Union Square</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03055</zip><lat>42.835243</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-672-2270 </phone><name>Pasta Loft</name><city>Milford</city><id>430400</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.649850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's eat lunch at Pasta Loft in Milford before we work it off by walking the Horse Hill Nature Reserve. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Pasta Loft:&lt;br /&gt; With specialty pizzas, fresh pastas and hearty entrees, Pasta Loft is an Italio-phile's dream. Appetizers include garlic bread, steamed mussels, fried ravioli and phyllo spinach wraps. Specialty pizzas include tomato basil (olive oil, fresh basil, roasted garlic, roma tomatoes and fresh buffalo mozzarella); farmers market (garden vegetables with homemade pesto and mozzarella cheese); chicken portobello (grilled chicken, portobello mushrooms, caramelized onions, tomato sauce and mozzarella cheese); white pizza (olive oil, herbs, roasted garlic and Italian cheeses); and chicken barbecue (grilled chicken, pancetta, onioin, barbecue sauce and mozzarella cheese). Or, you can create your own pizza with toppings like anchovies, artichokes, feta cheese, mushrooms, pepperoni, pineapple, prosciutto, roasted red peppers, shrimp, spinach, scallops and bacon. Italian specialties include manicotti, fettucini alfredo, tortellini pesto, chicken cacciatore, chicken marsala, veal saltimbocca and eggplant parmesan. Seafood dishes include baked haddock, broiled scallops and baked stuffed shrimp. A children's menu features smaller portions for about $4. Prices are moderate, with most entrees costing $10 to $15&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pastaloft.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pastaloft....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195493668000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195080413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lunch at Pasta Loft</name><id>6742344</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195320600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/6742344/</event_url></item>