<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Due to Saturday's Forecast of possible rain and winds gusting to more than 15 mph, this paddle has been change to a Level 2 (Intermediate) Paddle  You should be comfortable on choppy water and paddling in moderate winds. You should know more advanced paddle strokes involving bracing, boat control in winds and currents and have experience in performing a wet-exit with sprayskirt. You should be able to perform a self rescue with paddle float or assisted rescues.  You should dress for rain (although it may not rain at all) and possible immersion. Bring a set of warm clothes in a dry bag and lunch. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drop boats at the boat ramp located at the Squam Lake Association.  Pay $5 launch/parking fee.  Parks cars above in large lot next to the main building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddle will be 8-10 miles.  Squam is a large lake...so wind creates waves over the long fetch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lots of local restaurants for after paddle dining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've never paddled Squam...don't miss this great foliage paddle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;NOTE: This is a rain or shine paddle. We are definitely going. It promises to be a fun, yet more challenging day on the water. Hope to see you there.u]&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boat Ramp at Squam Lake Assoc. - Piper Cove</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy Foley</member_name><member_id>7753713</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223138353000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218732845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers - Squam Lake Foliage Paddle</name><id>8543956</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222527600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/8543956/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/d/global_5153213.jpeg</photo_url></item>