<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.373913</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Biagio Ristorante and Bar</name><city>Waltham</city><id>318775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236496</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come and join your Sitz friends and guests at Biagio Ristorante and Bar in Waltham, Ma. It is a new and exciting ristorante on Moody St. The restorante specializes in the extraordinary. Modern and traditional elements blend together in a fusion of rich colors creating an inviting and stylish two story brick building devoted solely to your night on the town!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, we will meet and greet in the Plush Lounge which resides on the second level atop the winding grand staircase. Couches line the room and candles run along the large cherry wood and granite bar. Flat panel TV's line the rustic brick walls which lead out to the roof top patio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come on over and join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Light appetizers will be provided compliments of the Sitzundjibers Social Club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biagio Ristorante and Bar is located at 123 Moody St. in Waltham near Main St. and over the river from Marguerita's restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can park at the Rockland Trust bank which is next to the ristorante over the commuter rail tracks. There is also on street parking and a municipal parking lot off Pine St. next to the Embassy theatre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purple commuter rail stops right at the ristorante on Moody St. for those interested in public transportation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319716682000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316809719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our 2nd Monthly Afterwork...Let's welcome Biagio's!</name><id>34721202</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319580000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/34721202/</event_url></item>