<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft  NERD New England Research &amp; Development Center </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1626763</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join &lt;a href="http://www.bostonphp.org/members/5046031/"&gt;Michael Bourque&lt;/a&gt; for a look into his new Meetup Group called "&lt;a href="http://www.reversestartup.org"&gt;The Reverse Startup&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have an invention for a new product or service?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.reversestartup.org"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/2/a/global_163781002.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;This new Meetup Group will explore how startups are born, make them happen, and show the world how it's done the open source way...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I meet all sorts of people with great ideas for products, innovations, and businesses. But most don't know how to move their idea forward.&lt;/span&gt; I currently have 25 unique startup ideas that I have no time to build myself. Every one of these startups is exciting, solves a real problem, comes with a domain name, product design templates, pitch/demo, software specifications, working prototype, UX screens, as well as an audience just waiting to get their hands on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea is that an team band around an idea and build it as an &lt;strong&gt;open source project&lt;/strong&gt;. We will share the code and the showing of how it is being built. The ultimate goal is to share this process as a reality show from our website. &lt;span&gt;Think "American Idol" for startups.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone interested can contribute to the project, as all across America people watch our startup in the making. &lt;span&gt;We will teach and learn as we go.&lt;/span&gt; Together, we can show the world cooperative entrepreneurship, and move our ideas forward with a bold and progressive process of developing ideas into reality--by doing things in Reverse!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to tell you more. Please join us for our first meeting, Feb 6 at the Microsoft NERD Center. Bring your ideas, your curiosity, your energy and creativity!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more here...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ReverseStartup.org"&gt;http://www.ReverseStartup.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361056035000</updated><rating><average>2.77999997139</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>128</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358170105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Reverse Startup</name><id>99510892</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360195200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/99510892/</event_url></item>