<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>71 South Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02025</zip><lat>42.239225</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 383-1704</phone><name>Brasserie Zapp</name><city>Cohasset</city><id>1129145</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.801563</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a chance that Mike missed once before: From now through the end of the year, &lt;a href="http://www.redlioninn1704.com/AboutBrasserieZapp.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brasserie Zapp&lt;/a&gt;, the restaurant in The Red Lion Inn in Cohasset, has many of its menu items at half price! That means, to give two quick examples, filet mignon for $14.50, and lobster for $13.00! Are you still sitting down?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, so maybe you are. That's alright, you don't have to stand to RSVP, but we do recommend that you take advantage of this chance to dine well yet make a surprisingly small dent in your wallet. And in case you're wondering just what kind of filet mignon you'd get for $14.50, let us refer you to Joan Wilder's &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/news/local/articles/2009/11/01/brasserie_zapp_at_cohassets_red_lion_inn_is_comfortable_place_for_meals_drinks_snacks/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Globe review&lt;/a&gt; of the restaurant - and the steak - in question.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope you'll join us inside The Red Lion Inn on Thursday, December 10th at 7:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brasserie Zapp (inside The Red Lion Inn)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, December 10, 2009 @ 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;71 South Main St&lt;br /&gt;Cohasset, MA&lt;br /&gt;781 383-1704&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.redlioninn1704.com/AboutBrasserieZapp.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brasserie Zapp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up to 2 per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Pretty Darn good! If you have Adobe Acrobat Reader, you can see their specials menu &lt;a href="http://www.redlioninn1704.com/HalfPriceMenu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Please note that on The Red Lion Inn's website it says that the specials are good through October, but we confirmed over the phone that the statement in the Boston Globe review is accurate and the specials are running through the end of the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members - None. Group Members and Guests - $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, December 9th at 7:00 PM. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer. Changes to No after this point will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions (Credit to Red Lion Inn &lt;a href="http://www.redlioninn1704.com/Directions.doc" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;/b&gt; Brasserie Zapp is located inside The Red Lion Inn at 71 South Main St in Cohasset.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FROM BOSTON AND POINTS NORTH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 South to Route 3 south.  Take Exit 14 (Rte 228) and turn left at end of ramp for Rte 228 North.  Stay on 228 North (6-7 miles) until junction of Rte 3A.  Cross over Rte 3A and take your first right onto East St. for approximately 3 miles (the road will eventually change names).  This road will bring you to Cohasset Village and the Red Lion is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FROM CAPE COD&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go over the Sagamore Bridge through rotary onto Route 3 North.  Take exit 14, (Route 228).  Follow same directions as above after ramp exit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FROM POINTS SOUTH OF COHASSET&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take route 3A North through Marshfield, Scituate.   When you see the sign for Cohasset drive approximately ½ mile to a set of lights.  Take a right at the gas station onto Beechwood Street and follow down, at stop sign, take a left onto South Main street.  The Red Lion Inn is on the left side in the center of Cohasset Village&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261181847000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259213555000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Zapp high dining bills!</name><id>11958589</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260489600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/11958589/</event_url></item>