<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Oren Harman&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;explains&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Price of Altruism:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George Price and the Search for the Origins of Kindness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: : :&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is delighted to welcome historian of science Oren Harman for a conversation about his new book, The Price of Altruism: George Price and the Search for the Origins of Kindness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the dawn of time man has contemplated the mystery of altruism, but it was Darwin who posed the question most starkly. From the selfless ant to the stinging bee to the man laying down his life for a stranger, evolution has yielded a goodness that in theory should never be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set against the tale of 150 years of scientific attempts to explain kindness, The Price of Altruism tells for the first time the story of the eccentric American genius George Price (1922–1975), as he strives to answer evolution&amp;#8242;s greatest riddle. From the heights of the Manhattan Project to the inspired equation that explains altruism to the depths of homelessness and despair, Price&amp;#8242;s life embodies the paradoxes of Darwin’s enigma. His tragic suicide in a squatter’s flat, among the vagabonds to whom he gave all his possessions, provides the ultimate contemplation on the possibility of genuine benevolence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Unselfishness is a dangerous thing. George Price, the subject of this striking and original book, became obsessed with it and it killed him.... the amount of reading Harman has done is colossal and his mastery of his subject is truly remarkable. Thomas Hobbes in the 17th century wrote that altruism was an illusion because if a man did good to others it was &amp;#8242;to deliver his mind from the pain of compassion,&amp;#8242; and therefore selfish. Harman does not quote this, but he is fully aware that it may be true, while hoping it is not.&amp;quot; —The Times (UK) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Information&lt;br /&gt;DATE: Thursday, July 8th &lt;br /&gt;TIME: 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: Harvard Book Store &lt;br /&gt;1256 Massachusetts Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge  &lt;br /&gt;TICKETS: This event is free; no tickets are required &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Oren Harman, who has a doctorate from Oxford University, is the Chair of the Graduate Program in Science Technology and Society at Bar Ilan University and a professor of the history of science. He is the author of The Man Who Invented the Chromosome, a documentary film maker, and a frequent contributor to The New Republic. He lives in Tel Aviv and New York.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278686744000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277987177000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Price of Altruism</name><id>13970007</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278630000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/13970007/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/3/global_15836403.jpeg</photo_url></item>