<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Hyde Park Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.299915</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Forest Hills T Stop</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>615772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113570</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This should be a great and inspiring event! We had a great time last year. Feel free to bring food for a picnic. I will be sharing lots of delicious cookies. Let's meet at the Forest Hills T Stop at 6:15p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Description from the Forest Hills Educational Trust **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our memorial Lantern Floating Festival is inspired by an ancient Buddhist ritual in which lanterns representing the souls of the dead are floated out to sea and prayers are offered so that they may rest in peace. Join us for this beautiful ceremony. Inscribe your own words of remembrance and hope on the shades of simple wooden lanterns, and then release them, glimmering with candlelight, onto Lake Hibiscus at dusk.&lt;br /&gt;Many people attend with friends and family, spreading out a blanket for a picnic dinner, and then working on commemorative lanterns. The evening starts with performances of drumming, dance, and choral music. Hear the dynamic Master Tsuji's Samurai Taiko Drummers and spirited music by Ron Murphy and Friends, some of Boston's finest gospel singers. Enjoy traditional Japanese Bon Festival dances presented in elegant kimona clad students from Showa Boston Institute and traditional Chinese folk dance by youth from Chu Ling Dance Academy. The haunting sounds of Japanese flute, followed by Scottish bagpipes, accompany the lanterns on their journey across the Lake&lt;br /&gt;Please note: bring a flashlight to help guide your exit from the Cemetery, as there is no electrical lighting after dark.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280442997000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Walkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Evening-Walkers</urlname><id>865474</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Evening Walkers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269754010000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Forest Hills Lantern Festival</name><id>13012634</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279232100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Evening-Walkers/events/13012634/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/e/global_9661918.jpeg</photo_url></item>