<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We're changing the format for Tuesday Open Studios...Let's just make it a kick-back-and-relax kinda evening, a mid-week break for art and company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some folks have used this time in the past for painting...trying out new things, experimenting with color, studying and emulating artists past and present.  You're welcome to continue or join this journey! Or if you have ATCs to make for the next Meetup, or a journal that you're working on, you're welcome to work on those projects as well.  Anything goes; just come prepared to relax, enjoy,  and make art!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; If you plan to paint:  Your choice of painting supplies for watercolor, acrylic, oil....whatever you like.  If you're just starting out, we can offer the use of a basic kit for either acrylic or watercolor You may want to wear an apron or old clothes. We have some aprons to borrow if you need one.  Otherwise:  Simply bring your basic art kit, and any project you'd like to work on...journalling, ATCs, altered books...and there's inspiration to spare, if that's what you need!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/strong&gt; Tuesday, May 1, from 7-10 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, some aprons, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; $10 to defray cost for the space.  This is an open studio event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/strong&gt; Anyone, but you must sign up on the NE ATC+ Meetup site (which requires joining that group; it's free with no obligation).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt; Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. Please RSVP for your guests as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; In the unlikely event that we need to cancel---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>emelengy</member_name><member_id>4250560</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335918068000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331042882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Studio:  Yes, You Can Paint!  (Or Whatever!)</name><id>qvlhqcyqhbcb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335913200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/55191922/</event_url></item>