<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1296 Washington Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.349343</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 964 8074</phone><name>West Newton Cinema</name><city>Newton</city><id>837390</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.226648</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Painfully funny&amp;quot; - Wesley Morris, The Boston Globe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joan Rivers: A Piece of Work takes the audience on a year long ride with legendary comedian Joan Rivers in her 76th year of life. Peeling away the mask of an iconic comedian and exposing the struggles, sacrifices and joy of living life as a ground breaking female performer. The film is an emotionally surprising and revealing portrait of one the most hilarious and long-standing career women ever in the business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'At the core of Rivers’ kibbitzy style of unvarnished truth-telling lies a deep reservoir of sadness, rooted in the suicide of her longtime manager, producer, and husband Edgar Rosenberg and the emotional scars incurred when Rivers’ mentor and early champion Johnny Carson had her blacklisted from NBC after she hosted a competing, ill-fated talk show on Fox. Much of A Piece of Work inhabits the tricky intersection of comedy and tragedy: the specter of mortality looms large for Rivers, as does the even more terrifying possibility of professional irrelevance. A Piece Of Work is funny, heartbreaking, and casually profound about the insatiable need for validation and approval that fuels so much stand-up comedy.' - A.V. Club&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ifcfilms.com/films/joan-rivers-a-piece-of-work" target="_blank"&gt;Joan Rivers: A Piece of Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My second (and last?) attempt to schedule a film at the West Newton Cinema.  18 members like this idea:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to suggest not-infrequent meetups at premium/arthouse theatres such as the Embassy in Waltham, the West Newton Cinema, and others. For those of us west of Boston, be that Newton or MetroWest, in-town attendance is often expensive, traffic-laden, and parking-poor. Frequent service via the &amp;quot;T&amp;quot; or commuter rail doesn't exist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A regular break out in the 'burbs won't hurt anyone and will help more than a couple of members! Thanks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last time I scheduled a Meetup at West Newton, there were exactly zero RSVP's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a 92% rating from rotten tomatoes, and a trailer that includes the heartbreaking line 'I don't have anyone in my life that I can say 'remember when', I can't resist a film that was nowhere on my radar, but which may be among the most memorable of the year.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's see if 'West of Boston' is viable as opposed to the often expensive, traffic-laden, and parking-poor (have you ever been to the Coolidge??) offerings that have been made in Boston &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/laughing.gif' border='0' alt='laughing' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's start a new 'venue' that can become a regular place for our group.  Hey, I live in Newton Center!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for me holding a Red Meetup Sign in the lobby after the film and closing credits.  We'll go to a nearby eatery for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277338147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>JOAN RIVERS: A PIECE OF WORK </name><id>13892895</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277668800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13892895/</event_url></item>