<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>La première Boston French Party de cette année 2009 aura lieu le 4 Février à Felt à partir de 19h30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suite au sondage, de nombreux changements ont eu lieu qui, nous l'espérons, vont vous satisfaire:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- La soirée commence désormais à 19H30 avec un apéritif Francais offert par le Petit Robert Bistro! dans une ambiance lounge et relax pour rencontrer du monde et pratiquer votre français.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Nous commençons 2009 avec cette soirée au Club Felt, en plein coeur du District Theatre, et continuerons tout au long de l'année à vous faire découvrir de nouveaux bars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- A partir de 22H, le format redevient habituel avec les meilleures musiques française et l'ambiance joviale et festive qui a fait notre réputation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venez nous rejoindre cette exceptionnelle soirée de lancement de l'année 2009!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first Boston French Party of 2009 will be held at Felt Club Boston, on February 4, 2009, from 7:30 PM on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After receiving your feedback on the evolutions you wished to see in the Boston French Party in 2009, we made some changes that, we think, you will like:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The party now starts at 7:30 PM with a French apéritif (courtesy of Petit Robert Bistro!) in a relax and friendly &amp;quot;lounge&amp;quot; atmosphere to help you meet people and speak French.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- This first party of 2009 will be held at  Felt Club Boston, one of the best bars of the Theatre District in Boston. We will do our best to change bars as often as we can to help you discover the great places of Boston nightlife.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- After 10 PM, the &amp;quot;usual&amp;quot; party starts, with the best French music and the festive and friendly atmosphere we built our reputation on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come and join us to party and eat great food in a great place for this first Boston French Party of 2009.&lt;br /&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julien</member_name><member_id>1573841</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235698415000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>voulezvous</urlname><id>541017</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Voulez-vous français Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230084727000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Party January Meetup</name><id>9382585</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233793800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/voulezvous/events/9382585/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/f/global_7101247.jpeg</photo_url></item>