<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Told in flashback, the romantic crime thriller &lt;b&gt;The Secret in Their Eyes&lt;/b&gt; is winner of this year's &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film&lt;/span&gt;. Benjamín Espósito (Ricardo Darín, Nine Queens) has spent his entire working life as a criminal court employee. In 1999, recently retired and with time on his hands, he decides to write a novel. Drawing on his own past life as a civil servant, he recounts a true, moving and tragic story in which he was very directly involved: in 1974, his court was assigned an investigation into the rape and murder of a beautiful young woman. Moved by the grief of the husband, only married a short time, Espósito tries to help him find the culprit, despite having to contend with the apathy, ineptitude and even hostility of the police and legal system. For assistance he turns to Pablo (Guillermo Francella), a close friend and underling at his office who seeks release from his routine by drinking himself unconscious, and his boss, the beautiful upper class lawyer Irene (Soledad Villamil), with whom Espósito is secretly in love. Espósito's investigation spanning decades takes him deep into the world of Argentina in 1974—a perfect backdrop for the violence, hate, revenge and death—no longer as an observer, but an unwilling central character. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sonyclassics.com/thesecretintheireyes/" target="_blank"&gt;The Secret of Their Eyes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.landmarktheatres.com/letters/secretintheireyes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;writer/director Juan José Campanella &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A chance to see the Academy Award winning film for &lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Best Foreign Film&lt;/span&gt;.  Any film that beat the &lt;u&gt;White Ribbon&lt;/u&gt; is worth checking out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, an opportunity for us to decompress from Boston's Independent Film Festival.  Go over all the films seen, all the films that should have been seen, all the films that should have been avoided, and all the ones to look for in distribution.  Look for John holding a red Meetup Sign after the closing credits.  We have reservations at Doyle's, and can sit outside if there is space.  Please change your RSVP if you will be unable to join us for the discussion so that we can give the restaurant an accurate count.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Eye  will be holding the Secret Meetup Sign at the Kendall After the film to lead the award winning group to the local eatery for discussion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271895430000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Secret In Their Eyes</name><id>13253569</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272753000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13253569/</event_url></item>