<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>190 TPK</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03452</zip><lat>42.805256</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jaffrey Airport-Silver Ranch (KAFN)</name><city>Jaffrey</city><id>2402251</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.993538</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;HERE'S A LINK TO THE THREAT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/metrodesk/2012/08/17/fireworks-show-jaffrey-cancelled-after-town-officials-receive-violent-threat/El5ATqFIy45hT5V7pQWuoL/story.html"&gt;http://www.boston.com/metrodesk/2012/08/17/fireworks-show-jaffrey-cancelled-after-town-officials-receive-violent-threat/El5ATqFIy45hT5V7pQWuoL/story.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Here's the plan:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet and leave cars at the Cheshire Marketplace, 497 U.S. 202, Rindge, N H. Drive into the Plaza staying straight and parking on the left of the parking lot(&lt;strong&gt;opposite side from Market Basket)&lt;/strong&gt;  Look for a white volvo.  We will carpool from there to Jaffrey Airport.  Please be there at 4PM.  Kathy and I can drive, fitting 5 in each car, we will have a lot of chairs, coolers and other gear so if anyone has a vehicle that is larger and can hold a lot, please let me know if you wouldn't mind driving.  The ticket to drive in to the Fireworks is $45.  That would be a per person cost of $9.  If only 8 show up instead of ten the cost per person will change to $11.  I would like to care of all the calculations in advance at the Market Basket plaza, so the drivers will have the money to pay for the ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What to bring: (please respond if I've missed something)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food/drinks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;chairs/blankets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;sunscreen/bugstuff&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;warm clothing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1vYRfTKxSyY"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1vYRfTKxSyY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jaffreychamber.com/events/fireworks/"&gt;http://www.jaffreychamber.com/events/fireworks/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would like to find a place to meet,  park cars and hike in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;Walk-in tickets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Advanced Sale:    Through 08/17/12    $ 8 per adult&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Day of Fireworks:   8/18/12                 $ 10 per adult&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Car pass (up to mini-van/SUV): advance sale $ 40                                                         day of fireworks  $45.     I copied this from a blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's an amazing show, I'd suggest everyone go at least once, if not more times in their lives. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

While I agree that walking in can be cheaper if you're going to be going as 1-2 people, it has diminishing returns, as if you can get more than 3 people in your vehicle, it ends up being cheaper that way. This includes the average $10-20 parking outside the airport. Prices for parking outside the airport generally increase the closer you park. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Most of the walk from parking areas outside the airport is uphill, if you're going to carry in anything relatively heavy, it's sometimes easier to just drive in and wait out the traffic while exiting the airport, depending on your fitness level. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Tips: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

1) If you plan on driving in, arrive earlier in the evening, as you'll be closer to the exit at the end of the fireworks. And there's usually lots of stuff to do and watch earlier in the day, starting around 5-6PM. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

2) If you drive in, it's helpful to have chairs, coolers, blankets close-by carried in your vehicle. Sitting on the ground isn't a whole lot of fun, and if you're bringing kids, the blankets can help stake out your "spot". &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

3) Cell phone coverage is spotty to non-existent in most/all of the area around/inside the airport, plan on having known meeting points and times ahead of time, rather than relying on cell phones to call each other. If you have kids that you feel are old enough to be on their own, the buddy system is generally recommended. If you use or are going to need any sort of gps navigation, be aware that without cell coverage, navigation built into many cell phones does not work, highly recommend a standalone gps unit, TomTom or Garmin are both good choices. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Average time depending on where you are in the line of traffic if you choose to drive in, is between 1-4 hours, although they seem to be getting the hang of getting people out faster every year, plan accordingly. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

More info can be had from the Jaffrey Chamber of Commerce events page: »&lt;a href="http://www.jaffreychamber.com/events/"&gt;www.jaffreychamber.com/events/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Whether you choose to walk in, or to drive in, I suggest bringing a small flashlight for each person in your party, it can be hard to find your vehicle, and/or find your way along the side of the road without it, there are no sidewalks in that part of Jaffrey. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Good luck and have fun, if you've never been, I guarantee you'll be back again and again, it's that good, and the fireworks are awesome choreographed to music &lt;img src="http://i.dslr.net/v2/lite/smile.gif" width="15" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>497 U.S. 202, Rindge, N H. Drive into the Plaza staying straight and parking on the left of the entire parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Lielasus</member_name><member_id>11490496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345376599000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343835051000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CANCELED DUE TO THREATS MADE - Annual Fireworks - Jaffrey Nh</name><id>75847442</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345320000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/75847442/</event_url></item>