<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>53 Marlborough St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.354078</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.912.0400</phone><name>French Cultural Center</name><city>Boston, </city><id>1451512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.074798</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For May’s Ciné Club de l'Alliance, the French Cultural Center is thrilled to present Welcome, a 2009 film directed by Philippe Lioret starring Vincent Lindon, Firat Ayverdi, and Audrey Dana. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Welcome is a compassionate and inspiring drama about the hope of new beginnings and the power of true love, centered on two couples contending with issues of separation and dislocation. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 17-year-old Bilal has spent the last three months travelling illegally across Europe, in an attempt to reunite with his girlfriend Mina who has moved with her family to England. The long journey is almost over when he finally reaches Calais, on the far northern coast of France; he can literally see his destination from across the Channel. But with all legal options exhausted, Bilal resolves that his only option is to learn to swim, and make the dangerous crossing himself. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 A huge critical and box office success in its native France, this profoundly moving masterwork was awarded the Ecumenical Jury Prize at the Berlin International Film Festival, named Best Film at the 2010 Lumière Awards, and received an astonishing ten César nominations including Best Film and Director. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This 2009, 116-minute film will be presented in its original French version with English subtitles. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The screening will conclude with an open discussion led by our in-house film expert, Barbara Bouquegneau. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;You will need to purchase your ticket before the event. Call the number below to buy your ticket.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Member Price: $5.00&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Non-Member Price: $7.00&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RSVP Required (call 617-912-0400)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>marianne</member_name><member_id>3771263</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369358849000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366833795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Film "Welcome"</name><id>116001942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369347300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/116001942/</event_url></item>