<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;South Kinsman 4358 ft. &lt;br /&gt;

 North Kinsman 4293 ft. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 North and South Kinsman are the highest peaks in the Cannon-Kinsman Range, which also includes Cannon Mountain (4100 ft.) at the northren end, and the three Cannonballs in between. The Kinsmans lie on the Appalachian Trail, and are easily reached from several directions. On a clear day the peaks offer stunning views of the Franconia Range (Lafayette, Lincoln, Liberty and Flume) to the east.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/d/4/event_100672692.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kinsman's ridge had the Lonesome Lake hut- so if conditions aren't perfect we can still have a protected hike. I will take charge of the casual pace hikers- I need some summit leaders for those who are working on the NH 48 list. I'm still building back up,  hiking for fun, not goal. Beautiful view there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lonesome Lake Trail&lt;/strong&gt; This trail runs from the Lafayette Campground to Lonesome Lake, where you can choose a route to the Fishing Jimmy Trail or Kinsman Pond Trail. Distance from the campground to Lonesome Lake area, 1.2 miles. The Lonesome Lake Trail continues on to the Kinsman Ridge Trail, just north of the third Cannonball, which is reached at 2.3 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt. Kinsman by Lonesome Lake, Fishin' Jimmy &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;10.0 mi 3,550 elevation gain  6:45 amc booktime&lt;/span&gt; add time for winter conditions and  casual pace hikers calculate a 1 mph average hike pace. A 1pm turn around time will be used to manage our day and get us home at a reasonable time. That means if we are no where near the summit, we will summit another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/4/d/event_7241037.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short breaks are better in winter to prevent getting cold than one long break- consider this when packing your food supply.  Water should be in 2 liter wide mouth bottles, wrap them in your extra clothes to insulate and store upside down, so if they start to freeze, it will not be at the cap and you will be able to open the bottles. Keep your food warm, in your jacket. a cold power bar is a jaw breaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;SNOWSHOES AND TRACTION are MANDATORY ON THIS HIKE.&lt;/span&gt; WELL MANNERED DOGS ARE WELCOME, BUT ARE NOT ALLOWED IN THE HUT. PACK HOT DRINK POWDERS FOR THE HUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;SET UP YOUR CARPOOL IN YOUR RSVP COMMENTS. MATCH UP WHO IS LOOKING FOR A RIDE AND CONTACT THEM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For those of us that are less fit, hiking is fantastic conditioning, but that stress level is hit much faster so replacement drinks are advised. Nuun, Powerade Zero, and Gatorade all make a good sugar free version for those who are controlling their sugar.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : center ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com" style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Click for weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/d/4/event_128896852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>8:30 am trailhead. may not be plowed at trailhead.  Park to the right at the information center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358008041000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351477409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Whites! Kinsmans Moderate &amp; Casual MX pace</name><id>qwjsbdyrcbkc</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357479000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/88980202/</event_url></item>