<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Avery st. (Roofdeck)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.349089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-375-8550</phone><name>Blu Restaurant (Roofdeck)</name><city>Boston</city><id>1334265</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060177</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A speaker/panel discussion with senior level executives from cutting edge companies based in Boston and doing business worldwide. This will be followed by a photo shoot to demonstrate the importance of image development in the fashion industry. The focus will be the marketing/use of fashion and music in today's marketing environment-with a particular emphasis on new media and technology as a platform.&lt;br /&gt;Featured speakers will include:&lt;br /&gt;Casey Jones, VP of Business Development for Mocospace will discuss the current trends in the music industry in relationship to the rapidly growing mobile area. Mocospace is the largest mobile social network in the US with over 6 million registered users and over 1 billion page views per month. The major record label Def Jam is among the labels that have partnered with Mocospace.&lt;br /&gt;John B. Davie, President and Founder of Fantourage&lt;br /&gt;www.fantourage.com&lt;br /&gt;From the Fantourage website:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fantourage is a free service that lets you earn rewards and recognition from Celebrities and Brands. Earn House points by simply posting and interacting with other fans.This is Where Celebrities and Brands recognize their loyal Fans!&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;Bettina Hein Founder and CEO, Pixability, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;www.pixability.com&lt;br /&gt;Pixability was founded out of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;From the Pixability website:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Pixability began with a big idea: Make it simpler than ever for businesses and organizations of all sizes to tell their story via video. We offer the easiest, quickest, most economical way to create quality video to help you market your company or organization. Now anyone, from company president to cashier, can be part of the web video revolution.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Tamara Rodriguez, Singer-will be interviewed by Evan&lt;br /&gt;www.tamaraonline.net&lt;br /&gt;A senior level executive will speak from Sonic Bids&lt;br /&gt;From the Sonic Bids website:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We're the world's largest site for gigging musicians – and for good reason. Our bands are paying members who use Sonicbids to connect with promoters across the globe. With our network of partners and community of emerging bands, we're able to develop innovative music marketing programs for a wide variety of national and international brands. &lt;br /&gt;The bands, fans and promoters who come together through Sonicbids create a powerful resource for sponsors looking to connect with the lifestyle of those driven by a desire to make, promote, and listen to great music. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ron Ranere of Positive Image Photography will do a fashion photo shoot after the panel discussion.  The shoot will show how image can be altered by changing makeup and accessories from the girl next door look to a hot edgy look.  What you need for your image depends on your music genre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The panel discussion will take place in the roofdeck at the Blu Restaurant at The Sportsclub LA.&lt;br /&gt;www.blurestaurant.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No admission fee.&lt;br /&gt;In lieu of an admission fee we encourage members to make a donation to Dress For Success&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dressforsuccess.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dressforsu...&lt;/a&gt; or Caitlin's Smiles &lt;a href="http://www.caitlins-smiles.org/donate.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.caitlins-s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go to the website's listed above to donate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Ranere</member_name><member_id>975035</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>2523024</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>yasu</member_name><member_id>3356319</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280496244000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>fashionandmusiceventplanning</urlname><id>1408370</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Fashion and Music Event Planning</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277855625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Event: Fashion and Music Marketing for 2010</name><id>13954114</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280440800000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fashionandmusiceventplanning/events/13954114/</event_url></item>