<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 Carby St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.235863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hale Reservation</name><city>Westwood</city><id>669427</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.231890</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>EVENT: Don?t miss the Mosaic event of the year ? our Annual picnic! We?ll celebrate &lt;br /&gt;our 17th year as a club with food, fun, and friends. We will also have our (brief!) &lt;br /&gt;annual meeting where we will elect new club officers. The picnic, once again, will be held at beautiful Hale Reservation in Westwood (10 miles West of Boston). We will have the usual opportunities for nature walks, swimming, and volleyball. This year, we will be having a deli buffet (with plenty of options for vegetarians). We need volunteers to help set, clean up and perform other important tasks. Please contact one of TCs listed above if you can give us at hand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEET 11-5 at Hale Reservation. Lunch at Noon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP: Because we must purchase food and supplies in advance, we are asking all members who want to attend to register in advance. The good news is that we are lowering the price to ten dollars, which makes this great event a real bargain. Please send a check for $10 made out to ?MOMC of MA? to: MOMC of MA, P. O. Box 1821, Brookline, MA 02446-0015. Please include your email address (preferred) or phone number. You will be contacted with directions when we receive your check  or go to &lt;a href="http://www.halereservation.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.halereserv...&lt;/a&gt;. If you have a Paypal account, you may also pay us on &lt;a href="http://www.paypal.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.paypal.com...&lt;/a&gt;. Send the money to mosaic_mass@yahoo.com. Opening a Paypal account is easy and free. Checks are due by Saturday, June 16. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE DO NOT RSVP VIA MEETUP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Late RSVP?s will be taken after June 16 on a space available basis only at a cost of $15. Please remember that this is a members? only event. If your membership has expired, or expires at the end of June (your expiration date is on your mailing label), you must rejoin the club and pay your annual dues to attend the picnic. We are including a membership form with this newsletter for your convenience, or you may download a form at &lt;a href="http://www.mosaicoutdoor.org/boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mosaicoutd...&lt;/a&gt;. Fill out the membership form and include your check along with your check for the picnic. You may also pay your membership dues via paypal and fill out your renewal form at the picnic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: $10 by June 16/$15 after June 16 on space available basis. You must be a club member to attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to  &lt;a href="http://www.mosaicoutdoor.org/boston/newmem.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mosaicoutd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to download a membership form&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541497000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180225408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOSIAC ANNUAL CLUB PICNIC!!!!</name><id>5822131</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182697200000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/5822131/</event_url></item>