<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8129392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120926</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brattle Theater is showing Studio Ghibli films for two straight weeks! I thought two of the double features would make good meetups. This is for the second one. See the full schedule at &lt;a href="http://brattlefilm.org/category/calendar-2/repertory-series/spirited-away-the-films-of-hayao-miyazaki-and-studio-ghibli/"&gt;http://brattlefilm.org/category/calendar-2/repertory-series/spirited-away-the-films-of-hayao-miyazaki-and-studio-ghibli/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday September 9th, the double feature starts at 7:00 with Sprited Away, and continues at 9:30 with Howl's Moving Castle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As with the last Brattle meetup, I'll be in front of the theater 15min before the movie wearing a red fedora, so I'll be really easy to spot, just come find me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a double feature, so the ticket price of $12 covers admission to both films. The double feature price is $10 for students, seniors, and children &amp;lt; 12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven't had the pleasure of seeing one or both of these movies, do yourself the favor of coming along and seeing some amazing, classic animated fantasy! These particular Studio Ghibli offerings go a bit darker than some of their other movies, with more complex storytelling, and I'd say really more aimed at older kids and adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Synopses from Brattlefilm.org:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spirited Away&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 in Japanese with English subtitles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(2002) dir Hayao Miyazaki [125 min]&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Hayao Miyazaki’s Oscar-winning masterpiece SPIRITED AWAY helped redefine the possibilities of animation for American audiences and a generation of new filmmakers. Wandering through an abandoned carnival site, ten-year-old Chihiro stumbles into a dream-like spirit world where she is put to work in a bathhouse for the gods, a place where all kinds of nonhuman beings come to refresh, relax and recharge. Here she encounters a vast menagerie of impossibly inventive characters and must find the inner strength to outsmart her captors and return to her family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Howl's Moving Castle&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 English language version&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(2005) dir Hayao Miyazaki [119 min]&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Sophie, an average teenage girl working in a hat shop, finds her life thrown into turmoil when she is literally swept off her feet by a handsome but mysterious wizard named Howl. Soon after this chance meeting, the young girl is turned into a 90-year old woman by a vain and conniving witch. Embarking on an incredible adventure to lift the curse, Sophie finds refuge in Howl’s magical moving castle. As the true power of Howl’s wizardry is revealed, and his relationship with Sophie deepens, our young grey heroine finds herself fighting to protect them both from a dangerous war of sorcery that threatens their world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347251770000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346043147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Castles in the Sky: Studio Ghibli Retrospective part 2</name><id>79521222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347230700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/79521222/</event_url></item>