<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Hello, Everybody&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is great to be part of this group and to that end, my first organized Meetup for Portland Out and About will be a super hike and picnic in and around the vicinity of Mount Agamenticus in York!  We will meet at 9:30, allow an extra 15 minutes for latecomers, and step off at 9:45.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This outing is very low key and relaxed and based on my past hikes is best enjoyed by those who do not have any day end deadlines to meet - and who have a certain degree of flexibility as to when the hike ends.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first part of the hike will be an approximate 3 mile round trip loop on the Ring Trail on Mount A.  The pace will be very relaxed.  The elevation gain is ~ 500 feet over 1.2 miles - elevation at the top is 692 feet with some great views of the White Mountains to the north and ocean to the east on a clear day.  Allow about 1 1/2 - 2 hours for this part of the hike, which will include a break at the top followed by a visit to the recently opened &amp;quot;Learning Lodge&amp;quot; which has a nice educational and informative display on the history and animal life of the surrounding area.   Hiking shoes / boots with solid grips for wet rocks and pebbles are recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the 3-mile loop we will be back in the parking lot again to pick up our picnic lunches.  Quick tip here:  There is no need to lug your lunches in a heavy back pack for these first 3 miles.  Since we will be circling back to the parking lot again, just bring beverages and snacks for the Mount A portion of the hike and keep your picnic in a cooler in your vehicle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this point we will pick up our lunches and hike another mile (a portion of which is on the road) onto another trail where we will enjoy our picnic (with luck, on a nice pond!).  Allow about another 2 hours for this portion of the hike (which includes the picnic).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A quick note on the picnic - it is meant to be a relaxing enjoyable picnic.  In the past, I've had some hikers who view the picnic as just a 10-minute break for an energy bar and water, which can cause a rushed atmosphere for everyone else.   Allow a full hour just to eat, converse, enjoy the natural surroundings - and maybe even make some new friends in the process&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be one of my regularly posted Meetups (I live not far from there) and plan at least two more during fall foliage season later in the month.  Even now, we should be able to see the very beginnings of some fall foliage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The directions from the north are as follows (let me know if you need the directions from another location): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you approach the York toll booths, be sure that you are in one of the right lanes, (since your Exit is just a couple of hundred feet on the right after you pay the toll).  This is Exit 7.  Bear right where the ramp splits.  Go ~ 6.3 miles to the base of Mount A (the paved road ends at this point, so you can't miss it).  This is Chase's Pond Road which becomes Mountain Road (same road; no turns).  There is a small parking lot, which is invariably full - you can turn around and park on the right side of the road - plenty of space - one of the reasons why we are starting fairly early at this time of year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting you then!  Please feel free to write with any questions -  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy &lt;br /&gt;RandyS@maine.rr.com&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For the first few hikers, we will meet near a silver Subaru Forester on the right side of the road. After that, we will gather at the edge of the parking lot near the boulders.  I will be wearing a Meetup sticker.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286205140000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284902459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike and Picnic Lunch in York!</name><id>14820368</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286112600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/14820368/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/3/global_18158419.jpeg</photo_url></item>