<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Nashua Mall</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.765755</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 883-9009 </phone><name>Haluwa Restaurant &amp; Lounge</name><city>Nashua</city><id>1061769</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.494635</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/5/5/event_20438741.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Karaoke this week on Thursday @Haluwa with the &lt;em&gt;premiere&lt;/em&gt; KJ in the area, DJ Big Don!  This is the guy all the other DJs in the area learned from!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be in the mood for chinese! (I love their Peking Ravioli, Rice w/Shrimp and Pu Pu platter!) Watch their Scorpion bowls, they seem to have a REAL affect! lol&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've seen Big Don at other venues around here and he IS great!  The regulars at Haluwa will love him and I think our group will too. That's why Haluwa godd a hold of him for a few weeks.  They love the Meetup group when we come to Karaoke Night and Big Don will too! You can sing and dance and eat; be part of our big group songs like Love Shack and Paradise by the Dashboard Light (where no one can tell if you're even singin'!); or just watch and cheer/laugh us on! They'll have the big TVs on local games as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Haluwa is off exit 6w in Nashua in the Nashua Mall, just beyond Denny's &amp;amp; Radio Shack, but before Shortys. We'll start at 8, karaoke is at 9, til closing around 1!. We're usually in the center section of the club, where we can add tables as we add people thru the night! So don't be afraid to come late if you have to. We've had some big crowds there and the late comers keep us up to the end! And we have fun with other groups there too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom D'A cell 603-521-8392&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Usually in the middle isle, towards the dance floor, with a few tables stacked end2end, like in the pic</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom D'A</member_name><member_id>5016514</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358489750000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358384078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DJ Big Don is doing Thursday Night Karaoke @Haluwa, Nashua!</name><id>99974392</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358472600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/99974392/</event_url></item>