<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In last December's meetup we did my &amp;quot;expanding circle of spirit&amp;quot;, and everyone &lt;i&gt;loved&lt;/i&gt; it.  It is a process well worth repeating; and Mark and I are offering it this month as our free New Possibilities class for the public.  This class is &lt;u&gt;totally&lt;/u&gt; related to law of attraction.  Connecting to your Source-Self is the foundation of easy allowing of all that you desire, after all.  Here's the scoop:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Your Expanding Circle of Spirit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I believe the most powerful thing you can do to bring greater harmony, happiness and success to yourself and to others is to be connected to your Sense of Spirit and to bring that into your daily living.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;  Could you use some help with this?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;  Would you enjoy it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will begin this class with a &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Sacred Journey guided meditation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; This will help you to access your sense of spirit and then to bring it into various aspects of your life - your environments, behaviors, capabilities, beliefs and values, sense of self and your greater vision. This alone is a very powerful experience; but we’re going to take it &lt;i&gt;even further&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From there, we’ll then do a guided group process that will have you bringing this strong sense of spirit to problematic areas in your life and other contexts in which you want to feel your spiritual self more present. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;You're going to feel your spiritual field &lt;i&gt;expand more and more;&lt;/i&gt; and we're going to connect that to the positive spiritual energy &lt;i&gt;everyone&lt;/i&gt; in our group is feeling. So it will expand &lt;i&gt;even more&lt;/i&gt;. We’ll be creating an&lt;b&gt; Expanding Circle of Spirit&lt;/b&gt; that will be carried forward into your daily life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Just imagine feeling connected to your sense of your Spiritual self - to all Source Energy, and expanding that feeling more and more and more!&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;So PLEASE find a way to join us! All are welcome.  Please share this with your e-mail lists and groups, your friends, and your family, and invite them to join you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Friday evening, November 20th, 7:00 – 9:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wayland Wellness, 15 East Plain St., Wayland, MA 01778 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP required. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I CAN'T WAIT! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warmest heart,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This free class is co-sponsored by Wayland Wellness and New Possibilities Coaching as a free service to their clients and the surrounding communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Ann Ide, M.A., Wayland Wellness’ New Possibilities Life Coach, is a certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and a certified NLP Life Coach.  Ann will help you to move beyond your struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success.  With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, she will help you become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness you want.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258935339000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257380924000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Your Expanding Circle of Spirit</name><id>11797866</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258761600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/11797866/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>