<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>472 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363930</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-866-777-8932</phone><name>The Middle East Restaurant and Nightclub</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669146</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101230</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From Pitchfork: &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An Oscar-nominated Hollywood heartthrob and his best friend round up a bunch of instruments-- some of which they don't know how to play-- and a massive children's choir and make a concept album about the supernatural. Seems like a recipe for disaster, right? Guess again.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet Dead Man's Bones, collaboration between actors Ryan Gosling (Half Nelson, The Believer, The Notebook) and Zach Shields. The duo plan to release their debut album, Never Let a Lack of Talent Get You Down, on their own label, Werewolf Heart, this summer. You might have seen their MySpace page, or a video for their song &amp;quot;In the Room Where You Sleep&amp;quot; floating around the web recently. In the clip, Gosling and Shields lead a bunch of kids, all dressed in Halloween costumes, through a spare acoustic lament. It's creepy and catchy. It sounds like a middle school assembly gone goth. And it's pretty damn good.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As far as celebrity music projects go, the quality level on this one is a lot closer to She &amp;amp; Him than, say, Joaquin Phoenix's rap career. While listening to tracks from the Dead Man's Bones album at the office, I've been asked by co-workers if I'm listening to Bryan Ferry or something by the Arcade Fire. No lie.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND THEY ARE COMING TO THE MIDDLE EAST!!! Just in time for Halloween tricks and treats! &lt;br /&gt;Seriously, check them out. They are a lot of fun. I know Loney Dear is playing and that is such a tough call, but I am crazy stoked about this and hope to get some of you on board too.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perhaps my feminine heart has fallen prey to Ryan Gosling's beauty, perhaps my nerdy bones have thrilled to the thought of a zombie band, potentially I am just a sucker for anything that utilizes a children's choir in a macabre way, but any way you dice it I will be there. I am always down for pre show PBR or in honor of the season a pumpkin flavored ale. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets= $15&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>To all yes rsvps I will send out my cell phone number.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jenn</member_name><member_id>10142965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255738079000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254367570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dead Man's Bones at The Middle East</name><id>11515598</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255564800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/11515598/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/a/1/global_10997025.jpeg</photo_url></item>