<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Harvard Yard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374237</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard University</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8366302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117096</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Fellow member AM suggests, more group meetings outside during the summer! Grab frozen yogurt (or whatever you prefer) then head to Harvard Yard for small group conversations of 3-4 people for 10 minutes, then shuffle to a new group. Repeat about 3 times and then have general social conversation to meet more peeps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well the weather is still nice so let's do this. Harvard Yard is ideal because it is close to the Harvard Station subway station on the MBTA red line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This link, &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/travel/boston/neighborhoods/harvard_square/harvardyardmap/"&gt;http://www.boston.com/travel/boston/neighborhoods/harvard_square/harvardyardmap/&lt;/a&gt; has a very useful map of Harvard Yard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll have snacks to share, a deck of cards, the board game Scrabble and dictionaries. If you're able I encourage you to bring something to snack on or game to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a fun easy going get together. No pressure to speak completely in Portuguese. You can become comfortable by just listening then jump in when you're ready to talk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're not required to take part in the group conversations. It is okay to have individual conversations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet until at least 8 PM....maybe longer if the conversation is flowing....so get there when you can, just please RSVP and let us know when you will arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MBTA: Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS: Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your driving route&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING: Very limited parking at meters on Brattle, Dunster and JFK Streets as well as Massachusetts Avenue. Check out &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx"&gt;Harvard Square Public Parking&lt;/a&gt; for garages and lots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can always get in touch with me through the "Contact Organizer" link on Meetup: &lt;a href="http://portuguese.meetup.com/316/suggestion/"&gt;http://portuguese.meetup.com/316/suggestion/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;email snowrover@yahoo.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walking directions from 1326 Mass Ave crosswalk. Cross Mass avenue then pass through gate into Harvard Yard. Continue straight on path until John Harvard statue on right. Will be in seats across from statue. Portuguese signs taped to seatbacks.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347498865000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343146527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portuguese Table Gathering in Harvard Yard - Wednesday September 12th 6:00 PM</name><id>74693812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347487200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/74693812/</event_url></item>