<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>28.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>John Scofield Trio&lt;br /&gt;FEATURING:&lt;br /&gt;John Scofield - guitar &lt;br /&gt;Steve Swallow - bass &lt;br /&gt;Bill Stewart - drums&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For EnRoute, Scofield wanted to focus on the high-wire interaction of a small, closely knit band in the heat of a live setting. He arrived at the Blue Note armed only with his trusty guitar, amp and whammy pedal, and left his more elaborate electronic gear at home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I wanted to make a real jazz-improvising statement in a live situation with two of my favorite musicians,&amp;quot; Scofield says. &amp;quot;It's really challenging. You don't rely on arrangements as much as on the way the group plays together. You don't rely on anything other than good playing, and you know there's no lifejacket or safety net involved. That doesn't happen as often in a studio setting: I think the big difference is the audience. There is a symbiotic affinity between the artists and the audience that makes for something special.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And in the end, that's what EnRoute is all about: three musicians grooving in front of an enthusiastic audience and the special synergy that unfolds between them. &amp;quot;It's impossible to judge your own work completely,&amp;quot; Scofield says, &amp;quot;but I think this is some of my best playing. We definitely hooked up as a group, and it brought us to places we don't usually get in the studio.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here you can find more info about the venue: &lt;a href="http://www.regattabarjazz.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.regattabar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.johnscofield.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnscofield.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.johnscofie...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540538000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonjazz</urlname><id>87187</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Jazz Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1158462435000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Jazz October Meetup</name><id>5135288</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1161734400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonjazz/events/5135288/</event_url></item>