<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>137 Warren Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.941685</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-746-1622</phone><name>Plimoth Plantation</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>975354</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.621976</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>28.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Bring family and friends to see Plymouth as it was in the 17th century:&lt;br /&gt;It is Native Wampanoag and Colonial English men and women living their lives, as if it were the 1620s. It is living off the land. It is cooking over the fire. It is managing conflict and navigating political relations in an uncertain time. See it, smell it, hear it and experience it here.  &lt;br /&gt;The 1627 English Village is a re-creation of the small farming town built by English colonists in the midst of the Wampanoag homeland. Find yourself immersed in the year 1627, just seven years after the voyage of the Mayflower. In the village you will be surrounded by the modest timber-framed houses, fragrant raised-bed gardens, well-tended livestock and fascinating townspeople of Plymouth Colony, the first permanent English settlement in New England.&lt;br /&gt;The people you will meet are costumed role players who have taken on the names, viewpoints and life histories of the people who actually lived in the colony in 1627, popularly known as the &amp;quot;Pilgrims&amp;quot; today. Each one has a unique story to tell. Learn about the colony's difficult beginnings or discover the gossip of the day. Ask about religious beliefs, medical practices or relations with the local Wampanoag People. Talk to a housewife and learn what a &amp;quot;pottage&amp;quot; is, or see how a duck or bluefish is cooked on the hearth. Help a young colonist pull up a few weeds in a cornfield, mix daub with your feet for a house under construction, or just relax on a bench enjoying the unique atmosphere of 17th-century New Plymouth.&lt;br /&gt;Your visit to the year 1627 is self-guided, so feel free to wander around the village at your own pace. Do not be afraid to walk in on colonists as they eat, question them as they work, or join a lively conversation in the street. Most of the objects in and around their houses are modern reproductions designed for everyday use and can be handled gently. You needn't be an expert in the language of Shakespeare to pose a question, either. Just ask and see what happens — you may be called upon to define &amp;quot;bathroom&amp;quot; or even explain what a &amp;quot;Pilgrim&amp;quot; is!&lt;br /&gt;Take this unique opportunity to explore the 17th-century perspective of the English who traveled across the Atlantic. You may be surprised at what you learn!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visiting Mayflower II is also an extraordinary experience. The details of the ship, from the solid oak timbers and tarred hemp rigging, to the wood and horn lanterns and hand-colored maps, have all been carefully recreated to give you a sense of what the original 17th-century vessel was like. Come aboard and learn about the 1620 voyage of the Mayflower, the perils of maritime travel, and the tools of 17th-century navigation. Explore the cramped quarters of the ship's passengers. Peer down into the lower level &amp;quot;hold,&amp;quot; where the food, clothing, furniture, tools and other items necessary to start a colony were stored. Admire the &amp;quot;spacious&amp;quot; Master's cabin, and compare it to the wet and windy accommodations of the common sailors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if we want to extend our experiences to include gastronomy, we can Enjoy A Taste of Two Cultures at the Visitor Center in the new Patuxet Café – brought to you by the talented chefs from Creative Gourmet and inspired by food from Wampanoag and English colonial traditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Menu Items for A Taste of Two Cultures&lt;br /&gt;Salmon Burger&lt;br /&gt;Venison Burger&lt;br /&gt;Stuffed Quahog&lt;br /&gt;2 Stuffed Quahogs served with Three Sisters Rice&lt;br /&gt;Nasaump&lt;br /&gt;Turkey and Cranberry Soup&lt;br /&gt;Seasonal Succotash&lt;br /&gt;17th-Century Cheesecake&lt;br /&gt;Peas Cods&lt;br /&gt;Mayflower Beer&lt;br /&gt;Indian Pudding&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FALL MENU INCLUDES:&lt;a href="http://www.plimoth.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Plimoth Plantation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maple Glazed Venison Skewers served with Acorn Squash and Green Beans&lt;br /&gt;Roast Duck with Sauce of Wine, Cranberries &amp;amp; Onions, served with Stewed Pompion and Savory Corn Pudding&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TALL STRAWBERRY BLONDE BUT LET'S ORGANIZE CARPOOLS</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen</member_name><member_id>3330386</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy </member_name><member_id>3699089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227017134000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>travel-575</urlname><id>418980</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Old and Not so Old Ladies Travel</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218020839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Plimoth Plantation and environs</name><id>8488136</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226844000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/travel-575/events/8488136/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/2/global_5058658.jpeg</photo_url></item>