<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What is the Boston Conservatives meet up?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First of all come to the meetings to find out.  We get lots of new members and welcome them.  Each of the members has different ideas of what should be accomplished, but while we figure that out we certainly enjoy each other's company in conversation of a political/conservative leaning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston-area conservatives can &amp;quot;meet and greet&amp;quot; and discuss issues of the day.  Many of us find our workplace-, extended family-, or friend-network-conversations' views heavily tilted towards the left.  This meeting can serve as an antidote, as a friendly respite, as a place to pass on and gain conservative perspective and ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course there is no one single conservative perspective on issues.  We debate, we listen, we learn.  This is a good meeting for friendly discussion.  The people who come are bright, lucid, open, and forthright.  Some people are more politically active than others.  There's no specific political activity requirement and there is no partisan angle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to having new members come.  Discussion is interesting, please bring your views, your self.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fourth Tuesday of each month, we will be at varying locations. This month at Cottonwood Cafe, Berkeley at St. James. in the Back Bay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thurman Smith, organizer&lt;br /&gt;Boston Conseraties Meetup&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the maitre d' for the meetup table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>THURMAN SMITH</member_name><member_id>1416920</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206659144000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>The main topic of the March meeting will be whether it's time to start a new political party.
For some ideas for platform plans visit www.constitutionparty.org.</why><group><who>Conservatives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>townhall-61</urlname><id>155655</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Conservatives' Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202259936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Conservatives' March Meeting</name><id>7271965</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206486000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/townhall-61/events/7271965/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/1/9/global_3409561.jpeg</photo_url></item>