<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>As the year comes to a close we are thankful for a beautiful evening together in the most richest interfaith group we have had to date. Muslim, Jewish and Christian souls were present in the warm, rustic environment of the &lt;a href="http://www.peaceabbey.org" target="_blank"&gt;Peace Abbey, an Interfaith Retreat Center&lt;/a&gt;.  There we completed discussion on our text, Tents of Abraham, by looking at the Muslim Interpretations of Abraham's Journey by Imam Murshid Saadi Shakur Chishti. It was a highly energetic conversation and wonderfully rewarding and insightful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We decided for our next meeting, January 15, which is already booked at the Peace Abbey again, would be a time for us to choose our next book for discussion. Each member is asked to bring one selection they would like to suggest for our perusal. You may choose your own, suggestions from Terianne or myself in the list I passed out. If we have time in the meeting after choosing our book selection, Joe and I will show a short film on Interfaith dialogue if you would like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have some spirited contributors in our group and I encourage all to continue to share our thoughts, inspirations and insights in our &lt;a href="http://www.interfaithbookclub.wordpress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Interfaith Book Club Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Merry Christmas, Happy Chanukah, and assalaam alaikum!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Carl Chudy and Fr. Joe Matteucig&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;Our Lady of Fatima Shrine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out our Interfaith Book Club Blog at www.interfaithbookclub.wordpress.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on Route 16, close to the Library and Town Hall Complex of Sherborn.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200843827000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>It will be a beautiful evening around the rustic fireplace of Peace Abbey. We will be choosing the book for our next selection in the next meeting.</why><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198028286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club January Meetup</name><id>6936201</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200443400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/6936201/</event_url></item>